Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world
has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto theGrand Line
in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Now, come on board, Franky...
Board my ship.
Don't be so cocky!
I guess I don't have much choice
but to help you guys out!
I, Franky, will be the shipwright on your ship!
Hey! Rejoice!
It's me!
Although we said all sorts of things
to each other, we're friends!
I'll let these little things go!
Stop...
joking.
If that's what you want...
...let me say one last thing.
You guys...
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for being bullheaded!
I was wrong!
Usopp!
Luffy...
You idiot!
Grab my hand already!
What do you think about this
for the ship's name, Franky?
The pirate ship...
...Thousand Sunny!
Coup de Burst!
It consumes three barrels of cola,
but it lets us fly one kilometer.
There's nothing the Going Merry
could do that this ship can't.
It exceeds the Merry in every way.
But the Merry's brave soul will be
inherited by the Thousand Sunny.
Yeah!
Well then, once again...
To Robin and Usopp, who came back to us,
to our new friend, Franky...
...and to our pirate ship, the Thousand Sunny!
Cheers!
Let's go!
Our next destination is Fishman Island!
Yeah!
Don't, Vigaro...!
Papa, are you looking at your
collection by yourself again?
Yeah.
Is everyone already here?
You were awfully quick.
We're going to get started
on the preparations now.
I'll make sure that you have
a special birthday, Papa.
Swap out with me, Jiro.
Go get some sleep.
I'll keep an eye on the captain.
"The Mysterious Band of Pirates!
Sunny and the Dangerous Trap"
Ah, this is bliss!
Pure bliss!
Nothing beats bathing in a massive
tub that sways on the waves!
Whee!
This here is my room.
"What seems to be the problem?"
Just kidding!
I'm so excited!
I wonder if I'll
get a patient anytime soon.
I caught something!
Looks like I got a cool shark!
Put it in! Put it in!
Let's put it in the aquarium!
Put it in!
In ya go!
Yay!
They dropped in another one.
Isn't it a shark?
Well?
Isn't this a nice room?
The room's great,
but I can't believe those
idiots tossed in a shark!
Great!
Now let's go see it!
Let's check out the aquarium!
Hey!
Did a shark come in?
It's an awesome one with horns!
Yes, it did, but you've lost all
of the other fish you caught.
Think about compatibility
before you throw something in!
Isn't that a no-brainer?
Darn it!
This punk's gonna be tonight's dinner!
Sanji, roast it!
We'll barbecue that stupid shark!
Wait, you amateur!
It's still a fresh fish.
I should either make sushi or serve it
boiled with a hot and sour miso sauce.
Tempura might be nice, too.
I'm starting to get hungry!
But seriously, thank you
for this great ship, Franky!
It's no biggie!
But you still haven't seen
its true power yet.
Its true power?
Yeah!
This ship's key features are
its "Soldier Dock System."
There are five docks ranging from
Channel 0 to Channel 4 located on the bilge.
Each dock is rigged to
handle different situations.
All of them will play a unique role
in assisting the Thousand Sunny!
Wow!
Then lemme see them in action!
Hey, hold your horses.
I'll let you see them as they're needed.
It'd be a shame to show them off all at once.
I can hardly wait.
Boo! Boo! Boo! Boo!
That was a great bath!
I thought it seemed a lot colder
than yesterday, and I was right!
I wonder if we've entered
a winter island's currents.
But Kokoro-san never mentioned
anything about this...
It's snowing?
Yay, it's snowing!
Yahoo!
Sweet!
Hey, Zoro!
You're spoiling the party!
This is how you're supposed
to act when it snows:
"Guys, it's snowing!"
I guess you still didn't know that.
Damn it...!
You really aren't that bright!
Dumb-dumb!
Nothing ticks me off more than
having them call me names!
Wow!
I haven't seen snow in ages.
I wonder if it'll stick.
I hope it does!
Maybe I should make something
warm for dinner tonight.
Hey, there's a ship!
Something seems a bit off.
It seems off?
How so?
What gives?
It doesn't have any sails,
let alone an ensign.
It doesn't have any sails?
That means it's just floating there!
It's either a ship in distress, or it's a...
Come to think of it,
some pirates play a nasty game
called the "Davy Back Fight."
Yeah, we know.
You don't think...
they fell victim to that game, do you?
Just a sec!
Some people just came out.
Fishing?!
They must be in distress.
They look horribly exhausted.
Hey, Captain!
Yeah, let's go check on them.
If they end up being our enemy,
we'll just send them flying!
There aren't any fish out there that'll
bite a hook without bait, are there?
Don't say that.
Don't even say that...
It beats doing nothing.
We've got time to kill,
so let's be patient and wait.
Wha--?!
Hey, are you guys all right?!
P-Pirates!
Pirates!
What?!
M-Make a break for it!
The rudder doesn't work!
And we don't have any sails!
Please show mercy!
What's up?
Dang, both you and your ship are
in sorry shape! You're both a mess!
Who are you guys?
W-We're just humble fishermen.
Fishermen?
Yeah.
About three days ago, we were
attacked by an unidentified ship.
Not only did they steal all
of our valuables and food,
but they also trashed our sail
and destroyed our rudder.
We've been floating out here ever since!
So you've got nothing to gain by attacking us.
No worries there!
Long story short, all of
you are hungry, right?
We were just about to eat, so come join us.
What?!
Are you serious?
Are you sure?
Yeah!
My cook can't turn a blind
eye to guys like you.
Don't be strangers!
Hey, Sanji!
Is it ready yet?
We're starving!
Yeah, it's just about ready,
but first...
Chopper!
You've been dying to get some patients.
Go tend to them.
S-Sure...
For starters, let's have
anyone injured come see me!
What?!
Is anyone too badly hurt to move?
Their pet just talked!
I'm not a pet!
I'm a pirate, too!
I'm worth a whopping 50 Berries! Damn it!
Ouch!
Sit still.
I suppose these are rookie
pirates who just hit the seas
with their new ship and stars still in their eyes.
Click.
Hello?
It's me.
How do things look over there?
Oh, hello.
To be honest, we're in the middle
of winning a pirate crew over...
uh, sir.
Hmph!
So what does their
Jolly Roger look like?
Uh, it's a skull wearing a straw hat, I believe.
Come again.
It's not like you'd go hunting
for bugs out on the ocean.
What could they be thinking?
Don't make small talk with me!
I'm sorry about that.
N-Now listen to me carefully!
Those are the Straw Hats,
with a total bounty of
600 million Berries on their heads!
600 million, sir?!
That's right!
You know what you must do, don't you?
Yes, all too well...
Listen, don't you dare let
them escape before we arrive!
Click.
600 million Berries on their heads...?
Good!
This is too good, Mister Eyebrow!
Seriously!
It's so good it's making me cry!
Are they crying drunks?
Wow!
You ladies sure are cute!
Sure are!
You're so cute you're making me cry!
So it would seem.
And they were late to notice us!
There...
Excuse me!
Huh?
Didn't you leave to eat?
What's the matter?
Doctor, please!
Doctor, after seeing what you can do,
there is someone else I'd like you to see.
Could you follow me aboard our ship right now?
What?
What?!
You're headed straight
for the New World?!
No one will think any less of you!
Turn around now!
It's hell over there.
What?
Have you been there?
N-No...
Uh, we've only heard rumors...
Supposedly it's a horrible place!
Stupid!
I don't care what the rumors claim.
I'll find out for myself if it's
like hell when I get there.
What was that?
Oh, sorry about that!
It looks like you've been
looking after my men for me!
Please let show you my gratitude!
I'm their commander.
The name's Stansen.
It's my best brew,
which I had specially ordered!
Please help yourselves.
Yeah?
Do you really have a patient down here?
Whoa, there.
Where does
he think he's taking me?
I-Is that the patient?
Yeah.
His entire body is seriously injured.
It's been days since the
last time he was conscious...
Please, Doctor!
You've got to help him get better!
What the heck?!
This is horrible!
His wounds are festering!
Why did you let him get this bad?!
It's not like I had a choice...
It's not safe to move him!
I'm going to begin the
operation right now.
This has a unique flavor.
So you had booze, even though
you didn't have anything to eat!
Pretty much!
But, wow, this is good!
It's like finding a port in a storm!
We really ought to do more to thank you!
Don't sweat it!
That isn't an option!
You really must drop by our port
so we can thank you properly.
"Drop by our port"?
In other words, you want us
to take you there, right?
You caught on?
Good guess!
You're one funny man!
All right, we'll take ya.
Really?!
I appreciate it!
Wait, Luffy!
What about Fishman Island?
If we visit any of the other islands,
it'll change our log's course.
Won't it be fine if we leave
as soon as we drop them off?
C'mon! What's the big deal?
They're in need of help!
Man, I'm glad you have such
an understanding captain!
Well, I'm counting on you to get us there!
You know, they say that the people
you travel with make the journey.
So I'd say we're due for another "cheers"!
Yeah, sounds good!
Cheers!
You have a hilarious captain.
How is he, Doctor?
I've done everything I can.
Now all we can do now is wait.
Thank you, Doctor!
We can't let our guard down.
He isn't over the worst of it yet.
What should we do?
Isn't it obvious?
We've got to do it!
I'm not excited about this...
They were such considerate guys, you know?
True enough!
And the girls were cute.
How could you say that?!
We don't have a choice in the matter!
He's right!
If we lay claim to this amazing ship, I bet we could take them on!
Not happening!
We are going to hand this ship over to them.
We are merely going to carry out
whatever missions they assign to us.
How could you call this a "mission"?!
Count us out!
We're going to steal this ship
and prepare to strike back.
As things stand now, Vigaro will
never be able to rest in peace!
Hey, punks!
You're free to argue
amongst yourselves...
...but I don't like the direction
this conversation's going.
W-Weren't you sound asleep?!
The smell of anesthesia was so
strong that I couldn't fall asleep.
You ruined my cuisine with that nasty drug!
You better be prepared to
pay for what you've done.
The three of them can
handle this on their own...
Happy birthday!
Click.
What is it?
I have managed to successfully
drive the prey into a tight corner.
Oh?
Some rookies are currently
onboard their ship right now.
Them?
They've proven surprisingly useful.
Sir, if I may be so bold,
it's still too soon to say.
After all, they have hooked a rather large fish.
A large fish?
Yes, sir!
Monkey D. Luffy and his
Straw Hat Pirates.
Their total bounty comes to 660 million Berries!
My, my.
How appropriate
for such a splendid day.
Indeed!
It certainly is!
Well, I'm counting on you.
Sir! You can leave this to me!
But honestly, you know, this really--
Click.
I expect this to turn into quite the party.
Isn't it troublesome when
you have unexpected guests?
I can deal with guests!
Hey, aren't we completely
surrounded by Navy ships?
You seem somewhat happy.
I'll show you this ship's super powers!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sunny's in a Pinch!
Roar, Secret Super-Speed Mecha"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!