Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
Take those two and beat it already
while you're still alive, you small fries!
The sky island exists.
Zoro!
Luffy!
The new era they're talking about is crap!
The era where pirates have dreams
will be over, they say?! Huh?!
People's dreams... have no end!!
"Legendary Family! 'Noland the Liar'"
Seriously... Seriously... Seriously...
Seriously... that darn orangutan!
He wrecked the ship even more!
This ship has really started to fall apart.
Maybe it's about time to replace it?
Don't you dare start saying
inconsiderate things, too!
Don't you dare!
You know exactly how we got this ship, right?!
Right?!
I know, Usopp.
Complaining won't get us anywhere.
Going Merry is an important part of the team.
You know exactly...!
You...! You...!
So let's work hard and repair the ship!
How we... How... How... How we...!
Luffy... You're such a...
Whoops.
You idiot!! Are you repairing
the ship or wrecking it?!
Well, I'm really trying to fix it, but...
Whoops, it got broke again.
Luffy!!
We left Mock Town and headed east
by circling around the island.
We're almost here on the map.
That man... what's his name again?
Montblanc Cricket.
So that man who talks of
dreams lives there, huh?
A-Amazing!!
That's his house?! That's a palace!
Is this Montblanc Cricket guy mega-rich?!
Idiots! Look closely.
A dreamer, huh? He does seem to be vain.
Why?
What the...?! It's just a board?!
What?!
The actual house is only half of it.
The rest is just a veneer.
He seems like a very cheap guy.
What kind of dreams did he talk about
that would get him driven out?
I don't know the details,
but I heard that he said a huge
amount of gold rests in Jaya.
Gold?!
Is that some pirate's buried
treasure or something?
Well, I don't know.
Gold!!
Dig the ground, Chopper! Gold will appear!
It will if I dig?
Living alone in such a remote area?
Hello. I'm coming in.
Couldn't you wait a moment?!
Hm? No one's here. Hello!!
No answer...
You idiot, wait! What're you
gonna do if this guy's dangerous?
Hey, everyone! No one's home!
Hm? This is...
...a picture book.
This is quite an old book.
Hm? It's titled "Noland the Liar."
Wow, that's a cool title! Nice idea for a book!
"Noland the Liar"?
You know it, Sanji-kun? But it says
it was published in the North Blue.
Yeah. I was born in the North Blue.
Haven't I told you guys?
That's news. I thought you
were from the East, too.
I grew up there.
Quiet, Chopper! What're you doing?!
What?!
"Noland the Liar"
This is a famous story in the North.
It's a fairy tale, but I've heard that this
Noland guy actually existed long ago.
This is a story from long, long ago...
A story that took place 400 long years ago.
A man named Montblanc Noland
lived in a North Blue country.
Noland, an explorer, always talked
about his incredible adventures.
However, the villagers couldn't tell
if those stories were true or not.
One day, he reported to the King
after coming back from his travels.
"I saw a mountain of gold
on an island in the great sea."
The courageous king set sail to the
great sea to see if the story was true,
taking 2,000 soldiers along with him.
After surviving great storms
and battling against monsters,
only the King, Noland and 100
soldiers made it to the island.
However, what they found
there was just a jungle.
In the end, he was sentenced
to death for the crime of lying.
Noland's last words were as follows:
"That's right! The mountain
of gold sank in the sea!"
The King and the others were dumbfounded.
No one believed Noland any longer
because Noland continued
to lie until his very death.
This book is based on the North Blue
fairy tale "Noland the Liar."
Montblanc Cricket is a descendant
of that Montblanc Noland?!
I heard that fairy tale a lot when I was a kid.
There isn't anyone in the North Blue
who doesn't know the tale.
We're all from the North Blue,
so we often got told
that if we lied a lot, we'd be
sentenced to death like Noland.
This is getting more and more interesting!
I never would've imagined that
Jaya was the island in that fairy tale.
And, after 400 years,
a descendant of Noland the Liar
is looking for the gold on this island, huh?
In order to clear the name of his ancestor,
who was called a big liar
and laughed at until he died...
This family cracks me up!
Does he really think that
he can clear the name
of his 400 year-old ancestor by
bringing back a few pieces of gold?!
Sounds like he's weak in the head!
Alas, the liar died...
...before he could even become
a brave warrior on the sea.
Don't look at me! And don't add in a
heartbreaking sentence on your own!
Luffy fell into the sea!!
What're you doing?!
Who the hell are you?!
You've got guts, relaxing at someone's
house without permission!
The sea in this area is my turf!
Hey, Usopp! Go grab Luffy!
Got it!
You're after the gold, aren't you? Die!
Sanji!!
Sanji-kun!
Don't worry. It didn't hit me.
Hold on!
Idiot... You shouldn't
underestimate your opponent.
Move! I'll handle this!
Hey, what were you doing?!
I saw... bubbles coming out of the water.
So I was looking in the water,
then suddenly a chestnut appeared.
The chestnut was actually a guy,
and he dragged me into the water.
Hey, old guy!
Bring more cold towels! Open up the windows!
Caisson disease?
Is this guy sick?
Yeah, it's a sickness that divers sometimes get.
But it doesn't usually become
a longstanding condition.
Due to a lack of decompression
when surfacing from the seabed,
the nitrogen dissolved in the
blood gets released quickly
and forms gas bubbles at that time.
Since the gas bubbles expand
inside and outside of blood vessels,
they cause problems to
blood flow, muscle and joints.
So it's some bizarre phenomenon, huh?
He probably kept diving
every day without giving time
for those bubbles to disappear from the body.
What for?!
I don't know, but he's taking a risk.
In some cases, caisson disease can...
...cause death.
Oh hey, it's you, Masira. So you're alive.
Alive? What're you talking about?
Never mind. In any case,
what was that gunfire about?
Exactly, brother! Do you think
something happened to the old-timer?
Let's hurry! I'm getting all worked up!
Old-timer! Are you all right?!
They've come to kill us!!
What're you guys doing here?!
What did you do to the old-timer?!
What? We're looking after this guy
right now, so go somewhere else.
Idiot! They aren't really gonna hear us out!
They're savages, you know!
You know!
Everyone, evacuate through the windows!
You...
...guys are so nice!
They're listening!
You guys live here, too?
Well, the old-timer's house is the
headquarters of the Saruyama Alliance.
But we sleep on our ships most of the time
because this house is too small for us.
It's because you guys are too big.
Well, to those Giant guys you
look like a ball of earwax, though.
Why are they getting along so well?
They can probably relate to each other.
But it's amazing that you guys
kicked him off when you're so small!
Really? You can do it, too.
Oh, really?
Yeah, you can because you're a monkey.
Luffy, he's come around!
He's awake?!
Hey, he's right, I can kick Masira...
Hey old diamond-head!
I wanna ask you something!
Sorry I caused you trouble.
I thought you were just
more idiots after the gold.
What?! You have gold bullion?
Don't go after it.
What is it that you wanna ask me?
Old guy, we wanna go to the sky island!
Please tell us how to get there!
Sky island?
You guys believe in the sky island?
Hey, stop it! He's a sick person!
There's no sky island, old guy?!
No one knows.
I know someone who said there is.
But people call him a legendary big liar!
His family became a laughing stock forever.
It's not me!
There's an old story that
most North Blue people know.
"Noland the Liar" is the one.
Like I said, it's not me!
He's got a different name, right?!
Come to think of it, Noland's name is,
if I'm not mistaken, Montblanc Noland.
Could it be that you're Noland's...
A descendant?! Could this place
be the island in that story?!
Hmph! He's my granddad's
granddad's granddad's...
He's my distant ancestor... What a nuisance.
I doubt there's a drop
of his blood in my body...
Although the Montblanc family
was driven out of the country then,
and has kept a low profile,
people continue to
denounce our family to this day.
But no one in the family hates him.
Why?
Because Noland was an
extraordinarily honest person.
But in that picture book...
Noland's last excuse in
the picture book is like this.
"That's right! The mountain
of gold sank in the sea!"
A stupid-looking face is drawn in this book...
...but he shed many tears
and died a regrettable death.
He was sure that the island
he reached was Jaya,
where he found the wreckage of a city of gold.
He felt that there was no way
it was just an illusion.
Noland insisted that the ruins had
submerged due to crustal movements,
but everyone thought he was
making excuses out of desperation.
Noland was executed in front
of the laughing onlookers,
and only the name "Liar" remained.
Oh, I see! You're looking for
the city of gold on the seabed
in order to clear the Montblanc family's name!
Don't be silly!
Usopp!!
I thought I'd die...
How honest my distant ancestor was,
or how great an explorer he was,
has nothing to do with me!
Can you understand how a kid would
feel being laughed at by strangers
just because he's the
descendant of such an idiot?!
That's how I grew up!
But... yeah, over the past 400 years,
many set sail to restore our family's honor,
though all of them went missing.
I was ashamed of such a family.
I ran away from home and became a pirate.
Oh? You're a pirate, too?
It's not that I wanted to become a pirate.
I just wanted to escape from Noland's spell.
And over time, I came to
have my own pirate group.
At long last, I entered the Grand Line,
and I spent all my time on adventures.
But ten years ago, my ship
reached this island by accident.
Strangely enough, only I,
who continued to hate the Montblanc
family and Noland the most, made it here.
The island didn't have a city of gold,
just like the picture book said.
As I stood on a cape of the island,
I felt that it was destiny.
There was no place to escape to.
Let's settle this, Noland!
Hell, no! Captain, we're not gonna have
anything to do with your family's problem!
If you insist on searching
for the gold, do it alone!
We're splitting here. Goodbye, Captain.
If it's there, that's fine.
If it's not there, that's fine, too.
It's not that I want to prove his innocence.
This is a duel with the man
who threw a wrench into my life.
I want to set the record straight before I die.
This is indeed a man's...
Then, what about them?
Why are those monkeys, here?
There must've been an exciting drama
spoken with the fists of men
committed to exploring the seabed.
Those guys are fans of the picture book.
Fans?!
That's a quite simple connection.
I think it was five or six years ago.
They heard a rumor about
me and barged in on me.
They said, "We think
Noland's gold definitely exists!"
Shojo!
Are you ready to take me on
after suddenly kicking me like that?!
Hey, that's an outrageous
false accusation, Masira!
Don't make me angry!
The sea around here is deep.
In the dark, cold sea, you're
haunted by a deeper solitude.
I just dived and searched alone every day.
They just came into my life
and became my underlings without
my permission, and they romp around.
Single-minded idiots like them...
make me feel relieved, to be honest.
Do you understand?
I do. Yeah, real comrades give
each other strength and...
Well, putting the story
about those monkeys aside...
Then, don't ask! Clench your teeth!
Like I said... I wanna go
to the sky island, old guy!
You're a hasty one!
Yeah, I did tell you, right? The witness
to the sky island is that Noland the Liar.
If you have anything to do with him,
you'll be laughed at like me.
What?! He's been to the sky island, too?!
Unfortunately, this doesn't say he did, but...
A logbook?! Could it be Noland's?
That's right.
Read around there.
Amazing... A logbook from 400 years ago...
Sea Ephemeris Year 1120, June 21st, Sunny.
We left Villa, a cheerful town.
Following the Log Pose, we should be
heading east-northeast from the harbor.
We got a rare item from a bumboat
that we came across during the day.
It's a ski-like one-person boat called a waver.
It's a mysterious boat that can generate wind
and move even on a day without wind.
It seems that you need to get the hang
of it to ride, and I couldn't manage it.
Right now, it's become
a perfect toy for my crew.
No way! What's this? I want it!
Never mind that, keep reading!!
The power for this seems to be a
product found only on the sky island,
and I hear that many peculiar
things like that exist in the sky.
Speaking of the sky island, one of my
explorer friends showed me a live skyfish.
I was surprised at how strange the fish looked.
Skyfish?
To our ship, it's still an unknown area,
but as a sailor, I'd like to go
to the sea in the sky one day.
Montblanc Noland...
He said "the sea in the sky"!
It's just like Robin said!!
And it sounds like the sky island was a
pretty normal thing for people back them.
So it really does exist!
Alright!!
Hey, old-timer! How are you feeling?!
Couldn't be better!
Glad to hear it!
Old-timer, this bastard...
Shut up and listen. Do you like those guys?
Why do you ask?
It seems like they wanna go
to the sky island at any cost.
Sky island... If they wanna go,
there's only one way to get there.
If they try on their own, they'll get
killed immediately, old-timer.
Exactly... so why don't we give them a hand?
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
We can finally go to the sky! To the sky!!
I wonder what kind of place the sky island is!
I'm so excited!
It's an adventure befitting me, Captain Usopp!
But it'll be a life-threatening voyage.
Yeah, it'll be a life-threatening...
What? Hey, Luffy, let's forget about it.
You...!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Steer for the Clouds! Capture the South Bird!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!