Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
While Buggy and Mr. 3 got out of level 4,
moribund Luffy had been treated by
Ivankov, the queen of New Kama Land...
...the land of vanished prisoners
and recovered miraculously!
I know what's going on in the world now.
The world is about to change with the Navy
and the Whitebeard Pirates as major players!
But he's not gonna make a move yet!
He's the mastermind of all revolutionaries
in the world and my comrade!
The revolutionary--Dragon!
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
What?!
Dragon is...
...your dad?!
After finding out that Luffy is Dragon's son,
Ivankov decided to accompany him in rescuing Ace!
The Vivre Card was pointing down
which means that he's still here!
Alright, Portgaz D. Ace!
We will take you to Marineford...
...where the execution ground is!
"Ace's Convoy Begins! Battle
on the Lowest Floor Level 6!"
Ace!
Hurry up!
Don't let them pass!
--They're coming!
--Move it! Move it! Move it!
Ready!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Dammit! Take this!
What an annoying trap! Ha!
Death Wink!
Heehaw!
We better hurry!
Oh! You're right! Hmmm?
W-Who are you people?!
Hey, you! Could you come
with us for a minute?
--No, wait! Let me go!
--Don't worry! You won't regret it!
Let's go! We can't spare even a second.
Don't hesitate! Attack him!
Clear the way! Gum-Gum...
...Ricochet!
The trap didn't work! And
the jailers are out cold!
Straw Hat Luffy! Ivankov--the king of queers!
Inazuma--the revolutionary!
The three criminals are
now entering... level 6!
Ace!
So this is level 6!
Only legendary criminals have been
held here in the Eternal Hell!
Where are you, Ace?!
I'm here to save you!
Ace, where are you?!
Ace!
You can't just yell blindly!
Would you like to tell us where he is?!
N-No, I would not!
Oh no, what should I do then?!
You have to be true to yourself!
W-What're you gonna do to me?!
Emporio...
...Female Hormone!
W-What happened?
Wow! He turned into a woman!
How do you like being your true self?
What?! Is that me?!
You're reborn!
You're not a jailer anymore,
you're a New Kama now!
Oh! How fabulous!
Thank you very much, Ivan-sama!
I found my true identity!
Oh, don't mention it!
--By the way...
--Where's Ace?!
That way!
Ace!
Is this it?!
Ace?!
He's not here!
Are you sure that this is the right cell?!
Yes, I am! I'm not lying...
We're a bit too late.
It's a straw hat! So he must be... Yes!
She said that my brother's here!
He's really here! He broke into
the impregnable Impel Down
and made it all the way down to level 6!
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
Yeah.
They took him just now!
Go! They've taken Ace-san to the elevator!
Go! You can still catch them!
Who're you, old man?
He's a big deal!
Okay, I got it!
Thank you! Whoever you are!
I can't believe it!--
Even after risking your life, it's almost
impossible to get all the way here!
Did he really get through all five hells?!
My brother would do something
like that! He does stupid things!
Since we were kids, he always
made me worry, that fool!
They took that to the upper floors!
Let's go!
They've left the iron door
to the elevator open!
Nice!
The operation system is locked! It's no good!
It doesn't work?!
But we can just climb!
Do it!
Okay!
T-That was close!
Of course, they wouldn't
allow us to climb it!
It's not usable! They're
already keeping an eye on it!
Let's go back up the stairs!
You can't get away!
Hey, they blocked the staircase!
They're trying to trap us!
We gotta break through! There's no other way!
Alright!
That's a lot of gas! Is it poisonous?!
Poison gas, again?!
Hey, you guys!
I don't know who you
are but don't make us suffer with you!
Shut up, you level 6 people!
-- I don't care if it's poisonous or not!
-- Wait!
It's sleeping gas!
How reckless you are, Straw boy!
You really need to stop...
We don't want to...
They wanna make us sleep
to stop us in our tracks!
Vice Warden, we've blocked
off level 6 completely!
The sleeping gas is potent
and there's no place to run!
Keep the guards armed and
on standby just in case!
Did you report to Warden Magellan?!
Just now!
Good!
My job is safe now!
Now I'll lay the blame on
Magellan for all of this mess
and then I'll become the warden...
The microphone's still on!
Whaaat?!
What unfortunate timing!
Straw Hat made it to level
6 just after we left!
L-Luffy!
We're completely trapped!
The emergency sleeping gas
has just been released!
It's only a matter of time
before they catch Straw Hat!
The Freezing Hell wasn't
punishment enough for him!
Since the cell that you were in is open now,
this time he'll be held on level
6 and will suffer greatly!
-- Luffy...
-- Don't stop! Keep walking!
You!
You better not resist because it's useless!
Luffy!
Your brother is also a pirate! There's
no way that he'll walk out of here alive.
I wished that she was lying!
Why did you come, Luffy?!
Anyway, no one can live after that much
poison no matter how strong he is!
How did you recover,
Straw Hat?!
We made it back to level 3!
We still got another half to go!
It was faster on our way down because
we often fell down accidentally!
I can't walk another step!
I'm thirsty!
What?! Let me take a break for a minute!
What are you...?!
Hello!
Gnocchi!
You're still here?!
Penne! Buckwheat noodle with an egg!
--Let us go!
Buckwheat noodle with fried tofu!
Wheat-flour noodle in curry soup!
Wheat-flour noodle?!
Do something!
The floor's gonna be filled with gas!
Help me!
Who is he?!
He's cutting the floor like paper!
Now he's flipping the floor like paper!
He blocked the gas with the floor!
That's amazing!
Inazuma ate the Snip-Snip Fruit
and now he's a scissor-man!
He can manipulate whatever
he cuts as though it's paper!
Oh, really?
Wake up! I'm fighting off
the urge to sleep but I...
I...
...Don't sleep!
Were you kidding just now?!
You're awake!
I wanna keep going! Crab-chan!
You've blocked the staircase but
now I can't catch up with Ace!
That was the only way to stop the gas!
If you fall unconscious, you can't save him!
I'm gonna save him even if I'm
unconscious! I don't want him die!
Don't be ridiculous!
It's simple but their plan defeated us!
We're confined to level 6! There's
no way for us to get out!
I'm sorry but this is all I can do now!
They can't see us anymore!
You have to realize--we're too late!
They must've gotten to the top
floor with Ace boy by now!
On the other hand, we have a lot
of obstacles standing in our way!
The Navy's convoy is pretty
quick! Look at the Vivre Card!
It's not pointing straight up, is it?
I think that Ace has already
been handed over to the Navy!
You're right on time!
We transfer custody of the criminal
- Portgaz D. Ace to the Navy!
Here.
It's just a paper.
Yes, but that paper will
lead us to one another.
You don't want it?
No, I want it!
Luffy!
We need to move on now!
I'll do my best to help you break
out of this great prison safely!
They'll hand over Ace boy to the
Navy Headquarters at any cost!
You need to give up on him!
I mean, you need to trust Whitebeard.
He's not gonna give up on one of his
own! He'll definitely do something!
--I'm going!
--Huh?!
I'm gonna go to Navy headquarters!
Don't be stupid!
There's a battle brewing between
the world's two leading forces!
What can you do?!
Do you know how strong Whitebeard is?!
What about the admirals, vice-admirals,
and Warlords on the Navy side?!
Don't you remember that you fought
just Magellan and almost died?!
Do you have that many lives to spare?!
What?
If I give up now...
...I'm gonna regret it!
I've seen this face so many times before!
It's exactly like looking at Dragon!
But first of all, how can
you get off of this floor?!
If you wanna get out of here, set me free!
I can create a hole on the ceiling!
What do you think?
You're being held here?!
Crocodile!
It's been a while!
Straw Hat!
Joining forces with Crocodile and Jimbei, Luffy and the others plan their escape.
Meanwhile, Hannyabal takes note of their actions
and is determined to settle things for his
own gain, so he turns his gaze to level 4.
The final showdown between the Straw Hats
and Impel Down is about begin!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ultimate Team Has Formed! Shaking Impel Down!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!