Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates
who are looking to destroy
the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken,
who is after Shirahoshi,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
If I join the Warlords,
Aladdin and the others who
don't want to be pirates...
...can live in this country
without being chased
under the amnesty of the Government.
Big Brother is dead!
We'll go our own way, just like we used to!
The Sun Pirates split into three groups
and went separate ways.
"Shaking Fish-Man Island! A
Celestial Dragon Drifts In!"
THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
I'm back!
I still can't believe that this day has come!
When we were the Celestial Dragons' slaves,
we were hopeless and all we
had was hatred toward them.
We got away from the Celestial
Dragons thanks to Boss Tai
but still they were looking for us.
I thought being a pirate was
the only way to survive.
But now we can even go back to
our hometown without hiding!
We are free!
Captain! No, Brother Jimbei!
I'll never forget what you've done for us!
Don't be so dramatic.
I won't, but we know what you did.
You needed the amnesty of the
Government to help free us.
That's why you joined the Warlords.
It's not as though you wanted to join them.
Quit this chatting and go
to your family already!
Look! They're becoming impatient.
--Honey...
--Dad!
--Baby...
--Just go to them.
--Dad!
--Honey!
Aladdin, you were a slave just like them.
But now you can get off of the ship finally.
Jimbei.
We will no longer be chased
as renegade slaves.
All of us can stay with family without fear.
But just like the mark
of the Celestial Dragons,
because of our terrible experience as
slaves, our hatred toward humans...
...will never go away!
Of course I understand what
Brother Tai truly meant...
But...
I can't believe that Boss Jimbei
is becoming a tool of the
World Government... or humans!
Did he forget who killed Tiger-san?
I've lost respect for Boss Jimbei.
I knew that there were many islanders
who didn't like the idea
of me joining the Warlords.
THE RYUGU PALACE
Thanks to Jimbei's momentous decision,
now we have a relationship
with the World Government.
In order to use this opportunity to
establish friendly relations with humans,
I will keep trying hard!
But even if it's for his friends,
I can't believe Jimbei took
on such a big burden-jamon.
When he gets an order from
the World Government,
he has no choice but to fight...
...whether he likes it or not-jamon.
He will put himself in
harm's way and occasionally
his blood will be spilled.
I know.
I won't let Jimbei's sacrifice end up wasted.
I have to do my best, as well!
But don't push yourself too hard.
Because I don't want you to
suffer another hangover-jamon!
Oh...
And then something happened that would
change Queen Otohime's life forever.
An uninvited visitor came to the island...
Ryugu Kingdom! Ryugu Kingdom!
This is border patrol speaking!
A huge wrecked ship is seeking
emergency entry into the country!
What are you waiting for?!
Accept them already...
It can't be true!
A Celestial Dragon is on board!
What?!
King Neptune!
A Celestial Dragon?!
Accept them!
--Send a rescue team immediately!
--Yes, ma'am!
I'll meet them myself!
Otohime-sama!
What is a Celestial Dragon
doing on the seafloor?
It's a Celestial Dragon's ship!
Must've been attacked by
some deep-sea creature.
They look down on us Fish-Men.
How come they were in such deep water?
Hurry up!
Damn! They are all dead! What weaklings!
Bring me a breathing mask now, you fishes!
A WORLD NOBLE (CELESTIAL
DRAGON) SAINT MYOSGARD
I can't stand this Fish-man's smell!
Bring me a mask now!
Hurry up and save my life, you fools!
He has no respect of us!
That's not how you ask somebody to help you!
Doctor!
I need a doctor!
--Is a medical team here?
--They're here but...
...they don't know what to do with "it."
We have to kill him.
They are the scum of the world!
The Seven Warlords are nothing!
I'm not gonna work for the World Government
or anybody, even if they beg me to!
That's our Captain Vander Decken!
Jimbei is no match for me as
a pirate in the first place,
no match at all, I suspect!
Hm? What's going on at the harbor?
Hey.
Captain, he said that a
Celestial Dragon is here.
Celestial Dragon?
Looks like his ship has wrecked
and he's asking for help.
Sounds like fun. Let's go see it.
This wasn't how it was supposed to be...
What?! The Fish-Man slaves
went back to their island?!
Why is it, My Daddy?
Here is the thing, My Son.
A Fish-Man named Jimbei just
joined the Seven Warlords.
Jimbei?
And the Sun Pirates which he belongs
to were hiding all those slaves
but their evasion charges were
dropped by the amnesty of the
Government so they went back home, My Son.
I think the slaves who escaped from
my place are among them, My Daddy.
I'm sure of it.
It makes me sick to think
that they are living a
free and easy life now.
I'm gonna go get them back, My Daddy!
Because I've spent a lot of money
to collect those Fish-Man slaves!
Gee! I didn't know that the deep
sea was such a horrifying place.
Hey, what are you guys doing?
What?
It's been a while, huh? Myosgard.
How dare you address me without my title! Oh?
Oh, you were my slaves!
You just have to come home with me!
I didn't give you my permission
to be free, fishes!
D-Don't do it, guys!
He's a Celestial Dragon!
If you kill him, the
amnesty will become void!
Don't do it, fools! Know your place!
Who do you think I am?!
I'm... I'm...
The Navy admirals will come to the aid of a
Celestial Dragon in danger
in the world above.
That's why people are afraid of your folk.
But you're on the Fish-Man
Island at the seafloor.
As long as the islanders stay quiet,
whatever happens to you here,
they'll think it was an accident.
He's right...
--I won't say anything!
--Me too! Of course!
He's barely alive. He's
gonna die soon anyway!
Let him suffer the same
way that you slaves did!
--Kill him!
--Make him suffer!
Show him no mercy!
What's going on?
I thought I was a respected man...
For the life of me...
I can't forgive you!
Hey, don't!
--Do it!
--Kill him!
Don't do it!
You stupid fishes!
Queen Otohime!!
The Queen has been shot!
Queen Otohime...
Everybody, drop your gun!
Children are watching!
Aladdin!
Where is the Celestial Dragon
who's ship was wrecked?!
I just got here, myself.
Boss Jimbei!
Our mother rushed out of the palace!
What?
Brother-sama, who are the Celestial Dragons?
They are humans, Shirahoshi.
Humans?
There are quite a few humans out
there and they are the scary ones.
I heard some gunshots too.
Let's go.
O-Otohime-sama...
It's just a scratch.
Why do you protect him?
You don't know what he did to us in the past!
He treated us like we were
animals, not even slaves.
I can feel your anguish - it's very painful.
Mother-sama!
I know it's hard but...
...you can't plant your anger and resentment
toward humans in children's mind!
They need a chance to meet humans
and figure them out on their own.
So, please!
Don't tell the people on the island anything!
Neither the tragedy we endured
nor of our anger towards humans!
Brother Tai...
Watch out, Mother-sama!
Don't move!
Oh no! Your Majesty!
Mother!
That bastard!
Queen?
To a Celestial Dragon like me,
the Queen of a fish country
is just another commoner...
...or even less!
What an asshole!
Mother-sama!
You fools! What are you doing?!
Get me a mask and a doctor! Otherwise...
Mother-sama!!
What?!
It's the Sea Kings!!
What was that?
It didn't look like a coincidence...
Shirahoshi... Don't tell me you are...
What's the matter, Captain?
According to the family legend, a long
long time ago, there was a Mermaid...
...who possessed mysterious power that
could even control the Sea Kings!
Vander Decken I decided to look into
the legend and headed for the seafloor.
My ancestors! I finally found her!
Shirahoshi is the legendary Mermaid?
You did it, Captain!
Shh! Don't let anybody hear about it.
It's a secret legend that only
my family knows, I suspect!
If I can control the Sea Kings as
I wish, I can do anything I want.
I can have anything I want!
So, what are we gonna do now?
Kidnap Princess Shirahoshi?
First, I have to marry her.
What?!
But she's still a kid now.
Hmmm... that's the problem!
Aladdin...
Let me treat him.
Thank you.
I'll treat you next.
A few weeks later,
when the Celestial Dragon
who's life has been saved was
about to leave for home,
Queen Otohime did an unexpected thing.
I'll get even with you!
Although I'm a respected
World Noble, you insulted me
and harassed me terribly.
You fishes, I'll make you
feel sorry for what you did!
Is that what we get for saving his life?
We provided a ship and
crew for him to go home!
How could he say that?!
We shouldn't let him go! It's
dangerous to this island!
Wait a minute!
You seem like you have more to say.
In that case, I'll come with
you to the world above.
To the world above?!
That's too dangerous, Otohime-sama!
Mother-sama!
Wait-jamon, Otohime! I won't let you do that!
If you wish to negotiate
with the Nobles, I'll go!
I'm sure humans won't catch you
since you're the King and a Great Knight.
Then let me...
No, there is no point if
it's a strong man like you!
We have to show that
even a weak woman can
go there and return home
if we want to prove to our nation
it's totally safe up there.
I'm physically more fragile than
anyone - that's why it makes
more sense for me to go.
--Mother-sama!
Otohime-sama!
Where are you going, Otohime-sama?
Otohime...
Trust the woman who you chose to be your wife
and the humans.
She's just a fish queen - how arrogant!
Mother-sama!
Jimbei...
No one can stop her.
All we can do is trust her and wait.
Your Majesty! Please be careful!
Otohime-sama!
Mother-sama!
Otohime brought a single
paper back from the surface.
It represents a light of
hope for Fish-Man Island.
Gathering numerous signatures,
her dream becomes the dream
of all of Fish-Man Island.
Fish-Man Island seemed ready to change,
when all of a sudden,
a gunshot rings out across
all of Fish-Man Island!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Sudden Tragedy! A Gunshot
Shuts Down the Future!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!