Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Foolish pirates.
You'd knowingly attack
the invincible fleet
commanded by Captain
Usopp-sama of the Going Merry?!
Attack them, men! Attack!
C'mon, you guys.
Show some interest in other people...
All done!
Look! A pirate flag!
Now that Usopp's joined
and we have four people,
we need to have our own mark!
That's our mark?
Whadya think? Nice, huh?!
A pirate flag is a symbol of death.
A symbol of fear!
I do sense fear, though...
Fear of your talent.
Wish you would've told me first!
Don't forget about me,
the gifted artist!
Gifted artist?
I've drawn graffiti on walls
for 50 years straight!
When it comes to painting,
I'm in a league all my own!
Awesome! 50 years?!
That means he's an old man now!
Not only that, he must have
5 or 6 grandkids by now!
That's awesome, too!
Hey!
Alright! Behold this work of art!
Tadah!
Who told you to make your flag?!
I guess that's more like it.
Wow, it's pretty good!
Yeah! It's good! I like it!
So this is our mark...
Alright! Usopp!
Draw one on the sail, too!
Right!
Alright! All done!
Now the Going Merry
pirate ship is all set!
"You're the Weird Creature!
Gaimon and His Strange Friends"
I'm pooped...
Is this the right way?
It seems kinda dangerous...
What?!
Wait.
That's it! That's the place!
No doubt about it!
Do you see something neat?
The legendary Treasure Island.
The legendary Treasure Island?
I've heard of that before!
Yeah! It's a famous
island among pirates!
As are the weird stories about it...
Weird stories?
That whoever gets near the
island incurs a god's wrath...
W-Were the rumors really true?!
Is this the god's wrath?!
That sounds kinda neat!
Luffy! You're not thinking of--
We sure are!
Let's go! Treasure Island!
This is one creepy island!
Yeah?
It's said that an extraordinary treasure
rests somewhere on this island.
Supposedly, lots of pirates
have landed here in the past,
but they've all fled in terror
before they could even look for it.
In terror?
Supposedly, one pirate's face
suddenly changed into a boar's face,
and another's mustache stretched
out and strangled him like snakes.
That's not real, right?
Though I'm sure the stories
are exaggerated somewhat!
D-Don't scare me like that!
I'm hungry.
I'm going to sleep.
How can he sleep in
a creepy place like this?
Yeah. What kind of
nerves does he have?
What are you doing?! Don't scare me!
N-No, I just thought I'd do
a little dance to liven things up!
See? See? See?
Stop that, Luffy...
W-What is this?!
Leave...
Who's there?!
Leave!
Where's it coming from?!
I am this island's protective god!
Leave this island at once
if you value your lives!
Protective god?
You guys're pirates, aren't you?
Yeah.
Pirates, just as I thought.
Why would a god ask
something like that?
Listen! Just try taking
another step into the forest!
The instant you do, will you
receive my divine punishment
and meet your doom?!
How should I know?
Why are you asking me?
What's the deal?
This guy seems kinda weird.
What did you say, straw hat boy?!
W-What are these things?!
Humans I completely transformed
when they came to look for treasure.
Then you really are a god?!
Look at all these weird things...
Is this a lion?
Are you sure it's not a pig?
Oww! Oww! Oww!
W-What exactly are you?!
I'm a rubber person!
I ate a Devil Fruit!
Devil Fruit?! Don't be absurd!
I heard rumors about them long ago
when I used to be a pirate, but...
When you used to be a pirate?
N-No! I'm not reminiscing
about old times at all!
No, I don't want to
hear about old times!
What're you talking about?
You're the one who said it!
Are you really a god?!
Shut up! If you won't leave,
then receive my divine punishment!
Now you've done it, God!
H-How are you all right?!
--There you are!
--Don't move!
I told you not to move!
That can't be!
Hey, God or whoever!
Pistols don't work on this guy!
But they surprise me,
so I don't like 'em!
M-Monster!
O-Over there!
Here it is. His pistol.
Where'd he go?
What is this?
This is a god?
It's moving!
Stand me up, already!
I said stand me up!
He's a person!
Neat! Is he a scrub brush?
What's so god-like about you?!
You thought you could trick us!
Shut up! Stand me up, I say!
Don't act all big after
you've fallen over!
I-I'll let you go for today!
Wait!
Huh?!
--Hey! Luffy!
--Luffy!
There. You're all set.
You're a pretty popular guy, God...
So you used these guys
to scare off everyone
who came to the island?
But I've never seen a person stuffed
inside a treasure chest before!
Are you a boxed and sheltered son?
Yeah. I've been overly pampered
since I was just a little boy...
Of course I'm not!
I can't get out of this box!
I've been alone on this island
and in this box for 20 years now!
20 years?!
You've been all alone on
this island for 20 years?
My hair and mustache
are just as you can see.
Even my eyebrows got connected...
It's also been 20 years since I've
conversed with anyone like this.
Can you understand how painful this is?
It seems ridiculous.
What did you say?!
Oh, here you are...
You were asleep this whole time,
even after all that happened?!
W-Who's this guy?!
Notice sooner.
He's a guy stuffed in a treasure chest!
Are you a boxed and sheltered son?!
Yeah. I've been overly pampered
since I was just a little boy...
Of course I'm not!
Don't do the same stupid gag twice!
Zoro! Gimme a hand!
Ouch! Ouch!
What are you doing?! Stop it!
You're pulling my head off!
You're right! You can't get out!
Don't be crazy!
Because of my lack of
exercise over the years,
this treasure chest fits
together with my body now!
If you try to break it,
my body'll get destroyed, too!
He's a strangely annoying guy.
But who are you guys?
You're nothing like any of the
other pirates who've come here.
I'm Luffy! The man who's
gonna be King of the Pirates!
W-What?!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates
and get the One Piece!
The One Piece?!
Don't tell me you're seriously
planning to enter the Grand Line?!
We even have a chart of the Grand Line!
Don't take it lightly!
That place is Hell, or a graveyard!
I once saw pirates who'd managed
to escape from the Grand Line!
They looked almost like people
who had died and lost their souls!
Something incredibly
horrific must've happened,
or they must've run into
monsters or something...
Not a single one of them
even tried to speak.
On top of that, rumors about the
One Piece spawn even more rumors,
so there's no telling what's true or not!
Some 20-odd years since the
start of the Great Pirate Era,
the One Piece is already a dream
within a dream beyond a legend!
So which is the Grand Line?
Dunno. Don't you know,
old scrub brush guy?
I can't read sea charts one bit.
Oh. Then we're the same.
That's not a pirate conversation!
Anyways, even if we do
enter the Grand Line,
earning as much money as we can,
then escaping, is the best idea.
I will find the One Piece!
I have good luck!
Where does all that
confidence of yours come from?
I will get it! You'll see!
Whatever you say...
You're the same...
You're just like me;
you even look like me,
like we're twins!
How in the world
does he look like you?!
I understand! Achieving
your dreams someday!
We used to think the same way!
We?
We were willing to put our lives
on the line to search for treasure!
It was that zeal that
changed my entire life!
W-Wait. What do you mean?
It was 20 years ago.
My fellow pirates and I
landed on this island.
To find the treasure that
was said to rest here.
200 men have searched for
a month now, but it's no use!
All we've found on this island
is this one empty treasure chest!
We're leaving, men!
What're you doing, Gaimon?
We're going on ahead!
Yeah.
Did anyone look up there?
The captain stayed down
here the whole month...
I'll check it out one last time!
I couldn't believe my own eyes!
I-I found it! It's up here!
Hey! Guys!
That's when I got stuck in the chest!
When I came to, my crew
was already far out to sea.
Crap!
Wait a minute!
Does that mean that
fortune is all mine?!
I can't climb up like this!
I can't get out! I can't get out!
Hey! Come back!
Even after all this time,
the fortune I only saw for an
instant has never left my mind.
Pirates have come to this island
in search of treasure countless times,
but I used these guys
to scare them all away.
That's how I've protected
the treasure for 20 years now!
It's mine!
Yeah! No question about it! It's yours!
Alright, Gaimon-san!
We'll get the treasure for you!
--R-Really?!
--Yeah!
Don't tell me you're gonna...
Aren't you a thief who
only steals from pirates?
How rude!
Even I know what's
appropriate and what's not!
Here?
I haven't been here for a while, myself.
The time has finally come!
Today is a great day!
I'm counting on you, Straw Hat!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Yes!
W-Well?! Is it there?!
What's he doing?
Luffy!
Hey! Luffy!
What the heck's going on?!
I found 'em! Six treasure chests!
W-Well done!
I finally got it!
The treasure! The treasure!
Toss my treasure down here!
--Hurry! Hurry!
--No.
What?!
No! I don't wanna toss it down!
What nonsense is this?!
Quit joking around!
Yeah! That treasure belongs
to Gaimon-san! Toss it all down!
Quit clowning around, you!
It's all right.
It doesn't matter anymore.
Of course it does!
Yeah! You've guarded that
treasure for 20 years, Gaimon-san!
Straw Hat. You're...
...a great guy!
What do you mean?
I had a slight inkling
that might be the case...
I tried to avoid
thinking about it, but...
They're empty, aren't they?
Yeah. They're all empty.
That's terrible...
The treasure he guarded for 20 years
was just empty boxes...
It happens all the time with
treasures that have treasure maps...
You go to look, but
someone's already stolen it.
That's how much of an ordeal
treasure-hunting is for pirates.
You can wait all your life, or lose
your life, and never touch treasure...
There are more pirates like
that than you can count!
Don't be so upset, old guy!
It's a good thing we
came after 20 years!
30 years later and you
might've been dead!
Straw Hat...
--Luffy...
--He's...
You've made this much
of a fool of yourself!
All you got left now is the One Piece!
Come be a pirate again with us!
You're... inviting me?!
No one's even tried to talk to me
before when they saw me like this!
How many years it's been
since I trusted someone!
Thank you...
You're really gonna stay
on this island, old guy?
Yeah, Straw Hat.
Even if there is no treasure,
there's something else I want to protect.
Eh?
Something you want to protect?
I've shared hard times and happy
times with these guys for 20 years.
I can't leave them now.
Now that I know there's no treasure,
I somehow finally feel free.
I think I can really
live a life I want now.
Plus, I've actually grown
a bit fond of being in this box!
Oh! That's too bad, then!
You're a neat old guy, too!
So the weird creatures
are your true friends...
He's the weirdest creature
of them all, though!
Say what?!
See ya! Take care!
Bye!
Straw Hat...
Strive for your dream, for me.
You, if anyone, will surely get
the legendary treasure,
the One Piece!
And then...
buy the world!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Hey, Zoro. When did you start
using the Three-Sword Style?
Oh, it--
You're so dumb! Zoro would
never tell anyone about himself!
Actually...
One sword is different
from the others, right?
--He just couldn't get a full set!
--Hey!
It's just some ordinary old sword?!
Shut up, you guys!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Three-Sword Style's Past!
Zoro and Kuina's Vow!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!