Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
"Upper Yard" "Angel Island"
The survival battle in
God's Land, Upper Yard, continues.
Priest Ohm, who serves God Eneru.
Wyper, a Shandian warrior.
Gan Fall, the Sky Knight.
And Zoro.
Their fierce battle for survival has started.
Ahhhh... That idiot...!
Aisa!
You're idiots who can't
even protect yourselves.
Quit worrying about others!
At any rate, no one will survive!
"The Ordeal of Iron!
White Barbed Death Match!!"
That's our Ohm-sama!
The survivors in the Upper Ruins
are four Divine Soldiers.
Since those two are probably still alive,
that makes four Shandians
and one Blue Sea person.
One giant snake and Holy...
In other words, ten people and two animals.
It'll be five survivors soon,
just like God prophesied.
Now, let's continue the battle, shall we?
I'll finish you off.
Ohm! You bastard!
How dare you harm Wyper?!
Oh? Even when this man is
but a speck in God's eyes,
he is that important to you?
Wyper is our leader!!
We've shared the Shandians' pride!
In order to take back our
homeland that was taken away!
Eneru's servant can't
understand the Shandians' bond!
Well, even if I understood it,
I wouldn't feel sympathy or empathy.
In other words...
...it's all for naught!
Die, Ohm!
Are you running away?!
It's the climax. Holy, it's time for that!
Dash, Holy!
What's he doing now?!
Dammit! What's that dog
doing?! This is trouble!
This surely is... the
Iron Ordeal's true form!
The white barbed death match!
Fence or no fence, I'm not running away.
You fool! It's not just so
you can't run away anymore!
You're surrounded by the white barbs!
So what?!
In other words...
...once you touch it, you'll get hurt!
So where do I get out when
I'm done with you all?!
You can think about that when you're done.
Eight more people and two animals left!
I'd better do something
about that giant snake first.
Nami's in it... and...
Sky Knight!!
...so's the guy who saved Chopper.
Wyper...
When we were small, you told me...
Our ancestors originally
lived in the Blue Sea...
...in the sacred city, Shandora.
The Great Warrior Calgara
protected our homeland.
But 400 years ago...
...Shandora was shot up to
Skypiea by the Knock-Up Stream.
They could never go back to the Blue Sea.
It must've been very tough for them.
But Skypieans took over the land,
calling it "sacred ground"!
Our ancestors were driven
out of their homeland.
We can't go back to our sacred city.
We aren't even allowed to touch
the ground of our homeland!
For 400 long years, we, Shandians,
have suffered humiliation!
That Upper Yard belongs to us!
We will take back... our homeland...
...as well as our ancestors' pride!
Once we defeat Eneru, we won't need
to revere a single bag of Vearth.
We're going back. To the 400-year-old
homeland of the Shandians!
Those who aren't prepared,
stay here. I won't blame you.
C'mon, Wyper! We're always prepared!
Are you prepared to abandon
anyone who falls during the fight?
Those who can step over comrades
and keep moving, come with me!
Today... Eneru's head will be mine!
Wyper!
Wyper!!
I'm glad I found you!
Laki!
Wyper! Listen to me!
Why did you come here?!
I came here to give you Kamakiri's message!
No one can... defeat him...
Get out of here, Wyper! Don't fight!
Eneru is in the forest!
Hey, Laki!
Eneru is lightning itself, which people
have feared as God since long ago.
Don't come near here! Get out of here!
There's no way we can defeat him!
Hey, stop it!
Wyper...?
You called me?
Eneru...
Stop it, Eneru! Don't!
She abandoned the battle!
Hey!!
Laki!!
Laki! Don't fight him!
Laki!
Run!!
You fool! Don't think you can survive
while you're worrying about others!
He's... invincible...!
He's lightning... which people have
feared as God... since long ago...
I got you, Wyper!
You fool!
Get out of here!
Eneru!!
Oh? It didn't work on him?
Then, I'll give you another shot!
You're softer than I thought.
Wyper, Shandian warrior!
Even if she's a woman, she's still a warrior.
I treat all those that challenge me equally.
Well, try your best not to die.
That's... God?!
Man, what a foolish woman,
insolently attacking God.
She received divine punishment.
Before I get out of here, I have
to take care of something.
You giant snake!
I have business with your stomach!
Don't stand in my way!
Holy! Shake hands!
Eisen Whip!
Axe!
Six people and two animals left!
Ow, ow...
Good. Looks like she wasn't seriously hurt.
Where on earth...?
We're in the snake's stomach.
We were swallowed!
Oh, that's right. It seems
to be quite a long stomach.
Hey, Aisa, are you all right?
W-Wyper, I'm sorry!
Huh?
What is this place?
Inside the snake's stomach.
Pay more attention! You're so slow.
Snake's...?!
Now, let's get out of here
before its stomach melts us.
I wonder if the waver still works.
In any case, why aren't you on the ship?
We were chased and had no choice but to run.
Well, more importantly,
isn't that girl Shandian?
Wha...?! God!
I'll eliminate you!
Hey! Stop it!
Anyway, can't we break
through this stomach wall?
Are you nuts?! What're we gonna do
if irritating it makes it go wild?!
Do you wanna die?! Try to use your head more!
O-Oh, that was a joke.
Are you crazy?!
You're really weird, weird knight!
Geez...
If there's someone who'd
seriously try to irritate this snake,
I'd like to meet 'em.
This sound...
It's footsteps.
What could be in a place like this?
Who is it?!
Nami! Weird old man!
You...
Luffy!
What're you doing?!
In a mystery cave like this?!
What are you doing in a place like this?!
I couldn't get out of this place.
I can't believe it!
To think that you were
swallowed by the snake too...
So the others are okay, right?!
Huh? I'm by myself.
What?! Snake?!
That's right. That's why we're here!
Oh, I see... That must've been terrible.
So, you guys were eaten by a snake, huh?
Like I said...
...so were you! We're inside
the snake's stomach!
Don't pull my nose!
That was my Usopp impression!
Who is this idiot?
I'd rather not say this,
but he's the captain of our ship.
Oh, you are the captain?
It's the end of the world.
Yeah, I guess that's how
people'd normally see it.
You must be really slow, not even
noticing that you were eaten.
Ahhh! Then this place is inside
that giant snake's stomach?!
W-Was I eaten, too?!
That's what I've been telling you.
Your clothes have melted too, you know!
Whoa! You're right!
Hey, then let's look for
its butthole right away!
Butthole?
Just where're you planning to escape from?!
We were eaten, so why not just
go "plop, plop" out of its butt?
No!! I'd rather melt!
Nami's scary.
A Blue Sea woman is brutal.
In any case, we were eaten because
this snake is in a bad mood.
Before it starts going wild again,
we'd better hurry up and...
In a bad mood?
That's right. It seemed like
it was in a very bad mood.
It was going wild all this time.
Why is it in such a bad mood?
Don't tell me...!!
Were you causing a ruckus
in here all this time?
Yeah, I thought I'd break
the wall to get out.
Er... So this was your doing.
Since I went a little wild, I got hungry.
Do you have something to eat?
Wh-What's the matter?
You... stupid idiot!!
Ha!
Groaning like a fool!
That's just what I want!
Don't let its stomach acid melt you, Aisa!
I'll tear open its stomach now!
You son of a...!
Hang in there somehow, Nami...
...and... er... weird knight!
Until I beat this guy!
Now... it's time for the finale at last!
Racing full speed ahead as always
A to Z, we run through it
We all have worries and fall many times
But we just need to rise to the top someday
What could be beyond the sea
in which the morning sun rises?
Let's go little by little toward
the brilliantly shining sun
I never treat you "bad"
How many times did we fall?
It's all right, we're definitely
pointing at tomorrow now
Smile! Come back to you, friends
Come back to you, friends
Okay! Let's hurry up and
get out from the butthole!
Like I said, I don't want to, you idiot!
Let's plop out!
What're you doing?!
How sad, swordsman from the Blue Sea.
No one can survive anymore.
Pray to God with all your heart.
Fine, you creep! But I'll never pray to God!
And I'll bring you down!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Bursting Slash! Zoro vs. Ohm!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!