Edited at https://subtitletools.com
That was close...
Th-Thanks...
Look at that. That big schedule
board got torn apart by a wave.
What's with the power of this ebbing?
The speed of the waves of
this Aqua Laguna are abnormal.
Is that right?! So Sanji went
to the station after that?
Yep!
So, anyway, no matter what means
we take to follow the sea train,
we can't do anything unless
we find Luffy and Zoro first.
Okay, got it!
Everyone, please help us out!
Guys! We're counting on you!
Yeah!
Jerry... Aurora Flicker... Jab!
Drop Kick!
This is a waste of time.
Brochette!
Where are you, Straw Hat?!
Answer us!
Hey! Look! Look!
Hmm...
Ah! Pirate lady! Hey, look over there!
There's something there!
Something?
Luffy...
Hm? That straw hat...
Isn't that your King of the Pirates?
Right?
That idiot!
Hey! Where are you going?!
Don't go down to the backstreets!
Do you wanna lose your life?!
Aqua Laguna is already coming! Come back!
This is crazy! The pirate
woman went down the stairs!
Hey! Come back! Don't go down there!
--Wait!
--Don't go to the backstreets!
Don't follow her!
Paulie-san!
It's not like all of you going
is enough to save her!
But...!
It's the sea we're up against!
You'll just end up sharing her fate!
If something happens,
I will handle things myself.
You guys just stay back!
She jumped off to the backstreets!
Boy, she makes me nervous.
So, she's headed for Straw Hat?
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Nami's Soul Cries Out!
Straw Hat Luffy Makes a Comeback!"
It's unbelievable that she
can run someplace like that.
She's really something else!
Idiots! This is no time to be impressed!
Hey! Come back right away!
You'll be swallowed by the sea!
A sea anemone...
A sea anemone is coming out
of a chimney. Why a sea anemone?
A sea anemone?
Ah...! Hey, wait, reindeer! Not you, too!
Zoro!
Nico Robin made a deal with
CP9 by giving up everything...
...for a wish that couldn't come
true if she was with you guys.
That the six Straw Hats, excluding me,
can leave this island safely!
For that, I don't care if the weapon is
brought back or the world is destroyed.
Robin! Wait! We'll fight for you
no matter who we're up against!
Robin!
Pirate lady! You're so amazing!
How foolish!
You won't make it back in time!
Just look offshore! The wave
is almost here already!
Oh, shoot! They're gonna die!
They can't make it back anymore!
Zoro! Zoro! Can you hear me?! It's me!
Chopper?
This is it. I can't go any further.
Luffy!
What the hell are you doing there?!
N... Nami! Are you there behind me?!
Well, hey, listen!
At any rate, that pigeon guy sent me flying
and I flew right into this gap.
Don't fool around at a critical time like this!
While you've been taking your
sweet time, Robin was taken away!
Robin intends to die for us!
She sacrificed herself in order to protect
us from an attack by the Government!
There's no place for me to go or go back to.
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
When she knew that she was going
to be killed if she was taken in!
Then...
...after all, Robin was...
...lying?
Yes!
Good...
Don't worry!
I'm not gonna let Robin die!
Look at that wave!
What the hell is that? It really is
several times bigger than usual!
Hey! This is seriously bad!
Pirate woman! Give up and run already!
Reindeer!
Ow! I'm being torn apart!
You aren't coming out!
How'd you get in there, Zoro?!
Owwww! Don't pull me!
What're we gonna do?!
The huge wave is almost here already!
"What're we gonna do"? How should I know?
Hm? Wait a sec. Are you carrying
the Kitetsu by any chance?
What? One of your swords?
Yes, I am. How'd you know?
For just that one, I can tell,
since it's a cursed sword.
So you were carrying it
for me, Chopper? Thanks.
Let me hold it in my hand! Hurry up!
Hurry up and run!
Climb up to a high place! Go to a higher place!
Oh, no, this is it! They're not gonna make it!
Pirate woman!
You're gonna be swallowed!
Aqua Laguna is here!
What is this...?
Goodbye.
Aqua Laguna is already so close!
What is this?
This is it!
Ahhh! What the hell?! He broke the buildings!
Zoro!
Stay back, Chopper!
One-Sword Style! Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Ahh! What the hell are they?!
Here we go, Nami!
What the hell is this?
Rumble! Jumping Point!
Hold on to me, Zoro!
Ahh... The backstreets are...!
Dammit!
Hey, look at that! It's them!
Wow! You did it!
They'll be safe, since they
got to the Great Bridge.
As big as the wave may be, it can't reach there.
You guys're amazing!
Good going, you guys!
Ahh! It's come this far!
What happened to the Straw Hats?!
Did they get swallowed by Aqua Laguna?!
No, look at that!
Paulie-san!
Dammit!
We're not safe yet! Run!
Run to the shipbuilding island!
Hurry!
The Great Bridge is gonna collapse!
What a wave...
Yeah... Unbelievable...
This is the shipbuilding island!
Even staying here doesn't seem safe.
Look! The tide is ebbing again.
It's just natural. It'll keep coming back.
The second wave... The third wave...
Just like the one we just saw!
Let us evacuate to a higher place, too!
Seriously... That was reckless!
Thanks. You saved us, rope guy.
I was shocked! So that's Aqua Laguna...
I still can't stop shaking.
If a big one like that had hit us every year,
this island would be long gone.
This year's Aqua Laguna is different.
You guys are really crazy.
I'm surprised you survived.
Ah! Monster Granny.
So you were on this island?
Of course! If we stayed in the middle
of the sea like that, we'd drown!
Ah! Pirate guy!
You were incredible! Like, wham!
Yeah, I know.
Are you trying to suffocate me?!
This idiot lost consciousness
while holding on to me.
Oh...? Come to think of it, Zoro,
why were you also being chased by the wave?
Were you in the lower side of town?
What? W-Well, not particularly...
He was stuck in a chimney.
Stuck in a chimney?
You're so clumsy, Zoro!
What'd you have to do to be in that situ...
Are you in any position to be laughing
at others?! You both are super clumsy!
Ah... Then what happened to
Sanji and Uso... I mean, Sanji?
Yeah... There're lots of things I need
to tell you. You listen, too, Zoro.
Hm?
This is my big chance.
With Buster Call, we can urgently summon
five of the Navy Headquarters'
vice admirals as well as ten battleships.
This is thanks to Aokiji for giving us,
CP9, the authority to exercise it.
Don't you think, Funkfreed?
Nico Robin, the woman whom the World
Government has been pursuing for 20 years,
has fallen straight into the hands of us, CP9.
At the same time, along with her,
we're taking in that detestable Cutty Flam,
that disciple of Tom's who
has the blueprints for Pluton.
Only two people hold the key to
the ancient weapon in this vast world.
And these two are on the sea train
headed to me right now...
The military force strong enough to
destroy the world is headed to me.
Now then...
Just wait, Robin-chan!
Your prince on a white horse is coming now!
Are you saying that Nico Robin
sacrificed herself for us?
That's right.
And the cook and Usopp are on the same train?
What do you wanna do, Captain?
There's nothing to think about.
Let's sail out right away and follow them!
There's no other way.
We're off... to rescue Robin!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
Hey! Let us borrow a ship!
A strong and fast one!
No. You can't make it through this storm.
Even if you leave now,
there's no chance you'd survive!
It doesn't matter!
Our friends are waiting for us!
There's one way-- just one way--
to get through this Aqua Laguna.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Another Sea Train? Rocketman Charges Forth!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!