Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
saa yukou
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Luffy and the Whitebeards
are trying to get to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their way.
The battle is heating up!
Then suddenly, a group of
the Navy's human weapons -
the Pacifistas appeared!
Look at the bay head! There's something!
Wh-What are they?!
So that's the human weapon of
the Government that I heard of.
K-Kuma?
"The Extermination Strategy in Action!
The Power of the Pacifistas!"
The Warlord--Bartholomew Kuma!
How come there're so many Kumas?
What's going on here?
They're the ones who ran wild
here on the Sabaody a while ago!
There're a number of Bartholomew Kumas!
Now they've got way more of them!
Head Office! Head Office!
I have big news!
Hello? Hello?!
Is this the real one?
I've heard about it from time to time
that Dr. Vegapunk was trying
to build a human weapon
and was repeatedly sending
prototypes to various places.
So they're the human weapon?
Why do they all look like Kuma?
Uncle! Didn't everything
go as you guys planned?!
I heard that pirates were
going to be easily encircled
inside the bay when we came out!
But they're scattered all over!
The broad-axe guy is yelling something.
I see what the Navy is up to!
First, they leaked the information
that they moved Ace's execution
to make us rush.
Then they slowly backed up
and lured all the pirates
inside the bay, and...
...blocked the bay head with the
human weapons to close the trap.
Checkmate!
That's why Whitebeard said that
we should sink the Navy
ships around us first.
He saw it coming.
We didn't get trapped, thanks to him.
Yeah.
Even though we couldn't trap them,
we can go at them from
the front and the back!
Attack the allied pirates
first as we planned.
Get rid of the ones who
wander off of the enclosure!
Did you hear that?
Uncle, is it okay if some Navy ships
get caught in the crossfire?
Keep it to a minimum.
Alright!
Let's begin!
I don't know what's going on but
you can't beat us that easily!
Oh... Oh no!
Go, Pacifistas!
He blew them away!
They're even willing to sacrifice their own.
Don't be afraid, guys!
Let's charge the plaza without stopping!
Backing down is not even an option.
I'll get to Ace before they get me!
Everyone, get off of the ship!
Counter the human weapons!
Come on.
I'll fight you!
All units, get off of the ice right away!
Don't let the pirates reach the plaza!
Fall back!
Hurry up!
I didn't expect that I'd get to fight the
world's greatest swordsman in this war.
How lucky I am.
You're the number one
swordsman of the Whitebeards.
Let me see the Flower Sword's swordsmanship.
You can have a good look at it.
Rose Rondo!
What kind of flower should I make bloom next?
Drive them in, Pacifistas!
I won't let you! Take this!
I got you!
What are they made of?!
They're not human!
Are they unbreakable?!
The picture...
No matter how much you struggle,
we will keep the upper hand, Whitebeard!
When all videos have been cut,
activate the encircling walls.
Thereupon, we will execute Ace
and round up all our enemies.
Yes, sir!
Outta my way!
Ace's in danger! I gotta hurry!
Go back to the beginning!
Luffy-kun!
Jimbei!
The admiral has come out!
Damn!
It's tough but we need to hurry!
We came here knowing that powerful
enemies would stand in our way!
Die, Dragon's son!
Ace's brother, are you out of energy already?
The commanders are here!
What a tremendous help!
You can't get blocked by just one guy!
Come with us!
Okay! That bastard!
The Navy is backing down
so now is our chance!
Let's break through at once!
That's kinda tough!
10th division commander--Curiel!
If you're gonna come for me,
I'll just knock you down!
You're dead if you stay inside the bay!
Ace will die and you guys
will be trapped and wiped out!
I couldn't care less about who's gonna win
but it'll nice to see Whitebeard to die!
I won't let Pops and Ace die!
Shall we put this match on hold, Vista?
Seems like it'd be good for both of us.
We're ordered to back down, Smoker-san!
We've got to go!
Yeah.
I know.
Straw Hat!
Luffy! Hurry up and save your brother!
Have you cut the videos yet?
No, give us another minute!
Hey, did you find it?!
N-No! We're still looking for it!
PLEASE WAIT A MOMENT
We're all set!
Gaffer, move aside.
They cut all videos except for one but...
Why do we have to wait?!
You're good to go on camera!
Okay, let's go on the air!
5 seconds to go!
4, 3, 2, 1, action!
The picture's back!
Er... Um...
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone.
Somebody's talking!
We're here at Marineford.
There're dead bodies of pirates and the Navy.
A commentary?
Hey! What's this?! What's going on?!
Hmmm?! The guy over there must be...!
Oh, he's...! Don't tell me that he's...!
He's been hiding his origin but...
...he was one of the legendary crew of
the King of the Pirates--Gold Roger!
Who's that?
The great pirate--Captain Buggy the Clown?!
Yes, that's who I am indeed!
It's top secret but I am...
...the legendary pirate.
H-Hey! Captain Buggy!
Your nose is bleeding!
Cut! Cut!
Wipe it up!
What the hell is this?!
I'm saying "cut the stupid video right away!"
We can't move on like this!
I-I'm afraid that...
...one of the Video Transponder Snails
has been stolen by the
prisoners from Impel Down!
What did you just say?!
Make-up!
We're ready!
Alright, now it's take 2!
3, 2, 1 and...
Oh! That guy right there!
He was one of Roger's legendary crew and...
...the sworn brother of "Red-Haired"
of The Four Emperors!
The great pirate--Captain Buggy the Clown?!
Yes, indeed!
Stop them right now!
Whoa! That was close!
They found us! Run!
You just got cut by the
famous "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk
but you don't seem like you got hurt at all!
Talking about me?
Yes, I'm Buggy!
The legendary!
Blow all of them away!
Let us see the war!
What happened to other videos?!
Let us see Ace who was about to be executed!
Let us see the group of Bartholomew Kumas!
They keep driving us to the corner!
Don't give up!
We can't go down until we save Ace!
Let's go!
Pops.
Squard!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Yeah, barely.
I see. I was calling for you a while ago.
How is it at the bay head now?
Your allies were beaten badly.
I made it here because
I found the way out luckily.
Sengoku has no mercy.
He's using all the forces he has
in order to defeat us.
Pops, did you notice what the Navy was up to?
I've known Sengoku for a long time.
I see.
It's better for us if they're
gonna attack us from the rear.
I'm gonna go forward, too!
We gotta invade without stopping!
I agree.
Squard? Why is he up there?
There are 43 allied captains here
and we are all in your debt beyond words!
We risk our lives for the Whitebeard Pirates!
Thank you.
But we are...!
I know.
You are fighting to save
a member of your family.
The pirate, Whitebeard,
won't give up on his family.
Everybody followed you to this hell
because you're that kind of person.
I wish that...
...we were also...
...members of your family.
No one expected Squard's betrayal.
As they see him approaching Whitebeard,
suspicion grows in the Navy men as well.
The strong bond shared among the
Whitebeard Pirates has been destroyed...
That is the scenario described by the Navy.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Akainu's Plot!
Whitebeard Entrapped!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!