Edited at https://subtitletools.com
In pursuit of Luffy, four of the
Straw Hats and the Franky Family
were nearing the courthouse. However...
Take us to the courthouse, Gomorrah!
Gomorrah!
Dammit! Who are they?!
"Guilty"
Not gonna be that easy... you damn trash.
All right! The second one is down, too!
If we get surrounded in a place
like this, we'll be goners!
"Courthouse" "Rocketman"
Meanwhile, Sogeking was
around the main island front gate.
All right! Oimo and Kashii are back in business!
Oh, no...
We don't have much energy
left to fight guys like them.
Is this it for us?!
How...
...dare you...
Huh?
...deceive us?!
Before we rejoice over
the safety of our bosses...
Before we grieve over our wasted years...
We'll take out all our anger
on them in a furious rampage!
Let's go together... king of snipers!
Sogeking is now headed to Luffy
and the others with Oimo and Kashii.
No need for formality! Hoist the
counterattack signal this time for sure!
Hurry to our comrades!
--This tastes terrible.
--You'll soon notice how big the change is.
This is the birth of new
Devil Fruit power-holders.
I look forward to seeing those powers.
Get a handle on your own powers
at least, while you have a chance.
"Courthouse"
Around the same time, Luffy was
waging a fierce battle against Blueno
on the rooftop of the courthouse.
Iron Body!
Wheel!
Door-Door!
A-A door just opened on the ground!
Door-Door.
Wh-What the heck?!
Were there small doors here?!
Crap! I got stuck! Dammit!
Revolving Door.
What?! What?!
Wh-What's going on?! I feel dizzy!
Wh-Wh-Which way is forward?! Stop!
Tempest Kick!
Hey, Cook!
Yeah, I saw it.
Luffy's already fighting CP9.
What?!
There's only one path left!
Yeah, we're gonna make
a dash for the courthouse!
That's the only choice we have.
All right, let's go, guys!
--Yeah!
--Wait!
All of you, don't get off!
Chopper?!
Hold on tight!
Gomorrah... Gomorrah says so!
Go! Gomorrah!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Almost to Luffy!
Gather at the Courthouse Plaza!"
Hey, Gomorrah! Why are you
trying to crash yourself into walls?!
What's going on? So he can't go on after all?!
Th-That's not it! He can't see!
--What?!
--His eyesight has weakened
because his retinas got hurt!
What?! You can't see?!
It started running like crazy!
Don't break the encirclement!
Stop the monster!
What're you doing?!
Fire the trench mortars already!
Stop, Gomorrah!
You're in no shape to keep running anymore!
He says that he promised Sodom!
He said to Sodom, "Leave the rest to me!
I'll run with everyone on my back for you!"
Gomorrah...
They were inside its stomach?
I can't eat anymore. I'm full.
Let's take them back
with us for emergency food.
Bro! There's trouble! Some pirates
beat up Sodom and Gomorrah!
You've got some nerve
messing with my underlings!
Hey! You're injured!
Don't dance! Sodom! Gomorrah!
There's a dead end ahead!
He'll crash into it and die!
Gomorrah! Stop! Don't run randomly!
Stop!
Dead end? Do you see one?
Nope... I don't see anything of the sort.
It's the courthouse, Gomorrah!
W-We're here! Gomorrah!
This report is for all units!
The King Bull with the pirates on it broke
through the encirclement in Block D!
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
They've just reached the courthouse plaza!
I repeat! The pirates...!
Look at this... Funkfreed.
It's a golden transponder snail.
Just like the authority to exercise Buster Call,
this shiny transponder snail
is indeed a valuable item
that can only be carried with the permission
of someone ranked admiral or
above in Navy Headquarters.
In order for me to exercise Buster Call,
Aokiji temporarily entrusted it to me.
Just wait and see! Once the revival
of the weapon becomes reality,
I'll be able to carry this myself, instead of
having some admiral entrust it to me,
and control troops at will.
Buster Call...
I'm exercising a Buster Call.
Commence concerted fire!
We're targeting everything on Ohara,
the island of archaeology!
Just by pressing this button,
an entire island can be wiped out.
Authority can be like a weapon too, huh?
Chief Spandam!
Ahhhh! That scared me!
What's your problem?! Knock on the door first!
I almost accidentally pressed the button!
I-I'm sorry. But I was told
that this is an emergency.
There's a call from the Enies Lobby main island!
What?! A call?! They should've
called this room directly!
Hm? Hey! The receiver is off!
This happens all the time! Who's behind it?!
Hm? You just said that it's an
emergency or something, didn't you?
Yes, sir.
Spanda!
Hey, Nico Robin!
There seems to be an emergency report
from the Enies Lobby main island.
It's probably not really an emergency,
but you can guess what it's about, right?
What happened to Straw Hat Luffy,
who worked hard to beat up
a whole five soldiers...
How your friends got stomped
by the strongest gatekeepers,
Oimo and Kashii...
Let's hear together what happened to the idiots
who went against the World Government!
You're so low!
Shut up, you punk!
Hey, guard!
This is Spandam.
Oh, is this the Chief?! Good!
I can finally give you a report!
I don't know where to start.
Calm down, you idiot! You wanna
talk about the Straw Hats, right?
What happened after the
last report? Oh, wait! Listen.
When you report, summarize
the crucial points briefly
and explain them clearly with a loud voice.
--Yes, sir! The invaders--
--Did you accidentally kill them?
Well, that's their own fault for being so weak.
The pirates, who number about sixty,
have invaded and pushed
into the courthouse plaza,
the farthest point in the
Enies Lobby main island!
To all units on Enies Lobby main island!
All soldiers! Head to the
courthouse plaza immediately!
You did a good job, Gomorrah!
We won't waste the boost
you two brothers gave us!
We're gonna attack, guys!
We'll rescue Big Bro Franky!
Yeah!
The pirates have reached the courthouse plaza!
Can you see Luffy?
No.
If the rooftop is that high,
we can't just climb up there.
No... It's not like we're made of rubber.
How many CP9 members did you see?
It was only the big horn guy we saw.
It's hard to believe that all of
them are in a place like that
with Robin-chan and Franky.
In any case, we have to
catch up with Luffy quickly!
We have to hurry up and rescue Robin!
Hurry to the courthouse plaza!
The drawbridge isn't down yet! Corner them!
Ribbit!
Whoa! What an amazing frog!
That's the iron ball that knocked
down Gomorrah! Who did that?!
Ribbit!
Over there! They're running away!
There are three of them!
Why are they running away?
They're the ones who started the attack.
You idiot! It's a waste of time chasing
after each enemy who runs away!
Shut up. I just went to check.
It wouldn't hurt to know what kind
of enemies would attack us, would it?
Whoa! He brought him down!
What is this guy?!
He must have Herculean strength
to swing around something like this!
Does he belong to a special
unit like the Watchdogs?
There may be more hiding. Be careful.
Now, let's hurry up.
The guards are closing in on us.
Corner them!
They're not gonna be able to open the
courthouse's heavy stone doors anyway!
Bring them down here in the plaza!
Come to think of it, these are huge doors.
How will we...
...get them open...?
Get a move on! I'll go on ahead!
H-He cut through that thick stone!
Zambai!
We'll split up and go to both sides
in order to pull down the drawbridge's levers!
O-Okay! I'm counting on you guys!
All right! We'll split into three groups!
Those who come with me will thoroughly
clean house inside the courthouse!
I don't need many!
Good luck, guys! Disperse!
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
Huh?
Also, the giant gatekeepers
at the main island front gate,
Oimo and Kashii, went over to the pirates' side!
They're currently around the center of the
main island running towards the courthouse!
Get outta our way!
The casualties of our guards are...
...over 2,000!
N-Not five...?
And the captain, Straw Hat Luffy,
who beat over 1,000 all by himself,
suddenly disappeared, so we're
searching for him right now!
This is probably unprecedented--
the worst situation we've had
in the history of Enies Lobby!
Blueno...
What's he doing in a place like that?
What's going on?
What the hell is happening
on this island right now?!
My face door finally closed!
Of course. An opened door is meant to close.
I'm surprised that you could
dodge the tempest kick.
Yeah. Well, it's a piece of cake.
I resent that.
You jerk!
He jumped!
Finger Pistol!
Shave!
Iron Body! Smash!
Gum-Gum... Bullet!
Iron Body!
Tempest Kick!
He's completely keeping up with my speed.
He changed the course of the Tempest Kick!
He's got unbelievable physical abilities!
No good.
Hm?
I'm no good like this.
When Aokiji defeated me, I thought...
"If I am to encounter more
strong guys like him in the future,
I won't be able to protect my friends...
unless I become stronger."
I have friends I want by my side
even if they're not strong.
So if I don't get stronger
than anyone, I'll lose all of them.
Then what're you gonna do?
I came up with a way to
fight with all my might...
...so that I won't lose anyone...
So that no one will go far away.
What's he doing?
What's happening inside his body?!
You'll now... no longer be
able to keep up with me.
What?
All my techniques will evolve one step further.
Second... Gear!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
I'm glad that I met you guys here.
Hmph! What kind of bluff is that?
You'll now... no longer be
able to keep up with me.
Can't be...! I can't see him at all!
Gum-Gum...!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everything Is to Protect My Friends!
Second Gear Activated!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!