Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from Buggy and Mr. 3 on level 3,
Luffy headed to the lower
levels with Bon Clay!
Summon all the other forces
of Impel Down to level 4!
Roger that!
If they manage to get away from Minotaurus
and come down here to the Burning Heat Hell,
I'll execute them with my own hands!
There's a huge amount of hot air and smoke!
It's hard to even stand here!
Right! But...
...this is level 4--the Burning
Heat Hell where you wanna go!
Burning Heat? Is it down there?
You said you were gonna break out!
Straw Hat!
I knew you'd want to come with me!
No one wants to follow you to hell!
Anyway, you take this! The
special weapon--Muggy Ball!
Alright! Gum-Gum...
...Mallet Rifle!
We did it!
We beat the monster of hell!
"All Forces Have Gathered! The Battle
on Level 4 The Burning Heat Hell!"
How much time left until Ace's execution?
29 hours. Everything's gonna
be over at 3 p.m. tomorrow.
But only if everything
goes according to plan.
We'll transfer Portgaz
D. Ace tomorrow morning.
Luffy!
If I could only know you
were safe, I'd want nothing else!
IMPEL DOWN LEVEL 3 INSIDE OF THE WELL TOWER
Alright, let me ask you once again.
Okay!
You still wanna go down to level 4?
Yeah! I knew you'd want to come with me!
I'm not going at any cost!
My body will melt away completely!
How many times do we have
to tell you, bonehead?!
Can't you see the plumes?!
It's the Burning Heat Hell!
We're not gonna go to level 4!
Why not?!
It's obvious!
We wanna escape! E-S-C-A-P-E!
That's right! We wanna go up! Understand, up?
Wow! I got a really big, bloody booger here!
You're not listening!
Whew! Straw-chan, let them go!
They don't have the balls to go further!
Whose nose looks like a ball?!
What's that?! How did you hear me?! Ha-ha!
I made up my mind! I'll just spin!
Ha-ha-ha! Gimme a break!
Hey! It looks like ceiling is rising!
Ah! You're right!
I hear a rattling, too. I
think if I'm not mistaken...
...that we are falling!
Oh no!
My Muggy ball was so powerful,
it caused the floor to collapse!
No way, it's because of my heavy kick!
You're wrong! It's because
my punch was so strong!
No no! My Wax-Wax power was...
Oh! I didn't do that much...
Then, shut up!
We're gonna get burned by hellfire!
Help us!
LEVEL 4--THE BURNING HEAT HELL
Hey, don't do it! You can't kill us!
Whatever happens, you deserve it!
How many people have you killed?
Get them!
--We deeply regret what we've done!
--Yeah, we're really sorry!
Don't!
I'm burning!
Help me!
Keep lugging firewood! Hustle!
It's too hot.
My whole body...
even my guts are gonna get burned!
I'd rather die than stay on this floor!
I can't take it anymore!
Get out of my way! Move it!
A prisoner is escaping!
Hey! Outta my way!
Do you want me to throw
you into the sea of fire?!
I'm gonna fall!
Hey! You're not allowed
to beat other prisoners!
Do you wanna get executed right here?!
FORMER BAROQUE WORKS ASSASSIN--
DAZ BONEZ A.K.A. Mr. 1
Your condition has been granted. Now, you...
I'm well aware!
I'll follow the orders
to convene as I promised.
Welcome back!
Thank you. Escort the Snake
Princess to her quarters.
Yes, sir. This way.
I'll bring you a meal right away.
I don't want it. Reduce
the amount from now on.
Really?
Don't question me! Such insolence!
I-I'm sorry, Madam.
Vice-Admiral Momonga!
What's wrong?
We got a report that Red-Haired
had a run-in in the New World!
Impossible! It must be a mistake!
Why now? Who did he fight against?!
It's hard to believe but it's
Kaido of The Four Emperors!
Kaido?!
Headquarters believes that
Red-Haired intercepted Kaido...
...and stopped him from attacking Whitebeard!
But it wasn't a large battle.
That kind of thing is bound to happen!
That's how insecure the sea is now!
A brush with The Four Emperors is...
a serious matter that's beyond our
control in these circumstances.
Maybe, there's absolutely no way that
we can avoid the war against Whitebeard!
Do you think that it'll be an all-out battle?
One side is Whitebeard Pirates - the
strongest pirate crew in the world.
The other side is all the forces of
the Navy including three Admirals
and The Seven Warlords of the Sea!
No matter who wins, the
war will become history!
--Let's hurry to Marineford!
--Yes, sir!
What's going on?
Magellan, Hannyabal, and the
demon guards are all here!
What's gonna happen on this floor?
LEVEL 4 IN FRONT OF THE STAIRCASE
THAT LEADS TO LEVEL 3
It's really hot here!
Fasten your fireproof coat!
Straw Hat Luffy and others
should come out from this door!
No information yet?
Maybe they got beaten by Minotaurus.
Wardens should not hide!
Come out of there right now!
Don't open it without
notice! It's too bright!
When you pass the seat on to
me, I want it to be more open.
Shut up! This was custom-made for me.
I prefer to stay closed up in a dark room!
I want to keep my heart closed from you, too!
It's coming!
No way!
What?! It's a toilet as well?!
That's so gross!
I can hear you!
If I knew that we'd have to wait this
long, we would've gone to level 3...
...directly!
No need to rush, Sadie-chan!
I'm fine but these kids are
always lusting for blood, so...
...they're losing their patience.
DEMON GUARD MINOKOALA (HAWKISH)
DEMON GUARD MINORHINOCEROS (BASHFUL)
DEMON GUARD MINOZEBRA (SHY)
There's been an update!
Straw Hat Luffy is now inside
of the Well Tower on level 3
so they can't monitor him!
What?!
If they make it out of there, I'll
lay the blame on Warden and...
Ouch! I really wanna become the warden!
I mean, it really hurts
to be hit by the warden!
It'll be easier for us if they
would just fall from there.
There's the boiling Pool of Blood under
there and they're all Devil Fruit eaters so...
...once they fall into it, they'll be dead!
I don't deserve this!
I don't wanna go to level 4!
Oh no! We're gonna fall straight
into the Pool of Blood!
I'm falling!
Warden Magellan! An update!
The invader--Straw Hat Luffy
- is already on this floor!
What?! What do you mean by that?!
It seems like he fell into the well!
There's the Pool of Blood underneath!
How are they still alive?!
I think the giant piece of the floor
that they were on enabled them...
...to avoid falling into the pool.
How lucky they are!
--There's another thing!
--What?!
Warden, it stinks!
I mean, wow, this situation really stinks!
Minotaurus the demon guard fell into
the well also and he's not moving!
No way! They defeated him?!
I think so.
That can't be true! I can't believe it!
Calm down!
Follow these orders!
There are only two ways
to get out from level 4 -
two staircases that they can take without
authorization by security guards.
Split our forces here into three.
Hannyabal, you take this staircase
which leads to level 3!
Sadie-chan, you defend the stairway
to level 5 with the demon guards!
No, I don't wanna defend...
I wanna attack!
Being on the attack
is my true calling, Warden!
I'll let them get away and
lay the blame on Warden!
Do you have any objections?
Please stop... sighing!
I didn't complain!
I can feel your evil intentions towards me!
Once you catch them, you can
do whatever you want to them!
Yes! That sounds irresistible!
All the rest of you, just go after them!
I don't care if they're dead or alive!
Yes, sir!
"Almost dead" would do for me!
I won't let Straw Hat Luffy and
the others toy with me any longer!
They'll meet their doom
in this Burning Heat Hell!
But first...
The Warden is finally going to make his move!
You have to take another dump?!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow... It's
insanely hot in this passage!
NEAR THE "POOL OF BLOOD"
Even my lungs are burning!
Hurry! I wanna get through this level!
Which way should we go?!
You guys are so pathetic!
If you just keep your cool, the fire
is like your queer little friend!
But I know how you feel!
This floor is a little bit
hotter than the upper level!
Oh? Yeah, it's a little too hot!
Hmmm... I can feel that my body's burning!
Oh? Ouch!
We can't handle any more of that!
It's that way! Let's go!
H-Hey! Where're you going?!
--It's too hot!
--Shut up!
Hmm... What must be there that
Straw-chan's running towards?
BON-CHAN'S ROUGH MAP OF LEVEL 4
It's the kitchen!
I'm hungry, too! Wait for me, Straw-chan!
Wow! That'd be nice!
It'll be even better if
they have drinks, too!
Wait a minute, Buggy!
Ouch, ouch, ouch...
Smells good...
Ouch, ouch... Smells good...
There he is!
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh! There are a lot of them!
This floor is really hot but once I
eat, I'll be filled with energy again!
Stop!
Gum-Gum...
...Fireworks!
We found Straw Hat Luffy!
Team A is fighting against him right now!
Team B has arrived on the scene!
They're closing in on him
together with Team A!
But they've taken heavy casualties!
They're requesting backup! What shall we do?!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Spin, spin! I'm spinning!
"Oh Come My Way" Kenpo -
Memoirs of a Summer's Day!
--Team A and B have been wiped out!
--C, D, and E have major losses!
Backup from upstairs won't do!
We can't compete with them!
We can't hold that
position any longer!
The position that I worked
so hard to gain is at risk!
What's up, partner?!
Take a good look!
There is a sea of guards down there!
And level 4 is about screams and cries but
there's not a single guard at the fire torture pit!
Let's go! It's up there!
We ought to check the staircases right away!
Maybe they ambushed us and
boxed us in on this floor!
If they've been waiting on level 4,
that means they only want Straw Hat!
Because we only came here by accident!
They all know our names and
faces as escapees anyway!
What I am concerned about is
that it is very likely that...
...they have the all-stars of Impel Down
on this floor to put an end to this fuss!
That means, on top of the
three other demon guards,
Warden Magellan might be here, too!
Then, we're through!
Get out of my way!
Stop!
Don't stand in my way!
Oh, that scared me!
I thought that it was a spear or something!
W-What's this?
Ow, ow, ouch! Is it jelly?! Or crap?!
Straw-chan, look up!
I've had enough of you running
around and playing by your rules!
Who're you?!
M-Magellan!
You're dead, you vermin!
Warden Magellan has finally
made his appearance!
The power of the Venom-Venom
Fruit makes him untouchable,
but Luffy risks it all to take him on.
However, faced with the might of
the Hydra produced by Magellan,
Bon Clay makes a surprising move!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Mighty Magellan! Bon Clay Bugs Out!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!