Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Super it's getting
pretty exciting, isn't it?!
There are 50,000 enemies. This is the
perfect opportunity to unveil them!
Them?!
What are they, Franky?!
There are 2 new weapons on the Sunny!
Who wants to ride along?
What?! New weapons?!
Three-Sword Style!
Black Rope Dragon Twister!
--It won't stop!
--It's like a cyclone of blades!
--Run! Or you're gonna get cut!
--Don't come after us!
It'll chase you to hell's end!
Huh? Where did he go?
Sky...
...Walk!
Cool! Sanji is in the air!
Diable Jambe...
...Poele a Frire...
...Spectre!
Doesn't matter if there
are 100,000 or 1,000,000!
We'll just beat them all!
"Unveiled! The Secret
Weapons of the Sunny!"
How annoying...
It's not over yet, Moss Head!
You can't top me, Nosebleed!
Why are they competing against each other?
Ignore them. They're always like that.
Honestly, that side of
them hasn't changed a bit!
Everybody's getting
pretty warmed up, aren't they?
Maybe it's time for them!
--By them, you mean...
--Finally, the new weapons?!
That's right! Follow me!
We've been waiting for this!
Oh, hey, wait!
G-Guys! Don't leave me alone!
You're bugging me! Go somewhere else!
You go!
Don't push your luck, you bastards!
--Shut up!
They're too strong...
What did you just say?
Nothing!
The humans are "too strong"?
How dare you call yourself a Fish-Man?
C-Captain!
I-I'm sorry!
Don't disappoint me.
I don't need a soldier who is afraid of...
...stupid humans!
Why don't you kill Shirahoshi already?
It's awesome down here!
Did you change something?
There wasn't a "5" or a "6" before!
You're right! And "0" is gone!
It's been renovated!!
I remodeled "0" to  create "5" and "6."
The new weapons are in "4"
which was empty before
and in the newly made "5."
Okay, hurry up! I wanna see
the new weapons already!
Alright, alright!
Take a look and be surprised!
Here they are!
Cool!
Let's finish this up already-dosun!
Artillery Unit!
Kill Shirahoshi!
I do not like it!
You want to hurt the world's
favorite Mermaid Princess?!
Party music!
What's going on? It got dark all of a sudden.
It's nice to have you along
on this festival night!
What the...
Is this...
...An amusement park?
Hey, let's dance!
Huh? Were we just dreaming?
Now, set off the fireworks!
This is fun!
It's beautiful!
Hey! I said "Kill the Princess"-bokan!
But...
Dosun-san, we're enjoying
today's joyous festival...
Okay, I cut you already.
What?
Quinto Tierce Fantasia!
Huh?
Ganging up on a weak woman?
You people are a bunch of brutes.
Mil Fleurs...
...Gigantesco Mano...
Legs?!
...Stomp!
Sorry!
--People are screaming outside.
--What's going on?
Hey guys, get out! It's too tight!
You have no interest in the
new weapons! You get off!
I'm here because I'm scared!
I don't wanna be alone, either!
Franky, do we have to wait much longer?!
Don't rush it!
It's all set!
I'm getting excited too!
Wait a minute! I need to
operate this thing so...
It got more spacious!
What's going on in here?!
Alright, here are the new weapons
on the Soldier Dock of the Sunny!
--I'm excited!
--What's gonna happen?!
It's time to unveil!
Deadly Venom Squad, go!
Even if you got giant legs or arms,
you're dead meat once
you're stung by our venom!
Hold it right there!
The Soldier Dock System!
Channel 4!
--The door opened!
--Destroy that stupid ship!
Black Rhino...
...FR-U 4!
The Soldier Dock System!
Channel 4!
Black Rhino...
...FR-U 4!
Cool! It's a cy-bike!
What is it?! Looks so tough!
What did you say about venom?
What the hell?!
Sting it if you can! This steel monster!
It's super cool, isn't it?!
Stop that guy!
All right!
Steel on steel!
I'll take care of it!
Here! Take this!
Hey!
The new number! Channel 5!
Brachio-Tank 5 is here!
It's like a dinosaur! I want it!
It's amazing!
Did you see my great shooting skill?
I bet this thing can do a lot more.
I thought he was a shipwright.
I am Commander Chopper!
I see some enemies at 9 o'clock!
Fire!
You're so cool, Commander!
Hey, you! Fight!
Wow! They're so strong!
There are only 10 of them but they're
kicking the asses of 100,000.
The Straw Hat Pirates...
Maybe, they can save us all and
the Fish-Man Island for real!
Go, Straw Hat!
Beat Hordy!
You're doing great, Straw Hat!
Boss Jimbei!
If you win, I'll let you eat as
much as you want at my restaurant!
You can drink as much as
you want too, at my bar!
--Straw Hat!
--We're counting on you!
Boss Jimbei!
Don't push your luck!
Come on out, Kraken!
No...
It's huge!
There are only 10 of them!
Just crush them all!
Then it'll finally be over!
Oh no! They got the
mythical monster - Kraken!
Watch out!
Even though the Straw Hats are strong,
they're finished once they
get crushed by that thing!
Oh, it's the Kraken! He'll do
whatever Captain tells him to!
He's as strong as hell!
See how formidable this
deep-sea creature is!
Hey, that's...
What are you doing?!
Kill them already!
I brought you here all the way from
the North Pole! You're my slave!
You have to work for me!
You can do it, can't you?
W-Wait a moment!
Fall back!
Hey, if I remember right, that's...
I don't think there are many others!
Huh? You two know him?!
I didn't expect to see him here.
Oh, hey, Surume!
It's me! Surume!
Oh? Don't you remember me?
How could you forget?!
You became my pet for a
while. I'm your friend!
Oh no, the Sea Bonze is...
Alright, that's enough. Stop!
Good job!
I can't believe it!
You really tamed the monster octopus?
Yeah, I'm gonna use him like
experienced people do! Right, Surume?
Let me ride on you again!
He did it!
Luffy-sama!
That tickles! Stop! Surume!
All right, Surume! Let's go!
The Kraken betrayed us!
Stop Kraken!
You stupid octopus!
Go Surume!
Help me, Captain!
Kraken, go that way!
Damn! What's going on?!
The Kraken is totally bonded to Straw Hat!
Listen, Surume! Stay here
and protect Yowahoshi!
I can't believe you knew the Kraken!
I'm so impressed! You have so many friends!
Yeah?
Um, thank you for doing this, Surume-sama!
There are still a lot of them.
All right! Let's go!
Using their new weapon, Franky, Usopp
and Chopper were making good progress,
until they fell into the trap Daruma,
an officer of the New
Fish-Man Pirates, had laid.
But then, the second of Sunny's
new weapons commences its docking!
A wondrous robot emerged!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Iron Pirate!
Here Comes General Franky!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!