Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
"THANK YOU"
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Together with Red-nosed Buggy
and former Baroque Works
agents Mr. 3 and Bon clay,
he reached level 4 the Burning Heat Hell...
...but was poisoned by Magellan,
the warden of Impel Down
and taken into custody!
As Luffy was taken into custody
on level 5--the Freezing Hell,
Bon Clay tried his hardest
to find a way to save him!
No way?!
I mean, what do you mean that
you can't make an antidote!
A miracle?
Oh yeah! He is in Impel Down!
The queen of queers--
Ivan-san!
We better find him now!
"A Paradise in Hell!
Impel Down Level 5.5!"
T-This is no good!
We have no choice!
We should lock ourselves up!
Alright! I'll draw their attention!
Open it quick!
Dammit! Chew on this,
my special weapon--Muggy Ball!
Ha! How's that?!
What?!
I did it!
Did you?!
I did it... I broke the key!
What're you doing?!
It's too late!
Candle Shield!
That was close!
You better get into the cell now!
We don't need to!
I have an idea!
Stupid wolves! You can't get us now!
It's no use biting it!
This Candle House is as hard as iron!
Even with your big fangs, you can't break it!
Let's go!
Oh yes!
1, 2! 1, 2!
Wow! This is nice!
They can't even touch us!
It's heavier than I thought!
I made it thicker than usual to protect us!
Yeah? Well, good job!
Even if it's a tortoise's pace,
as long as we can get to the stairs,
then we can get out of here!
That's right!
And as long as we're in here,
we can avoid the cold wind!
Alright!
1, 2! 1, 2!
Wait! Let's go back a little!
What's the matter?
Something is wrong.
What happened to the wolves?
Yeah, where the hell do they go?!
All of them are gone!
What's that noise?
T-This must be...
That was pretty clever of them!
Who the hell is this guy
all covered in blood?!
Earlier, I was...
We have no chance to win!
I'm sorry but I gotta run!
Straw-chan! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry that I ran!
How do you know this guy?
I'm his friend!
Straw-chan! I'm not gonna let you die!
We better go now!
He left the keys!
I never thought about breaking out.
I gotta find Ivan-san as soon as possible!
Ivan-san?!
How should I know
where that queer went?!
Who the hell are you?!
Emporio Ivancov?
Oh yeah, I remember him!
He must be dead!
What are you looking at?!
Why are you looking for a missing person?!
How did you get out of your cell?!
Why don't you set me free?!
Do you know where the man named Ivan-san is?!
Hello?! Can you hear me?!
Hey, why don't you say something?!
It's no use!
They're all frozen in that cell!
I wanna know...
Yeah, I heard you.
You're looking for that fairy, Ivancov, right?
Do you know something?
Look! Do you see the forest?
Yeah.
There's an abandoned jailer's room in there.
I once saw a strange guy moving around there.
Really?!
Why don't you go and check?
Thank you!
No problem!
I thought that's where the wolves live.
Oh? Is that so?
People have disappeared
occasionally in Impel Down.
They didn't break out because
some of them could barely move.
They just disappeared without a trace.
We call it "Demoning away!"
We all fear these unnatural disappearances,
and assume that they're pulled
into the gate of hell.
That's why we call it "Demoning away!"
"The gate of hell?" "Demoning away?"
Yeah, right!
I don't think that's the reason
that Ivan-san disappeared!
I've never met him but he's a miracle-worker!
He must be able to work miracles
in a place like this, too!
Ivan-san is the God of all queers!
Please!
Save Straw-chan!
If antidotes won't help him...
...you're his only hope!
And I won't give up on hoping!
Aak! No!
Straw-chan!
What do you think you're doing to...
...Bon-chan?!
Leave Bon-chan...
...alone!
S-Straw-chan! What did you do...
...to them...?
The public execution of Ace is in...
...26 hours!
Damn!
Where are you?!
This place is too hot! It's like hell!
Wow! Nice! She's exactly my type!
Healthy, young and beautiful!
Wait a minute! But...
...where's that quick pansy prisoner
who beat all of these guards?!
Who are you?!
That doesn't matter, sweetie!
Why don't you come here?
Huh?
I'm all sweaty!
Can you help me undress?
Please!
Puff-puff!
Why don't you unlock this door?
Yeah, alright!
Smash!
Here you go!
Alright, how can I help you?
Ha ha! Do you have extra clothes?
I got you!
I can't take this!
That queer! I'm coming after you!
It's nice to be able to
lay the blame on Warden
but I don't like the fact he outsmarted me!
And I wanna become the warden!
I used too much poison!
My stomach! Oh, my stomach!
Yes, the riot is completely
under control now!
We put all the prisoners back in their
cells and got the keys back but...
...I think some keys are missing.
What a pain in the butt!
You got to... mmm... find him!
Catch him alive now!
This queer must be... mmm... on this floor!
Yes, Madam!
Several hours later, Mr. 2 Bon Clay is...
Where... is this?
Oh yeah!
Straw-chan?!
Where did Straw-chan go?!
I hear people talking...
This is it!
It's so bright!
What?!
Oh! So you finally woke up, young man!
You've been sleeping quite
a while! Want a drink?
Cheers to the newcomer!
Cheers!
We've been watching you guys on the monitor!
I really enjoyed it!
What is this place?
I'll take you to your seat!
What floor did you come from?
We got plenty to eat! You must be hungry!
Wait! Where am I?! Where's Straw-chan?!
Do you think that you're outside the prison?!
Don't worry! You're still in Impel Down.
No way! No one's wearing
their jail clothes here!
And you're eating and drinking as you want!
Is this some kind of paradise?!
Oh yeah, I remember!
I was chased by the wolves
and Straw-chan helped me!
And I just passed out!
Then, am I dreaming?!
No! I think I died from the cold
so I'm in heaven now!
Did you wake up?
You've been sleeping like a
baby for about 10 hours now.
10 hours?!
Are you kidding me?! Who are you?!
My name is Inazuma.
You're being rude!
I'm the one who moved the two of you.
You were nearly dying of exposure!
What? Did you say "two?"
Straw-chan is here, too?
Where is he? Is he alright?
Are you people jailers?
What is this place?!
Now, now, calm down.
He is going to tell you!
W-Who is He?
Oh! The lights are going down!
The shows starting!
Let's go to the front.
What is this?
Did you sleep alright, candy boy?
No, you're Mr. 2 Bon boy.
Who are you? Why do you know my name?!
Thank you for coming.
This is...
You're great! Very sexy!
Down the sewage line of Impel Down
and just take the route that shouldn't be there,
then, you'll get here!
It's a paradise for prisoners!
You've got everything here, so enjoy!
Drinks!
"Weapons!"
Games!
And most of all, we have freedom!
Yes, that's right! We're all free!
Yes! The jailers are
panicking today as usual!
"Prisoners have disappeared!"
"They've been pulled into hell!"
Just like that!
I'm sorry but they're all here!
Do you say that this is hell?!
Maybe you're right,
but at least it's a gay one!
The underground that nobody knows!
Welcome to...
...Impel Down--Level 5.5!
It's a secret garden for prisoners!
New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
Who are these perverts?!
Yeah! Ivan-sama!
What?!
Ivan-sama!
Ivan-sama?! No way!
He is the legendary...
...Queen of Kamabakka Kingdom.
Heehaw!
Emporio Ivancov?!
Bon Clay implores the miracle-worker,
Iva-san, to cure Luffy's poisoning.
However, Iva-san's remedy is
a cruel procedure that will
leave Luffy battered and torn.
A fierce battle commences against the poison.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's Treatment Begins!
Ivan-san's Miraculous Power!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!