Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
"The Gold and Waver Recovery Operations!"
All right, then! Here we go, guys! Ready?!
Yeah!
Wait, wait! Wait, you guys!
What's wrong, Usopp?
Geez, you guys! Are you just gonna go
without thinking this over?!
This doesn't bode well at all.
Seven people running around will
stand out way too much!
That's true, come to think of it.
And even though it is disguised,I'm
worried about Merry!
Yeah, given this level of quality.
They'll notice, even though it's so perfect?!
There's such a thing as worrying too much.
No one's gonna take this junky--
Don't call it junk! Besides,that
isn't the issue here!
Honestly! I'm the only onewho
considers the unexpected!
There's no doubt it's gonna getsunk
the next time it's spotted!
Plus... Nami!
Huh? Me?!
What happened to the Waver?!
Oh, no! I left it hidden in some grass!
See what I mean!
My bad!
Forgetful Nami-san is lovely, too!
Well, stupidity aside...
All right, men. I'll now
explainthe plan. So listen good!
Tadah!
Okay, gentlemen!
I'll now explain the plan!First,
the gold recovery team!
This will consist of Luffy, Zoro,Robin,
and me, Captain Usopp-sama!
And the Waver recovery team
willconsist of Nami and one other!
Sanji!
Nice plan, Usopp!
Let's work hard, okay?!
Yeah, yeah.
Dumbass eyebrows.
What was that?!
Hey, Usopp! Are you leaving
mealone with the ship again?!
Don't worry!
Merry's completely disguised,so
you can almost rest easy!
Almost?!
Plus, who's gonna tend to
ourinjuries if something happens?!
Super Doctor!
You dummy! Praising mewon't
help you, you jerk!
Listen. Here's where we are now.
The gold recovery teamwill
avoid all regular routes
and take the shortest path alongthe
coast to the storage vault.
Nami. Do you rememberwhere you hid the Waver?
Yes. By the bay on theeastern
side of the island.
At the base of the rim... Right around here.
Almost the exact opposite side...
It'll take too long to go by land...
Yes! Right there!
Nami! You two rush across
the bay in that boat!
And we'll all meet back
here,at the Going Merry!
Right!
Huh? You're still there? You can leave now...
The head chef has ordered me to stand watch
until you've eaten everything on your plate!
Even if you dine in yourprivate
quarters, rules are rules!
You must eat every last bite!
That lousy Jessica...
You too, General!
Eh?!
We've prepared plenty for you!
Please eat up!
You don't like broccoli either, General?
No, for me, it's tomatoes and carrots...
Oh! Lieutenant Commander!
Oh, are you eating? I'll
come back later, then.
No, no! This is an exception!You
came at just the right time!
Sir?
I was just about to call for you!
O-Oh...
Commander! I apologize for letting theStraw
Hats escape three separate times!
Oh, that doesn't matter right
now!Say, have you eaten yet?
--No...--That's not good! Not good at all!
You can't fight on an empty stomach!
In fact, it's your duty as
ahigh-ranking officer to eat first!
It's harder for lower-rankingpeople
to eat otherwise!
Right...
There's no need to act
reserved! Eat right up!
Tell her it was exceptionally delicious!
Understood.
I'll crush you fools and
this hedgehog in no time flat!
Look forward to it, you damn commander!
"Justice"
It's almost time...
Looks like we'll need
to reorganize our units.
So the plan is to hurry aheadof
them and block their path?
Yes. General, contact each unit immediately.
Yes, sir!
Attention, all warshipson
standby! Urgent orders!
Monitor the area aroundthe
Sea Gate and the bay!
What about my unit?
Send your men to the Sea Gateas
soon as they've finished eating.
Understood!
You!
Why, hello there, Condoriano-- Oh, pardon me.
I mean, Special Inspector Major Shepherd!
Commander Jonathan. I hear youlet
the Straw Hat pirates escape.
Not at all. They are likely
stillhiding inside this fortress.
Oh? And you can eat a leisurelymeal
knowing that, huh?!
You must not have a care in the world!
It's no wonder they secretly
callyou a peace-addict hedgehog.
Oh, I'm sorry.
No, think nothing of it.
So, I assume you know whatthey're
sneaking around for?
For the most part.
I believe they'll come back toretrieve
some gold they forgot about.
Gold, huh?
Still, we've certainly declinedfrom
our former dauntless selves.
Major. If you have anysage
advice, might I ask for it?
I could put you in charge of anespecially
skilled unit if you'd like...
Don't be absurd.
You know you're the most worthyto
command this "skilled unit."
Incidentally, where are the menwho
mistook me for a Straw Hat?
Why do you want to know that?
So I can court martial them, naturally.
It was I who gave the orders tocapture
all suspicious people on sight.
All they did was follow those orders.
Am I a suspicious person?
Under
those circumstances.
We seem to have a conflict of views.
I've just remembered something I need to do.
I'll return here once I'm done.
Commander. Will you be all right?!
He's a proud HQ inspector whoinsists
that G8 is wholly unnecessary.
He would never takecommand
of this branch base.
That wasn't what I meant!
Now, then.
Prepare to dispatch the
mostpowerful squad in all of G8!
Not more of your jokes...
I am serious.
Those damn fools...
Hey!
The Stan Marey entered portthis
morning-- where's its captain?!
Sir! He's been in the
infirmary this entire time!
The infirmary?! What's he doing there?!
Apparently, many of his crew were injured,
so he's probably there
out of concern for them.
Call him here! Right now!
Yes, sir!
He said they're after gold...
And there's only one placein
this fortress that could be!
Just you watch, you worthless commander!
I'll catch that Straw Hat myselfand
crush this entire fortress!
I hope everyone is all right...
I'm so lonely!
The stars! The moon!
And I'm all alone with Nami-san in
a boat beneath them!
What a wonderful situation!I
feel like I'm dreaming!
The warships in the bay are moving!
What are they doing? I havea
bad feeling about this!
Sanji-kun! Go faster!
Yes! As you wish!
Oh, but row quietly!
You got it!
All clear on the left and right...
There's no telling wherethere
could be soldiers,
so we gotta move around unnoticed!
It'll be a miracle if we don't get noticed!
Long-nose! We'll be fine for a while.
Why couldn't you say so sooner?!
What are you sleeping for?!
Get your act together, will ya?!
He has no sense of tension at all...
Commander.
Placing units all along the bay
willleave the base itself undermanned.
It can't be helped.
Against this adversary,cautiousness
amounts to nothing.
But having them prance around as
ifthey own the place is a bit much.
What do you say we mobilize the new recruits?
No. It's too dangerous for them.
I thought you might say that,so
I kept it quiet until now,
but many have actuallyalready
volunteered to do it.
They are already members of our forces,
and have the same feelings offondness
for this fortress as we do!
Is that so?
In that case, order themto
observe and report only--
no getting involved.
Yes, sir! I'm sure they'll be delighted!
By the by. I have one otherrequest
for you, General...
Yes?
What?! That's insane!
The Stan Marey is crippled andstill
being repaired as we speak!
That doesn't mean every ship inyour
fleet is out of commission.
That's true, but there are
soldierswho still can't even walk
after the storm we ran into on our way here!
Captain. Are you arguing with me,
a special inspector dispatched from HQ?
N-No, it's not like that... But...
Then gather all your men!
Half will stay with me;
the rest will board the
Pinepeakand wait for my orders!
I'm gonna show this useless
fortress'fools the power of Navy HQ!
Hey! Zoro! You keepin' up?!
Just shut up, will ya?!
Robin! Are we almost there yet?
Just a little more.
Is it really there?!
There's only a door!
Yes, assuming the map is correct.
Then the vault is behind there?!
Yes. Breaking in through thereshould
be the shortest route!
Then it's decided!We've
got no choice but to go!
All right! Let's do this
thing! Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
All right!
Let's go, Usopp!
Eh?!
"Aaahhhhhh!"
W-We're gonna crash!
Usopp. Don't get left behind.
Say, wanna do that again?!
Screw that! I'm never doing that again!
All right! No marines!
Pardon the intrusion!
Nami-san. Watch your step.
Thanks.
We can't afford to cause an uproar.
Looks like our only choiceis
to go along the coast now.
There's no time for us
tobe dealing with marines!
Sanji-kun! Let's hurry!
Okay!
We're almost there, men! Push forward!
I see it!
It's right down there!
The vault is at the end here!
All right! I'm coming for you, gold!
We made it here so
easily.Something's not right...
All right!
P-Pirates!
Y-You're not going any further!
Knock it off. We're notplannin'
to do anything crazy,
like destroy the fortress or slaughter you.
Quiet! As disrupters of
peace,you have to be punished!
We just told you, we're
not gonna do anything!
Like I can really believe some pirates!
We are proud to protect these
waters,together with our commander!
In other words, you're trying to
say you'll risk your life?
Obviously!
Then go eat a lot and train some damn more!
What is this?! Awesome!
That's quite heavy security.
Yeah, this is definitely
theperfect place to hide gold!
I bet there's lots of other goodstuff
in there besides our gold!
So, what do we do?
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Sorry, Zoro.
Hey!
Sorry...
Brute strength won't open it!
With this vault, you turn these
dials,and when the numbers match,
the gears above turn, the boltscome
undone, and the door opens!
Got that, lady and gentlemen?!
That's far enough!
So they were waiting for us.
It would seem so.
You're trapped like rats!Give
yourselves up quietly!
Do so now and--
What proud, great pirates would ever give up
when there's treasure right in front of 'em?!
They're all yours now!
Hey!
Damn you pirates!
How dare you?! Fire!
Usopp! Take care of the vault!
Consider it taken care of!
Well, Long-nose? Can you handle it?
This is really Nami's specialty,
but a lock of this levelis
a piece of cake for me!
All right!
First one!
W-What?!
It's instant death if those hit you.
They come off?!
One slip-up, and my headcould get smashed in!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Now!
Luffy! Don't stretch your armsout
too much! They'll cut 'em!
Right!
Yes! The second one!
Lt. Commander. All ships arenow
at their designated locations.
Good! Tell them to wait
as-isuntil orders are given!
Yes, sir!
Fifty more minutes...
I surrender!
Nice, Robin!
I'm surrounded...
Treinta Fleurs!
They just keep on coming!There's
no end to 'em!
Usopp! Is it open yet?!
It's open!
Yes!
Damn you!
Whoa!
All hands, retreat!
Wow! This vault is so neat!
What?!
There's no gold at all!
I won't let you escape
from Navarone so easily.
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,
on the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give in,
even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared of,
we can overcome it
It's payback time for all
yourcountless insults toward me!
Oh!
My special unit from HQ will
take care of you Straw Hats!
Oh!
This is the latest portable
bazooka, the Eagle Launcher!
Oh! So cool!
Now you die!
Yeah!
Hey, you!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The One Fell Swoop Plan!Jonathan's
Surefire Secret Tactic"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!