Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law.
Now, they have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
Their plan was to destroy the SMILE
manufacturing factory and rescue a samurai
but after Zoro's sword was stolen,
they got separated.
Please! Hold me!
Or I will... fall for you.
BANG!!
My name is Violet.
Could you escort me to the next town
if you don't mind?
The next town?
And...
...I want you to kill someone!
What?
The champion will get a Devil Fruit?!
On top of that, it's none
other than "Fire-Fist" Ace's
Flare-Flare Fruit?!
Oh, here, here! I want to enter!
Enter! Enter! Enter! Enter!
What?
What?!
No, you don't! You're too old!
"A Formidable, Unknown Warrior!
Here Comes Lucy!"
Grandpa, I'm currently accepting
entries for the competition
in the Corrida Colosseum.
I know! I'm entering!
Huh? Does that old man want to enter?
Is he nuts?
Does he have any idea about
the other competitors?!
I don't think so.
Because, in addition to
all those powerful people
from the New World, looking
to win the Flare-Flare Fruit,
there are some formidable fighters
from the Don Quixote Family!
Hey Luffy, listen. Promise me just one thing.
You can fight as you like
but don't ever let them know who you are.
Okay!
Sign your name.
Luf...
You idiot!
Beyond this point, competitors only.
Follow me.
Just go ahead and beat them all up.
But keep a low profile.
Count on me!
I'll be back with the Flare-Flare Fruit!
As I thought, she entered. Rebecca...
Hey.
Huh?! Wh-What do you want?!
Were you born in this country?
Of course! I was born and raised here!
I'm a pure Dressrosan!
I see.
Can I ask you something?
Do you know if the big guns of
the Don Quixote Family
are here today?
Don Quixote?!
Keep it down!
Do you know or not?
Why do you wanna know such a thing?!
I can't tell you why.
Alright, then do you know something
about the factory?
Th-The factory?!
I said "Keep it down"!
Thank you!
Huh?
The food was really amazing!
Now I know.
I've been improving my
skill in cooking but...
...it was all for Violet-chan!
That's so...
Thank you!
Somebody's coming again!
This way!
Yes! I will follow you
to the end of the world!
Oh! We're like runaway lovers!
The more they chase us, the closer we get!
The more we turn the world against us,
the more the flame of our love burns!
I wish this happiness would last forever!
They can easily spot us if we keep running.
Let's walk.
Okay! Oh?
It was a short-lived dream.
What?
Th-Th-This is...
Let's go.
This is the dressing room
for the competitors.
You're free until we call you.
Wow! It's filled with excitement!
The Flare-Flare Fruit is mine!
No, it's mine, idiot!
Move! You're in my way!
What did you say?!
Hey, who is that little guy?
I see.
Can we use any weapons we like?
Hey, who is he?
Oh, he's the last person to enter.
What is that little guy here for?
This is the kind of joke I hate the most!
SPARTAN - A GLADIATOR AT THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
(WON A MONTHLY TOURNAMENT 51 TIMES)
Hey, fake-bearded brat!
This is a fighting arena!
Don't, Spartan!
It's no fun seeing a weakling get pummeled!
The spectators only get excited
when the strong go head-to-head!
This is not a place for you! Go home!
Go home now!
Nice to meet ya!
Hey, what's wrong with that little guy?!
He took down Spartan!
No way!
He's one of the star gladiators
of this Colosseum!
Maybe, he just tripped over himself.
That wouldn't lodge someone in the ground!
Now, where should I sit?
Did you just start that fight?!
You'll have to leave now!
You're disqualified!
What?!
We don't need hooligans like you
causing scuffles before a match...
Whoa-whoa!
Hold it right there, you fool!
That big one started it!
If you wanna throw someone
out, it's got to be him!
He passed out though.
Oh! It's Sai and Boo from the Kano Kingdom!
Even Don Chinjao is here!
He's a legend!
SAI OF THE CHINJAO FAMILY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
BOO OF THE CHINJAO FAMILY -
DON CHINJAO - A LEADER IN THE CHINJAO FAMILY -
A GANG FROM THE KANO KINGDOM
Is it true?
Yeah, it is. Spartan started it.
I see.
Then Spartan has to go.
Lucy, you can stay.
Okay!
You saved me! Thank you!
Don't mention it, fool!
Boy, you don't have to mention it...
You don't have to say "Thank you"...
I don't like to hear the words "Thank you."
Take back your "Thank you," you bastard!
You don't have to refuse
his thanks that much, brother!
Don't ever say those words to me, idiot!
Sorry. He's easily excitable.
There are all kinds of people in the world.
Hey! Stop ganging up with other powerhouses
in your block, Dagama!
Huh? What the hell are you
talking about, Kelly Funk?
Hey hey, look at them.
Yeah, there are a whole bunch
of big names from each and every country!
FUNK BROTHERS
ASSASSINS FROM A NEIGHBORING COUNTRY
It's like a war for the Devil Fruit between nations!
KELLY FUNK
(THE OLDER OF THE TWO BROTHERS)
Ganging up and paying people off?
Hey, you make me sick!
BOBBY FUNK
(THE YOUNGER OF THE TWO BROTHERS)
It's an individual fight.
Even if you cheat like that, only one winner per block
can go to the next round.
DAGAMA
A TACTICIAN OF THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
Cut that crap!
I know you two are here on your country's order, too!
Possessing the Flare-Flare Fruit,
which is more powerful than any weapon,
ELIZABELLO II - "THE FIGHTING KING"
THE KING OF THE PRODENCE KINGDOM
would give any country an
advantage in diplomatic relations.
Look around you. See those faces?
There! He is a class-A war criminal
who was involved in the Sea Battle of Dias
- Suleiman the beheader!
They're former bounty hunters
who bombed a government
institution - Abdullah and Jeet.
He's a fake adventurer -
"The Surmounter" Orlumbus.
He's sponsored by the Don Quixote Family -
a sadistic pirate who's worth over 100 million -
Bellamy the Hyena.
And "Pirate Noble" Cavendish is here...
...as well as the crazy rookie Bartolomeo
who became notorious a year ago.
Now, do you really think all
of these ill-famed people
are not plotting anything?!
It's crazy if they don't have a plan!
I'm sure you guys have something! Don't you?
Hey, aren't you gonna serve food?
No.
The first round is a battle royal.
Only one winner per block
will go to the next round.
Yeah!
Block A's match will start soon!
And then, B, C, and D will follow.
There are 550 competitors here.
And only four of us may win the first round!
It's not that easy to win.
So I guess...
...you brothers are in
the same block because
of paying somebody off, am I right?
It's just a coincidence.
It's a coincidence.
Which block am I in?
I'm sure the receptionist told you already.
Your number is 556 so you're in Block C.
I know everybody has a different purpose
but the world could fall
into chaos depending on
who gets the Flare-Flare Fruit.
Let's cut the crap and
do our best, everybody!
Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for waiting!
Let me explain about today's competition!
For the first round, competitors
are divided into four blocks
and it's gonna be a battle royal!
A battle royal is a match in which
all competitors fight at once
so everybody is your enemy except yourself!
And the last one standing without being
eliminated
or getting killed will be the winner!
A competitor will be
eliminated if he gets thrown
out of the ring or if he
gets killed in the ring!
Meanwhile, in the water outside of the ring,
the Colosseum's unique attraction -
a school of Little Fighting Fish are
waiting to attack whoever falls!
Doesn't matter if you're
in or out of the ring!
It's Hell! That's the Corrida Colosseum!
We're about to get started!
All right!
It's the first round of the special
event in the Corrida Colosseum!
A battle royal of the
Block A - 137 competitors!
Let the battle begin!
Take this!
Armor! Helmets!
This is awesome!
Can we use anything here?!
You can use anything
except projectile weapons.
A half-naked statue of an old warrior man!
Cool!
Can I have it?!
No.
I will wear this armor!
And a helmet that's cooler
than that old man's!
Oh! This is good, too!
I'm gonna use this big sword!
This is nice! I look awesome!
So cool!
I wish Usopp and the others
were here to see me!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Th-The nobleman is so...
Nobleman?!
All of the female staff are fainting.
What?!
No, I can't take it anymore!
Look, that's Cavendish!
The Pirate Noble?! Is he alive?!
I can't believe how beautiful he is!
This is the dressing room, huh?
Hey you, right there.
That's no good.
There is a weight limit for gear.
LUCY - A GLADIATOR
Huh? Is that so?
But it's so cool...
Well, whatever you do,
there is no chance for you.
I will win the Flare-Flare Fruit.
Yes! That beautiful power belongs only to me.