Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Deliver Princess Vivi!
The Luffy Pirates Set Sail"
Damn, they're annoying!
What's their problem?!
This can't be! What strength!
Unbelievable!
Alright, then. Let's settle this!
Yeah!
Knock that off!
What the heck are you guys doing?!
It's just a good thing you
managed to keep the girl safe!
You almost let a billion
Berries get away from us!
Understand?!
What are you talking about?
Why did you save me?
Right! We need to talk about that!
It's like this...
Won't you make a contract with me?
Contract?
Quit fighting!
Oh! You shoulda just said so, Zoro!
I just figured you cut them all down
'cause they didn't
make any food you liked!
Don't compare me to you!
C'mon! Don't sweat it!
Shut up, you two!
So there you have it!
As compensation,
I'd like one billion Berries.
You saw how strong these guys are.
It's a pretty good offer, if you ask me.
I can't!
I do appreciate your
saving me. Thank you.
Why can't you?! You're a princess!
One billion shouldn't be much...
Do you know of the kingdom
known as Alabasta?
No.
It's a peaceful kingdom known
as a great civilization and nation.
Well, it used to be.
Used to be? What about now?
It's in the middle of a civil war.
For years now, signs of a
revolution have begun to appear.
The people revolted, and the
kingdom fell into total chaos...
Then, one day, I heard the
name of an organization...
...Baroque Works!
I learned that the populace was
being manipulated by this group.
But there was a tight lid on
any other information than that,
and there was nothing I could do.
That's when I asked Igaram,
who always meddled in my business
since childhood, for help.
The old tube hair guy?
Tube? Oh, yes.
I asked him if there was a way
I could infiltrate Baroque Works.
Because that would let us see
who was pulling the strings,
and what their goal was.
You're a pretty high-spirited princess.
So? Did you figure out
this goal of theirs?
"The founding of an ideal nation."
That's what Igaram-san said, anyway.
Oh, does that mean...
Yes.
The boss says it's to
create an ideal nation,
but it's an enormous lie!
The true goal is to
take over Alabasta Kingdom!
I have to hurry back, tell everyone
the truth, and stop the fighting!
If I don't do something...
I see.
So that's the deal.
Now everything finally connects.
There'd be no money
during a civil war, huh?
Hey.
Who is pulling the strings?
T-The boss' identity?!
You shouldn't ask that!
You know who it is, right?
Don't ask me! Anything but that!
Your lives will be put in danger, too!
I think I'll pass on that!
After all, these are guys trying
to take over an entire country!
They're obviously
insanely dangerous people!
Yes! They are!
As strong as you people may be,
you'd never stand a chance
against one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea,
Crocodile!
Who, now?
You just said it.
What was that bird and sea otter?!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Are they going to tell someone?!
Hey! A Warlord!
Not too shabby!
I-I'm very sorry!
It just slipped out!
Like that really fixes things now!
Why did you have to
drag us down with you?!
Being hunted by a Warlord the
moment we enter the Grand Line
is too much to handle!
We're lucky we can see him so soon!
I wonder what he's like!
Shut up, you two!
It's been a short acquaintance,
but I thank you for everything!
Where are you going?
They don't know what we look
like yet! I'm running away!
Wow! That's so good!
I guess this means there's
nowhere to run now, huh?!
I'm sorry!
She's funny!
Where was she planning
to run to, anyway?
Guess that means all three of us
are on Baroque Works's hit list now.
That's exciting for some reason!
I-I do have 500,000
Berries in savings...
Fear not!
It's...
Ma-ma-ma...
It's all right! I have a plan!
Igaram! What are those clothes?!
You look hilarious in those, old guy!
It's idiot after idiot...
Vivi-sama. Please listen to me carefully.
Once Baroque Works's intelligence
network learns of something,
pursuers may come after
you almost immediately.
On top of that, if you
know the boss' secrets...
You know what happens.
A thousand or so people
will come after you.
Therefore, I will pretend
to be you, like so,
and sail straight to Alabasta
with three dummies on board.
These are us?
A decoy, huh?
While the pursuers are busy with me,
all of you will head to
Alabasta via the normal route.
Hold it!
Who said we were gonna
take the princess there?!
We still haven't come
to an agreement, you know!
Take the princess there? What now?
You haven't heard?
Pops here wants us to take her home.
Oh, that's what this is about? Sure!
Crocodile is gonna
come after us, you know!
Is Crocodile really that strong?
He's one of the
Seven Warlords of the Seas.
He's a legally recognized pirate,
and thus has no bounty on his head.
However, the bounty he did have
long ago was 80 million Berries.
80 million?! That's four times
Arlong's bounty! Say no!
Will you do it?
Yeah! It sounds like fun!
I am ever grateful!
Ma-ma-ma... Now, then.
I, Vivi, will leave from here.
That's a perfect imitation, old guy!
Imitation of who?!
Now then, Princess.
Please give me the Eternal Pose.
Eternal Pose?
You've never heard of it?
I suppose you could say it's a
permanent version of a Log Pose.
Whereas a Log Pose always
leads ships to the next island,
an Eternal Pose will never forget
the magnetic energy of the island
that is stored in it.
Meaning it will forever
point to that island alone.
And this one is set to Alabasta.
You're going to use this to go to Alabasta?
Vivi-sama. Please take the indirect
island-hopping route to Alabasta.
I've not taken the path myself,
but it should only be two or three
islands if you follow the Log.
Please take good care of the princess.
Yeah!
Igaram...
I expect it will be a harsh journey.
Be careful on your way.
Iga--!
You, too!
Let us meet safely at our motherland.
You must save the kingdom
by your own hand!
There he goes.
He was a funny old guy, to the very end!
He really is reliable.
No!
That's impossible!
They're already after us?!
He was a great person!
Nami! What's the Log say?!
We're okay! It's stored up!
Bring her with us!
We're setting sail!
Vivi! Vivi!
Hurry! If they find us,
it'll all be for nothing!
Don't worry! We will get you there!
I know they don't look like it...
Luffy! Go wake those two up!
...but they saved the East Blue!
I'm going to the ship!
Just the four of them!
Alright! Leave it to me!
Baroque Works?! Crocodile?! Ha!
The Seven Warlords are nothing at all!
Let's go!
What the--?! Oww! What the--?!
What the hell're you doing, Luffy?! Hey!
My nose is coming off!
Let go, dammit! What's goin' on?!
Hurry, Vivi!
R-Right!
Karoo is missing!
A decoy. How foolish...
Hey! I brought 'em!
Get on! We're ready to leave anytime!
Huh? These guys are still sleeping!
There's no time to look for him!
But I can't just leave him here!
Still!
Hey! What's the problem?!
She says her duck is missing!
He won't come when we whistle for him!
This him?
You're there?!
He was here even before me.
There's a tributary just up the river!
We can use it to get
out to sea a little faster!
Alright! Let's go!
Hey.
Mr. Bushido...
Just how many people are
gonna be chasing us down?
I don't know.
There are about 2,000
people in Baroque Works,
and I've heard there are several
town-like bases like this one nearby.
They really might send 1,000 people?!
H-Huh?!
Hey! The ship's leaving!
Finally awake, I see.
Wait! Let's stay just one more night!
Yeah!
This town is great!
And the girls are cute!
There's no telling when
we'll have this much fun again!
Let's take it easy! We are pirates!
Plus, it's not even morning yet!
They have some nerve.
They don't even know anything...
Hey! Explain to them!
Yep! I just did!
That was fast...
Yeah, I left out the complicated parts.
We should be able to
leave the island soon...
Cool! There's fog now!
It's almost morning...
It's good we managed to
escape the people chasing us!
That's for sure!
We need to be careful not to
crash the ship into the rocks.
Just leave it to me!
Wait. Was that you, Luffy?
Nope.
This is a nice ship.
Who're you?!
Y-You're...!
I ran into Mr. 8 a short while ago,
Miss Wednesday.
You killed Igaram!
Who cares about that?!
What're you doing on this ship?!
Who are you?!
What are you doing here...
...Miss All Sunday?!
Miss All Sunday?!
What number is she partner to?!
She's the partner of Mr. 0... the boss!
The bo-- Crocodile?!
Is she bad?
She was the only one
who knew the boss's identity.
We found out who he is by following her!
More accurately...
I allowed you to follow me.
Oh! Then she's good!
I know that!
You're also the one who told him
we discovered his identity, right?!
Correct.
So she really is bad!
Pipe down, you!
What exactly is it you're trying to do?!
Good question.
You were all so intent and serious
that I found myself helping out.
The idea of a princess trying
her hardest to save her kingdom
while making herself
an enemy of Baroque Works...
It was just so ridiculous, you see...
Don't you mock me!
Hey! Sanji! You do realize
what you're doing?!
No, not really.
I just sense that my beloved
Miss Wednesday is in danger...
I'd appreciate it if you wouldn't
point such dangerous objects at me.
You don't mean...!
A Devil--
A Devil Fruit?!
Which one?! What's her power?!
Oww...
Upon closer look,
you're actually a beautiful lady!
Now, now. Don't be so hasty.
I haven't been given any orders.
I have no reason to fight.
So you're the straw hat captain
I've heard so much about...
...Monkey D. Luffy.
Hey, you! Gimme my hat back!
Are you tryin' to start a fight?!
I deem you an enemy! Leave this instant!
How unlucky you are...
You people who picked up a princess
Baroque Works is out to kill...
And a princess being protected
by a mere handful of pirates...
But what's even unluckier is the
course your Log Pose indicates.
The name of the next island is...
...Little Garden.
We don't even need to do anything;
you'll be wiped out long before
you can even reach Alabasta.
Will not! Gimme my hat back!
You wish! You big dummy!
What are you, a kid?
Do you not think letting yourself
get wiped out is a bit foolish?
An Eternal Pose?
You can skip past Little Garden with that.
It points to an island just before Alabasta:
Nothing At All Island.
None of our employees know that course,
so no one will chase you.
What? She's a good person?
Why are you giving this to us?!
It's a trap, isn't it?
Is it, now?
What do I do? I don't want to
accept this from someone like her.
But now that they've let me onboard,
taking the safest route might be best...
Who cares about that?!
Are you an idiot?!
She just went out of her way
to show us a nicer course!
What if she's actually a good person?!
You're not the one who
decides this ship's course!
I see. That's too bad.
Urgh!
She blew up the old tube
hair guy, so I hate her!
I don't hate high-spirited people.
If you survive...
...let's meet again.
No!
Let's go, Bunchi!
W-What is that?!
Don't tell me it's a Sea King!
No...
A turtle!
What a huge turtle!
I can't tell what that
woman is thinking one bit!
Then there's no point
in thinking about it.
We already got someone
like that on this ship, anyway.
Hey! Explain what's going on!
None of this makes sense!
Oh, Miss Wednesday!
Don't tell me you've joined the crew?!
Hey! Explain already--!
Whoa! There's an ostrich onboard!
C'mon, what's going on?!
Is it for food?
Explain what's going on!
I see.
It's too bad I missed out on it,
but there's still opportunity
for me to shine, too.
Don't worry!
Now that this sleeping prince has awoken,
your safety is guaranteed!
Whoa! Good thing I slept through it!
Nami-san. Jealous any?
Nope!
Is it really all right
for me to be on this ship?
I'll only trouble you all...
What're you talking about?!
We know who you are now!
If you didn't want to trouble us,
you should've done so from the start!
I'm sorry.
Right, Luffy?
Yeah! I'm hungry!
Maybe it doesn't matter at all?
For now, looks like our
next destination is set.
Little Garden, huh?
H-Hey, now! Will we be alright there?!
Who knows? Let's go, men!
Yeah!
It'll be quite the sight...
Little Garden...
You've got me!
Ah, gentle song
Make it there for us
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
If you find the world is full of enemies,
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
You've got me!
Ah, my love
I'll hold you in my arms forever
You've got me!
Next is Little Garden!
What do you think it's like?!
But we need to hurry to Alabasta!
Oh, that reminds me of him!
"Him"?
A friend of mine named Coby!
The guy at that axe-hand navy freak's place?
Axe-hand?! You mean Morgan?
Think he's still at that guy's place?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Try Hard, Coby!
Coby-Meppo's Struggles in the Navy"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!