Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
The giant ship, Noah, has just lost its power
and is starting to fall
towards the island again!
What?!
About Hordy Jones...
I found out who he really is!
Hordy is...
...a monster who was brought
to life by our environment!
The New Fish-Man Pirates are a group of
monsters created from an ancient grudge!
What did you go through in the past?!
Answer me, Hordy!
What did humans do to you?!
Nothing.
We were chosen by heaven to punish humans...
...and granted powers!
Their hatred is...
...not rooted in their
experience or true beliefs.
They have no substance!
They are completely "empty"!
"Back to Zero! Earnest Wishes for Luffy!"
Their hatred is not rooted in
their experience or true beliefs.
They have no substance! They
are completely "empty"!
Empty? What does he mean by that?
Hey, you guys, you got to keep
moving! Get off of the island!
You can see the shadow of the
Noah up in the sky already!
--Hurry up! It's gonna come within range soon!
--I'm hurrying!
How much longer? How much
inflation do we have so far?!
87%!
Make it in time! Make it!
Hurry up, Yowahoshi!
Hordy-sama looks even more
terrifying than before!
Humans are lowly creatures.
Remember, Hordy.
They are evil.
This is it! We're doomed!
Since the Pirate Era began, we've kept
losing our friends day after day!
Humans have kidnapped some young Mermaids
and sold them to the Human Shoppe!
We're all doomed! The
Fish-Man Island will fall!
--Damn humans!
--We have to kill them all!
Kill them! Kill them! Kill them all!
Damn! Humans!
They get on my nerves!
Oh, you got stronger-ch!
Wow!
It's great! We have a hero!
He blew up the Human Shoppe sacrificing
his life! Pay him your respects!
Let's not forget his death!
Hero?
That serves you right, humans!
This is awesome!
Yeah.
Heroes are cool-ch!
Dosun!
Arlong-san sank another human pirate ship!
This is a crusade!
Ages ago, the filth we call "humans"
envied the chosen and gifted Fish-Men
and feared our existence.
And...
...they decided to persecute us.
Humans were everywhere in
the world, like maggots.
So they exploited their only
advantage - their number,
and drove us down to the seafloor.
Listen, everyone! Never forget
our grudge against the humans!
Humans know and fear that
their reckoning day will come!
And that's when we'll make them pay!
Never forget our history.
Feel the disappointment of the dead.
Take over their resentment.
Hold a grudge against humans!
There is this human named Rayleigh
who I knew for a long time
and he's different!
He doesn't make a face
even when he sees me...
Hordy?
I don't like your story, Hachi-san.
It makes me sick.
Humans are afraid.
Take over the resentment. Okay, Hordy?
Remember, Hordy.
They are evil, lowly creatures.
Hate humans.
Hate them. Hate them! Hate them!!
This is terrible!
Tiger-san, the hero who freed the
slaves, has been killed by humans!
What?!
So Tiger was not the chosen hero.
Who are you people?! Go away!
I heard you gave your blood to humans.
So what?! There was a
human who was dying so...
Dad!
Even the members of the royal
family are crazy in this country.
She wants to forgive humans.
Screw that!
Did you hear about Jimbei-san
joining the Seven Warlords?
Only the Arlong Pirates keep
the purity of the Fish-Men.
We need a hero.
This country...
...needs a hero.
Otohime-sama has been shot!
You see? That's what humans do!
They show no mercy even to someone like
the Queen who was so friendly to them!
If the royal family won't
seek revenge out of pride,
we'll never trust this country again!
We don't need such a spineless country!
The leader of those disgraceful
ones has been punished by heaven!
Those villains who want to
forgive humans must die-dosun!
It's time for our revenge!
Heaven chose us finally and granted us power.
--Don't tell me it's...
--That legendary drug-ch?!
I can't believe you got it-dosun!
Can you make a lot of it, Zeo?
I'll try.
The people of the Fish-Man District who are
disappointed with the
country will come together!
This is a crusade! Get ready!
Prepare to kill as many humans
as you can until your own death!
We were chosen...
...to inherit the duty of vengeance!
The reckoning day will come!
Evil lowly creatures - humans!
We're devoting our life to this vengeance!
It was too late!
I don't know when but we lost
contact with the Fish-Man District
and they've become something like an
isolated, dark side of the Fish-Man Island!
We pretended not to see the twisted hatred
building up in that lawless ditch...
...in the deep water!
--Hey you! Where are you going?!
--Let me go! The Noah is...
No way!
I filled my mother's shoes
and collected signatures
but I was only dealing
with superficial matters.
But I thought I was making a progress!
I know it's hard but...
...you can't plant your anger and resentment
toward humans in children's minds!
It was too late!
People like them are the ones
that my mother feared the most!
Brother-sama!
We should have fought within ourselves first!
We should have fought our
own feelings toward humans!
Mother was...
Mother was killed by the grudge
growing on the Fish-Man Island!
It was too late! People like them are...
...the ones that my mother feared the most!
We should have fought within ourselves first!
We should have fought our
own feelings toward humans!
Mother was...
Mother was killed by the grudge
growing on the Fish-Man Island!
Maybe she knew it!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Don't let resentment or hatred get
the better of you for my sake.
But a part of me held that resentment
and hated humans for killing my mother!
Prince...
Dead people take their regret to the grave.
So a grudge is an illusion that the living
create and they alone cultivate it!
Because I hated humans - even
a bit, I overlooked the
resentment in the Fish-Man District
and when I finally noticed, it had
become too powerful and beyond control!
If nothing is done, the
Fish-Man Island will...
...destroy itself through its
own hatred toward humans!
Be careful!
Unlike the bubble protecting the
island, this one can overshoot the ship!
It has to surround the
Noah! It can't go too far!
Straw Hat! Please!
We don't need the past!
Reset our history to zero!
Wipe out those phantoms who shut
the island away from the sun!
Okay, now!
Go!
Bring the Fish-Man Island back...
...to zero!
Shut up, Fukaboshi!
The Fish-Men's grudge will last forever!
Brother-hoshi.
As long as you let me handle
it my way, don't worry.
H-Hey! Those guys fighting against
Hordy's crew at the plaza are...
--Yes, it's the Straw Hats!
--And Boss Jimbei!
What?!
--Luffy-chan's voice!
--Oh yeah!
Yes! It's in the bubble!
Our minds were made up when
we arrived at the plaza that,
along with Jimbei, we wouldn't
let anyone harm the island!
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
We're friends, right?
I cannot believe we suspected
a human like him!
Hey, what's wrong? Don't stop!
We have to run! Hey!
--I'm gonna stay on the island!
--What?!
Me too!
--Me too!
--I'm not gonna run either!
Me too!
--Luffy-sama! There is air on the Noah now!
--Yeah!
You can't get away from me!
Hordy-sama!
Yowahoshi! Stay with me! I
promise I won't let you be hurt!
Okay!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-sama!
Take this! The Wings of Ikaros!
Wings?
That's not tsubasa (wings).
That's tsuba (spit)!
Squid!
Ink?
It's too bad for you-ch!
That was my alter ego made from squid ink!
Don't underestimate us officers of...
Franky Fireball!
Oh, I don't wanna become a dried squid-ch!
Yes! General Franky's new attack!
He shot a fireball from his stomach!
Huh?
You breathed it?!
How could you drop your guard-gaban?!
Weight Boost!
T-shot!
Heavy Gong!
He stopped my hammer with his bare hand?!
Ow... Maybe this transformation is not
suited for a fight against a hammer!
Hey, Chopper!
That was the form that gave you the most
human-like look but now
you look like a monster!
I don't care now.
I wanted to look like a human
because I wanted friends.
Now I wanna become a monster
who is helpful to Luffy!
I see.
Smiles make me wanna slice!
Bring the strongest swordsman
on the Fish-Man Island!
You're not even able to kill my boredom.
Straw Hat!
It's all over now!
Weren't you listening?
I won't let anyone harm the Fish-Man Island!
It's finally time...
...for the climax of the Straw
Hats' battle in Conchcorde Plaza.
And on the Noah, Hordy, transformed
into a living weapon...
...mercilessly attacks Luffy.
In order to fulfill his
promise to Fukaboshi...
...Luffy puts everything he's got into
his fists in order to crush Hordy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy's All-out Attack! Red Hawk Blasts!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!