Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
Wicked rain will get in my way
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy reached the Maiden Island...
...only to became depressed by
his own feelings of weakness.
What is it that you still have?!
"Reunited with Dark King Rayleigh!
Decision Time for Luffy!"
CALM BELT
THE BAY AT THE CLIFF COAST
OF THE MAIDEN ISLAND
He stopped screaming.
Now that you mention it, I
wonder where Straw Hat is.
He's gonna die if his wound opens up, right?
I got one!
What's wrong?
I think I just saw a fish...
Th-That's big!
Look! That's a huge Sea King!
Is it fighting?
It's dead! It got killed!
--But it's huge!
--I couldn't see what did it!
It's scary around here.
Huh?!
--A man?
--Hey! Who are you?!
Oh boy...
D...
--Dark King Rayleigh!!
--What?!
Oh, it's you guys. We met
at Sabaody Archipelago.
He was the first mate of Roger,
the King of the Pirates!
Well, my ship sank in the storm
and I had no choice but to swim.
Storm?! The Calm Belt is always
calm - it's never rough!
There shouldn't be a storm!
That means his ship wrecked further
away and he swam all the way here?!
I have a good breaststroke.
That's not the point.
Then, that Sea King was fighting with...
...you?!
Only a legendary pirate could do that!
Oh, I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?!
Oh yeah!
I assume Luffy-kun must
be here on this island.
Did you hear
THE CENTER OF THE ISLAND:
THE FEMALE-ONLY EMPIRE AMAZON LILY
that Snake Princess-sama and the others...
...have just gone to deliver food to Luffy?
I wanna stretch his body again!
They said they'll invite him
over when he gets better.
I can't wait!
I didn't expect to see him again this soon!
Men are interesting!
If I could become a man, my body
would be stretchable like his!
I can't wait!
Yeah, maybe I'll make
clothes for him again...
...without frills!
We're separated although we're newlyweds!
I feel like a tragic heroine!
"But Hancock... No, my dear wife!"
"Y-Yes!"
"No matter how far away from each
other we are, our love is forever!"
"Luffy!"
Oh, my sweet husband! My heart is aflame!
Like I said before, Snake Princess,
just because someone hugs
you and uses your name,
it doesn't mean you are married.
Then, what counts as marriage?
Hmmm... That's a difficult question.
You can't go to Sabaody now with that wound.
But I wanna see my friends
as soon as possible.
I have to be there just like I promised.
But...
Hmm? The submarine is gone.
Oh, Luffy-kun!
Huh?! The old guy Rayleigh!
I'm glad to see you this soon!
Why are you here?!
I was about to head to Sabaody
using the Vivre Card.
Did you see my friends?
No, I don't think they made it there yet.
I gave my Vivre Card to Shakky...
...in order to go anywhere I want.
Dark King Rayleigh! Is it really
you? I can't believe it!
You must be the former Warlord...
He's Jimbei, he saved my life.
What's wrong?
Well, I didn't expect to
see a living legend here.
Here. Isn't this hat important to you?
It is. Thanks.
It doesn't feel right without it after all!
Have you seen a group of pirates here?
If you're talking about
Trafalgar Law, he just left.
He said that you have to rest
in bed for 2 more weeks.
He saved your life, didn't he?
What a waste! We got that far...
I wanted to get in the female-only empire.
They were allowing bears in.
Shut up!
I'm sorry.
So weak!
I wonder what the Dark King is up to.
Whatever it is I'm sure that "D." will
cause quite a storm once again...
Can't wait to see him again.
Oh, Rayleigh?! You must be Rayleigh!
Oh, Gloriosa! It's been awhile!
--Rayleigh!
--Ray-san!
Oh, you two are here too!
Luffy!
Hey, Big Sis! How could you ignore
the man who saved your life?
You know the old man Rayleigh?
--Yes!
--It's a long story.
Luffy, so you're awake now.
I haven't
slept for days worrying about you.
You must be hungry. I brought some food.
So go ahead and dig in...
You can't even look at him.
How could you call it marriage?
Serve him...
Serve him a meal already!
Jimbei! These are not for you!
You can have just a little bit.
O-Okay. Luffy-kun, why don't we just eat?
Luffy-kun, you have to eat. Eating is living!
That's it! That's my Luffy-kun!
Jimbei! I said "just a little bit"!
Thank you for bringing me
the letter from Shakky.
Sounds like she hasn't changed.
Yeah, she's just the way she was
when you were living in Sabaody.
She's doing fine.
These girls have become very beautiful
and strong over the past 13 years.
Rayleigh, Shakky, Granny Nyon.
You three protected us when we were
running from the Celestial Dragons.
But we have a problem.
We should be providing shelter
for Luffy from the Navy.
Even though Rayleigh
knows Luffy from before,
if it's easy enough for someone
to guess that Luffy's here,
we should be worrying.
Huh?! What an old familiar face!
You're Rayleigh, aren't you?
You just noticed?!
How mad are you about him?!
No, I don't think the Navy
can guess that he's here.
First of all, the one who sent him away
told me that he sent him in this direction.
Kuma...
I work for the Revolutionaries army.
Since I have a connection with them.
I wanna let them get away from here.
Oh, I can't believe it.
And where's Monkey-chan now?
I don't know.
I'm sorry about my abrupt manner earlier.
Can I talk to you for a moment?
I don't have...
...much time left.
Straw Hat should be...
In the direction that Bartholomew
Kuma blew Luffy-kun away,
there is the Maiden Island.
That's not all.
I found out some interesting
information about the War of the Best.
It's with regards to the prison break at
Impel Down by Luffy-kun and the others.
When I thought about how Luffy-kun was
able to infiltrate the great prison,
it dawned on me that Luffy-kun
must have stowed away on a
Navy ship with Hancock, but...
Since Hancock hates both
the Government and men,
I don't think that she'd
get on a Government ship,
especially not to help a man.
Now, this part is all theoretical.
But how about this?
Say that Hancock fell in
love with Monkey-chan,
everything makes sense.
Monkey-chan is a good-looking guy.
And if I were Hancock,
I'd give him refuge on the Maiden
Island to spite the Navy.
That's a very subjective theory, Shakky.
Women's intuition is unbelievable.
--That's my Shakky!
--She couldn't be any more right, as you can see.
Yeah? You like it? Good!
The Navy won't take action based
on a ridiculous theory like that.
So this place is safe.
Now, let's get down to business.
Luffy-kun.
You said you're gonna head
for Sabaody, didn't you?
I need to see my friends.
Is that what you really want?
Sabaody Archipelago.
Remember what happened to
you guys on that island?
Everyone focus on escaping!
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
I couldn't save even one of my friends...!
Do you think you can face those
tremendous powers as you are now?
But I...
Do you want to be reunited with your
friends just to endure the same fate?
I have a suggestion for you.
Of course it's up to you to...
...do it or not.
Meanwhile, on the Bowin
Islands in the Grand Line...
GRAND LINE - BOWIN ISLANDS
Stop! Usopp'n!
Don't stop me, Heracles'n!
Usopp is...
...shaking his body which has grown huge
from eating an abundant variety
of food in the forest...
...and running.
It's impossible'n!
No, it's not! That's why I'll try again!
I can do it this time!
There you are!
Get out of my way!
Sure Kill...
Oh no'n! Usopp'n!
Are you okay, Usopp'n?
Damn...
You can't do that. If you try
to get off of this island,
terrifying living things
will stand in your way
and push you back to the forest'n.
Nothing will stop you from
entering the island'n
but once you've set foot on it, you're dead!
No one ever leaves this island alive'n!
And my name is Heracles'n!
Oh?! Usopp'n! Where did you go?!
Oh, he's in danger'n!
The sea creature has just
come onto the island!
Usopp'n is in danger!
The sweet scent from Bowin Islands
draws the attention of...
...giant insects and giant birds...
...and even sea creatures and Sea Kings.
It's a sea hippo!
I shouldn't get fascinated by it now!
The scents lure them
deeper into the island...
...where they find the
forest filled with food.
It's easy to enter the island...
But it's hard to leave...
Outta my way! Sure Kill - Exploding Star!
I'm gonna get out of here!
Don't get in my way!
I have to go back!
To Sabaody!
Exploding Star!
Usopp'n!
The islands are gonna move again!
What?
Usopp'n! Hang onto a tree!
It's happening again?!
It's gonna eat something!
The name of this flower that
looks like an island is...
People call them the Bowin Islands
but the scientific name is Stomach
Baron: a meat-eating plant!
Usopp'n!
What's the matter with you, Usopp'n?
You changed since reading the
newspaper that News Coo brought!
I...
...have no time to waste here now!
Luffy lost his brother in the war!
He must be having a very hard time now!
When your friend is having a hard time,
you should be there for him!
Luffy!!
Luffy's friends take
action, concerned for him,
but Nami is held captive by
the researchers of Weatheria.
Meanwhile, on Winter Island, Franky heads to
a certain place in search of an ice-breaker.
What extremely dangerous
button has he found there?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Back to Our Captain!
A Jail Break at the Sky Island and
the Incident on the Winter Island!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!