Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After being ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma,
Luffy was separated from
his friends and arrived alone
at the female-only empire of Amazon Lily.
After his capture,
it appeared that Luffy had
successfully escaped, but...
The Snake Princess is about to bathe!
Is this a bath?
A man!
Hey...
That thing on your back...
It seems familiar somehow...
You saw it, didn't you?!
"Heartless Judgment!
Margaret is Turned to Stone!!"
Big Sis!
Big Sis! What happened?!
Who is that? A man?!
What is a man doing in this land?!
What in the world happened?!
Oh, I, uhh...
He saw my back.
Then he'll have to die.
Huh?! H-How come?! I only saw her back!
I dunno why,
but I could swear I've seen it
somewhere before...
We would rather die
than let anyone see
what you saw on my back!
That thing? How come?
Who are you? How come?
Take everything you saw to the grave!
Love-Love Beam!
Slow-Slow?!
A Slow-Slow Beam?!
Oh no!
I'm turning slower! Slow...er...
Love-Love Beam!
Why won't he petrify?!
Does he not feel any excitement
from seeing me in the bath?!
That's not possible, Big Sis!
The beauty of your naked body would
charm anyone of any age or gender!
His fear of death must be
overpowering his wicked thoughts!
He's a pathetic, yet lucky man!
I dunno what's going on,
but I'm getting outta here!
I just wanna talk to someone important!
He jumped out from this height!
He won't get away!
Pistol Kiss!
Huh?! They don't bounce off!
They're not metal bullets?!
That man is an intruder!
Seize him, Kuja Pirates!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
A man?! What's a man doing here?!
Let's just catch him for now!
That hurt!
It's in your best interest to do as we say!
Ran! No man would ever try
to defy the Kuja Pirates!
Besides, he looks weak anyway!
It's a man!
A live man in the village...!
Are you the all-women pirate group?
Do you know where your boss is?
Why do you want to know that?!
Your boss owns a ship, right?
So I wanna find her
and ask for a ride on her ship
and hurry onto the sea!
What nonsense!
Men are forbidden in Amazon Lily!
Do you honestly think
you'll get to leave alive?!
Stupid man!
This is no time for me to get caught!
Gum-Gum...
Seize him!
...Rocket!
What the...?!
After him! Quickly!
The Snake Princess's orders!
Don't let him escape, no matter what!
A man!
There's a male intruder!
A male?!
The Kuja Pirates are chasing him!
Let's help out, too!
Alright! Let's go!
Of all things, allowing a man onto the
island when the Kuja are in peril...
This is unprecedented.
I can't help but worry what
the future holds for this land.
Catch the man!
The Kuja Pirates!
So he did return to the village...
There he is!
Over there!
I would've thought she'd
be in a tall building...
Where do I go to meet someone important?
Those pirates caught up to me already?!
Let's kill him before the
Snake Princess catches him!
Oh, it's them again?!
He fell off!
There he is! The man!
Crap!
Halt!
Wait, you!
It can't be!
Why would this rookie worth
300 million be in Amazon Lily?!
There he is!
Well, I gotta run!
Wait! Let me see your face again!
I said wait!
Even the old ladies here are strong?
There's no escape now!
Oh no! The Kuja Pirates caught him!
I guess there's nothing we can do now!
This man really is...
Damn! Come off, you stupid things!
What are these iron rope-like snakes?!
We were too slow.
Let's just hope they don't
ask how he arrived here...
He's going to be killed, isn't he?
What's with this place?
There really isn't even one guy here.
Snake Princess!
Marigold-sama!
Sandersonia-sama!
Let me ask you this, man.
How and why did you come to this island?!
Seriously, I don't know, either!
I suddenly went flying through the sky
and before I realized it, I was here!
Lies.
You can't fool me with that ridiculous story.
You must be after something.
Well, you could give me a ship!
I'd appreciate getting a lift most of all,
but anyway, there's a place
I need to leave for right away!
If you're the most important person here,
then please! I want to set sail!
What nonsense is this?!
The Snake Princess is right!
He's obviously lying!
He must be plotting something!
You can't fool us!
Oh, I've been thanking you non-stop!
Is there anything I can do for you?
As long as the others are
still alive like I am,
that's all that matters.
As long as they're alive,
I can keep fighting again and again!
How dare he speak so rudely and
tastelessly to the Snake Princess?!
He's appalling!
Don't think you can leave this place alive.
Your death is inescapable!
Please wait, Snake Princess!
I-I don't think he's the
kind of person who can lie!
Margaret!
Snake Princess...
Snake Princess.
E-Everything this man says is sincere.
He hardly seems like the type
to bring harm to our land!
Oh! You!
Yeah! Tell her for me!
A defense warrior?
My name is Margaret!
Men are forbidden here.
His death sentence was set in stone
the moment he stepped foot on this land.
Why do you protect him?
I feel I owe him.
The person who let him into this country...
...was I!
Margaret! Why?!
Snake Princess! W-We can explain!
Yes!
We found him in the forest
covered in mushrooms!
We thought he was from the village
and carried him here!
Sweetpea! Aphelandra!
We're also responsible for
the crime of bringing him here!
That's right!
Stop, you two!
I'm the one who suggested
bringing him to the village!
Does she know what this means?
Margaret is way too honest!
Oh, you guys!
You guys tried to kill me,
but you're actually nice after all!
Only I'm guilty of letting
him into the country!
Margaret!
It's all right.
Look up, honest Margaret.
I like honest people.
Tell me.
Do you wish for forgiveness?
Y-Yes...
You may rise.
Is the Snake Princess going to forgive
those three for their great crimes?!
That's the Snake Princess for you!
She's not only beautiful,
she's so compassionate too!
Snake Princess!
Love-Love Beam!
What the...?!
The fools...
Hey! What happened to you guys?!
What happened?!
They turned to stone! How come?!
Hey...
Hey...!
Hey, you! What did you do to them?!
They saved my life, you know!
Yes.
They were punished
because they helped you.
It's my fault that they...
Wait! Turn them back to normal!
Just who do you think
you're giving orders to?
Turn them back now!
Bring out Bakula!
Bakula?!
It's all over for that man now!
I told you to turn them back!
This is the warrior nation of Amazon Lily.
The strong are beautiful.
Fight your hardest and perish.
We will watch and see you off.
That black panther's name is Bakula.
A carnivorous beast that
has served as executioner
for this land's empresses for generations.
After each execution,
not even a single bone remains.
Bakula seems to be quite starved.
Yes, Big Sis.
I'm told it hasn't been fed
for several days now.
Be happy, man!
Bakula will gladly eat even
a scrawny monkey like you!
Never mind that...!
What about these guys?!
Will they go back to normal?!
How dare he speak so rudely
to the Snake Princess?!
Get 'im, Bakula!
Bakula!
Go!
He's strong!
He knocked out Bakula in one hit!
He didn't use Haki!
Then that was just brute strength?!
You guys are screwed up.
That woman...
She turned your comrades into stone,
so how can you all sit
there and laugh like that?!
Th-The savage man is yelling at us!
Unbelievable! What a vicious creature!
I feel bad about those three,
but the Snake Princess was
right to do what she did!
They're the ones to blame!
They broke the rules of our land!
Whatever I do...
...I will be forgiven.
The reason for that is,
yes...
...because I'm beautiful!
Snake Princess!
Wouldn't you agree, too?
You piss me off!
Big Sis! Stay strong!
This can't be!
No man exists that won't be my slave!
I cannot stand that man's existence!
How dare you say that to the Snake Princess?!
Hurry and execute him!
Execution!
Execution! Execution!
Go! Marigold! Sandersonia!
Take that man's head!
Yes! Leave it to us, Big Sis!
These guys have powers?
Execution!
Execution!...
Sandersonia and Marigold transform
using the power of the
Snake-Snake Fruit, in order to execute Luffy.
Luffy does his best to
dodge and counter-attack.
However, it proves useless.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Difficult Fight for Luffy!
The Snake Sisters' Haki Power!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!