Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
"A Big Rice Cake Tossing Race
at the Castle! Red Nose's Plot"
A joyous new year has arrived
in the country of Grand Jipang.
Well, what a blessing that is.
We wrapped up the restless days at the end
of the last year. Why don't we take it easy?
The new year has just started.
What's going on?
I just said we should take it easy,
and now things already seem restless!
Who the heck is causing it?!
Outta our way! Outta our way!
Outta our way! Make way for us!
Well, you don't have to
shout like that, Onami-san.
Huh?
There's no one around here.
Oh... you're right.
The sun is already high, and yet
this town is like a ghost town.
I wonder if everyone's still in bed.
Oh, come on, Doctor, wake up!
They've already gone to the castle.
In any event, today is the day they
hold Grand Jipang's popular event,
the New Year's Big Rice Cake Tossing!
If you were a resident of this town,
you'd rush straight to the castle.
Oh? Is that right?
Anyway, it's a rice cake tossing event.
They can't start it without rice cakes.
"Purveying to the Castle"
It can affect our business reputation, too.
Please rush to the castle!
Okay!
But don't they usually do the rice
cake tossing at temples and shrines?
Here, our lord tosses them at the castle.
Every year the scramble for them is
so crazy that there are even casualties.
What?!
Oh, he's just joking, Doctor.
There're no casualties.
But when it comes to that Boss
Straw Hat, he might go that far.
I wonder if someone's talking about me.
Setting aside Boss, I didn't know that
people in this town were so gluttonous.
It's not like that, Doctor.
What they're after are not regular
rice cakes, but a jackpot rice cake.
Huh? Jackpot?
That's right.
Tens of thousands of rice cakes will be
tossed from the top of the castle tower.
And among them is a single jackpot rice cake.
In this rice cake, there's a
treasure called a diamond.
And believe it or not, it's worth
more than 10 million Ryo-Berries!
That sure is magnificent, don't you think?
I'd definitely like to get it.
"New Year
Big Rice Cake Tossing Event Held Here"
But how do I figure out
which one contains the jackpot?
Beats me. I've never seen one before, so...
Hey, do you know?!
Ah... No, I don't.
In any case, I think you just have to grab
whatever you can lay your hands on
and break them to see inside.
It kind of sounds like a wild goose chase.
If I get the jackpot one, I'll buy lots of books!
I wanna take a trip to a health spa
with everyone at the row house.
Hey! You're open for business
already this morning?
Yes. Since today is the 7th, I'm selling rice
porridge mixed with seven spring herbs.
Would you like a bowl, too?
Yeah, sounds good.
Hey, Usopp! It's not fair that you're
eating by yourself! I'll have some, too!
You can't, Boss! You have to
stay there and stand watch!
This is rice porridge, so I can't
throw it to you. So just give up!
Whoa! Wh-Wh-What the hell is this?!
All right, here it comes! Thanks!
Boss! Once you finish eating it, please go
to the front and stand watch, okay?!
Geez...
Your duty must be tough.
Well, the jackpot is worth
10 million Ryo-Berries, right?
Someone blinded by greed
could be up to no good, so...
Sitting around and waiting for the jackpot
when you don't know where it's gonna fall
is just a pain in the neck! I can't do that!
There's a way to get it for sure.
In short...
...we'll get all the rice cakes
before they toss them at the castle.
Then, we'll get the jackpot one
for sure. Yeah, that's my plan!
You're right!
Men! Get them flashily!
There's nowhere to escape on the bridge!
Geez... When we're almost to the castle...
We don't have time to turn back, guys!
Let's go, Doctor!
Yeah!
That was close!
Not bad.
Onami...
That was cruel.
Take this, too!
Doctor! Watch your back!
Mellorine! Mellorine!
Richie!
You son of a bitch!
Stop, you bastards!
If you don't wanna die,
leave all the stuff on the cart here!
Boss! They got away!
It's not gonna work anymore!
They'll enter the castle
before we catch up with them!
Don't be ridiculous! It's 10 million
Ryo-Berries we're talking about!
I'm not gonna give up!
But...
...I'm not gonna let them get away...
...as I've already prepared my next move.
If you get it, come back
up already and get ready!
Yes, sir!
Father.
Looks like it's getting lively down there.
Yes. They seem like they can't wait.
Yeah... By the way, looks like we still
haven't received the rice cakes yet.
Right...
I'm having someone stand watch,
but I haven't received any report yet.
I'm a little worried that something
might've happened on their way here.
Oh, that's right.
You know the people we're
getting the rice cakes from well.
I wonder if we should send someone for them.
Ahh... Since she said, "We don't
need guards, so pay us generously instead,"
I didn't send any guards. I hope
Onami-san and the others are okay.
Hm? There they are!
What took Onami so long? Rice cakes
taste better right after they're made.
Hm?
What's that kite doing?!
Hey! What's going on?!
Whoa! We're floating in the air!
Hold on tight!
They're waiting in ambush again?!
Those bastards!
Who are you?! Actually, you're from
the Buggy Family, aren't you?!
You're left... I mean, you're right!
By order of Boss Buggy,
I came to take all the rice cakes.
My name is Hachi. Nice to meet you.
"And there's one more person right here!"
"I, the martial artist Gedatsu
of the Buggy Family!!"
Well, don't worry. Once I get the
rice cakes, I won't even touch you guys.
I'll make sure to put you
back on the ground safely.
Don't be ridiculous!
If we can't deliver them after coming this far,
our business reputation will be
totally ruined! Do something, Sanji-kun!
Well, I can't do anything like this.
--Argh!
--Ahh! Help!
Hey, hey. Don't move around.
Don't blame me if you fall.
You rice cake thief! Surrender peacefully!
Gum-Gum...
Idiot! Don't cling to me!
Hmm... Why am I falling too?
Oh, that's right! I should've let the
kite string go! How careless of me!
--Ow, ow, ow...
--Well, we're okay now.
No, we aren't! The cart is...!
Those guys...!
Look at that, guys! The rice
cakes are coming our way!
The jackpot's gonna be mine!
Igaram-san!
Chaka! Pell! Get the cart!
Yes, sir!
How dare you get in my way?!
It doesn't matter who they are!
Take them down!
What're you guys doing?!
But, Boss... We're carrying
this heavy stuff on a slope.
Let's take a little break.
Stop whining! Just go after them!
Onami-dono!
Are you okay?
Yes! Well then, we certainly
delivered what you ordered.
Yes. Thank you.
What about the payment?
I can get it right here and now, right?
The task was more dangerous than we thought.
Oh, about that...
Hey... This is business with the castle.
You can't put it on a tab.
Princess Vivi said that she
herself will bring it to your place.
So wait until then.
Well then, goodbye.
Tell Vivi to stop by any time!
They still haven't given up yet?!
Don't worry about them, Sanji-kun!
Let's go to the event site.
Just leave the rest to the
castle people. It'll be fine.
Hey, Boss! If it turns out that they can't
do the rice cake tossing or something,
you'll be forbidden to come to our eatery!
So work hard, got that?!
Yeah...
Boss! They're already going into the castle!
Shut up! It doesn't matter!
We'll force our way through!
We'll do it flashily!
They've started the rice
cake tossing? I got a late start!
Intruders!
Don't let them get away!
It's the Buggy Family!
They're after these rice cakes!
Got it. Please hurry!
Hey! Where's the event site?
Hm? Oh, it's you!
Good timing! Give us a hand.
--Huh?
--A rice cake thief showed up!
I heard that he's going
on a rampage in the castle!
What?! I've been looking forward to
those rice cakes! Where's the thief?!
--Over there!
--All right!
Trying to get them all
to himself?! How despicable!
Those rice cakes are mine!
What? Hey, hey... You too?
Rice cake thief! I'm gonna
capture you at any cost!
Where are the rice cakes?!
We're not gonna let him
destroy the castle any more!
Well, I have an idea as to where he's headed.
I know a short cut. Leave it to me!
Let's catch up with them quickly, Mr. Monk!
Hey, Usopp. Who have you
been talking to all this time?
Hm? Oh, Boss! Who've I
been talking to? Of course...
Huh?! He's gone! When did that happen?
Anyway, I'm going on ahead, okay?
At any rate, that monk
isn't reliable. Where did he go?
Where are the rice cakes?!
Ahhh!
H-H-Hey...
Oh, no! Oh, no! Oh, no!
Amazon-dono! Are you okay?!
Someone!
What's going on?!
A deviant is in here!
How rude!
What did I do?!
Hold it!
All right! Just go ahead and charge in!
Boss!
It's all over for you, Buggy Family!
I won't allow any more violence in the castle!
Be prepared!
Oh, my, my... Princess.
Thank you very much for greeting me yourself!
You don't know the Chop-Chop Fruit's powers?
This is your own fault for butting in.
Oh, don't get me wrong.
I didn't come here for her. I came
here to get the jackpot rice cake!
Bring the rice cake cart here right away!
I'll exchange her for the cart. Move it already!
Don't blame me if the
princess's neck gets broken!
Wait! We get it.
We have no choice but to do what he says.
Oh? So a lackey realizes the situation
faster than the samurais, huh? Okay, then!
You go and bring the cart here.
Well, the jackpot rice cake isn't on that cart.
Then, where is it?
The jackpot rice cake is...
Don't!
...with our lord!
Oh...?
Is that right?
It's over there.
What?! I-Is it okay to take it so easily? Huh?
That's fine.
I-I-It...
It's empty!
Oh? So that's where big nose was?
You son of a bitch! You flashily deceived me!
Yep.
Buggy, was it? Look outside
the window. On the ground are...
Hey! Don't break the castle!
Hey, big nose! We're not gonna let
you have the jackpot, you bastard!
Like I said, it's empty!
I'm gonna beat you till you cry!
Well, listen. On the ground
are this town's residents
who have been looking forward
to this rice cake tossing event.
This event is held for them so that
they can start the new year cheerfully.
This is a gathering in which
they try their luck, so to speak.
It all depends on your luck
whether you get a prize or not,
but the chance of winning
should be equal for everyone.
So I can't give it to you alone now.
If you want the prize, then go down there
and wait with everyone for
the rice cake tossing to start.
Just as we'd expect from you, my lord.
Splendid persuasion. I'm impressed.
Yep.
Say, my lord. Let's start it already.
If we don't hurry up, Onami is gonna beat me.
Hey! You're being rude! To think
that you speak to our lord that way!
I give up!
I won't need such a small thing!
How dare you mock me?!
I found something better, my lord.
Forget the 10 million Ryo-Berry jackpot!
If I kill you, I'll have this
entire country all to myself!
Now that it's come to this,
I'm gonna blow you up flashily!
Men! Prepare the Special Buggy Ball!
Yes, sir!
I'll teach you a lesson for
deceiving me! Be prepared!
It's ready.
There's no need for formality.
Go ahead and fire now!
--Rice cakes!
--The rice cake tossing has started!
Ah! You bastards!
The one with the jackpot might've
been among the ones we just tossed.
Well, he said he didn't want it anymore.
You bastards! It was a slip of the tongue!
You're causing trouble!
Time for you to go flying!
Good job, guys!
You guys got it, right?!
Find the jackpot no matter what!
Alrighty!
This one-thousand-year-old famous
Alabasta Castle now has three big holes
in its castle tower. This is all because of...
Hey, Straw Hat!
Luffy-san has already gone
down to pick up rice cakes.
Yummy! Yummy!
What's the matter, Igaram?
Why don't you toss the rice cake, too?
This is no time for that, my lord!
The castle tower is the stronghold of the castle!
Showing such a pitiful figure is unprecedented!
This'll hurt the country's dignity, too!
Where are you saying the damage is?
Huh?!
Look at them, Igaram.
They all look like they're having fun.
A country is its people.
People's vitality is indeed the
source of the country's dignity.
The country wouldn't decline
for a reason as small
as the appearance of the castle falling apart.
Here you go!
If people are full of energy,
the country will become full of energy,
and that will become our vitality, too.
Although there was some trouble,
everyone is rejoicing.
That's all we ask, right?
A country is its people.
That certainly is true, right, Igaram?
Indeed...
But my lord, how will you come up
with the repair cost for all this?
Do as you see fit.
Yes, sire.
You're too avaricious, Boss.
This isn't the one.
Where's the jackpot?!
Onami... I can't eat anymore.
Thanks for waiting! I gathered more!
No way!
Come to think of it, Father,
where's the one with the jackpot?
Oh, that's right.
--Oh, my...
--I almost forgot.
Let's see who'll get it.
There!
Whoa!
I finally got a rice cake! Thank heavens!
What's this? A rice cake with a seed?
I can't eat something like this!
Oh, boy...
He sure doesn't have any interest in money.
"Happy New Year"
My strength... is ebbing away.
What'd you do to me?!
Can you figure out the mystery of my powers?
I'll let you fully experience them now.
Oh? You thought I'd stay
on the floor without fighting?
Just watch! You're mistaken if
you think I'm just a cute beauty!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Bubble Master Kalifa!
The Soap Trap Closes in on Nami"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!