Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Where did the 100 million
Berries we had in here go?
Oh, that. I gave it to them to buy meat
and booze and stuff for the party.
Gave it to them?
Well...
...we got a good deal with the ship,
so there's no problem, right?
Oh, Nami! I'm gonna go out and have fun,
so give me some spending money.
@#$%&!!
You're not getting anything!
"A Girl in Search of Her Yagara!
Great Search in the City of Water!"
What is it?
What is it, Aobire?
Was it a dream?
How nice of you, Chopper. Thanks for
treating me to this water-water candy.
No problem! After all,
she did give me 10,000 Berries.
I'll use the rest of the money
to buy medical books.
Oh, yeah?
Hm?
Isn't that Straw Hat?
You're right!
Hey, everyone! Our town's hero's here!
--Whoa!
--Yo! Party King!
We had fun yesterday!
--Thank you!
--Let's do it again!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
After Nami just got done scolding you...
"Missing Yagara"
This'll do.
Anyway, the way you ate
was really something else.
I was really admiring, Party King!
Why don't we pick up where we
left off yesterday at my place today?
What? Are you sure?
--If that's the case, come to my place!
--That's...
--He's coming to my place first!
--If I remember correctly,
--No, my place!
--My place!
--he's the pirate who saved Iceberg-san...
My place!
--My place!
--If it's him, maybe...!
Abi! You left without having breakfast again!
Maybe you should give up on finding Aobire!
Abi...
This time, I'll have him eat at my place!
No! We'll have a party at my place first!
--No! He'll come to my place!
--Your place is tiny!
Straw Hat!
Hm?
I have a favor to ask!
My family's Yagara went missing!
Help me find him... I mean, please!
Hm?
Hey, that's Abi, the photographer's daughter.
So she's still looking for him?
It's been three days since the Aqua Laguna.
I feel bad, but he's probably gone.
Yeah.
He was already over 100 years old.
That big wave was too...
Don't lump him with the
stupid Yagara you have!
That big wave wouldn't be
enough to take out our Aobire!
--What'd you say?!
--Now, now... Calm down, Abi.
As you say, he might have
survived the Aqua Laguna,
but he hasn't been back for
three days now, so he, um...
Yeah, he's right. You shouldn't
drag Straw Hat into it.
You're from Water Seven,
too, so you should know
the story about Yagaras seeking out
their "final nesting village"...
Ahhh! Shut up! Shut up!
No one has seen that place,
so I'm not gonna believe it!
Aobire appeared in my dream!
He asked me to help him!
Say, Straw Hat! You pirates
love treasure, right?!
Here!
This is all the money I have!
If you find him, I'll give it all to you!
Oh? You'll give it to me?
That's if you find him!
You shouldn't bother, Straw Hat.
If you, by any chance, come to step
into their final nesting village...
You, shut up!
Scary!
I don't quite get it, but it is true
that pirates can't just pass up
treasure that's right in front of them.
That treasure of yours...
I'll make it all mine.
Really?
Yeah.
It's a deal.
I'm Abi! Nice to meet you!
I'm Luffy.
This is Chopper, our ship's doctor.
N-Nice to meet you.
Th-The little raccoon dog spoke!
Who're you calling a little raccoon dog?!
So... what am I supposed to find again?
Whoa...
Weren't you listening?!
Aobire! My family's Yagara!
Look!
You'll know it's him by the blue fin on his head.
His fin is blue, so his name is Aobire, huh?
I like it. It's easy to understand.
All right, then! Leave it to me!
Go! Go!
And why are we starting our search here?!
Why not? This is the best place to
look out over the city, don't you think?
I-I'm scared!
Go back to town already!
Well, hold on.
Oh?
That's Zoro.
Hey, Zoro! I'm here!
I'm right here! Can't you hear me?!
Hey, it's shaking!
There's no way he can hear you!
We're gonna fall!
Huh?
That was dangerous!
You are dangerous!
Get your act together!
How about this one, Robin?
That's nice! It looks good on you.
Oh?
--Hey! Nami! Robin!
--Not again!
--Hey!
--Oh...
Oh, that's right. If we ask Robin...
A Yagara with a blue fin on his head, huh?
Okay. I'll try.
Ojos Fleur!
Robin, did you find him?
I'm sorry, but I can't find him.
I see. Thanks anyway.
Let's go, Abi.
Abi!
Later, Robin.
Okay.
I was really shocked!
Thanks to Robin, we now know that
he isn't on the shipbuilding island.
The good news is that it saved us some time.
Say, Abi. Can I ask you a question?
What is it?
What is the final nesting village that
the townspeople were talking about?
It is said that when Yagaras realize
their lives are about to end,
they leave their groups or their owners
and go to a certain place to die.
That's the final nesting village.
I see...
--But...
--But?
...if humans see this final nesting village...
If they see it...?
...they'll also be taken to the netherworld!
Nooo!
It's just a superstition!
There's no need to worry!
Oh, hey, captain! Do you need
a sniper for your pirate group?
This humble, flattering plan isn't that good.
Is there something else...?
Whoa! I got a bite!
Oof! I'm not gonna let you escape!
I give up.
Aobire! Where are you?!
He isn't around here.
Let's go check the backstreets, shall we?
Okay.
I thought I was a goner.
Hey, Luffy!
I found someone who heard Aobire's voice!
Uh-huh, uh-huh...
So on the night of the Aqua Laguna,
you heard someone around here say,
"I'm coming to rescue you, so hang in there"?
He says it was definitely
Grandpa Aobire's voice.
--Abi!
--Yeah! Thank you, little guy!
It's incredible that you
understand the Yagara's language!
Oh, stop it! I'm not a "little guy," you jerk!
Now that we know that, let's thoroughly
search this area, shall we?!
Yeah!
Go!
Hey, you're gonna fall.
It tickles!
I'm looking all over for him, and yet, why...
How is it? Is it warm?
Whoa! Watch out! Not that direction, Aobire!
Dad, is it true that Aobire can't see?
Yeah, he's an old Yagara who
turned 100 a long time ago.
I was told that there's no chance
that his sight will come back.
Oh, no...
Aobire has been serving our
family very well for generations.
But we can no longer deny
the decline in his strength.
We should start preparing ourselves...
But... I don't know how
best to explain it to Abi.
No! Aobire's coming, too!
We can't take him to the evacuation facility.
We do this every year. You should know that.
No, no!
What?!
Our house is in the center of the city.
There's no way he'll be swallowed
by the Aqua Laguna, Abi.
Aobire...
Aobire!
I wonder if he really was
swallowed by the Aqua Laguna...
Or...
No fish would drown.
He asked you to help him, right?
Then you shouldn't give up!
He's right, Abi.
You can cry later.
I'm not crying!
Ah, I see.
All right, then! We know the
area we should be searching.
Let's check it one more time.
Hm?
What's this?
Ah!
This is Aobire's...!
Did it come from there?
That's an entrance to the
underground waterways!
This is the place!
--Hey! Aobire!
--Say something!
--Where are you?!
--Aobire!
--Hey!
What's wrong?
H-Hm?
The water is...
We can't go any farther on the Yagara like this.
There's no water ahead of here.
In any case, let's try moving ahead.
Yeah.
You stay here and wait for us, okay?
See you later.
What's this? There's a town
underneath the town.
What's going on?
My dad told me once that they built
new buildings above the old ones
and kept doing that.
I see...
Hm? What's that light?
H-Hey! Abi!
I'm sure he's there!
I'll see him soon!
I'll see Aobire!
What's this?!
I-I can't breathe!
Help...! Help!
Aobire!
I'm alive...
Luffy! Little guy! Are you guys okay?!
Good!
Wh-What's this place?
What's the matter, Abi?
Luffy... Aobire is here.
This is the same place that I saw in my dream!
Don't tell me... this is the final nesting village?!
That can't be right! The final
nesting village is a superstition!
Don't talk like Aobire is dead!
That's just a story created to
explain mysteries about the Yagaras!
What?
Good! So you were there!
Aobire! Come here! Let's go home together!
Chopper!
He says, "I'm sorry, Abi."
Why are you apologizing?!
I wanted to see you all this time!
We're not mad about
your sudden disappearance.
Forget that! Let's go home together!
What?
What's he saying?
Er... Yeah...
He says he can't do that.
Why?!
"Now I can feel at ease."
"Thanks for everything."
No! Don't go!
Aobire!
No! Aobire!
We were always together!
I'm coming with you to the final nesting village!
Let go of me!
Aobire!
What is this?!
--What's that?
--A Yagara's voice...?
His heartbeat is weak...
...but I think he'll be able to pull through.
Looks like the scarf kept him
warm and helped him survive!
Th-That's the scarf that I gave to Aobire...
"I'll rescue you now, so hang in there!"
So Aobire tried to save him...!
That's why he appeared in my dream...
Here!
That's okay. I couldn't keep my promise, so...
No...
Thank you, Luffy.
Thanks to you two,
I was able to see Aobire again.
I was very glad!
Also...
...I was able to grant his last wish...
I was able to save this baby Yagara, so...
I see.
Yep.
Then...
He'll need lots of food in
order to get strong, so...
Thank you.
Say, do you think that place
was the final nesting village?
Well, it doesn't really matter.
After all, the world is full of mysteries
that we know nothing about!
Okay, then, everyone!
We're gonna go shopping!
Listen. I have nothing to do
with you guys! Why do I...
Well then, carry the younger ones on your back.
Sure, I can carry two babies on my back...
Hey, that's not the point!
Are you listening to me?! Hey!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Mothers Are Strong!
Zoro's Hectic Household Chores!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!