Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
They freed the toys who had
been forced to labor as slaves
but Doflamingo trapped everybody
in the country in the Birdcage
and put prices on the heads
of Luffy and 11 others.
You have no time to wonder what to do.
People are falling and
towns are burning moment by moment.
Either you kill me...
...or kill the 12 criminals.
Now the game is on!
Our plan was to destroy the SMILE factory
and provoke a conflict between
Doflamingo and Kaido.
But if we kill Doflamingo now,
Kaido will direct all his anger over losing SMILEs,
...at us!
Then we'll have to fight face-to-face
with the angry Emperor!
That's not an issue now.
Take a good look at this country!
If I stop now, what's gonna happen to it?!
Issho-san, don't we need
to capture Doflamingo?
Restrain as many out-of-control people
as possible
and focus on Straw Hat and
Law's pirate alliance!
What?!
Send that message to all units!
Stop it.
He who shoots oft at last
shall not hit the mark.
The Navy admiral!
The gambling old man!
"With a Rumbling of the Ground!
The God of Destruction - Giant Pica Descends!"
I'm gonna go kick Doflamingo's ass!
Get out of my way!
You are quite brash. But...
...I'm not going to step aside.
You wanna fight?
What an unpleasant chore this is.
THE ROYAL PALACE
Doflamingo-sama!
Straw Hat Luffy and the
others are clashing with
Fujitora and Navy soldiers at this very moment!
Is that so? Let them fight.
The Navy and the pirates,
if you allow me to create havoc...
--The voice!
--His voice is...
I can take care all of them by myself!
PICA - A TOP EXECUTIVE
OF THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
His voice is so high!
How could a giant man like that
have such voice!
Oh no... I still can't get used to it
even though I've heard it so many times!
But if I burst out laughing, he'll kill me!
We're in no hurry.
You see, this game is like an
election to select the king.
I asked the nation of Dressrosa.
Who is more fit to be their king?
Is it the Riku Family or the Don Quixote Family?
People choose their king.
It's their legitimate right.
It's bothersome!
You idiot!
Do you want him to kill you?!
We should just get rid of all the pests!
Hold it! You have to hold it!
All we have to do is
repel the ones who are coming
and sit back and watch the
others kill each other.
Doffy! I...
Whoa! I-I'm sorry, Pica-sama!
Please forgive him!
He's new and he was sort
of taken by surprise...
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'm gonna bury you alive!
You'll be stuck in stones...
Wait, Pica-sama!
Armsmorphosis!
Gatling Girl!
If you handle it,
you'll destroy his body completely!
Then his family can't bury him.
Thank you, Baby 5!
You.
Y-Y-Yes, sir!
Do you have a family?
What? Yes, I do.
How about you?
Oh, yes, me too.
I lost my mother when I was eight
and killed my father when I was ten.
The members who are ranked
as executives and above are
my family who I've been
through thick and thin with.
They are all I've got!
I won't forgive anyone who laughs at my family!
Got it?
Y-Yes, sir!
The Five-star - Usopp is in the Colosseum!
That way! Go after him!
Kill him!
Leave me alone!
Usoland is a man of 500 million!
Everybody wants him!
That's our legendary hero!
It's not something to be proud of!
But I have to accept it.
Nobody can help chasing after a star...
like me.
So cool!
A round of applause!
--You guys...
--Stop fooling around and hurry up!
Robin-san, how can we get
to the King's Plateau?!
Because of the geographical
shift, the outer wall of
the Colosseum is connected to the plateau!
If we climb from there,
we can meet up with the others!
Found them!
They're increasing in number!
That's good!
I'm gonna take care of them all at once!
--Hack-san?!
--Leave them up to me!
Get out of our way!
You money-blinded idiots!
I can't believe you people
knuckle under to Doflamingo!
Four Thousand Brick Fist!
There they are!
--Rebecca, you go ahead!
--Robin-san!
They are ours!
Bartolomeo!
I'm thrilled to hear
Robin-senpai call my name!
I-I'm gonna hold the enemies back here
so please go ahead with Sniper King-senpai!
Thank you!
Robin-senpai thanked me!
I'm all fired up now!
I'm not gonna let anyone go after them!
Don't stand in my way!
You used the strange technique again!
Oh no... We have no role to play here.
Let's go back to
the Young Master-sama for now-in!
All right.
Oh? Where did Señor go?
You know how he is-in.
He must be looking for that pervert
to have some kind of a hard-boiled face-off-in!
A hard-boiled face-off?
Wait for me, Little People!
I'm gonna super destroy the SMILE factory
and save you all!
Now we're here but...
How do we climb up there?
Count on me.
Cien Fleurs!
Spider Net!
Awesome!
A round of applause!
Y-You guys did it again...
--Leo, you guys go first!
--Okay!
Bartolomeo-san! Hack-san!
We can climb up from here!
Let's go.
If I climb up there,
I can see Luffy-senpai and
Zoro-senpai, can't I?!
I'm so excited!
The key to Law's handcuffs
should be somewhere...
There it is!
Father-sama, Rebecca and
the others are down there!
What?!
There is the criminal!
Catch her!
Stop it!
You're...!
Tank!
Rebecca-sama!
I, Tank, will guard you with my life!
Oh! That's Captain Tank!
King Riku-sama!
I'm glad that he's okay!
Grandfather-sama!
Rebecca!
Wait for me, everybody!
I will take back the real Dressrosa!
A-Are you okay?
Thank you.
--Is this the junkyard?
--Yeah.
As its name suggests,
there's trash everywhere.
Hey, what's going on out there?!
I'm not sure either.
Anyway, do you people know
a samurai warrior named Kanjuro?
Kanjuro?
What the...
What the hell!
What's going on?!
What are they up to this time?!
I-It's happening again!
What in the world is happening?!
Th-This is...
--Is that...
--Finally, he shows up!
When that guy emerges, it's all over!
No one can fight back anymore!
What the hell is that?!
A giant man?
He's gigantic!
That is...
Pica!
Pica-sama!
In...
Now, those of you who rebel
against our family...
What?
I'm gonna fight you!
His voice! It's so high!
But it totally doesn't fit!
What a funny voice!
Straw Hat!
P-P-P-Please stop!
Hey, hey, stop laughing, Straw Hat!
Pica-sama is sensitive about
his high-pitched voice!
If he runs wild with that massive body...
You idiot! You made Pica-sama mad!
How can you guys not laugh at it?
We can't!
Because we don't wanna die yet!
Run!
It's not just a punch!
It's like a part of the town falling onto us!
No! Pica is pissed!
Let's head for the Palace as we run-in!
It's so thrilling!
I feel something terrible is happening!
Issho-san, please run!
A giant stone man is...
Luffy! You have to stop messing
with your enemies...
I won't let you get away!
See! You can't help laughing either!
You guys...
It's coming!
Run! It's gonna crush you up!
I am running!
Luffy!
Luffy!!
The super-giant Pica smashes up
Luffy and the others!
Facing this worst-ever enemy,
the warriors who once
fought against each other
to the death in the Colosseum
come together and join Luffy,
and the group of unique
characters who are looking to
take down Doflamingo, start
making a significant advance!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Gathering into a Powerful Front!
Luffy and a Group of Brutal Warriors!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!