Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesometreasure
at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be Kingof
the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse ofthe
tail end to the future
The horizons everyonedreamed
of were separate at first
but now they can be seenthrough
a single telescope
A bitter compass of destinyis
leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieveyour
dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse ofthe
tail end to the future
See ya, fortress guy!
H-Hey! It's me!
Hey!!
Imprison him!
You should thank Robin.
I see... She thought that it'd
besafer for me to be with you...
It might've been better if
I didn't check into it...
To think that there's
only one escape route...
"Daring Luffy and Sanji!Their
Great Rescue Operation!"
Among the Straw Hat Piratesthat
we already captured,
there was a man wearing a uniformwho
pretended to be a Navy officer.
Listen up! You can report it later!
When you see suspicious
individuals,imprison them immediately!
Yes, sir!
Did you hear?! That long-nosed guywas
a crew member of the Straw Hats!
Yeah. But why did he takethe
trouble to come here?
Yeah. In the bay, there're lots ofships
that are better than this one.
They could've taken oneof
them and quickly escaped.
That's how stupid pirates are!
You're right!
Oh? Are you already donefor
the day, Mechao-san?
Don't slave-drive an elderly man.
He says he's "elderly"!
As if!
You damn idiot! At least try to be careful!
S-Sorry.
Geez... This is such a complicated fortress!
I wonder where Zoro and Usopp are...
Well, since they got caught,they
were probably sent to jail.
Okay! Then we'll go to the jail!
Do you know where the jail is?
You don't know, Sanji?
How would I know?!
Hmmm...
I think that belly button
islandis suspicious after all.
What makes you think that?
Dunno, I just do.
But in any case, that sounds about right.
It's surrounded by the sea.
On top of that, the only way
toescape is to cross that bridge.
It's a pain, but I guess we should go there.
Alrighty!
Dammit! Going the way wecame
is also gonna be a pain.
Yes, sir! This is District
4 in Block F. All clear!
Keep searching!
Yes, sir!
They're in contact with each
otherusing Mini Transponder Snails.
This isn't gonna be easy.
Hey, Sanji.
Hm?!
This is kinda exciting, isn't it?
Get moving already, you damn monkey!
Ouch!
Where am...?
Freeze!
"Port Entry Records"
This is strange. There're times whenno
ships enter or leave. Why is that?
I'm being watched...
Hey, you! What do you think you're doing?!
Who do you think I am?!
You told us over and over on our way here.
You're Special InspectorMajor
Shepherd, right?
If you know that, get
meout of here right now!
I have business with Commander Jonathan!
Major Shepherd?
Oh, I see! This is the guyRobin
was pretending to be!
Enough of your nonsense! There's no way
So they've mistaken him
for one of us instead!
a Navy major from Headquarters wouldlet
his ID and his coat be stolen so easily!
If that's the case...
Stop it now. It's disgraceful!
Hm?!
A man should know when togive
up! Let's not struggle...
...my comrade, Condoriano...
C-Condoriano?! What's
that?!Who the hell are you?!
Hey, hey... Stop making bad jokes...
You expect us to believe you'veforgotten
my face or your own name?!
Hey! Don't come near me! I'm not your buddy!
I don't know him! I don't know this man!
Ow, ow... What happened to you?
Oh, no... Did the impact from the
fallcause you to lose your memory?!
How sad... It's too sad!
Hey! Please! Would you let at least him out?!
He's not the same Condoriano that I knew!
That settles it.
Yeah. There isn't even apoint
in interrogating him.
Wh-What do you mean, "that settles it"?
Wait! What're you going to do with me?!
Wait! Don't you get thatI'm
telling you to wait?!
Condoriano!
Who's Condoriano?
Shut up already!
Nice move, Zoro!
It went well! You should thank me, Robin!
You look creepy, Usopp.
Commander...
...there still haven't been any reportsof
the other Straw Hats being seen.
What should we do, Commander?!
They're probably having
ahard time finding the jail.
I guess we'll lead the way.
Huh?
You go ahead of them and wait.
Be sure not to act hastily.
Yes, sir!
Well, why don't we ensure ourvictory
by making the first move?
Ow...
What're you doing, Sanji?
Shh!
Dammit! I guess we have toforce
our way through after all.
Hey, it's unguarded down there!
Let's go, Luffy! We'll head down there!
Okay!
Hello!
Reporting, sir!
The one we captured earlier
turned out to be a Straw Hat
memberwhose name is Condoriano.
Condoriano?
Yes, sir!
He insists that he's Major Shepherd...
...but we think that it's clearly a lie.
Okay, thanks.
So there're two Shepherds, huh?
Well...
Hey, Zoro... Don't youthink
this is kinda strange?
Yeah. It gives me a bad feeling.
Hm? Oh?
You're... Mechao-san...
Wh... What're you doing
in a place like this?!
What am I...? I just hada
little matter to attend to.
Pull them back already!
Hmph! I see...
So, what's your business?
It's not with you! I need to talk
tothat long-nose held captive there.
Wha...?! Wait! I can't let
youtalk to a prisoner so freely!
It won't take long. Cut me some slack!
Hey!
Ah! You're the guy from...!
Don't tell me somethinghappened
to the Going Merry!
Don't worry. Your ship is okay... for now...
Good...
You're the one whorepaired
that ship, aren't you?
Hm? Oh, sort of...
The way you did it isn't acceptable.
Unless you use splices,even
if you nail the iron sheets,
it'll break in no time whenstrong
winds blow, you know.
Splices?
What? You don't even know what splices are?
Well, actually, I'm not a maintenanceman
or anything like that.
The one that did those repairs was...
Someone did them in just one night?
Yeah. That was when we werein
a place called a sky island
that was 10,000 meters up in the sky, though.
Hm? 10,000, you say?
Yeah, yeah... You probablydon't
believe it anyway, do you?
Come to think of it, that shipfell
from the sky, didn't it?
What? You believe me?!
Since I saw it with my own
eyes,I have to believe it.
Considering the angle at which it fell,
it probably fell from
aconsiderable height, so...
You're right! We had a reallyhard
time on the sky island!
There was God and there wereangels...
It was really tough!
God and angels?
You talk as if you died once.
Far from just once, there weretons
of times that I thought I'd die.
There were, huh?
By the way, about what you told me earlier...
Was it foggy the night that this
someonewho repaired the ship appeared?
Yeah! Exactly! How did you know that?!
Oh, do you, by any chance,know who that was?!
That could be, you know...
Uh-huh...
Wh-What're you doing?!
That's it, old man.
We're quite busy with various things.
Escort him out.
Yes, sir!
Hey, hey!
W-Wait! Hey! Tell me who that was!!
That's right. I forgot to
tellyou something important!
Listen, long-nose! When you repair the ship,
pay attention to the areasthat
you usually don't.
Those areas are often theones
most in need of repair!
If you treasure your ship, don't forget that!
You got that?!
Yeah! I got it, old man! Thanks!
Someone just came out!
Yeah. But that place really is fishy.
All right! Then shall we go?!
Hold on! This is a little strange.
We arrived here after
wetook the deserted route.
It's as if they're telling us whereZoro
and Usopp are... Which means...
I get it! The fortress guy is a nice guy!
It's a trap. A trap!
They're probably trying to savetime
and send us straight into jail.
Who cares?
Either way, we can't rescue Zoroand
Usopp unless we go inside, right?
Idiot! Why would we want to gettrapped
by our enemy so easil--?! Hm?
It's true that it'd be better than
wastingtime wandering around aimlessly.
I'm also worried aboutNami-san
and Robin-chan.
Sanji, are you thinking it over?
No, I'm not!
You did, didn't you?!
I said I didn't!
There's nothing in here!
Never mind that, get moving already!
Alrighty!
Hey, Zoro! Usopp! Where're you guys?!
Oh? Did you hear Luffy's voice just now?
Hey!!
It's really Luffy! Hey,
Luffy! We're right here!
Sure you wanna do that?Those
guys can hear too, you know.
Luffy, don't come!No, I
changed my mind! Come get us!
Hey, what should I say?
Beats me. Tell them to comeif
they want to or something.
Come if you want to!
I heard a voice!
It's this way!
Umph!
Oh, no... They came...
Be careful, Luffy!
They're here!
Hold on! I'll get you... out...
What the...?!
Oh, I see! This is the
Sea Prism Stone's doing!
We've been waiting for you!
Surrender obediently, Straw Hat!
Ha! You are making light of us, aren't you?!
You think that's enough to stop us?!
Is this still not enough?
It's all the same to me, idiots.
Now, what should I do?
For starters...!
What's he doing?!
Ha! It's painful to watch!
Those bars can't be broken unlessyou
use a cannon or something.
Dammit! These bars sure are tough!
Cannon...? Oh, yeah!
Sanji! Hey, hey, hey...
Take what's inside my pocket!
Your pocket?!
I have an Impact Dial in there.Use
it to break these bars!
Impact Dial... Hey, it causespain
to the user, you know!
This is no time to worry about
that!Now, take it already!
What're they talking about now?
Give up gracefully!
Well, wait a sec, gorilla man.
I'll show you something remarkable,so
keep your mouth shut.
A seashell?
It won't be my fault if
youget hurt standing there.
Oh, yeah, that's right...
Here we go!
"This well-tempered snake"?
That total moron!
What's that? Are you trying totell
us that's your secret weapon?!
Shut up! Or I'll gut you!
Yipes, he's scary! A backlash!
Ah! Um, Sanji-kun, sorry!It's
actually in the other pocket.
Here. It's this side. This side... This...
Flavor... It stinks!
Th-This is...!
I-It stinks!
Who the hell stored a fart in my Flavor Dial?
I... I'm... sorry...
I guess I didn't have to ask.
Watch out! It's gonna explode! Get down!
An explosion in the jail!
It's an emergency! Hurry up!
Hey, are you okay?!
Escape... successful?
Looks like it.
Ouch!!
Help...
Geez! What a pain in the ass!
Now, there's no point
staying here any longer.
Let's get out of here already!
Thank you!
Let's go, Luffy!
Alrighty! Guys, get out of here!!
Ahh! Hey, hey! Wait a sec!
Don't let Zoro go first! It
won'tbe my fault if we get lost!
Usopp, you jerk!
Is everyone okay?!
Y-Yes, somehow...
Okay, then! Those whocan move, come with me!
We'll go after the Straw Hats!
Those fools! Our men shouldbe
in place outside by now!
We'll attack them from both sides andsend
them to the netherworld this time!
Oh?
See?! We're lost!
Where are we?!
How can you get lost?! That's impossible!
Shut up!
Commander! I'm sorry!I
failed to catch Straw Hat!
What about the other members?Are
Roronoa and the others with him?!
Yes. Uh, well...
Witnesses told me that they didn'tsee
Condoriano with the others.
I see... Lt. Commander,the
bridge is guarded, right?
Y-Yes, sir!
Good! Well, don't be so discouraged.
We'll still have manyopportunities
to catch them.
Looks like those kids made their move.
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,on
the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give
in,even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared
of,we can overcome it
A trap?!
Which means something fun might happen!
Well, worrying about
annoying crap is annoying.
We'll see what kind of trap it is.
So you think you can escapefrom
Navarone? And from me?
We won't get caught! We're pirates!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Enter the Hot-Blooded Special
Forces!Battle on the Bridge!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!