Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
The look in Arlong's eyes changed!
You inferior human!
What did you do to me, a fishman?!
A Shark Saw!
That room is...
You can no longer escape.
This is the top floor of Arlong Park.
What's this room?
Full of papers...
These're not just ordinary papers.
This room is where I make that
woman draw sea charts. It's...
...the survey room!
Nami's room...
These're all sea charts that Nami drew.
She's good. She draws
quite accurate sea charts.
In the past, as well as in the future,
her talent should be
used for us fishmen!
Nami is our friend.
Friend?
So don't interfere anymore...
...you damn rubber man!
What's that look in your eyes?!
She is...
Nami is...
...our navigator!
"End of the Fishmen Empire!
Nami's My Friend!"
You plan to make her the
navigator of some shabby boat?
You'd only end up wasting her talent.
Just look! How many people in this
world can draw such accurate charts?
The girl has a gift.
There's nothing as
unfortunate and foolish
as letting a natural-born
talent go to waste.
Staying here and drawing sea charts
is the greatest happiness for her!
This pen is stained with blood...
Nami's charts are absolutely vital
if I'm to attain world supremacy!
She's going to continue drawing
sea charts! For my ambition!
And once her charts give me full
knowledge of all the world's seas...
we fishmen will be invincible,
and the world will become our empire!
Our first stepping stone is this
island... and the East Blue!
Could you use the girl
as efficiently as that?!
Huh?! The Shark Saw
won't move one bit!
What?!
"Use"?!
What's goin' on inside?!
Dammit...
What happened, Big Bro Luffy?!
I can't tell what's
going on up there at all...
Luffy...
What do you take her for?!
An inferior creature, but a smart girl.
If all other humans are sewer rats,
I'd say she's a cheeky-as-hell cat.
After all, she is adorable.
And I'm going to keep on feeding
her and buying clothes she likes.
She'll have everything
she needs to live.
All she needs to do
is keep drawing charts for me.
She will forever be my tool...
...no, my friend.
What's that?!
A desk...
It's a desk!
W-Whew, just a desk.
Man, that scared me. I thought
it was Big Bro Luffy for sure...
Hold on, partner!
Are you sayin' you don't have
faith in Big Bro Luffy's strength?!
Huh?! You were scared too, Johnny!
D-Don't be stupid!
I was, uhh, you know...
O-Of course I thought
it was that damn Arlong!
Huh?! That sounds
kinda fake if you ask me!
Say what, you jerk?! Of course
there's no way Big Bro Luffy'd lose!
Luffy?
What do you think you're doing?!
What in the...?!
There's an awful lot of stuff flying!
Alright! As of today, this is your room!
Your desk, your pens...
Everything you'll need is here!
Stop that!
The charts!
M-My charts!
You damn brat!
Don't think you can trick me,
drawin' fake charts like that!
Do you have the time to be
drawing crap like this in secret?
Try to fool me again and I'll drag
people from the village one by one
and make you watch as I crush them!
Just like I did with her!
Damn you! I spent eight
years making her draw those!
I invested eight years in
those charts! In my ambition!
Bellemere-san...
Nojiko...
This... is a pretty intense fight!
Yeah! Looks like a fight to the death!
Definitely!
Thank you...
You've gone too far,
you damn rubber man!
"Fishmen are great"
and "sea charts" this,
"circumstances" that...
I don't know much
about any of that stuff...
But I finally figured
out how to save her!
She can't go because this room is here!
If she doesn't want to be here,
then I'll just destroy it all!
Gum-Gum...
Don't get cocky!
Arlong Park can't ever be brought
down by you inferior beings!
Shark Tooth Drill!
...Battle-Axe!
L-Look! That shock's
caused Arlong Park to...!
Impossible! It's gonna collapse!
This is dangerous!
Everyone, get away!
Big Sis Nami! Hurry!
But Luffy's still inside!
Big Sis!
Luffy! Luffy's still...!
Luffy!
I finally figured out how to save her!
She can't go because this room is here!
If she doesn't want to be here...
...then I'll just destroy it all!
Luffy!
Luffy...
Oww!
What's all this damn noise?
Luffy...
Arlong Park... has collapsed!
Big Bro...
What on earth happened inside?
Which one won?!
Given all this debris...
Don't tell me it was--!
Luffy...
Luffy!
Big Bro!
Is he okay?!
Nami!
You're my friend!
Yeah!
H-He won?!
He won...
He won!
He won!!
Arlong Park has fallen!
We did it, older sister!
Gen-san!
This... This isn't a dream, is it?
I never thought this day would come...
Way to go, Luffy!
You get my praise, too!
Though I'd be praising you even more
if you would've been the
star performer instead of me!
Man, talk about being
on pins and needles...
Take care of things quicker
from now on, you damn jerk!
This is awesome!
Hold it right there, you!
He's...!
What a lucky day today is!
Well done. I watched the entire fight.
Fluke as it was, I never once
imagined the fishmen would lose
to a bunch of nameless pirates like you.
However, thanks to you,
all the money I was to give Arlong
and all the money and valuables
stored in Arlong Park are now mine!
Everyone drop your weapons!
I, Colonel Nezumi of Navy Branch #16,
hereby take credit for
what you've done here!
Zoro!
Don't ruin people's fun
when they're finally happy!
J-Just you try laying a
finger on me! You'll be sorry!
He's still sayin' it?
This is for shooting Nojiko
and tearing up Bellemere-san's
tangerine orchard.
Huh?
Colonel!
Thanks, Nami! That felt good!
Give 'im 1,000 more of those!
You guys are gonna clean
up after those fishmen now!
And you're gonna help
rebuild the town of Gosa!
And you're not gonna touch any
money or valuables in Arlong Park!
That's the island's money! Got it?!
Oww! Oww! I-I'll do what you say!
And one other thing!
Give me my money back!
I'll give it back! I'll give it back!
I don't care anymore...
I'll get you, you rotten pirates!
Straw hat man!
Your name's Luffy, right?!
You're the captain, right?!
Don't forget this!
Some major stuff's gonna happen
to you now! You've made me mad!
It's too late to regret
what you've done!
I'm gonna get revenge on you!
Just you wait and see!
Says some major stuff's
gonna happen now.
How does he know I'm
gonna be King of the Pirates?
That's not what he means!
Man, you're stupid!
H-Hey, what do we do?! What if we
really do wind up in big trouble?!
Hey! Hey! Hey, I said!
Alright, everyone! This is no time
for us to be the only ecstatic ones!
We need to tell everyone on the
island about this big incident!
Arlong Park...
Arlong Park has fallen!
Good for you, Nami!
To think we'd end up
being saved by pirates...
You never know what's
gonna happen next.
You seem to be in excellent
spirits, pathetic humans!
As of this moment,
this village-- no, this island--
is now under my control!
Gen-san! Help!
Keep your hands off the children!
T-That's an Arlong tattoo!
You...!
You can stop now...
You fought very well, carrying our
lives on your back all this time...
Gen-san...
And then it went boom!
We didn't know each other long!
Now, Bellemere's spirit
can finally go to heaven...
Hello?! Hello?!
Yes. This is Navy Headquarters.
Headquarters?! Navy Headquarters?!
Hello! This is Colonel Nezumi
of Navy Branch #16!
Marine Code 00733!
I have a request for HQ!
You don't need to shout.
I can hear you.
Listen! There's a pirate named Luffy,
who wears a straw hat!
I deem him and his four crew members
as enemies of the government!
"Luffy"...
They managed to take down Arlong,
the fishman of Arlong Park who
was purported to be invincible!
Based on their threat
and dangerousness,
a large bounty has been placed
on their captain, Straw Hat Luffy!
Now sending a photograph!
Roger that.
Huh?!
Couldn't you have taken
a better one than that?!
No, that's all I could get...
After a quick verification,
I will submit it for approval.
Don't forget, now!
He's a vile pirate! "Dead or Alive"!
Put him on wanted posters
throughout the world!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
It's finally goodbye
to Cocoyashi Village!
Nami! Bet you're happy to be onboard
with Great Captain Usopp again!
You idiot! Nami-san is joining
me on a journey of love!
No! Raw ham melon!
Bellemere-san. It took eight years,
but we're finally free!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Setting Out with a Smile!
Farewell, Hometown Cocoyashi Village"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!