Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
We're out! We're out!
Make chase at once!
O-One other thing, Lt. Commander!
While in pursuit of them,
Eric-sama also reappeared
and has just returned to ship!
Look at 'em come! Look at 'em come!
The Going Merry is faster and more agile,
but what are we going to do
when we get to Warship Island?!
--We'll be okay!
--How will we be okay?!
We just need to find
the dragons' nest first
so Grandpa Ryu can get better, right?!
Doesn't look like that's
going to be an option...
The small fries have leapt forth...
Open to the left and right!
Crane Wing Formation!
What now?! They have us blocked off!
Jump onto a ship, kick the guys off,
and cut the links!
That's the only choice, obviously!
Doesn't sound too bad to me!
Okay! Let's go!
Alright!
"Luffy, Completely Surrounded!
Commodore Nelson's Secret Strategy"
Marvelous! A truly marvelous view!
Listen, now! Do not let
the attacks falter even a bit!
Yes, sir!
But do not hit the raft!
Yes, Commodore!
For so many years I've sought
the Millennial Dragon...
And I've finally found it!
The elixir of immortality,
the Dragonite, is now as good as mine!
Sir! The commodore's flagship
says his plan has succeeded!
He says his attack is still ongoing!
Looks like our mission is over now.
If they fall into
Nelson Royal's hands now...
Hold on, Lt. Commander!
Do you still want something?
Prepare one paddleboat
and three proficient seamen.
A paddleboat?! What for?!
Because a mast would get in the way.
Don't tell me you're going
into the enclosed area?!
Just do it already.
Apis! It's dangerous! Go back inside!
I can't leave Grandpa Ryu all by himself!
Hey, you! Wait!
That's dangerous! Get back here!
It's your fault if you fall!
Grandpa Ryu!
Just hang in there a little longer!
I promise I'll take you
to the dragons' nest!
Man, she's brave!
Dammit! That moves me to tears!
Alright!
I'll break through the front lines
and take you to the dragons' nest!
Oww!
Hey! We've been hit from behind!
Hey! Sanji! We've been hit! Sanji!
We're done for! We're sunk!
Pipe down! We ain't been hit.
Eh? Seriously?
Yeah.
I'm saved!
Who the hell thought
of this plan anyway?!
It was you.
That's it! That's it! Go!
Hey! A ball's coming this way!
I can't do any more than this!
Do something on your end!
Okay! I'll do something!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
No way...!
No way!
You impudent bastards!
How dare you damage one of my warships?!
What are you doing?!
Hit them with the Super Giant Cannon!
Yes, sir!
There's no escape!
There's no escape for you!
Prepare to fire the Super Giant Cannon!
The pirate ship has
been trapped up ahead!
Ready to fire!
What is that?!
A direct hit from that and our
ship'll be blown to shreds!
We'll be okay!
I'll just bounce it back again!
Don't be stupid!
I'll turn the ship about;
you guys work the rear sail! Hurry!
Yeah!
An eye for an eye!
I got a shot ready for you, too!
Here we go!
Eat this!
Fire!
What just happened?!
An enemy cannonball hit
our main cannon perfectly!
W-What?!
Hurry and lift me up!
Yes, sir!
Howdya like that?!
This is what happens when
Usopp-sama gets serious!
Not too shabby, for a fluke.
You're so full of it.
--What?! I can do that anytime!
--Wow... He hit it!
You're cool, Usopp!
Yeah!
It'll be okay! Don't worry!
You just keep Apis safe!
Who're you talking to?!
Grandpa Ryu.
Huh?
Now's our chance!
Let's act quickly and
cut some links to open a path!
Right, Nami-san!
Luffy.
Leave it to me!
Gum-Gum...
...Bridge!
Alright!
Grandpa Ryu!
Just hold on!
Here goes!
Sorry, Zoro.
Why, you...!
Report! What are they doing?!
Yes, sir!
Three people from the pirate ship
have boarded portside Ship #1!
Huh?! Say what?!
Steel chains, huh?
Think you can cut 'em?
There's nothing I can't cut!
Really? Then they're all yours.
Talk about coming out of the woodwork...
I like it when things are lively!
Sure, whatever.
I leave the small fries to you.
Yeah!
In the name of the Nelson Fleet,
we won't let you break through here!
Yeah! That's it! That's it!
You're so wonderful!
Keep it up!
Chop those things up good!
Curse you! How dare you
lousy pirates try to break my links?!
Capture them, at all costs!
Or else I'll maroon
every last one of you!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Here they come! Here they come!
Gum-Gum...
...Slingshot!
Hiyaaaaaah!
Wow...
I didn't know they were like this...
There's only one chain left!
Let's get moving!
Aye-aye, sir!
No, no! Someone stop them!
Oh! Eric!
Well done! Now the
Millennial Dragon is mine!
That scared me--!
You're the Sicko Sicko Fruit guy!
Not "Sicko." The Sickle-Sickle Fruit!
Girl! It's time to hand
over the Millennial Dragon!
No! I'll never give you Grandpa Ryu!
Hand it over like a good little girl!
No!
I can chop you into pieces with
wind slashes at any time, you know.
Stop right there!
Lay a hand on the kid and you'll pay!
Y-Yeah! I, Usopp-sama,
won't sit by quietly either!
Fools.
I made that wind slash
just now miss on purpose...
Get in my way,
and this time I won't miss!
I'll blow your entire ship apart!
What's wrong?
It's him.
Huh? What's he doing?
--Tie the raft to our boat!
--Looks like he's planning to take
Apis hostage and steal the dragon.
--Yes, sir!
--Looks like he's planning to take
Apis hostage and steal the dragon.
That's bad!
Stop! If you lay a hand on him,
he'll take out Apis and Nami
and the others with his technique!
Oh! Right!
Then I'll use my foot!
--Huh?!
--Listen better!
I'm taking the Millennial
Dragon now! Nothing personal!
You fight dirty! Give Apis back!
Eric! Well done! Now, bring it here!
No thanks. This isn't for you.
Eh?! What did you say?!
The only reason I obeyed you
was to use the Navy's
information-gathering capabilities.
What?!
It's not like you were any different.
You tried to use me, too.
I hired you for a great sum of money!
I think I've worked off
that chump change by now.
I have no obligation to obey
a sea lion like you anymore!
S-Sea lion?
You're calling me a sea lion?!
I'm going to use the Dragonite
I get from the Millennial Dragon
to make myself perfect!
You'll pay! You'll pay for this!
Shoot that backstabber!
Shoot him! Shoot him!
They're starting again!
If you don't want to
get blasted into pieces,
you'd better start rowing!
Stop...
Stop!
I'm begging you! Please don't
harass Grandpa Ryu any more!
He hasn't done anything wrong!
Be quiet.
I have to take him to
the dragons' nest right away!
So please stop this!
What're you doing?!
Let go! Let go, I said!
Listen, girl. You're a hostage.
And I'm taking the Millennial Dragon.
I'll never let you have
Grandpa Ryu! Never! Never!
I've had enough, girl!
Any more shouting
and I'll chop you apart!
Oww!
Let go!
Damn kid, giving me trouble...
Hey! What are you running for?!
Get back here!!
Dammit!
Grandpa Ryu!
You want some of this? It's yummy!
Hey, Grandpa Ryu!
Eat lots and get better soon, okay?!
That's so cute!
It really suits you, Grandpa Ryu!
I can't stand this!
Oww! My ears!
Grandpa Ryu let out a sound...!
Oww...
Grandpa Ryu!
You can move! That's great!
That's great!
What?
Really?!
What the...?!
You don't suppose he's...
Yeah! You can do it,
Grandpa Ryu! You can fly!
You're flying!
You're flying, Grandpa Ryu!
No! If the Millennial Dragon
is just going to escape,
then I don't care if we kill it!
All I need is its Dragonite, anyway!
Fire! Fire! Fire like mad!
Stop!
Grandpa Ryu! Run!
Run to where the
cannons can't reach you!
That's it! Shoot him down, quickly!
Stop that!
Now's your chance to run, Grandpa Ryu!
What are you doing?!
Attack it with this ship, too!
Yes, sir!
It must be shot down!
Grandpa Ryu!
No! Don't go that way!
What?! It's coming this way!
Shoot it down, quickly!
It's coming!
Shoot it, quickly! Shoot it!
Grandpa Ryu!
Grandpa Ryu! Hang in there!
Hey, now! What are you saying?!
Don't talk about dying!
Yeah. I know. I will save Apis!
And take you to the dragons' nest!
So try hard to stay alive!
Grandpa Ryu!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Hang in there, Grandpa Ryu!
What happened to going to
Lost Island?! Try hard to stay alive!
Damn those Navy guys!
This isn't good.
Luffy can't swim, right?
Hold on! What is this?!
The whole sea is shaking!
What in the world's happening?!
H-H-Hey, now! What's that?!
It's coming this way!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Through the Sky They Soar!
The 1,000-Year Legend Lives Again!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!