Edited at https://subtitletools.com
"Tower of Law"
In the Tower of Law,
Robin realized that Luffy and
the others had come to rescue her.
Wait! That's not what we agreed upon!
In return for my cooperation, you were
supposed to let them escape safely!
They came here after leaving
Water Seven safely, right?
They're hopeless scum. They don't
have a shred of morality in them.
Huh? What'd you say?
Shut up, you trash!
To start with, we don't even have to
keep our promises with you criminals!
Take this! Take this! You bastard!
You too!
Don't get so cocky, you bitch!
You dirty coward...
The receiver is off.
We'll take Cutty Flam to Impel Down
and Nico Robin to Navy Headquarters.
As soon as the escort ship is ready,
we'll go through the
Gates of Justice and sail off.
You guys go back to your rooms
and take it easy for the time being.
What dependable guys my subordinates are.
As long as I have them, I feel like I can't lose!
Meanwhile, urging the King Bull
on in pursuit of Luffy,
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
the Straw Hats were moving
forward without a hitch, however...
Don't get on without permission!
Things are going smoothly! Good thing
we've got you guys on our side!
We're counting on you to
get us to Luffy, King Bulls!
He's asking, "By the way, was it
okay that the guy with the mask
didn't get on with you guys?"
--What?!
--Hm?
--What?
--Hm...?
What?! I-I can't find Sogeking anywhere!
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
L-Lieutenant Commander!
There's trouble!
What's the matter?!
Straw Hat Luffy...!
We lost Straw Hat Luffy!
Find him! Find Straw Hat at any cost!
As for Luffy, he finally reached
the rooftop of the courthouse.
That must be the last building.
All right.
What the heck?
Air Door.
Ah! You're that bull guy
who was with the pigeon guy!
I did think that there was no way
there'd be only five casualties.
Boy, that was a big surprise!
Since the start of the World
Government, it's unprecedented...
...for a man to step this far
into the Government's entrance.
How long are you planning to keep fighting?
Until I die.
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Give Robin Back! Luffy vs. Blueno!"
Ahhh! Wh-Wh-What're we gonna do?!
In any case, we don't have the option
of going back to get him at this point.
I'm sure he'll work things out on his own.
But there are guards everywhere on this island.
He isn't Luffy. If he's by
himself, his life will be...
After surmounting each island,
we got stronger without knowing.
He, too, always survived
life-or-death situations on each island.
No one in our group would die so easily.
"Always"? "In our group"?!
What're you talking about, Zoro?!
Sogeking came here to help us rescue
Robin because Usopp asked him to!
He is an invincible hero, right?
That's right!
Sogeking is a super hero
for justice. He'll definitely...
"Main Island Front Gate"
I failed to get on the King Bull...
What am I gonna do? I'm way behind now.
Battleship Cannon!
At any rate, those shipwrights are amazing!
In any case, I left the group. Shall I just run?
N-N-No! Running is the last thing I'll do!
I'm Usopp! I'm a man! I went so far
as to hide my identity to follow them!
We're facing a crisis where Robin is
sacrificing herself to protect all of us!
I have to do it at all costs!
All right... There's only
one way to get to everyone.
I'll carry out "Operation Disguise Myself
as One of the Government Personnel
and Pass by Them Unnoticed"!
Yeah, that'd be good.
Huh?!
Whoa! What?! What?!
Are they trying to drown me?!
Enemy attack! Enemy attack!
How regrettable!
Ahhh! The giant woke up!
We screwed up in our 50th year!
I'm sorry, bosses!
Bosses?
We are a disgrace to Elbaf!
E-Elbaf?
Elbaf... Bosses...
Don't tell me...! I-Is it possible that
you're from Elbaf, that warriors' village?!
Who are you?!
I-I-I am Sogeking from the island of snipers.
Could you explain to me what
you're talking about in detail?
You're a total stranger from God knows where!
Why do I have to tell you?!
Calm down! Warriors from Elbaf
are the proudest men in the world!
And yet, you're crying a river here.
It must be a big deal.
So I want to know why.
Please...
There's no use in telling you about it, but...
Me and Kashii were pirates
up until 100 years ago
and we ran amok all over the world.
--What?
--But one day on some island...
Cheers!
Each one of 'em bagged an
insanely huge Sea King, after all!
Even though we're Elbaf giants,
nobody can take down those jumbo-sized
beasts except for our bosses!
Right, men?!
Those ones were definitely the biggest ones...
Yeah! The biggest ones we've ever caught!
So which one was bigger?
--Which...
--...one?
Mine is slightly bigger!
You wish! Mine's a whole
three centimeters bigger!
Say what?!
What's your problem?!
Bosses!
Please stop!
The two bosses started a duel.
It's a battle in which they put their
pride on the line. It can't be helped.
That's the signal for the duel.
The group was split up
and everyone ended up
going back to their hometown.
The central mountain... That's Little Garden...!
It was a life-or-death battle between warriors.
At the very least, the winner was
supposed to come back to the village,
but even after several decades,
neither of them came back.
After 50 years passed, me and Kashii
thought something was wrong,
so we set out to sea to go get those two.
But on our way, we got caught by the Navy
and they made us tell them everything.
Then, in return, we were told a shocking story.
They said that our bosses,
who were very strong,
were confined in the government's large prison!
--Huh?!
--That was about 50 years ago.
Hm?
The Government presented conditions.
If me and Kashii worked for
the Government for 100 years--
in other words, if we could protect this
gate in Enies Lobby for 100 years--
they'd release our bosses
and let us all go home to Elbaf.
Since a giant's life span is 300 years,
we thought 100 years was nothing.
So we accepted the conditions and
have kept fighting for the past 50 years.
But the gate was broken open today by pirates!
To think something like this happened...!
Dammit! Our bosses will now be
imprisoned for the rest of their lives!
Hey, hey! H-H-Hold on a sec!
There's something funny about that story.
There's nothing funny about it!
If you're gonna laugh at our pride, then...
No, no, I didn't mean it that way!
I meant that it's weird!
Weird, you said?!
Because during our journey before
we came here, we met those two!
The two you're talking about,
the Elbaf warriors Dorry and Broggy,
have been fighting an evenly matched duel
on that island for the past 100 years!
What?! How come you know their names?!
What?! That can't be right!
If you wanna hear more proof,
I'll tell you as much as you want!
And...
You still don't believe me?! What do I
have to tell you to get you to believe me?!
About their weapons?!
Their techniques?!
73,466 duels...
I know everything!
73,466 draws...
We really met them!
You fought desperately to protect our pride.
As such, no matter what
manner of enemy there may be...
...we will not let them
destroy your pride, friends!
Have faith in us, and continue straight ahead!
Let's meet again someday.
Without fail.
Straight ahead! Straight ahead!
We've already been eaten!
Hakoku Sovereignty!
We're flying out of it!
They cut... the very sea itself...
This is the strength of Elbaf warriors!
Now go!
I swore to myself to look
up to them as my masters
and become a man of great
pride like them some day!
And yet, you don't believe me?!
It's a big fat lie that they
got caught 50 years ago!
Our bosses are alive...
Yep, yep...
I see... I'm relieved... I'm so relieved.
"Main Island Front Gate"
"Courthouse"
Look! We're almost to the courthouse!
Bring them down without fail!
Crap! King Bull!
All right! We brought down one of them!
Sodom!
This is bad! I have to treat him right away!
Sodom! Stand firm! Don't fall yet!
Guys! Move over right away! Hurry it up!
Sodom can't go on much longer!
His pectoral muscle got hurt by a trench mortar!
Move over now before he falls!
No one's gonna be saved
unless you guys move forward!
He said, "Go!"
It's coming down!
No one's riding it!
What?!
Hey...
Let's go, Gomorrah!
So Robin is in that building behind you, huh?
Get out of my way, bull guy!
It seems that you guys haven't noticed...
...that what you're doing is a world-class crime.
Hm?
Just get to the point already.
The World Government is a
huge, powerful organization
that counts more than 170 countries
around the world as its members.
Invading this island,
which is under its possession,
is an act of revolt against all those countries!
Upon their dignity, the Government
will expose all of you to public ridicule
and bestow a merciless death upon you.
You guys are only a few dozen people.
That is nowhere near enough.
All I did was tell you to get out of my way.
My point is that you who entered the gates
of Enies Lobby already have no future,
whether I move out of
your way or not. That's all.
Fighting is a waste.
I thought you got a good taste of our
Six Powers at Galley-La's mansion...
...as well as the difference in
our levels of fighting ability.
Yeah, that's true...
But for some reason, I don't feel
like I'm gonna lose at all now!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body.
...Rifle!
What?! I don't remember him
being as powerful as he is now
when I fought him at the mansion!
Gatling!
Shave!
The world this, the Government that...
It's not my problem.
We just came here to get Robin back!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Gomorrah!
This is bad. Enemies are gathering
from the front and the back.
This is terrible! There're thousands of enemies!
If we get surrounded in a place
like this, we can't move forward!
--What?!
--What's the matter, Chopper?!
Gomorrah... Gomorrah's saying something!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Don't Stop! Hoist the Counterattack Signal!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!