Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
who's been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, at the Colosseum,
the final round of the competition is about to start.
I know your background.
My background?
It's gonna get a little messy, maybe,
but I won't do you wrong.
Launcher!
Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats!
The Navy is putting the Toy House
under complete siege!
Huh?! Why is the Navy doing that?!
What?
Somebody, tell me what's going on-in!
I'm just a newcomer
picked through the World Military Draft
but since being appointed as a Navy admiral,
there is something I want to do.
What is it?
It is nothing less than...
...the complete abolition of
the Seven Warlord system!
We'll raise the prize on you, Heavenly Demon.
It sounded like you were suggesting
that I'd better kill you now.
--Alright!
--What?
Okay, see you guys!
--Hurry up, Luffy!
--Get in now, Ninja Woman!
What?!
It's him!
The man who has risen to
prominence in this competition!
Here comes our favorite - Lucy!
Watch over me, Ace!
"The Final Round Starts!
Diamante the Hero Shows Up!"
This is the first time Lucy has
entered into these competitions! But...
...his likable character
captured the crowd's heart!
Oh? The next contender coming in
is the man who antagonized the crowds!
The captain of a pirate group, Barto Club,
Bartolomeo the Cannibal!
Here he comes!
The captain of the first ship of
Emperor Blackbeard's group -
Jesus Burgess!
The Flare-Flare Fruit will be ours!
But good luck to you, Straw Hat!
Oh! Now coming in to the sound of
the crowd's boos and jeers is...
...the "Phantom Princess" of
the heinous King Riku Family!
Rebecca!
Rebecca is... What should we say?
The devil incarnate, maybe?
How did she survive the Block D battle
against such tough contenders?!
It's still a mystery!
G-Gyats-san, are you alright?!
You're getting too excited!
I need some water...
I thought I was gonna die!
And now, these four competitors who
won each block by beating so
many strong contenders are...
...going to fight another battle in the
final round to be a champion
of the Corrida Colosseum!
It's going to start soon!
Who is that? He's not the Lucy that I knew.
Now, let me introduce the man
who is going to fight these four!
He saved this country along with our king,
Don Quixote Doflamingo,
and is one of the top
executives of the Family!
He is also the promoter of
the Corrida Colosseum Battle Tournament,
and our hero!
There he is!
Mr. Diamante!
N-Now, they're all there!
It's the final here in the Corrida Colosseum!
DIAMANTE - A TOP EXECUTIVE
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
The four winners from the first round
and Mr. Diamante!
The winner of this round will get...
...a Logia Devil Fruit,
the most powerful type!
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
It's mine!
Don't start!
Take Rebecca out of the ring!
Redo the Block D match!
Whoa! We have some kind of problem!
We won't accept
such a confusing result, Rebecca!
We couldn't have been beaten
by a little tramp like you!
We're gonna to get it right!
Yeah! Kick her ass!
Hey! Get out of our way!
Don't be such a poor losers! It's over!
Don't ruin my event!
What the hell?!
Now, charge into this!
--Is this a bullfight?!
--Screw you!
Lock.
Although it ripples, it's a steel cape.
I ate the Ripple-Ripple Fruit
and became a flag human!
I can make any material
flap in the wind like a flag,
even my body, just by my touch!
Lock.
Corrida Glaive!
You'd better go back, guys!
We have special kind of Fighting Fish in the water
just for the final.
They love the smell of blood.
It's flying...
Did you guys see that?!
How the Fighting Fish attacked?!
They're so evil! They're
not gonna follow the rules!
They'll attack fighters
while they're still in ring!
They're so savage!
They're not like
the Fighting Fish we had in the first round!
They're the deadliest Fighting Fish
from different schools!
And one of them has...
...the prize of this competition, the Flare-Flare Fruit,
on its back!
The rules of the final round are simple!
The one who gets it
and remains standing in the ring
will be the champion!
All right! The final round starts soon!
It's going to be a battle royal of the five
including Diamante the hero!
A scramble for the Devil Fruit!
A death match involving the Fighting Fish!
Which one of them will win
the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
Okay! Here we go!
The battle is on!
Now, the final battle finally begins!
Ready or not, this is it!
Who is going to win the prize -
the Flare-Flare Fruit?!
None of them are making a move yet!
Who is gonna take action first?!
Oh! Burgess is going at it!
Oh?! Lucy has started running
on the outer circle of the ring!
What is he up to?!
Here it comes.
This is not the one.
Tsk! We don't need the
ones that don't have it!
Don't even show your face!
Are you trying to lure the one
with the prize out, Straw Hat?!
This one doesn't have it, either.
The final is fun!
Of course, it is!
This is the Corrida Colosseum!
I'm running this show!
Every little tool here is
for entertaining the audience!
You mean we're "tools," too?
Well, just enjoy.
It seems like nobody's here.
Alright, we made it!
Wait!
Could you close the door?
IN FRONT OF THE RAMPART TOWER
BENEATH THE "ROYAL PALACE"
Is that the entrance to the palace?
No, it's the entrance of the Rampart Tower
which stands under the palace.
Under?
Yes. To reach to the palace,
we still have to climb up.
The Rampart Tower also has a secret entrance.
Let's go.
Don't let the guards see you.
If we make a scene, they'll call the
executives and then we'll be stuck.
Particularly, if the executive
named "Pica" finds us,
all hopes of facing Doflamingo will be lost.
Where's Luffy-dono?
Hey! Look!
Gum-Gum...
What the hell is that carp doing?!
...Giant...
--What's wrong with this carp?!
--Is it a blowfish?!
...Pistol!
What?!
What the hell is he doing?!
--It's open!
--That's not the issue here!
I can't believe it!
Are you a bubblehead?!
We have no choice! Let's go in!
Since it comes to this, it's faster this way!
Can I take this thing off?!
Do as you like!
Whoa-whoa!
That's...
This is the front entrance
of the Rampart Tower!
Straw Hat Luffy has snuck into the tower!
The Fighting Fish attacks!
But Lucy dodges easily!
Only he can move like that!
What is he talking about?
Was it really him?!
Yes, it was!
He has broken the gate and...
But it can't be him!
Straw Hat is fighting at the Colosseum
under the name Lucy!
This is the Rampart Tower B-2 -
in front of the main dining hall!
It's no mistake!
One of the intruders is Straw Hat Luffy!
And Pirate Hunter Zoro!
And... V-Violet-sama!
Th-There is one more person!
Lucy is showing it off!
Straw Hat Luffy has snuck in?
Then, who is the guy
fighting at the Colosseum?!
What the hell is going on?!
Where are you, Mingo?!