Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
I can't fall in a place like this.
I've got an important mission...
How pitiful...
...losing against just one swordsman...
Mr. 5! Miss Valentine!
Why are you here?!
You really have no idea?
There're criminals here that
are big enough for the boss
to send us here to deal with.
These're the boss' words:
"They've found out my secrets."
Of course, I don't even know what
kind of secrets they are, but...
So, when we very carefully
investigated who learned his secrets...
Oh boy, we found out that a VIP
from a certain kingdom
sneaked into Baroque Works.
They know! It's all over!
Die! Igarappappa!
I won't let you lay
a finger on our princess!
On my name as Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security!
Igaram!
Igaram, Squad Captain
of Alabasta Kingdom Security!
And Princess Nefertari Vivi!
In the name of the Baroque Works'
boss, we'll eliminate you two.
"All-Out Battle! Luffy vs. Zoro,
Mysterious Grand Duel!"
Damn...
And I left Luffy down there, too.
Quickly, Vivi-sama! Please escape!
Igaram!
It's no use!
You monsters!
You're a princess, Miss Wednesday?!
Quit being dumb, Mr. 9!
This is one screwed-up night!
You guys can do whatever you want!
V-Vivi-sama...
Igaram! Are you all right?!
Vivi-sama! Never mind me!
Just please... escape from here!
For our motherland...
Without you, our kingdom
of Alabasta will be...
Please! Hurry!
You think you can escape from us?
Don't mess with me!
I'm having a hard time
swallowing what's going on here,
but we've been a pair for a long time.
I'll buy you some time!
Get going, Miss Wednesday!
Mr. 9!
Pretty manly, wouldn't you say?
Bye-bye, baby!
Hot-blooded Bat...
Mr. 9!
All we need is the will to
accomplish our missions.
A pathetic sense of camaraderie
will only bring about death.
Time to learn that the
hard way! Nose Fancy...
...of Guts!
...Cannon!
Mr. 9!
Whoa, now! That's some
dangerous snot he's got!
What the hell?!
Sir Swordsman!
Upon seeing your skill, I have a request,
unreasonable as it may be!
Yeah, right! Screw that! Let go of me!
As both of those people possess
Devil Fruit powers, I can't stop them!
Might I ask you to protect
the princess in my place?!
Please!
Huh?!
Karoo! Run!
There she goes.
She can't get away from us.
Let's get her, Miss Valentine!
Right, Mr. 5!
If you can safely deliver the princess
to the great kingdom of
Alabasta far east of here...
...I promise that you
will be rewarded immensely!
I humbly beg of you!
Please, keep the princess safe!
Screw that! You were trying to
kill us until just a minute ago!
Don't make me cut you some more!
Is this "immense reward" for real?
I'll take up that offer!
How does one billion Berries sound?
Nami!
O-One billion Be--?!
Ma-ma-ma...
I thought you were asleep?
Come on, now.
Who in their right mind
would sleep carelessly
in an overly suspicious town
that welcomes pirates?
It was all an act! A-C-T, act!
I could keep on going if I wanted!
That so?
Ma-ma-ma...
So, will you promise us the
one billion, Squad Captain?
If you don't ask for our help,
your princess probably will die...
A mere soldier like me can't
promise such large sums of money...
You're not suggesting a princess
is worth less than that, are you?
Pay it.
Now she's threatening him!
In that case, if you're willing to
safely deliver the princess there,
it would be best if you negotiate
the terms with her directly!
Meaning I gotta start by saving her, huh?
Even as we speak, her life is in danger!
Alright, then.
I'll save your princess for now.
Okay! Go get her, Zoro!
Yeah, right, you idiot!
Why do I have to go along
with your money-making schemes?!
Geez, you're so stupid!
My money is mine, but my
contracts belong to all of you!
That's the kind of logic a bully would use!
What's the big deal?! All you
gotta do is cut those guys down!
I don't like bein' used,
unlike that idiot cook!
You're just afraid you can't beat them!
What?! Just try saying that some more!
Bathroom.
Quit repeating that crap!
Hey, now. Have you forgotten?
You owe me money.
Huh?! I don't owe you nothin'.
I lent you 100,000 Berries
for some swords in Loguetown.
I gave you the 100,000 right back!
Someone gave me some swords,
so I didn't use the money!
But you did agree to pay me back 300%--
300,000 Berries total.
There's something I wanna buy.
Sure, I can lend you money!
If you pay me back 300%!
You haven't paid back the
other 200,000 Berries yet.
I gave you the 100,000 Berries
back the same day! Gimme a break!
Nope!
Can't you keep even a single promise?
Do what I say,
and maybe I'll call us even!
D-Dammit! You're not gonna
die a good death, you know!
Yeah. I'm going to Hell.
Damn woman!
Thanks a bunch!
I'm so ashamed...
If only I'd been stronger,
I could have protected the princess!
Don't worry about it!
He's insanely strong!
If anything should happen to
the princess-- to Vivi-sama...
...the kingdom of Alabasta
would be finished...
She must live!
Run! Run, Karoo!
There's a ship docked
behind the cactus rocks!
We're going to use it
to escape from this island!
And then we'll go to Alabasta!
Much better! Now for more sleep!
What in the world?!
Hurry, Karoo!
Karoo! Stop!
Mr. 5...
They've found us! Karoo!
This way! Hurry!
Such pointless struggling.
Miss Monday!
Go on. You can get to
the ships through here.
I'll hold them off here!
But...
Thanks to that
freakishly strong swordsman,
we're all going to get punished
for failing our mission anyway.
Plus I'd much rather get my
butt kicked shielding a friend.
C'mon, what're you standing around for?!
If you get killed, Mr. 8 and Mr. 9's
sacrifices will be for nothing!
Get going!
Thank you.
First Mr. 9, and now you...
...Miss Monday?
I won't let you pass.
I bet my pride on it!
You're so funny!
You're a disgrace...
...to Baroque Works!
Miss Monday...
I'm a "bomb man"-- I can
make my entire body explode.
Thanks to this Bomb-Bomb Fruit power,
there is no mission I haven't completed!
Using my Kilo-Kilo Fruit power,
I'll bury that backstabbing
Miss Monday into the ground!
I'm able to change
my body weight at will!
Right now I'm light enough
to be lifted by the wind!
But now it's time to get heavy!
2 kilograms... 3 kilograms...
5 kilograms... 10 kilograms... 100 kilograms...
1000 kilograms!
10,000 Kilogram Press!
Well? Do you still think
you could survive that?
There is no possible escape from us.
I will survive... I will return...
I will return to Alabasta alive!
Take this! Nose Fancy...
...Cannon!
Mr. Bushido!
T-The street!
Who's he?
I cut his booger!
Damn you! You never give up!
Now, of all times!
Don't get hasty. I'm here to rescue you.
Eh? Me?
Say...
What is Baroque Works, anyway?
A secret crime syndicate.
None of its members knows
their boss' face or name.
Its main work is espionage, assassination,
larceny, and bounty-hunting.
It's all done at their boss' command.
Why would they listen to their boss,
whose identity they don't know?
Baroque Works' ultimate objective
is the founding of an ideal nation!
Everyone who does well
within the company now
will be guaranteed a high social
standing within the ideal nation
that the boss will be
creating before long.
I see...
The boss's codename is Mr. 0.
In other words, the closer a
person's codename is to zero,
the higher that person's
future standing will be...
...and more than anything,
the stronger they are!
The strength of those from Mr. 5
and above is especially incredible.
So you're the swordsman who cut down
all of the lowly employees in this town.
Why would you want to protect
the princess of Alabasta?
I got some circumstances
of my own, you see...
Well, no matter. You're our enemy,
one way or the other.
You're in our way.
Yeah! He is!
There you are!
Zoro!
Now what?!
Luffy! Thanks, but I don't need any help!
Or does that wench got you in debt, too?
I'm gonna make you pay
for what you did! Let's fight!
Huh?!
What nonsense are you
spewing this time?!
Shut up! I'm gonna kick your ass
for being such an ingrate!
Ingrate?!
That's right!
Hey! What happened?!
Who did this to you?!
Your green-haired swordsman friend...
What?!
Everyone in town welcomed us
and gave us lots of yummy food!
But you cut down every last one of them!
Well, yeah, but...
You will pay for this!
W-What a dull-headed person!
Internal strife, huh? Talk about lame.
Let's just get rid of everyone
who interferes with our mission!
Hold on, Luffy.
Listen to me.
They were actually bounty-hunt--
Don't make excuses!
What?!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Yeah! Die!
Dammit! Listen to me!
Hey!
That idiot!
He's serious!
Mr. 5.
It doesn't seem like
they're here to stop us.
It would seem not.
Then let's accomplish our mission quickly.
Our mission to eliminate Princess
Vivi of the Kingdom of Alabasta.
Why, you! Quit running away!
H-Hold on, Luffy! Hear me out!
Let's do it, Miss Valentine!
Yes, Mr. 5!
Quit screwing around, dammit!
That dumbass!
Now you guys've really gotten in our way!
Ugh! What the heck's going on?!
If you two wanna kill
each other that badly,
then we'll kill you both
ourselves while we're at it!
'Kay?
Now I'm really annoyed!
Time to die at the hands
of my Kilo-Kilo Fruit power!
Get ready! As I ride this explosive blast,
I weigh only 1 kilogram!
Mr. Bushido! You have to dodge! She's...!
Shut up!
This isn't the time for that right now!
That was a good workout!
Finally managed to digest that food!
M-Mr. 5?! No way!
He took out a Baroque
Works officer agent?!
Now I can fight for reals.
Hold on, Luffy.
Here I come!
Calm down and hear me out.
I can change to 10,000 kilograms!
Everyone in town was a bounty hunter.
Our enemy, in other words.
Hey! Don't ignore me!
Liar! Enemies wouldn't
give us food to eat!
Take this! 10,000 Kilogram Press!
Luffy.
Looks like trying to talk
sense into you is pointless.
You dumb dimwit!
In that case, I'm gonna fight to kill, too!
Don't regret it when you die!
Sounds great to me!
Hold on! What's going on?!
Weren't these two people friends?!
Gum-Gum...
Oni...
...Bazooka!
..Giri!
This is the perfect chance
to see which is stronger,
brute force or swordsmanship!
Yeah! Let's find out once and for all!
Tatsu-Maki!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
What now?
I want to escape, but will we be
all right if we pass through here?
Damn it!
The title of Baroque Works
Officer Agent will be shamed
if we let these guys make fools of us!
Mr. 5! Let's show them how
truly terrifying we can be!
Let's do it, Miss Valentine!
Yes, Mr. 5!
Don't mock us!
We're Baroque Works Officer Agents!
Quit being so damn annoying!
You're interfering...
...with our fight!
You've got me!
Ah, gentle song
Make it there for us
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
If you find the world is full of enemies,
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
You've got me!
Ah, my love
I'll hold you in my arms forever
You've got me!
Who decided she's coming with us?!
Now we'll have lots
more people after us!
I'm so excited!
We're lucky!
It feels like we've hit the big time now!
Do you guys even understand?!
We're in big trouble!
Oh, come on. We've already
decided to take Vivi with us!
You will compensate me in full,
just so you know!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Deliver Princess Vivi!
The Luffy Pirates Set Sail"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!