Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices
on the heads of Luffy and
11 others, and now they're being
hunted by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
"The Little People's Princess!
Captive Mansherry!"
Well done. Guys!
It's a robot!
A robot came to save us!
Thank you!
--A robot!
--Cool!
Is everybody okay?!
How are you?!
We all came to save you!
To save... us?
I-I'm so happy for all of you!
--Thank you, Robot-san!
--His name is not Robot!
He's our savior, a Big Human - Fraland!
A Big Human?!
Princess Mansherry!
Is she alright?!
As for Princess Mansherry,
Mouji is...
...looking now...
S... S... S...
She's not here.
Princess Mansherry is...
...nowhere to be found! No way!
Princess? Princess? Princess?
Where are you?!
Not here!
The princess isn't here!
We've been fooled! I can't believe it!
Stop!
Princess, please be safe!
I, Mouji, am coming to save you!
Princess!
Wait, Mouji!
Where are you?!
Not here! Not here!
Princess? Princess? Princess!!
Prin...
...cess!!
What?
Princess!
--Mouji, wait!
--Where are you?!
Princess!
Oh? I hear a strange noise.
Oh, just rats!
I gotta find her! Princess!
Wait!
We all looked... but Princess Mansherry may not be here!
What?!
You can't find Princess Mansherry?!
What kind of person is Princess Mansherry?
Princess Mansherry is...
You fools!
How dare you pay no notice to me
for such a long time!
Is she the princess?
No way!
The factory...
...is...
...my life!
I'm the factory manager.
I'm the most powerful figure in this factory!
You're Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats,
aren't you?
You're a One-star criminal.
How did you make it this far alive?
What did you do to Pink-sama?
That fool?
A FEW MINUTES AGO
I saw a weak old granny
having trouble in the back street
on the right!
I just remembered I have
some minor business to attend to.
I guess it's tough to live a hard-boiled life.
What're you talking about?
There's no old granny!
Anyway, I won't let you do as you like in this factory!
I'm gonna take your life!
Watch out! Run, Fraland!
Fraland hugged the factory manager!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
LEVEL 3
--We're totally surrounded.
--Aren't they increasing?
Destroying them all is
the only way to advance, it seems.
Alright!
Kick all their asses, you mean?
--Yes.
--That's right.
Gum-Gum Gatling!
Oh? My leg is stuck!
Whoa! Thank you! You saved me.
Kid, you give me a lot of trouble.
It's coming.
--They're coming one after another!
--We can't spend too much time here!
I'll take care of them all at once!
--I will!
--No, me!
First come, first served, then!
H-Hey, what's going on?!
What are you doing?! Let go of me!
Fraland hugged the manager!
Did Fraland fall in love with her?!
She's Fraland's type?
That cyborg idiot, how dare he fool me!
There's no troubled old granny anywhere.
Well, I'm relieved to know that.
Oh! So hard-boiled!
Señor Pink!
I'm ready! Bring it on anytime!
Ready?! Bring it on?! You ready for what?!
Cut it out! Are you nuts?!
So manly!
He's so aggressive.
That idiot!
Oh! So cool!
Hey, stop messing with
the morals in the factory!
That bastard has been throwing me around with suplexes!
Was he...
...trying to dig up a hot spring or something
with the back of my head?!
What are you talking about?!
Drop dead!
Cat-Ear Punch!
Franky Southland Suplex!
No! The manager is...
That hurt, you jerk!
How could you use my head like a hammer?!
How dare you treat me so cruelly!
I'm the factory manager!
I'm the most powerful figure here!
Once she gets mad, nobody can stop her!
Please run, Fraland!
Now, what should I do with you?!
I can do anything I want!
I have the power to punish people
in this factory!
You're sentenced to death! Death!
Because you deserve it!
Insulting me is a grave crime!
I'll cut up your body and
suck your guts up with my vacuum
then pound them into pieces!
Why don't you cry like a baby, you...
Fraland kissed the factory manager!
H-He kissed...
This guy just stole a kiss from me...
--Now, get up, you swimming idiot!
--H-Hey!
Wait a minute!
What are you thinking?!
Why did you do that?!
B-Be a man about it
and become my boyfriend!
You fool!
The manager just became a bit
more feminine...
You can't blame him, factory manager.
What?
--You got involved. It's your fault.
--Pink-sama! But...
You cut in to a fight between grown men.
When a woman does that,
how else can we seal her mouth?
Getting upset over a kiss or two makes you
just an immature little tramp. So don't talk about...
...love or relationships
or that sort of stuff!
That's right.
Love with a little chick like that...
...Would drive me nuts!
So hard-boiled!
Señor! Franky!
How hard-boiled you two are!
It's getting intense!
Is that what "hard-boiled" is?
I won't let you destroy the factory!
Humph! Prove it with your fists! If you're a man!
Franky-sama! Pink-sama!
It's gonna start! The men's fight!
Diaper Bombs!
Nipple Light Special!
All right!
I beat up the most!
IN FRONT OF THE PLATEAU -
LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
THE STATUE OF PICA
You stop that assimilating with the stone crap?
How dare you let Rebecca and
the others get away!
Thank you!
I couldn't have done it without you.
Don't think shitheads like you guys
can escape this country!
He never learns!
Zoro-senpai!
I'm still so impressed!
Rooster-kun, get yourself together!
We're almost there!
But Zoro-senpai was so cool!
We're almost there at the second level!
Be careful where you land!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
--Hello, this is Leo.
--It's Mouji!
Mouji! I'm glad to hear from you!
It means our friends have been released!
But Leo, we have a big problem...
What is it?
The princess is...
Princess Mansherry is...
...nowhere to be found in the factory!
What?!
The poor dear...
She must be locked up somewhere
and crying "Mouji! Mouji!"
No...
Get to the old King's Plateau!
Yeah!!
Catch King Riku and God Usopp!
THE OLD KING'S PLATEAU
N-No need to be afraid.
They can't climb up here that easily...
Kill God Usopp!
Father-sama, I just got a call from
the Tontattas in the factory!
Oh, are they alright?!
Yes.
But they told me
they can't find Princess Mansherry anywhere.
What?!
What are you guys talking about?!
Everyone in this country is looking for us!
Let's run now!
Where are you gonna go when
everyone in this country is looking for you?
It'll be fine.
They know the truth about the past.
They're not gonna harm Father-sama.
--What about me?
--Viola.
--Yes.
--Am I being ignored?
If they're hiding Princess Mansherry elsewhere,
it must be in the Palace.
Search there with your ability.
Okay.
Awesome!
You can see inside of the Palace from here?
Yes, with my Clairvoyance.
I can send my sight wherever I want.
Sanji would kill for your ability.
Princess Mansherry, please be safe.
I wonder what kind of person
Princess Mansherry is.
If I remember correctly, Leo said she's capricious,
selfish, and short-tempered.
Who the hell are you?!
Stop it!
K-Kin'emon!
--Oh, Usopp-dono!
--You know him?
Yeah, you can let go of him...
There's some kind of weirdo!
He's Kanjuro, who I've been looking for.
Oh, that was you!
Indeed!
I'm a samurai from the Wano Kingdom.
My name is Evening Shower Kanjuro.
What's that pathetic creature...?
Anyway, we surfaced earlier
and were surprised.
Tons of people are heading
towards this plateau
so I wondered what's going on.
That's right!
I think they can't climb up this high but...
Don't worry, long-nosed goblin man!
They were having trouble so...
I made a net for them!
What?
They will be here in any minute.
Why did you do such a thing, you fool?!
Catch God Usopp!
This rope sucks!
--They're coming to get me!
--Was it unnecessary?!
How foolish I've been...
I made a blunder! I failed my savior!
I'll commit hara-kiri to show my regret!
Don't, Kanjuro!
Okay, I won't.
Shut up! Do it!
What are you gonna do about those climbers?!
I don't see her anywhere.
When I was living in the Palace as Violet,
I never heard they'd captured
the Tontattas' Princess Mansherry.
Is she really here?
Father-sama,
I don't see her anywhere.
She must be somewhere.
Search every nook and cranny.
I don't think
Doflamingo has killed Mansherry.
I know he needs her ability.
Though we need that ability
more than him now...
Princess Mansherry, where are you?
There must be a place I haven't looked yet.
A place that I haven't looked
in the last few years.
I had been living here since I was little.
I used to explore all over the Palace.
I snuck into places no one would enter
and I created some mischief
and got scolded by Father-sama and...
Maybe...
I haven't looked at that room!
At the back of the chapel,
there was a room...
Here. Your food.
I want to go back to Green Bit!
Come and save me now!
Leo!
There you are, Mansherry!
Violet finally finds out
Princess Mansherry's whereabouts
with her Clairvoyance
and it gives Leo and the others hope but at that very moment,
Luffy and the others are completely surrounded by
eerie Headcracker Dolls that keep up their
relentless attacks, no matter how many times they get taken down!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Invincible! A Gruesome Army of Headcracker Dolls!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!