Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Hey, Kumacy! Kumacy!
The Risky Brothers are
carrying the casket over.
Get it from them and take the
casket to Master's dance hall.
Got that?
Did you get that or not?!
--Ye...
--Don't answer! You're so not cute!
I'll be directing the Treasure
Retrieval Party on the ship,
so come get me if anything happens.
Do you understand?
That's right! You're cute
as long as you're quiet!
Take care...
Punk! You just whispered something!
That old zombie wannabe said that
Gecko Moria's had his eyes on us
ever since we were invited to this island.
Perhaps the curly cook's disappearance
has something to do with Moria.
That stupid cook! He had it coming.
But I never expected to run into
one of the Seven Warlords here.
Why would a pirate want
to steal people's shadows?
I would love to know!
I-I don't know anything!
I promised that geezer I'd kick Moria's butt,
but that'll have to go on hold.
Your missing friends are
already screwed anyway!
In fact, you're in no position
to be worrying about others!
Not anymore...
Quit oinking and lead the way,
you stupid piggy!
Usopp!
Chopper, look out! Behind you!
Usopp! Chopper!
You're in danger as well.
Don't hurt her!
Bastard! Why'd you attack an ally?
That woman is the enemy!
You're supposed to kick her butt!
I don't know who this lady is,
but even if it means
defying the master's orders
or sacrificing myself,
I won't kick a woman!
Hey, Oinker! Did you pull another
fast one on us? Out with it!
Haven't I been telling
you that I'm in the dark?
Don't laugh! It gives the
impression that you're lying.
How strange. I wonder if he was
strangled so he couldn't utter a sound.
Why were your circuits
wired to be so ominous?!
This is so weird! Now Zoro's missing.
"The Vanishing Straw Hat Crew!
A Mysterious Swordsman Appears!"
Damn it!
I wonder what happened.
This is so strange.
Where the heck did those two wander off to?
Perhaps the ghosts were behind this.
I hope they haven't been executed.
If you have time to think
up all these creepy ideas,
figure out how to save them instead!
Where'd they go?
I can't believe Zoro and Sanji!
Jerk! Don't goof off at a time like this!
Hey! Isn't it every man's dream to don
a random suit of armor lying around?
Damn! It's every man's dream?
That's a solid argument!
Has that steel body made your
heart forget the spirit of wonder?
Cut me some slack! I never meant
to turn my heart to steel!
Yay! Sing!
Ever since I lost something important,
a draft has blown through my heart.
Please listen to "The Cyborg
Traveler's Steel Sentiment."
Do they understand the situation they're in?
Hey!
This opens up to a large hall.
Really?
Could this be...?
Robin! Where are Usopp and the others?
I don't know. In fact...
...this hall leads directly outside.
What's with this room?
It looks just like an arena.
If only it were that forgiving!
You oughta say your prayers!
You'll never make it outta this room.
Wha--?!
Franky!
Who are you?!
Wow! Moving armor!
I'm sure it's a zombie.
It's moving with spears piercing though it.
Zombies shouldn't get all
geared up and spook people!
Strong Right!
The wall--!
Your swordplay can get a taste of my...
Weapons Left!
You were a pain in the butt!
What is he?
What?!
Wha--?!
Whoa! He took down Franky!
I don't believe it!
I'm not gonna lose!
Not to some corpse!
He's getting up again.
This is getting nowhere fast.
He's completely different from
the other zombies we've faced.
Let that be a lesson to you!
This is what makes zombies truly terrifying!
He managed to get really far away!
Even if we take some damage, it doesn't hurt!
All of the armed General Zombies
were robust warriors who made names
for themselves when they were alive.
One was a kingdom's Captain of the Guard
while another was a heinous criminal.
There is a legendary samurai,
a pirate, and a gunslinger!
These monsters are as good as immortal!
You losers don't stand a chance.
None of your pals are okay!
How do ya like that?!
You bastard!
Wall Zombie!
On it!
Gah! They blocked the path!
The path behind us is not the
only one that has been cut off.
Based off of my experience,
I'd say these guys are definitely
more than we bargained for.
There is a whole bunch of armor!
I went nuts against one
and it hardly did a thing.
We're just gonna burn through energy
if we take all of these guys on.
Yeah, I guess you have a point.
It's not like this is the last battle.
If we make it out of this hall,
we should enter the inner courtyard.
Great! Then let's meet up in the courtyard!
I don't want anyone else
going missing, so be careful!
Right.
Charge!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Lola!
Where the heck did she go?
Ab-sama!
Kissy! Kissy! Kissy!
Kissy! Kissy-po-po-po! Kissy-po!
Knock it off, Lola!
Please give up on me!
Didn't I tell you that I'm
going to marry this woman?
Ab-sama, you belong to me and only me!
I won't show any mercy, Cat Burglar!
Stop it, Lola!
I'll crush the life outta her!
Don't!
I won't go easy on anyone
who tries to harm the lady!
What's going on here?
Isn't that dog-penguin hybrid our enemy?
The fighting style he just used...
He couldn't be...
Bastard!
Rookie, you're stepping way out of line!
That woman is the enemy!
What is wrong with you?!
I will beat table manners into anyone
uncouth enough to harm a lady...
...you damn zombies!
I'm sure of it! That dog-penguin is...
This ship belongs to Straw Hat, the man
who defeated Crocodile, and his crew...
I can't wait to see what type of
treasure they're lugging around!
Hey! Lemme outta here!
Isn't anyone around?
At least gimme a response, dammit!
It's so dark I can't see a thing!
Where the heck am I?
Who're you?!
Hey! Put me down! What're you doing?!
Who the hell are you?
Answer me!
What's with this light?
Hey! What're you doing?
Wh... What?!
Strong Right!
Don't get a big head!
Treinta Fleurs!
Move it!
Great! Now's my chance!
Gosh darn it! Zombies shouldn't
be givin' us a hard time!
Clutch!
Don't get in our way.
It looks like they won't let us
walk through without a fight.
Damn it!
No matter how many times I
take them down, they get right back up!
Dang, they're persistent!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
One-Sword Style...
...Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
That move... Zoro?!
Hey, Zoro! What was that for?!
That was dangerous!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame!
But I am covered in scars.
Who're you? Are you actually Zoro?
My name is Jigoro!
Jigoro? What, so you aren't Zoro?
How come you were able to use Zoro's attack?
I've had enough of your yapping, pirate!
You're my foe, aren't you?
I'm gonna slice you in half!
You really sound just like Zoro!
You're practically identical!
That was close! Take this!
Damn it! There's no end to them!
Franky!
Grab on!
Dang! They're really persistent!
I've got the perfect thing for zombies!
Fresh Fire!
Prepare the buckets!
What?!
Crap!
Once Fleurs!
Slam!
Where's Luffy?
It looks like he's still back there!
Even if we go back, I can't tell
where that idiot is with him in armor!
Damn it! He better not
have gone missing on us!
But we can't stay here and wait for him.
The zombies are hot on our heels.
Hey! Straw Hat!
That hurt, you bastard! Lemme out, dammit!
--What was that?
--Bastard, lemme out! I mean it!
I'll let you have it if ya don't
let me out! Open the lid!
--A casket?!
--Lemme out, bastard! I want out!
Open the lid right this second!
Lemme out right now! C'mon!
--That voice...!
--When I say I want out, I mean it!
It's Luffy!
Are you tellin' me Straw Hat is in that?!
--Let's go after him, Nico Robin!
--Yeah!
What's he doing?! Sheesh!
Did that idiot get caught?
Straw Hat!
I won't let you go after him!
Hey, hey! Monkey, monkey, monkey!
I'm the spider monkey that you were
talking about back at the harbor!
It's a giant spider!
This ain't an arachnid
anymore! It's a monster!
Lemme out, you jerk! Lemme out, dummy!
Open the--
And there goes another one!
Shit! There goes the casket!
What are you gonna do to him?!
Don't you worry!
You'll get to personally experience
what is about to happen to him.
I'd be more worried about
myself if I were you!
You're trapped with me in front
and the armored warriors in the rear!
With this, your crew is finished!
Hey, you're one insolent Wild Zombie!
Out of my way!
The small island is unable to
escape the whirling storm of love!
That's right! This is a Love Hurricane!
I've had enough of your nonsense!
Get out of my way!
I won't let you pursue that lady!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Chivalry Remains! The Traitorous
Zombie Protects Nami!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!