Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
Tra-guy!!
However, after reuniting
with Zoro and Kin'emon,
Law was shot by Doflamingo before their eyes.
How dare you shoot Tra-guy!
Law was originally my subordinate.
Responsibility for dealing
with him falls to me!
"Luffy Astonished!
The Man Who Inherits Ace's Will!"
Oh! Sorry, sorry!
I didn't want to make you suffer before
dying but I've missed a vital spot!
I-I don't buy it!
What?!
I pledged my loyalty to Joker!
Don't make things up, Dellinger!
Spring Death Knock!
Uh-huh, uh-huh. I know how you feel.
But we don't need...
...a lame duck in our family.
Damn! I can't believe
running is all I can do!
But I don't buy his words!
Where are you, Joker?!
I need to hear it from you!
You just don't know when to give up.
Don't cause Young Master-sama
any more trouble.
Goodbye, Bellamy!
Barrier!
What do you want?!
Bartolomeo?
It's none of your business!
Yeah, you're right.
I just created this barrier because I felt like it!
This is our family's problem!
I'll kill you, too, if you get in my way!
Try it!
But no one can break my barrier!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Clank.
What?! I'm in the middle of something!
It's me, Dellinger.
Sounds like you haven't killed Bellamy yet.
You're so dull.
Shut up! I got interrupted!
Oh well, finish it up later.
There's another order from Doffy.
Guard the Toy House with
Lao G. and the others.
It's urgent!
Wait a second, Diamante!
I can just finish him off first!
Knock it off!
Can't you follow Doffy's order?!
Clank.
"Another order"?
That means...
...I've really been...
Screw them...
Screw you!
Get out of my way!
I'm gonna kick the life out of Bellamy!
Go away!
No.
I'm not gonna lower the barrier!
You just got called, didn't you?!
Just go already!
Damn your barrier shit!
This is not over, you fools!
I won't let you guys walk away
alive from Dressrosa!
Just beat it, stupid brat!
That was certainly Diamante
on the Snail.
So was it really his order?
Did Doflamingo really tell him to...
...kill me?
You'll promote me to executive of the Family
if I win the competition?!
Yeah.
You can do it.
I'm counting on you.
I will win!
Let me take you to the medical room.
Mind your own business!
I've lost my reason to live!
Why do you wanna save me
in the first place?!
In the battle royal earlier,
I was there in the ring
determined to kill you all!
I know!
But when two men fight in the same ring,
they become war brothers!
And I'll never walk out on my brother!
DRESSROSA - THE FLOWER FIELD
So I've filled you in on the
history of this country.
Now, the plan to save those
UNDER THE GROUND -
THE KING RIKU ARMY HEADQUARTERS
poor people from the darkness,
I call it...
..."Operation Dressrosa SOP"!
"SOP"?
What does it stand for?
There is a vast underground world
beneath this country that nobody knows.
Down there is a trade port for a black market
and a mysterious factory...
...where our friends of Tontatta and
THE FACTORY AND THE TRADE PORT
the people who became toys
are forced to work 24/7.
Oh! So what does SOP stands for?!
We'll sneak in there through
an underground passage which
took us a year to dig,
and rescue them all!
I see! Which means
there must be a deeper meaning to SOP, right?
Franky, enough.
Then, we'll destroy all the facilities there
and bring down the Doflamingo Family
and take Dressrosa back for King Riku!
That is the goal of this operation!
You make it sound so easy but...
Of course, it won't go that smoothly!
No one can even predict what's
gonna happen in Dressrosa
10 or more minutes in the future.
So there is one thing that
needs to be done first!
One of Doflamingo's subordinates
turned us into toys.
We have to knock out
this Hobby-Hobby Fruit eater!
--Hobby-Hobby Fruit?
You can imagine what will happen then.
Oh! It will break the spell?!
That's right!
All the toys in Dressrosa will change back into
their human forms at once!
And everybody will get their lost
memories back at the same time!
We can't predict
what will happen after that!
How many people will fight together with us?
What will people think and
what action will they take?
What will Doflamingo do?
What will the Navy do?
The only thing that's for sure is
the country will briefly destabilize!
Where is the Hobby-Hobby Fruit eater now?!
He or she must be strong, huh?
According to Tontatta's scouting unit,
she's in the underground trade port now!
The Don Quixote Family - the
Trebol Army - Special Officer...
...Sugar!
She is a girl
who can turn anything into
a toy merely by touching!
She looks like a child
but anyone who eats the
fruit stops aging from the
moment they ingest it!
Since she's the most important figure,
the top executive, Trebol,
is always guarding her!
So if we can knock her out,
all the toys can change back?!
That's right!
We'll frighten her out of her wits
and make her pass out!
And that's Operation...
Sugar!
Oversurprised!
Panic!
That's what Operation SOP stands for!
What a great name for the operation!
If the enemy is just a girl,
follow me, you all!
Alright! I'm getting all fired up!
Franky Hair Salon!
Combat Hair!
Fraland!
--Usoland!
--You're so dependable!
That's right! Since you've got us...
You're not gonna lose!
Take us to the underground passage,
little ones!
The Usolanders!
Meanwhile, Luffy is looking for the exit
in the Corrida Colosseum.
Huh? Forget about the exit,
where am I?!
So I will become
Luffy-senpai's henchman someday!
That's my dream.
--Don't leave it open!
--Oh, this is the bathroom!
Oh! Crest Head!
Glad to see you here!
L-L-L-Luffy-senpai!
Hold on, Bartolomeo!
Do you wanna miss an opportunity
to talk to the King of the Pirates?!
Oh, Bellamy!
Damn! He's so dazzling -
I can't even look at him!
Luffy-senpai, did you get
to see Zoro-senpai?!
Yes, I did! Thank you for that!
My pleasure!
Now I gotta go somewhere
so I need to get out but
I can't find the exit.
There is no exit in this Colosseum.
What?
Oh?
You're more wounded than before, aren't you?
Once a competitor
steps into the Colosseum,
he can never get out!
It's no use looking for the exit!
What?! What do you mean?!
Did you say "Never"?!
There's no exit?!
You're Doflamingo's subordinate, aren't you?!
Don't you know a way out?!
Subordinate?
I couldn't even become his subordinate!
Please! My friend is in danger!
I'm gonna get out of here now.
If you follow me,
maybe you can get out, too.
Yeah? Thanks!
So are you gonna take me?!
I'm just saying if you choose to follow me,
you might be able to find
your way out by chance.
You're not telling me
to betray my boss, are you?
Because I can't betray Doflamingo!
I look up to him!
Hey, a few moments ago,
you were...
Shut up!
I've still got some principles
that I have to stick to!
Okay! I'm gonna follow you!
But Luffy-senpai,
what about the Flare-Flare Fruit?
I wanna keep it out of
the hands of a few people
but I don't have a choice!
My friend's gonna die!
In that case, you can count on me!
Luffy-senpai! I was gonna
bring the precious keepsake
from Ace-sama to you once I
won it, from the beginning!
What?! I can have it?!
Of course! It belongs to you!
Your accent is getting heavier
as you speak.
I promise you I will win
the Flare-Flare Fruit
so you can go out without worry!
Who are you talking to?
Thanks! I appreciate it!
I won't let you have the Flare-Flare Fruit.
"Straw Hat Luffy"!
Who the hell are you?!
Hey, hey, hey! Where you from?!
You can't talk to Luffy-senpai so casually!
He is the legendary pirate
"Fire Fist" Ace-sama's brother
and he will become the King of
the Pirates one day, you idiot!
I've known that from way back.
What's your problem?!
You can't just appear and say
you won't let me have the fruit!
What's wrong with that guy?!
He's talking to Luffy-senpai
in such a cheeky manner!
See? Luffy-senpai's mad!
Y-You are...
It's been a while!
Luffy!
THE PLAZA IN FRONT OF THE COLOSSEUM
You've finally made it out
so why are you crying?!
You can't find Pirate Hunter?!
I told you not to let your
guard down repeatedly!
Call the Vice Admiral now!
Yes, sir!
The Navy's totally believing
we're just toys in the town!
Just barely!
You've chosen weird animals!
I thought these animals were kewl!
Especially, carps?
Stop crying already!
Don't you wanna save Tra-guy?!
I'll save Tra-guy!
And I'll kick Mingo's ass!
Plus, the Flare-Flare Fruit is in good hands!
In good hands?
I heard Robin-san's here
in this country, too.
I hope I can see her after such a long time.
KOALA - AN ASSISTANT MASTER OF FISH-MAN KARATE
THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
I'm glad that you got to see him.
Yeah... I thought he was gonna punch me.
Are you crying?
I don't cry!
If you were there, do you think...
...you could've changed something?
Nobody knows.
Yeah.
--Let me know when you find
out about the underground.
Okay.
In any case,
I will win Ace's Flare-Flare Fruit!
We will inherit his will!
I-I never imagined he'd be alive!
Who are you talking about?!
I-I thought...
...he died...
...he died at that moment!
THE STRAW HATS ARE BACK