Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
while Zoro, Usopp and Brook get
captured by Hordy at the Ryugu Palace.
Get out of my way, Jimbei!
You gotta let me go!
No, I won't! Leave it up to me!
You bastard!
Then I'll just beat my way past you!
I'll fight you as many times as
I have to till you understand!
What did you say?!
Oh, I see some soldiers from the army!
Water Shot!
"The Battle is on!
At Conchcorde Plaza!"
Captain Hordy is awesome-ch!
I can't believe that he was just writhing in
agony from an Energy Steroid overdose-ch!
N-Neptune's army's been beaten!
They got wiped out!
Exactly how strong is Hordy?!
Minister of the Right-dono!
Minister of the Left-dono!
Neptune-sama!
King-sama!
Let's go to Conchcorde Plaza!
Oh no, Neptune-sama!
Neptune-sama!
We were almost...
...almost there!
Your efforts were expected to bear
fruit at the World Summit this year!
Queen Otohime!
But then they started this all of a sudden!
Please save him!
If nothing is done, they will kill King-sama!
Please! Please save the King!
Mom!
What's gonna happen to this country?!
Captain! Hey Captain!
Captain Decken,
things will start looking up soon.
You fool! I don't need you to comfort me!
You guys don't know how painful
it is to be broken-hearted!
I mean, Shirahoshi was
just a kid when we first met.
And I decided to marry her to
fulfill my ancestors' dream!
And how did it all turn out?
You're not my type!
"Not my type" she said When the words came
to my ears I felt my true love grow, I suspect.
A haiku with extra syllables.
By Vander Decken IX.
She broke... She broke my heart!
I was dumped so I cut my hair!
Only the top?!
I wanted to kill her but she's still alive!
I know it because I still
can throw things at her!
That Straw Hat fool must be protecting her!
Oh yeah.
What's wrong?
I got an idea!
What don't I just destroy
everything altogether?!
It's gonna be great!
Let King-sama go, Hordy!
Stop! Or we'll open fire!
Run, soldiers! Don't die a
meaningless death-jamon!
I won't let them get away-ch! Sea Bear!
Dammit!
Finally, you're here! I got tired of waiting!
Hyouzou-san, we're here!
Don't get too close! He'll cut you!
I'm here as you wish-dokan!
You folk have nowhere to... run!
We can't get in! The entrance
to Conchcorde Plaza is locked!
Neptune-sama!
Let's climb the wall!
Maybe we can see inside.
Boy, he gave me a lot of trouble...
We've wasted so much time.
Let's go, Princess-sama.
Okay!
Take care of Hachi, Camie!
Y-Yes.
Go, Megalo!
I thought you soldiers had
to protect this country!
Soldiers...
Hordy!
That soldier is up to something.
Which one?
He's gonna launch a suicide attack
to kill anyone around him-bokan!
I'm gonna become a piece of
dried squid if he does-ch!
Before the Princes gets here,
if I can kill at least one of their officers!
Oh no, he's gonna...
Water Shot.
What's that? How far can it go?
MERMAID COVE
--What is that?
--Huh?
I hear something.
Hey, I thought the Water Shot
was fairly weak, wasn't it?
I know you took a lot of Energy
Steroid but still, that was great-ch!
Your hair turned white
and you've gained muscle.
How do you feel, Captain?
Couldn't be better!
The soldiers...
Why didn't they wait for us?
Fukaboshi! Ryuboshi! Manboshi! Be careful!
All the sea monsters and the
Fish-Men have taken the drug!
I thought Neptune's army
wouldn't be beaten so easily as long
as playing field was level-re-mi-fa!
We'll save you, Father!
Why don't you understand, Hordy Jones?!
You folk are the weakest on this island!
The other islanders were trying to ignore
the history of discrimination by humans
and to forgive the murder of their hero
and queen who died at the hands of a human.
They endured their pain in
order to change the future
and signed their names.
--Prince!
--Fukaboshi-sama!
Why can't you appreciate the boldness
and kindness of their decision?
Kindness?
It's a meaningless gesture.
You all want to be fooled by the humans?!
Merman Combat!
Spear of the Ages!
Seven Great Treasures!
Dragon Tower Gate!
Th-They beat the sea monsters!
You folk are just seeking your
revenge out of your own hatred!
But I won't let you take the King's life,
or the island that belongs to our citizens...
...or the Ryugu Kingdom!
They're so strong! After all,
they're the strongest men in the Kingdom!
You think you win because
you beat the sea monsters?
We won't lose! Because we were
given the great power from above!
That power will allow us to
rule the real Fish-Man country!
We'll beat you all and lead the way to
peaceful coexistence with the humans!
If we let you have your way,
Fish-Men and humans won't get another
chance at friendship for hundreds of years!
Say whatever you like! But after all,
this country will be ruled by...
...the winner, right?
They look strange!
Here they come!
Wh-What the...
Too slow.
Hurry up, Megalo!
Father-sama, please be safe!
He will be fine! It's going to be alright!
So that was the true power of the drug!
Attempting to free Neptune,
Shirahoshi and Jimbei
but they are caught in Hordy's trap.
Displaying his prisoners, Hordy affirms
his complete control of Fish-Man Island.
and reveals a surprising, long-hidden truth!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Surprising Confession! The Truth
Behind the Assassination of Otohime!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!