Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
"Boss Luffy Returns! Is it a Dream
or Reality? Lottery Ruckus!"
This is Grand Jipang.
It resembles a certain era of
a certain country quite a bit,
but, well, let's not get too specific.
Although there were some troubles last year
after some rogues wandered into this country,
peace reigns over this land for the most part.
People are fully enjoying peace
and spending cheerful days.
However...
Idiot! Watch where you're going!
Ouch! You're the ones who bumped into me!
Are you okay?
Hm, yeah. Oh, shoot! I don't have time for this!
Come to think of it, Dr. Bluenose
hasn't shown up lately.
Yeah, I don't know what's going on,
but he seems quite busy.
Hm? Who are you?
Y-You are...
Ah! You guys are from that clown group!
These guys are dangerous.
They're always hanging out with Straw Hat.
What about me?!
You sure are making a
racket out in broad daylight!
What'd you come here for?
Straw Hat! Why are you here?!
What're you saying when you're
the one who came in here?
If you're here to pick a fight, I'm up for it.
Hey, let's get out of here.
He doesn't seem to be here anyway.
Y-Yeah. Looks like we were given a bum steer.
W-We're leaving now! Let's go!
Yeah.
What on earth was that?
Seriously, we don't get decent customers.
Sanji-kun! Scatter some salt!
Okay!
What's the deal, Onami?
Were there more annoying customers?
It's no use saying anything
to someone who's oblivious.
Boss. Where's your payment?
Oops! That's right! I have to get going!
Sorry! Put it on my tab!
Thanks! That was delicious!
Seriously... Maybe I should
report this to the police soon.
On second thought,
don't worry about it, Sanji-kun.
They'll keep coming back anyway.
Besides, come to think of it,
salt is expensive these days.
Okay!
Straw Hat again?
W-Well, he just happened
to be in that eatery, that's all.
It's not like he's gotten in our way yet.
Arrrgh! How irritating!
Ever since we came to this town,
our earnings have dropped considerably!
Then we should go to a different town.
--You idiot!
--Ow!
How could I, the great Buggy,
just get my butt whipped and leave?!
Hey, who's saying I got my butt whipped?!
I never did, you bastard!
I'm gonna slice you into three and eat you!
His mood is quite nasty, isn't it?
He's really getting into the habit of losing, so...
In any case, we'd better find him quickly
and shake him down, or we won't
be able to welcome in the new year.
Hey!
Orika! How's he doing?
Oh, hi, Boss!
He seems to be getting quite a bit better.
He ate some rice porridge earlier, too.
I see. That's good.
Orika, Pepper and the others
are worried about you.
Let's go and play with them.
Well, but...
That's fine, Rika. I'll watch pops.
What? What is it?
Yeah... Yeah... Okay.
Pops tells me to go, too.
Good.
Hold on a minute, okay?
♪ It's warm on the southern islands! ♪
♪ Pineapple-ple! Their heads
are nice and warm! ♪
♪ They're all idiots! ♪
Next, the second verse!
Yeah!
♪ It's cold on the northern islands! ♪
♪ Freezing, real freezing!
Their heads are shivering... ♪
Hm?
What the heck is this?
Beats me.
A horse...? No, it's not a horse, is it?
I know what it is! It's called a camel!
He doesn't look very tasty.
So... what's he doing here?
What's wrong? Does it hurt somewhere?
He seems to have a slight fever.
Boss, could you carry him to my house?
I feel bad leaving him here.
He seems to be hungry, too.
That's no problem, but with pops, too,
your place is too small for all of you.
But...
It might be okay to just leave him by
the well at the row house on the back alley.
But if he's hungry, then we should...
Hm?
Even so, don't just bring anything to our place!
We're running a business, you know?!
Oh, come on! Your place
is pretty empty anyway.
That's none of your business!
Dr. Bluenose isn't around when we need him.
You can leave things to Orika.
She's used to taking care of the sick.
I thought a camel would be cooler than this.
Me, too.
Boss!
There's trouble! There's trouble!
There's trouble, Boss!
Hm? What the hell is that?!
It's a camel.
Orika took him in and is nursing him.
Orika is?!
More importantly, what's the
matter, Usopp? What's going on?
Oh, yeah! There's trouble at Orika's house!
--Come with me right away, Boss!
--What...?
At my house...
Hey, walk briskly!
To think that you were
hiding in a place like this...
Did you really think that you could outrun us?
Pops!
Please stop it. He's a sick man!
Shut up! He's a guarantor of a loan.
If you wanna complain,
do so to the guy who skipped town,
forcing the deed on him!
We're just collecting the money as agreed.
Hey, don't bother with her! Let's go!
--Yes, sir!
--Hold it!
Let go of pops!
You bastard! You think
you can get away with this?
Shut up! You guys are the ones
who're doing something terrible!
We've got the deed.
Come back when you get a clue!
A deed for such a large
amount can't be possible!
If you're still gonna take pops, I'll take you on!
You blockhead! There's this
thing called interest.
We're gonna make him work for
the rest of his life to repay us.
This is no time for you, a policeman, to butt in.
Pops!
Stop it! Let pops go!
--Orika!
--Wh-Who's this brat?
You had a kid?
Okay, then. We'll take you too and sell you off.
Come!
--Rika!
--Boss!
Gum-Gum...
...Billy Club!
All right, Boss!
D-Dammit! How dare you...?!
You won't get away with this!
Yaay! All right! Get out of
here and don't come back!
But this isn't good.
It's hard to think that clown would
back down without doing anything.
Don't worry. It'll work out okay.
That sounds terrible.
So what happened to pops?
He's resting at home.
He's almost better, but he tries
to push himself and go out.
So I scolded him, saying that
he should lay down and rest.
You can twist even pops
around your little finger, huh?
Mr. Camel got his energy back!
Oh? Good timing. I made his food
using leftovers. You can have it.
Thanks, Sanji-san!
What, Sanji? Isn't my food ready yet?
You ate just a bit ago!
--Here you go!
--Thank you!
Whoa! You're making some tasty-looking food!
Ouch!
These are expensive dishes
for delivery, you damn jerk.
Don't touch them.
What's wrong, Mr. Camel?
Aren't you gonna eat? I'm sure you're hungry.
If you don't eat, you can't get better.
He doesn't want them? Then I'll...
No!
What's the matter?
Oh? What is it?
You bastard! I made these dishes using
expensive food! They're for delivery!
Hey! You bastard!
I'm gonna slice you into three!
Just as you'd expect from Sanji!
To think that he can make
such tasty food with leftovers!
You bastard! I'm mad! I'm seriously
gonna slice you into three!
Wait, Sanji-san! Please don't blame Mr. Camel!
I'm sure he ate those
because they looked tastier.
Even so...
You bastard! Who do you think
you are?! You're just a camel!
I'm sorry, Sanji-san, Onami-san.
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Onami, you sure are generous today.
Normally, you'd have beaten
the crap out of the person by now.
To tell you the truth, I'm thinking this
might be some sort of turn of fate.
This. Take a look at this.
I bought a Year-End lottery ticket.
A lottery ticket? What does
that have to do with this?
"Camel"
Ah! Camel, 1356?
So you think it might be good luck?
You got it!
Today is the drawing day.
I asked Usopp to go there and check.
Third prize! Camel, 1356!
A million Ryo-Berry third prize?!
Yeah. I checked many times!
There's no mistaking it!
I-It's true...? It's like a dream!
All right! We can now welcome in
the new year without any problem!
We'll be out of our desperate
financial situation!
That's amazing!
Now my bills will all be wiped out, right?
It wasn't you who hit the lottery.
Thank you, camel!
You really were a good-luck camel!
I'll let you eat whatever you like,
since this is definitely thanks to you!
Who said you could eat the lottery ticket?!
Spit it out! Spit it out!
A million Ryo-Berries! Spit it out!
He must really like expensive stuff.
This is no time to be impressed.
Hey! Spit it out! A million Ryo-Berries!
Give it back to me at any cost!
Mr. Camel...
A good-luck camel? What a joke.
I came to check just in case...
They sure are connected by fate.
Seriously, I wish they wouldn't
pull me into things like this.
I don't want you to call me out so easily.
Well, don't be like that.
In order to join hands, we have to settle things.
I've been having a hard time with that tomboy.
This is a good chance.
You don't have to hold back.
Then, Commissioner, it's okay
to flashily get rid of Straw Hat?
It shouldn't be a big deal for a
policeman or two to disappear.
Fortunately, it's he who's at fault this time.
I can help you without any hesitation.
--Gulp.
--That's reassuring.
After I get rid of him, you and I will
control this town and do as we please.
That's right.
Well, then...
"Confectionery
Carefully Produced"
These are golden-colored confectioneries.
You're bad.
Not as bad as you are.
What's the matter, Cabaji?!
Well... Seems like it was my imagination.
Don't scare me like that, you moron-ji!
I-I'm sorry.
I'm so busy! I'm so busy!
Th-There's trouble! There's trouble!
Boss! There's trouble!
I sent Boss out for delivery with that camel.
What's the matter?
What bad timing! Orika got
kidnapped by the Buggy Family!
What?!
I heard that she got caught by them
out of the blue on her way home.
Seems like they were after Orika from the start.
Hey, Straw Hat.
Hm? Ah! You guys are...!
Is it really okay with you? That girl
will be sold off to repay the loan.
What'd you say about Orika?!
She should be leaving the harbor soon.
Shouldn't you be on your way to rescue her?
Let me go!
Give up.
You are an important piece
of bait to trick Straw Hat.
This time, we're collecting
money based on a deed.
If he tries to raise his hand against
me in front of the commissioner,
he can immediately get fired and be exiled.
On top of that, I'll get
money from selling you off.
Just you wait, Straw Hat!
Buggy! What're you gonna
do with Orika?! Let her go!
Sorry, Straw Hat. I'm taking this girl
as collateral for that man's loan.
There's no reason for you to butt in
this time! Mind your own business!
Let's go, men!
--Yes, sir!
--Help me, Boss!
I said...
...let her go!
You interfered with us, Straw Hat!
A policeman beating up commoners
over personal matters?
What's your problem?!
Hey, what do you think about
his act?! Commissioner?
I'm disappointed in you, Straw Hat.
What have you done?
Ack! The commissioner?
What's he doing in a place like this?!
The commissioner?
Yeah. Just like our boss, Koza-sama,
he's a town commissioner and
the top person in this town.
Whoa...
To think that you'd use violence
towards commoners who
are not at fault like this...
As a commissioner, I cannot overlook this.
Straw Hat Luffy! I hereby strip you of
your role as policeman. You're fired!
Leave this country immediately
and never set foot here again!
--What?!
--Why?!
Got that, Straw Hat?!
It's your punishment for meddling
in our business all the time!
Thanks for all your hard work!
If you get it, then hurry up and leave!
What're you guys talking about?
Why do I have to leave here
just because I tried to save Orika?
I don't get it.
You're still talking like that, you blockhead?!
It's unseemly, Straw Hat.
Are you trying to talk your way out
after everything you've done?
I can immediately call the constables in
and have them arrest you, you know.
You're the one who should
be arrested, Commissioner!
Hm?
A town commissioner joining hands
with criminals? It's quite inexcusable!
I'm removing you from your position right away!
What? Who are you?
You sure talk like a big shot.
Do you say that knowing that
I'm the North Town Commissioner?
Oh? That's...
How insolent! Kneel down!
Who do you think this is?
She's the daughter of Shogun Cobra! Vivi-sama!
Ack!
You're being disrespectful! Kneel down!
--Vivi!
So it was really you, Vivi!
It's been a while, everyone.
B-But... what's the princess doing here?
My investigation has shown
that you took a bribe
and are working with the
clown to trick Boss Straw Hat.
Give up peacefully.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Don't "Yes ma'am" her, you stupid jerk!
Dammit! Now that it's come
to this, I'll flashily withdraw,
taking the loan collateral with me!
--Like I said...!
--Huh?
Orika can't be collateral for the loan!
Because she isn't pops' daughter.
--Huh?
--This way! Hurry up!
She called him pops!
They're clearly father and daughter!
There they are! Hey, Boss! I brought him here!
Oh, thanks!
Oh, hey, pops!
I heard you collapsed. Are you okay now?
Don't push yourself, pops!
Things just aren't the same
at Pinwheel without you!
--Wh-What?
--Let's have a drink together again soon, pops!
In this town, everyone calls him "pops."
There's nothing odd about
Orika calling him that, right?
But he was sleeping at her house!
Pops made his cold worse and
collapsed the other day on the street.
And Orika happened to pass by.
She's the kind of girl who can't
just leave someone like that.
Then this girl has nothing to do with the loan!
I told you so!
Which means that...
You're just a kidnapper!
Shock!
Mom!
Rika!
You get it now? Then I'm
gonna do it this year again.
Time to get blown away, Buggy!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
Good job, guys!
Our lord's pet?! This camel is?!
That's right. Lashes has been lost for a while,
so we've all been looking for him.
The reward is a million Ryo-Berries.
What?!
Vivi! You don't mean...
Yes, we'll definitely pay the reward.
Ahhh! All right!
Since this is becoming a routine,
it's hard to tell you this,
but isn't it Orika who deserves the credit?
That's okay. Let's share it. We all
took care of him, so... Right, Mom?
Yeah, you're right.
Geez... I love you, Orika!
Okay, then! Let's have some fun today!
We'll celebrate pops'
complete recovery as well!
Come to think of it, what're these decorations?
You don't know?! Today's called
Christmas Eve in foreign countries,
and it's a joyous day.
It's nice to be cheery like
this once in a while, right?
I see...
Say, Onami-san. Can I ask you a favor?
--What is it?
--Orika took in someone who
collapsed on the street again.
We've already brought him here and
he's outside. Can we bring him inside?
Collapsed on the street?
I'm starving...
Hey, monk. If a foreign celebration is
okay with you, why don't you come in?
We've got lots of yummy food.
Yeah, sounds good.
All right, then! Let's really
whoop it up, shall we?!
Come to think of it, where's Dr. Bluenose?
Seems like he's still busy.
Since he can understand animal languages,
Lashes' problem could've been solved
right away if he had been around.
Now that you mention it, you're right.
I'm telling you, today is a
really busy day for reindeers!
Boss! There's trouble! There's trouble!
For some reason, there's always trouble!
Oh, eat a rice cake or something
and calm down, Usopp.
This is about rice cakes!
They're gonna have a
rice cake tossing event at the castle,
and one of them will have
an amazing treasure inside!
I wonder how big of an uproar it'll cause!
Oh, that. Our lord is asking us to protect it.
Oh, that'd be a lot of work. Hey, we are?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Big Rice Cake Tossing Race
at the Castle! Red Nose's Plot"
I'm gonna be a policeman!!