Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
Impact!
Sanji!
Life is suffering.
Now, for the other two!
'Kay, let's do this! Center of the ship!
I'll put it on the main mast,
so if anyone's in trouble,
they can get the whistle from here and blow it!
Now it's fair!
A-All right! Good thing this was here!
Huh? You're the only sacrifice I get to kill?
"Chopper in Danger!
Former God vs. Priest Shura"
What do you think? Don't they look amazing?
Huh?
This year's pumpkins are very good.
"Knight"
Yes...
I don't know what to say
to express my gratitude.
I'm sorry. Now I am staying with you, as well.
If they decide that your daughter
let those straw hat fellows escape,
they'll consider you an accomplice.
So you'll be in danger as well.
This time is on the house...
Eneru's Mantra does not reach this far.
How are things on Angel Island?
Yes?
I'm referring to crops.
How are this year's crops coming?
Yes, I hear they're coming along quite well.
Is that right? I'm glad to hear that.
This is juice made from the
pumpkins that I grew in my field.
It tastes good.
Yes. I'm sorry. Thank you.
Conis-san, have some, too.
Young lady, are you aware that there are
those called pirates in the Blue Sea?
No.
They are criminals who travel on the blue sea.
Their ships all fly a black flag with a skull on it,
although each pirate's flag is different.
Those straw hat fellows
are probably pirates, too.
My word! Are you saying that
they were already criminals?!
Well... It is probably true that they
do not live by the rules of the Blue Sea.
In any society, there are always
those who don't blend in.
Right now, how are you any different?
Who can say for certain that society is right
and that those who don't blend in are wrong?
Sometimes it's not so clear-cut.
To put it in extreme terms, a "hero" in wartime
is simply a killer if he lives in a different time.
I also have a pirate friend.
He came here when I was still
God over twenty years ago.
He was quite the big-hearted
and pleasant fellow.
I hated to say goodbye.
Right now, though it doesn't
look it at first glance,
Skypiea is a land of endless battles.
A land where battles between
those of us from the sky
and Shandians, also known as
guerrillas, rage continuously.
The Shandians are still challenging Eneru.
Your attempt to coexist with the
Shandians when you were God
offered hope that the several-hundred-year war
would end in peace.
Yes... I was very close to succeeding,
but my status as God was taken away by Eneru.
I'm sorry. Everything went
down the drain because of that.
Wh-What're you saying?!
There's no need to apologize.
In Skypiea, there is this legend
passed down from long ago.
Long ago, on the day that Upper Yard,
the sacred ground, was born,
the island's beautiful singing
voice enveloped Skypiea.
That's when the battle between the
Shandians and those from the sky began...
...as if that voice was a cue.
So, when we hear the "island's singing voice,"
the legend says that this battle will end.
The island's singing voice?
That's right.
The sacred ground will sing again...
...someday, for sure.
What's the matter?
Please look after this place. I've got a job.
Let's go, Pierre!
Father, what tasty pumpkin juice this is!
Yes... I'm really glad...
...that you can enjoy it.
"God"
Now, offer your life to God Eneru!
Fire...!
Why do you struggle?
There's no way that you can escape death!
Die gracefully!
What?!
The ship is...!
Hmph! So he's gonna get big...
Darn it! Come on!
Hey, hey! Why do you care when there
won't be anyone to get on board?!
You and your friends cannot escape death.
Who the hell are you?!
Stop it! Don't harm them!
Then... offer your life instead!
No!
Stop it! Stop it!
Don't harm the ship! Just don't harm the ship!
Dammit!
You bastard!
You bastard! Stop it already!
I-I'm in charge of this ship!
They asked me to look after it.
Well, what should we do, Fuza?
"Thirty-foot Bird
Fuza"
He says not to harm his friends.
He says not to damage the ship.
He says he doesn't want to die.
What a dilemma.
"Skypiea Priest
Sky Rider Shura"
Such a damned selfish animal!
He really irks me!
Gan Fall...
Hey, Nami! Get a move on!
Shut up! Don't talk to me right now!
What'll you do if I fall?!
Hey! Are you all right?!
Yeah...
...somehow...
My apologies... for troubling you so often.
No problem.
What's wrong? Did you see God or something?
No... a well.
A well?
The ship... your friends... and yourself...
You don't want to lose any of those?
If you want to live so much,
then why are you so weak?!
Stop it! That spear burns things!
Stop it!
Dammit!
You creep!
Wha...?!
Are you trying to live...
without sacrificing anything?
What is this guy?
It's as if he can predict my moves.
For someone to live, another must die.
That's how life is.
Did you know that this is a sacrificial altar?
Y-Yeah! I heard something like that.
It's true. The rest of your group
is desperately trying to get here.
There are four separate areas
that we, the priests, govern.
"Swamp" "Iron" "String" "Ball"
The rule is that when the
targets are in one area,
the other priests aren't supposed
to do anything to the targets.
But this sacrificial altar doesn't
belong to any of those areas.
"Swamp" "Iron" "String" "Ball"
"Sacrificial Altar"
In other words, it's a free area.
So it doesn't matter who
strikes the ones at the altar.
But it should be after those who're
receiving the ordeal in some area die.
What?! Then, Luffy and the others are...?!
Don't freak out. My coming here doesn't
mean your friends' death... unfortunately...
I came here for a different reason.
What?! A different reason...?
Ah, but does that mean we can also
get out of here if Luffy and the others
come to rescue us?!
Yeah, that's right...
...if you can get out of this free area.
What...?
But, hold that thought.
The reason I came here is because,
although those are the normal judgment rules,
when there's an exceptional
situation, the rules change a little.
Exceptional...
Yes. For example, when three of the sacrifices
escaped to the forest over there
without permission using vines...
I see... that's an exceptio...
God's on this island, right?
I'm gonna go meet him.
He's the culprit!
What's with her, wandering off on her own?
What a selfish woman!
I don't think I could take
being called selfish by you.
Huh?!
Because of you, I feel that I've gone through
so many hardships that I wouldn't have had to.
Err... really?
Someone has to die to atone
for the others' crime of escaping.
Sacrifice is a fact of life.
Especially if they are to come back,
in order that they can more
deeply realize their own fault
when they see their friend's death...
...offer your life... to God!!
No!!
Die!
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Sky Knight!!
Hmph! Looks like a surprise guest showed up!
Gan Fall!!
Sky Knight!!
He is quite good. He is a worthy opponent.
Let's get rough with him, Pierre.
What's that old previous God doing here?!
Shall we play with him a little, Fuza?!
Just keep barking!
We don't need two Gods on this island!
Go!!
Sky... Knight...!!
We need to give him one
more push, Pierre. Let's go!
You son of a bitch!
You probably came here knowing this, but...
...you're already a criminal!
Ahh, I'll show you what I do
to aggravating fools like you!!
String Ordeal!
You're still alive?
Impressive indeed!
Well, then, as a reward, I'll give
you my prized finishing blow!
Surprise Balls! Ball Dragon!!
Even if we're far apart
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
You have a friend here to share the pain
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
I won't let it just be a dream
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Whoa! What a fight!
You bastard! What did you do?! I can't move!
Sky Knight!
Ah! What's this?!
I've finally caught him!
Sanji, give him a good pounding!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Profound Mystery!
Ordeal of String and Ordeal of Love?!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!