Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Alabasta's Hero and
a Ballerina on the Ship!"
Out of our way! Out of our way!
Crocodile-sama...
Crocodile-sama!
Crocodile!
Huh?
Ahh... Crocodile-sama!
As always, he came for us!
Crocodile?!
Don't tell me it's the Crocodile,
one of the Seven Warlords...
Shut up, ignorant people!
I just came to get that pirate's head.
He's so wonderful...
That's what you always say,
but you always save us.
Hurray for Crocodile!
Alabasta's Guardian Angel!
Crocodile!
King of the desert! Crocodile!
Well, call me what you will.
Anyway, pirates, don't cause
a ruckus in this country.
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Aren't you underestimating us?
Are you planning to take
on all of us by yourself?!
You're the government's dog,
one who sold his soul to authority!
Who do you think you are,
acting like a hero?!
Those who don't wanna die,
lay down on the ground.
Is he an idiot or what?!
He's a perfect target for us!
Get him! The money and
valuables in this town are ours!
Yeah!
So this is what the famous
Seven Warlords are like?!
Humph...
I'm a pirate on a
different level, you pig.
Ah!
Crocodile!
Crocodile! Crocodile...
Crocodile again...
"Alubarna Palace, Alabasta Kingdom"
He was one step ahead again?
By the time we got to Nanohana,
it was already...
I see...
Either way, it's fine as long
as the citizens are okay.
"King of Alabasta, Nefertari Cobra"
He does a lot for us.
There's no mistake.
This ship is heading to Alabasta.
I'll be there soon...
Luffy! Don't lie!
Tell me what you know.
Hey, why are you looking away?
Look me in the eyes!
Well, seriously... I don't know anything.
Then let me ask you something.
How did enough food for 8 people,
which I carefully divided so that
it'd last until we get to Alabasta,
disappear during the night?
Stop fighting, it's pointless!
You've got a horrible poker face.
Burp...
Hey, you have something
around your mouth.
Ah! Shoot! Food crumbs?!
See, it was you!
Geez...
Ahhh, Nami-san...
You saw it, right?
The large rat trap
is no longer good enough.
Please buy a lockable refrigerator.
Well...
I'll think about it... since it
can be a life or death issue...
Hm?
Well...! We'd better catch
something for Sanji-kun...
Hey, any luck fishing?
W-Well...
I feel good...
Seriously, I can't take my eyes
off these guys for a moment...
Ahh... I'm starving...
The fish aren't biting at all...
Luffy! It's your fault!
It's because you even ate the bait!
If we don't have bait,
the fish won't bite!
You ate it, too!
Well... I only ate the
stuff on the bait box cover.
Luffy-san. Usopp-san.
Have you caught anything?
Ahh!
Karoo! Oh no!
I wonder if we can
catch a shark or something...
I wanna catch a Sea King.
What're you two... doing to Karoo?!
What's that?
What the heck is that?
I wonder if it's cotton candy...
I'll go get Nami-san!
Hm?
Nami-san, there's a problem!
Come right away!
Ahh... don't worry.
It's nothing. It's just steam.
Steam is coming up from the sea?
Yeah. It's a hot spot.
What the heck is that?
It's an area where magma is produced.
There's an undersea volcano
underneath that area.
I see...
A volcano even though it's undersea?
That's right. There're more undersea
volcanoes than above ground ones.
Woah...
I don't really care...
since it's not food.
With the volcano like this,
a new island will be born here over
thousands or tens of thousands of years.
You're so cool, Nami-san!
Tens of thousands of years...
I wonder if I can live that long...
Well, you're a human. So you should
try dying sometime before that...
Have you caught anything?
Oh hey, Sanji. I'm hungry.
Cook something.
You guys're hopeless...
I'll go search the storage thoroughly
to see if there's anything left.
Whoa!
Ahh! It smells of sulfur!
We can't see anything!
There's steam everywhere!
Bear with it. We should
be through it soon.
Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
What is it?!
There's smoke at 12 o'clock!
It doesn't matter! Cut through it!
At any rate, unless we take care
of Mr. 3, I'll be in danger!
Yes sir! We're going in!
What is this foggy thing?
We can't see ahead!
Ah!
We got through!
Ahh! Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama is gone!
Look for him in the cabins!
We can't find him!
Can't be!
Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Whoa...!
Shoot!
Why did I jump on the duck
that I suddenly came across?!
Is he a human?
Dunno...
Oh?! Ahh!
Help me! Please!
I can't swim--!
I thought I'd die...
Well... I'm really swanny.
To think that I was saved by
pirates who are total strangers...
I will never forget your
kindness for the rest of my life!
Also, may I have a cup of warm soup?
We don't have it!
We're the ones who're hungry!
Oh, hey you! What a cutie!
You're my type!
I wanna eat you! Smooch!
Such a weirdo...
So you can't swim, huh?
That's right. I ate a devil fruit.
Really? What kind of fruit?
Well... since there's no need to rush
until my ship comes to pick me up...
In lieu of entertainment,
I'll show you...
This is my power!
What're you...
Wait! Wait! Wait!
I just told you that
this is entertainment!
What?!
Gimme a break!
Ah?!
That's me!
Surprised?! Surprised?! Surprised?!
If I touch my face with my left hand...
See?! I'm back to myself!
This is the power of the
Clone Clone Fruit I ate!
The voice, too...
The body was also the same...
A... Amazing!
There...!
Well, for that matter,
I don't have to knock you down...
Now, look!
All I have to do is...
touch faces with my right hand.
As you can see, I can...
mimic anyone!
Bodies, too!
Ahh!
Ouch!
Stop it!
Hey, are you all right?
Ow, ow, ow...
Well... sorry, but I can't
show any more of my power...
You're amazing! Do it more!
Ahhh... Well... if you insist...
I guess I'll show more...
Yeah! Show it! Show it!
Gee, he's actually into it!
We wanna see! We wanna see!
Furthermore, I'm equipped
with a memory feature!
Here we go!
Whoa!
Ah!
Spin! Spin! Spin!
How stupid!
Spin! Spin!
So how was my secret talent?!
I usually never show it to others.
Cool!
Gimme a break! Gimme a break!
Amazing! Amazing! He's amazing!
Oh whatever!
That's my ship!
Amazing! Amazing! He's...
Whoosh!
It's already time to say goodbye...?
What a shame...
What?!
Please don't go!
Don't be sad!
Journeys are always
accompanied by farewells..
But don't ever forget this.
Friendship... has nothing to do with
how long we've known each other.
Don't cry!
See you again!
Now, let's go, guys!
Yes sir! Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama!
Mr. 2?!
So he is... Mr. 2, Bon Clay...!
Vivi! You didn't know his face?!
No... I've never met Mr. 2
and Mr. 1 as well as his partner.
I don't know their powers, either...
though I've heard of rumors...
Mr. 2 is...
a ballerina with a large frame...
who talks like a woman...
He always wears a swan coat that
has "Bon Clay" on the back...
You should've noticed!
What's the matter, Vivi?
Among the faces that he
showed from his past memory...
from his memory...
I saw my father's face...
the face of Alabasta's King,
Nefertari Cobra...
If, for example,
you could mimic a king...
you'd be able to do
quite bad things, too...
We let a troublesome
guy slip away, huh?
Then he's our enemy?
He's certainly quite a problem
if he's on our enemy's side.
If he realizes that we're his enemy...
If he transforms into one of us
using his memory from earlier...
we won't be able to
trust our own friends.
Ah...!
Really? Huh?
Listen, Luffy...
Well, hold on.
It's true that his opinion
doesn't have any basis,
but he's right about us not
having to be scared of him.
We should consider ourselves lucky
that we got to see him now...
because we can figure
out counter-measures.
Mr. 2, Bon Clay-sama is in a
very good mood for some reason.
Un, deux, trios! How do you say 4?!
I found a small friendship!
Something came out!
Sea Cat!
It's a sea monster!
It's the first meal in 4 days!
It's a meal!
We're on the right track.
I hope we get there pretty soon...
It's a meal!
Whoa! It backed away!
Have the ship go back! Go back!
W-W-W-W-W-We can't!
Ah! Don't let it get away!
Capture it without fail!
How should I cook you, cat monster?!
No!
Vivi! You jerk! What're you doing?!
W... Why... Vivi-chan?
You can't eat it!
Sea Cats are a
sacred animal in Alabasta!
You should've told us sooner!
There sure are many kinds
of creatures in the sea!
Being scared of things like that...
You've still got a long way to go...
Okay then!
I'll tell you a story about when I
bravely fought Sea Kings in the Calm Belt.
Fought Sea Kings?!
Big ones! They were this big!
O... Our food got away...
But don't worry. You'll be
able to stuff yourself soon.
Really?! What cat will appear this time?!
Vivi! The wind and weather
seem to be becoming stable.
Yes.
We've entered Alabasta's climate area.
A Sea Cat appearing is also the proof.
And what we see behind us...
is probably also proof
of Alabasta being close...
There're so many ships!
When did that happen?!
Hey...! They all have
the Baroque Works' symbol!
Its employees have started gathering...
They're probably Billions...
the Officer Agents' subordinates.
Which means that our
enemy is at least 200...
On top of that, they are the
200 elites of Baroque Works...
They're far from those bounty
hunters in Whisky Peak.
Should we fire at them while we can?!
Let's get on it already!
It's quicker if we go
there and beat them up!
No, wait! We have to eat first!
Idiot! Don't bother. They're small fries.
He's right.
If we lose our real target, that'll be it.
There're only 8 of us.
Anyway, tie it tight.
Our enemy this time
has too many mysteries.
I see...
If we check this, we don't
have to doubt our friends.
Does that Clone Clone Fruit guy really
become so similar when he transforms?
You've no idea! It's not "similar."
It's "the same"!
It's too bad! You should've seen it.
We even danced with him.
I'm not interested in a male ballerina.
Knowing someone like that
is among our enemy,
we can't carelessly act alone.
Hey, what should I do?
Ahh... Do what you can do.
You don't have to do anything more.
It's okay to run away from
the enemy you can't defeat!
Aren't you telling that to yourself?
What I can do, huh?
Got it!
I can see the island now!
Let's stop at the town called Nanohana.
We have to hide the ship.
All right! At any rate,
no matter what happens,
this thing on our left arm is
the sign of our friendship!
Well then, we'll land!
To a restaurant! Oh, and to Alabasta.
It's a side note?
The enemy this time is an
assassination gang, Luffy.
Yeah, it is.
Be careful about acting
on instinct, okay?
You're right. I got it.
Yeah! That's right! Yeah!
Got it!
Even this sleepless town
has dozed off for now
From today forth,
something's going to change
I'm sure I can start fresh,
since I'm not alone
Just by having you by my side,
I feel I can become strong
I wonder how far I can go,
towards the place that leads to the future
Off in the distance it shines,
encompassing the world
Before dawn
Food! Food! Food!
So this is Alabasta!
It's a town full of life!
It's... quite hot...
The town still seems peaceful.
When will the riot actually occur...?
We have to stop it, right, Vivi-chan?
Yes.
Food!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Off to the Desert Kingdom! The Rain-
Summoning Powder and the Rebel Army"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!