Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Incredible!
The Straw Hat Dangers
come from behind to win
the final round of the Davy Back Fight!
I lost... And so did my Slow-Slow Beam...
All right! We did it!
Thank goodness! What a relief!
--It all worked out in the end.
--Yep.
Now it's time to take someone!
Who do you choose, Straw Hat Luffy?!
Chopper! Come back!
Oh, no! Choppy!
Thank you! I'm so happy!
Don't cry! You know we'd never lose!
The grueling Davy Back Fight
has come to an end!
Both teams ultimately reach a
draw as the Straw Hat Pirates
take back their ship doctor, Chopper!
--The competition is now ov--
--Hold it! Hold it! Hold it!
There are no "draws" in the pirate world!
It's either plunder or be plundered!
Right, Straw Hat?! Well?!
Wh-What's he tryin' to say?!
What do you say to another
three-coin game right now?
Is he an idiot?
Seriously! Who'd agree to
more of these lame games?!
Ack! You can't be serious!
You're on!
--What the heck are you thinking?!
--You stupid rubber monkey dimwit!
--You idiot! Moron!
--How can you be so stupid?!
This is the last time... I won't do it again...
We have to fight them again?!
Nothing we can do now.
He's already agreed to it.
He must have something in mind.
I wouldn't be so sure...
Or maybe he's planning
to snag us a shipwright?
"Screaming-Hot Bombardment!
Pirate Dodgeball!"
It's time for the second three-coin game!
The events are a team-wide ball game,
a six-on-six all-star retro game,
and a one-on-one fight!
Like last time, each person
can only participate twice!
Lineup changes won't be allowed!
They're gonna take me for sure this time...
No, it'll definitely be me...
It's my fate to wind up as their idol...
--Not interested.
--Huh?
--Why not?
--You're weak.
--And scary.
Okay, it's time for Round #1: Hit and Dead Ball!
As always, I'll explain the rules!
Two balls are used!
Players throw these balls at
opposing team members on the court!
Get hit and you're disqualified! Outta the game!
Whichever side runs out of
on-court members first loses!
You're free to choose which members
should be on or off the court!
But keep in mind that although
off-court members can throw the balls,
they're not allowed to enter the court!
I see. So it's basically a variation of dodgeball.
Be sure to carefully read the rule book
for other miscellaneous details!
--Rule book?
--It's rather thick...
Yes! Hit and Dead Ball is the greatest
and most time-honored Davy Back Fight game!
Many rules have been added
over time, little by little,
to make it a more clear-cut game!
There's no point in having strict rules
if you're not gonna follow 'em!
It's obvious you're just gonna
keep ruling in their favor again!
Non, non, non! Read the very first page!
"Referee Regulations."
"He who makes a judgment contrary
to these rules shall be beheaded."
Beheaded?! Yikes!
There you have it!
Incidentally, this game will be
officiated by a team of five referees
headed by Rokuroshi,
a fifty-year veteran referee!
Looks like it might actually
be a fair game for once.
Team Foxy has a veritable crowd
of players! A truly grand spectacle!
But the diminutive Team Straw Hat
pales in comparison...
As usual, they have a measly seven members!
Drop the "measly" part!
Okay, let's get it started!
We'll begin with the double jump!
Each team, bring two players forward!
I wanna do this, Zoro!
Be my guest! Go jump your heart out!
Yeah!
Oh! Ship's doctor Chopper has changed form!
He appears to have mysterious abilities!
He could be formidable indeed!
Oh, my! What is that? That's not cute at all...
All right! Let the game begin!
Oww!
All right, that's it! Now clobber 'em!
Okay! Here goes, Chopper!
Aim for Split-Head!
Right!
Our boss is in trouble!
H-He's already out of the game?!
All right! We showed their boss who's boss!
Doesn't count! Doesn't count!
What?! That was a clear hit!
Article 23! Hits to the face don't count!
What?!
Darn it!
You okay, Boss?
You shouldn't laugh, Hamburg-san...
Now's our chance!
Hit 'em like crazy and win!
Okay! I'll hit them like crazy and win for us!
Here they come! Run for it, ya know!
Th-There's no need to get that fired up...!
Eighteen members of Team Foxy
are out for going out of bounds!
Yes!
Amazing! They each knocked
nine people clear off the court!
Ugh! The same number as you?!
Way to go, Sanji! Way to go, Zoro!
So sorry.
Wow! Nine people each!
Okay! I'm next!
Gum-Gum Slingshot!
Ten members of Team Foxy
are out for going out of bounds!
All right! A new record!
Wow, another big group is out of the game!
But Team Foxy finally has one of the balls!
Now it's my turn!
Get 'em, Chopper!
Knock eleven out for a new record!
Okay! You got it!
Oh! Our very own Hamburg
has fended off the attack!
Team Foxy now has both balls!
It's finally time to fight back!
Well done, Hamburg!
--Give the balls to Big Pan!
--Right!
Eep!
Get 'em, Big Pan! Send 'em all flying!
Whoever he hits is a dead man! A goner!
Oh, no!
Wh-What is this?!
Long-nose and 22 Team Foxy members
are out for going out of bounds!
Usopp! Are you all right?!
I-I'm somehow still alive...
I got the ball now...
Big Pan took out Usopp,
the long-nosed sniper, with his power throw,
but wound up knocking out a slew
of his own teammates in the process!
Team Foxy is down to two players!
Have their superior numbers
backfired on them?!
This doesn't bode well!
What will they do now?!
--What now, Boss?
--Whadya mean, "What now?"
I can't use my Slow-Slow Beam as long
as that archeologist chick is there...
So there's only one thing to do...
You mean... you-know-what?
Yes. You-know-what.
Oh, my! Now Hamburg is out of the game too!
Nice, Robin!
The top of the head doesn't count!
No, Page 103, Article 54 states
that the top of the head does count.
She's correct.
Don't do anything shameful!
Do you want to be beheaded?!
Sorry...
Wow! Robin has a sharp mind!
Has she memorized the entire thick
rule book in such a short time?!
You're amazing, Robin!
I haven't read all of it yet, though.
All right! Just one left!
Finish 'em off, Sanji-kun!
Yes, Nami-san!
Sanji-kun!
Yes?!
Please don't hit him...!
Give us the ball, okay?
--Of course!
--Ack!
Thanks!
Now please get out of the game!
Okay, Twirly Eyebrow Man?
My pleasure! Please hit me wherever you like!
What are you doing, Sanji-kun?!
Oh! Love Hunter Sanji has been
blissfully and passionately knocked out!
He's the second Straw Hat out of the game!
Bye-bye!
You mellorine moron!
He never changes...
Still, their boss is the only one left.
You never know for sure, until the very end.
Precisely.
Huh? What is that?
Huh?
There it is! The top-secret
item of Hit and Dead Ball!
Say hello to the Mr. Accu-Cannon!
Hey! You're just gonna allow that, Ref?!
It's clearly against the rules!
That's the Mr. Accu-Cannon?
What's with that "I already knew
about it" reaction of yours?!
I didn't know what it was referring to,
but I came across it in the rule book.
Yes! Rule 322: the only weapon
allowed is the Mr. Accu-Cannon!
Is that really a rule?
It's so cool! I like it!
This is stupid!
Hey! Bringing that thing out now
still ain't gonna help you!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Porche! Are you ready?!
Sure am, Boss!
Here goes!
Flower Hypnosis!
Crap!
It's hypnosis! Don't look!
Always pulling these tricks on us...
Now, Boss!
All right!
You're all mine!
Having your eyes open or closed...
...makes no difference to a swordsman.
Incredible! What power!
Swordsman Zoro sliced the ball in two
with his bare hands and with his eyes closed!
Oh, no...
Zoro of Team Straw Hat is out!
What for?!
Rule 645!
No slicing the balls!
Team Foxy gets a new ball.
What?!
Too bad!
Oh, what a shame!
Swordsman Zoro is out of the game!
Zoro...
...got knocked out of the game...
Crappy swordsman...
You got knocked out first, lousy cook.
Things are really getting good now!
It's two against one!
Now to pick up where I left off!
Yeah! Give us your best shot!
Bring it on!
Ultra-fast Level 5!
Let's see you dodge this!
Oh! Choppy!
What a beautiful self-sacrifice
by ship's doctor Chopper!
--But this means...!
--The face doesn't count, right?
F-Face?
I-it's extremely difficult to tell
where his face begins and ends!
Talk about brave!
Hey, Ref! You're a man of the sea too,
ain't ya?! That was his face!
Yeah! That furry fella has some serious guts!
You ain't men if you can't see that!
It hit his face! It hit his face! It hit his face!...
What the...?
We "ain't men"...?
I can't just ignore that!
The call is clear as day!
It hit his face! He's safe!
All right!
However...!
However...?
Although it hit you in the face,
you're unfortunately still out of bounds!
Oh, my! He's regrettably out of bounds!
Just after his gutsy face
catch was given the okay!
What a pity! Ship's doctor
Chopper is out of the game!
Even so, he's still a true man of the sea!
Choppy!
You okay, Chopper?
Yeah... But I'm out of the game now...
Just leave the rest to me!
But never mind that. Thanks, Chopper.
Hearing that doesn't make
me happy at all, you jerk!
Not bad, Choppy! Now I
wanna have you even more!
I won't let you take him!
It's now one against one!
Both teams have their backs to the wall!
It's the final showdown!
Take my advice and lose like a good little boy!
I absolutely won't lose!
What nonsense!
Take a good look around you
before you spew such drivel!
Here it comes! The Omni-Directional Shift!
Say your prayers!
Yikes! What the heck?!
Hey! What's the deal, old ref!
What's with all those balls?!
There's no rule whatsoever
against using fake balls.
I knew it. You really are on Foxy's side.
Damn! They'll always have the upper
hand unless we get a ref of our own!
Don't worry, Luffy! Only you
and their boss have a real ball!
Don't let him fool you!
Ack! That's right!
What's with this guy? Is his brain split too?!
My brain... split too...
Oh! Then I'll just send that
entire Mr. Neato Thing sky-high!
Here goes!
Huh?
Try this on for size!
Oh! Right over here!
You stretched your arm too far!
All right, everyone! Shuffle!
Shuffle! Shuffle! Shuffle! Shuffle!...
Oh, no! Now we can't tell
which is real and which are fake!
Once again, which one is the real deal?!
You'll need to figure it out
before it hits you, though!
Shut up! It doesn't matter
as long as I catch all the balls!
Don't get snarky with me!
You're one sore loser, you know that?!
All right, men! Throw like crazy!
You're...
...finished!
Luffy! Look out!
Luffy! Let it hit your face!
You're a heartless monster!
Yes!
All right!
Straw Hat Luffy is out!
What for?! Getting hit
in the face doesn't count!
Rule 999! No swallowing the balls!
It's right there in the rule book!
He's right. It's on the very last page.
A l-lousy rule like that...?
Team Foxy emerges victorious in
Round #1's game of Hit and Dead Ball!
Stupid!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Round #2 is that game from my childhood!
This is a pirate game! All weapons
and obstacles are allowed!
--Go get 'em, Zoro and Sanji!
--You're a member too!
But that cheetah and the others are back!
Me and Nami are too weak and scary anyway!
Zoro-kun? That's a scary look! Stay away!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Showdown on the Cliff!
Red Light, Green Light!"
Huh? Zoro's lost again?!