Edited at https://subtitletools.com
She sacrificed herself in order to protect
us from an attack by the Government!
Then...
...after all, Robin was...
...lying?
I'm not gonna let Robin die!
One-Sword Style! Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Paulie-san!
We're not safe yet!
There's nothing to think about.
Let's sail out right away and follow them!
There's no other way.
We're off.
Hey, rope guy.
Please let us use a ship. No, rather than a ship,
isn't there any other sea train leaving?
Puffing Tom is the only sea train in this world.
It's a miraculous ship that is the result
of the combined efforts of a team
led by a legendary shipwright.
Then, let us borrow a ship.
The strongest and fastest one in this town!
Enough already, you idiots!
Didn't you see what just happened?!
You were almost pulled out to sea by that wave!
He's right! There's no way you
can set out to sea right now!
Are you stupid?!
Are you fools?!
Even with the usual Aqua Laguna,
no ship has made it through!
You saw the collapsing backstreets, didn't you?
The town that had never been
damaged by Aqua Laguna up until now...
...is now wrecked. How terrible...
On top of that, the Aqua Laguna
this year is incomparably huge.
If you put out a ship now, even if you
challenge it with the biggest galleon,
it'll shatter the ship immediately.
I can't let you sail out when I know you'll die.
Wait until morning.
Once the storm passes, there's no
problem letting you borrow a ship.
Hey, you guys go to the
evacuation site or someplace.
We're done searching for missing people.
It wouldn't be funny if you got taken out to
sea by the wave while just standing around.
Yes, sir!
If...
Hm?
If we are to wait until morning,
can our wish come true?
I know Enies Lobby.
When I heard it was a Government island,
I remembered something.
Isn't that the place...
Isn't that the place where
the Gates of Justice are?
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Another Sea Train? Rocketman Charges Forth!"
Isn't that the place where
the Gates of Justice are?
What's that?
Enies Lobby is the
Government-owned judicial island.
What's there is a court in name only.
Being taken to Enies Lobby itself
is considered to be proof of guilt.
After passing through this
empty court without stopping,
criminals soon reach huge, cold steel doors.
These doors are called the Gates of Justice.
Once criminals go through them,
they won't see the sunlight ever again--
they're doors of despair.
This is because there are only
two places that you can reach
after sailing out from the
harbor beyond these gates.
"Navy"
One is the greatest military force for
justice in the world-- Navy headquarters.
The other is Impel Down,
the large, deep-sea prison,
where torture rooms and gallows stand
side by side, that holds vicious prisoners
who once ran amok all over the world.
In other words,
Enies Lobby is a judicial institution
that criminals are just dumped into
without being shown any mercy.
Isn't that right?!
Robin's got a bounty on her head.
No matter where she's taken,
she'll see hell beyond that point!
Each moment we sit here talking,
she gets closer to the Gates of Justice!
There's no way we can wait until morning!
If you know that much,
I've got only one thing to say.
Even if the sea were calm
and you were able to sail out,
you shouldn't go there.
Don't forget that you guys
yourselves are pirates.
As you said, Enies Lobby is the front door
that leads to the World Government's hub.
Naturally, battle lines are
drawn up taking that into account.
No pirate would think to get back
crew members taken to that island...
...because it's crystal clear what would happen.
Are you trying to pick a fight with
the hub of the World Government?!
H-He's right! You should give up!
You can't sail out until morning
because of Aqua Laguna!
Even if you go after them, you'll get killed!
There's no chance of you guys surviving!
Luffy...
Then, we'll...
...steal a ship and go!
We're gonna sail out now!
Our friends are waiting!
Don't stand in our way!
E-Even the wave got angry, too!
--Wha...
--Does he wanna fight?
Boy, that scared me.
Fine. I'll take you on!
Hold it, you guys!
Kokoro-san!
It's you who's wrong here, Straw Hat.
Paulie is right, you idiot.
Shut up! It's none of--
None of my business... huh?
Well, listen. If we let you be,
you're gonna risk your lives, aren't you?
Look. If there exists a ship that
can get through that Aqua Laguna,
it could only be a sea train
built by a legendary man.
But it's not here right now!
That's why we're trying to go in a ship!
If you're prepared to die, then come with me.
I'll give you a ride... on a sea train!
--Who's that?
--Beats me.
You fools! What're you doing?!
Besides the criminals,
everyone here is wearing a uniform!
G-Get him!
So it turns out this way anyway, huh?
I thought I had a good plan...
"Operation Play Innocent"...
Hm?
What?! S-Sanji!
Hold it!
We're not gonna let you pass through here.
Twins, huh?
Collier...
...Frit!
Sanji! Why are you on the sea train?!
I wanna ask you the same question.
How about it, you... Well, I don't know
what your name is, but you over there...
Oh, what a load of crap, you jerk!
Hm?
Hm? Whoa!
There you go, transponder snails!
Phew, all right! Geez,
there are several of them here.
I wonder if this is also a communications room.
Those government officials from the car earlier
had only stupid stuff, like masks and costumes!
I can finally contact Nami-san using them.
So you two are... pirate friends, huh?
Former friends.
Who the hell are you?
I'm Franky, demolition worker and the
face of the Water Seven underworld.
So you're Franky?! You damn bastard!
How dare you give our long-nose
a terrible time, then?!
How many pieces do you want
me to cut you into, you jerk?!
Ah, wait, wait, wait...
Ah, Sanji, hold on a sec. All sorts
of things happened after that.
You son of a bitch!
Just you wait till I get untied!
Stop saying things like that!
Well, he saved the Merry once.
Oh, that's right... The Merry is...
Hey, hey, wait a sec!
This is no time to start moping!
Anyway, mister, please untie me!
Who'd untie you?! You should stay
captured for the rest of your life!
You bastard! How dare you talk
like that when I asked you nicely?!
Stop it...! You guys!
If we don't hurry up, they'll find us, right?!
You're getting on my nerves!
--What'd you say?!
--Shut up, both of you!
Just untie me already!
Don't order me around!
Arrrrgh! Stop it already!
Ah... Captain T-Bone...
Franky is with them, too, you said?
Yes... but the sea train has already departed.
All the craftsmen are also looking for
Straw Hat and the other one, but...
There's no limit to their strength
when they know it's okay to save her!
Whoa...
Underground!
This warehouse has been abandoned
for more than eight years.
When it comes to the sea train, it's been
untouched for more than twelve years.
--Let's go, Chopper!
--Yeah!
It may no longer run, though!
Hey! That would be a problem!
Hey, hey, wait for me.
Even if you go in a rush, you can't
get inside without the keys.
Hm...? What the heck?
It's open, huh?
Whoooa! There it is!
This looks cool!
Amazing!
I'm warning you, this is a crazy train.
Its name is Rocketman.
We can't even allow passengers to be on board.
Rocketman!
It sounds fast!
Cool!
What's up with that face?
That shark head is attached as a joke.
Hm?
Ice pops!
Straw Hat... So you really were okay.
It's just like what the pirate girl said.
So you brought them here, Kokoro-san?
Looks like you survived, huh, Iceberg?
What're you doing here?
The fact that we both are here means
that we were thinking the same thing.
Hm?
We just can't help giving idiots a hand, can we?
Use it. I've finished servicing it.
Water and coal have been loaded
and it's storing the steam right now.
So you were getting it ready for us, pops?!
Oops.
Wait to rejoice until you survive the ride.
After all, this was a failure built
before Puffing Tom was completed.
No matter how much you tune it up,
its steam engine can't control the speed.
I can't guarantee your lives.
Okay! Thanks, Ice pops!
All right! Let's go!
Guys! Get on board!
Granny! We're leaving as soon as Nami comes!
Ooops!
Luffy! Are you okay?
You've been shaky on your feet for a while.
He probably bled too much.
I kinda feel weak. If only we
had some meat or something...
Hurry! This way!
Wait!
You don't have to go to a place like
that, right? Why don't you eat here?
That's right! You're starving, right?
There's no way I could eat that much!
What?!
Sorry it took so long!
--Nami...
--Hey! What're you doing?!
Hurry up and get on board, you idiot!
Wow, amazing!
So this is a sea train, too?
Whoa... I never knew there was
another one in a place like this.
I'm surprised!
Where have you been, Nami?!
Who was it that said we didn't have time?!
What's that stuff?!
--Meat and beverages.
--I'm sorry that I complained.
Here we go.
If you can get on the railway after going out
to the sea via a canal, that'll be
a success for the time being.
Don't worry. I'm more experienced
in operating it than you are.
You take it easy and rest here.
Sorry.
Chimney and Gonbe should be playing
around there. Please take care of them.
Yeah.
Well, I bet he's fine.
Hm?
We're talking about a guy who
survived being hit by a sea train...
On top of that, we have the
King of the Pirates and his friends.
Straw Hat!
They are...
The Franky Family!
At a busy time like this...!
Please... take us with you!
I heard from the Galley-La people
that you're going to Enies Lobby!
Our Bro, Franky, was taken
in by the Government!
We want to go after them... but we can't
get through Aqua Laguna by ourselves!
It's the World Government you're up against.
It doesn't matter who it is!
We're gonna get Bro back!
We'd give up our lives for him!
Please!
Help us out! Straw Hat!
Please! Bro is in danger!
Give me a break! Do you know
what you've been doing to us?!
We do!
We're swallowing our pride and begging you!
We want to save Bro!
--Get on.
--What?!
Hurry!
Straw Hat...
Hey, Luffy!
Oh, it'll be fine.
Thank you!
We're deeply indebted to you!
Hurry up!
Ah! But we don't have to get on the train.
Hm?
We'll jump out to the sea using our
King bulls at the same time you do.
So all you need to do is to let us
hold on to the end of the train.
King bulls?
Thanks for letting us go with you!
Well then, see you later!
Let's go!
Yeah!
All right! We can go rescue Bro!
--Yeah!
--Hurry up!
How is this?
Okay! Well then, let's go, shall we?!
Now... pirates! Don't go
getting thrown off, okay?!
Now departing Water Seven for Enies Lobby...
Here comes the sea train Rocketman!
All right! Depart!
We're gonna go...! To get everything back!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
Go! Rocketman! Don't be
beaten by Aqua Laguna!
Hey, Luffy. Somehow,
there are weird guys in here.
Straw Hat! Thank you for helping us,
the fifty members of the Franky Family!
This is good. Everyone here
has the same enemy!
We'll work together and beat them up!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Rescue Our Friends! A Bond
Among Foes Sworn with Fists!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!