Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices
on the heads of Luffy and
11 others, and now they're being
hunted by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats
fighting the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Doflamingo stood in
Luffy and Law's way to the Royal Palace!
Isn't there any...
...hope left for me?
You always wanted to become a pirate.
But not me.
Anything was fine with me.
As long as I could...
...destroy this world!
Is that...
Roger that!
Pink Bees, the next message!
FIGHT!!!
I guess you need another beating
to understand things.
I don't know what's going on
but one thing I know is...
Friends don't lie!
--Shut up!
--Sanshita!
Go ahead, Straw Hat!
Leave this mess here to us and go!
Make sure to take him there,
Cavendish!
Hey hey,
I'm not public transportation!
We gotta win this war!
"The Second Samurai!
Evening Shower Kanjuro Appears!"
Don't let Straw Hat and the others
proceed to the third level!
Bring them down at any cost-in!
You guys!
We won't let you go any farther from here!
--Don't bother us!
--Go away!
You go away!
Destruction Cannon!
Damn! Those meatheads were
disorganized before
but now they've teamed up!
I don't like it but I have no choice
but to count on you guys now!
Cavendish!
Take Straw Hat to the Royal Palace
at any cost!
They're saying whatever they want!
Let's go, Farul!
I won't let you get away!
Destruction Cannon!
Your back was un"g"uarded!
There's the "G"!
Prepare to be shattered into pieces!
Mine Pop.
--He did it!
--That serves them right!
You idiots, just go after Straw
Hat and the others already!
Y-Yes, sir!
Armsmorphosis!
Revolver Girl!
I thought you guys didn't believe in
teaming up with others!
Garp's grandson is worth
bending our beliefs!
Here I go!
Head-Arms!
Hm? She got away?!
Entertain me, K-I-N-G!
Pistol High-Heel!
I guess a king's life is very valuable!
I couldn't get him...
Thank you!
Humph!
I just wanted to kill that bastard!
Ten-Ton Vise!
Hajrudin!
Don't lower your guard-in! Dellinger!
I was just playing with him.
I can kill him anytime.
Way to go!
As my allies, they're all reliable warriors.
--This doesn't mean I became your ally!
--Don't push your luck, Dagama!
Keep them away from the Royal Palace!
Bring down Straw Hat!
Secure the way for Straw Hat!
Yeah!
This battle... Now is the crucial point!
Looks like that guy is taking command.
He's annoying!
Daruma!
What the... Hey, let go off me!
You jerk!
Get to the top! Straw Hat!
--Shoot, shoot!
--Keep them off at any price!
Blade of Beauty! Saint-Exupéry!
Gum-Gum Jet Gatling!
THE EXECUTIVE TOWER
THE JUNKYARD
KIN'EMON
So creepy.
Is there a beast or something?
It's coming from around here.
I said I can't eat anymore...
Could it be...?
What?!
Is it morning already?
How's that possible?
Somebody was in the wall?!
K... K...
Ka...
Kan...!
I missed you so much!
I'm glad that you're okay!
Kanjuro!
Oh, Kin'emon!
This is great!
Really!
I'm sorry.
I think I made you search for me a bit.
Some strange things happened
one after another
so I was planning to hide
myself in the wall for a while
A SAMURAI FROM THE WANO KINGDOM
EVENING SHOWER KANJURO
but I fell asleep before I knew it.
Anyway, Kin'emon,
I can't believe you came back!
What are you saying...
Oh no! Momonosuke!
Go after Momonosuke! Don't worry about me!
Sorry to keep you waiting for so long!
I trusted you so I didn't mind even a bit.
Don't be so stiff and formal, friend.
With my sorcery,
I didn't have a problem getting food.
Oh well, I'm not hungry at all but...
Want some lettuce?
No, I don't.
Your food never agrees with my stomach.
Well, as long as
you and Momonosuke are okay...
Yes, we are, thanks to you!
Good. I hope I can see Momonosuke soon.
Yeah, Momonosuke is looking
forward to seeing you, too!
So many things happened since I last saw you
but I can't put it all in a nutshell!
We have a lot to talk about!
I'll tell you later!
Okay, got it! Let's get out of here!
Get out?
Is there a way to get out of here?
How is he gonna do that?
Is he...?
Drawing something?
Come on out!
Spring Sparrow!
--What?!
--No way!
--His drawing started moving!
--Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
That picture of a bird came to life!
But the drawing is terrible...
Although his ability is amazing,
because of his drawing skills,
that sparrow doesn't seem
to be too good at flying...
--Now, Kin'emon, let's go!
--Uh-huh.
We can fly straight up to the ceiling
with this Spring Sparrow!
Wait a sec!
We're former King Riku
army soldiers and citizens
that had been living as Toys all this time.
We don't know what's going on
but is King Riku alright?!
Our families are in the town!
Take us out with you! I beg you!
Kanjuro!
Don't say another word! It's unnecessary!
--Awesome!
--Thank you, samurai!
We can get out from here finally!
Take turns climbing out!
Since it's a pictorial
ladder, it breaks easily!
The lines aren't straight
so it's hard to climb!
Stop complaining!
You've got a lot of nerve!
THE COLOSSEUM ARMY
THE ROYAL PALACE
Stop Straw Hat and the others!
Why don't you aim at us?!
Guillotine High-Heel!
There! I aimed at you!
Oh, the Longleg got beat!
Don't look away, Straw Hat!
We must get to the Palace where
Doflamingo is, at any cost!
I knew it when I heard Doflamingo's speech!
It's a game to kill me.
Kill or get killed.
Everyone in this country will become hunters!
The only way for you to survive is...
...to kill somebody!
This game called the Birdcage is all fake!
As soon as the weapon trafficking
and the secret with the toys were revealed,
all the people currently in this country
were sentenced to extermination, I think.
Doflamingo won't let any
information out of the country.
That's why he enclosed the island
in the Birdcage.
Which means Dressrosa is...
...is a solitary island,
cut off from the rest of the world!
Believing in miracles and
waiting for the end of the game...
...will get us all killed!
The only way to get out
of this island alive is
to move forward and kill Doflamingo.
There are a variety of troubles
in this country...
So many unexpected things
are happening around him
but it seems like Doflamingo is enjoying it.
I don't know anyone
who's more cunning than Doflamingo.
Doflamingo is a notch above
all the others on all fronts
but he made just one mistake:
He brought in all those
odd, tough warriors from
all over the world for the
event at the Colosseum.
We're not gonna be defeated!
Because, after all,
I will take down Doflamingo!
What are you talking about?!
I said I'm gonna kick Mingo's ass!
I said it would be me, Straw Hat-ya!
I'm very impressed, but I'm gonna do it!
Soldier! You said you wanna kill
one of the Executives!
That's a personal thing!
Taking back King Riku's country is my inevitable duty!
I have to put an end to the tragedy
that started 10 years ago!
If you talk about time,
I have a grudge from 13 years ago!
Then, mine's from 30 years ago!
Don't lie! There's no way
that you're older than me!
--You guys, get off!
--You get off!
--It's my horse!
--You told me to get on!
The road's ending!
Almost there! The third level!
All right!
Go straight to the fourth level like this!
Horse!
What's the matter, Farul?
What are those giant dolls?!
The group of dolls stands in
Luffy and the others' way!
Meanwhile, Pica who's been fighting Zoro,
throws a punch with his gigantic
fist aimed at Robin and the
others who're heading for the Royal Palace!
When it seems like his attack is unavoidable,
Zoro's never-before-seen
sword attack strikes Pica!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Hard-Fought Battle Against Pica! Zoro's Deadly Attack!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!