Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
While Buggy and Mr. 3 ascended to level 4 in order to break out,
the moribund Luffy was injected with a Healing Hormone by Ivankov,
which will cure him, but rob him of 10 years of life!
Food!
I'm...
...recovered!
"Luffy's Back! Ivan-san Begins the Breakout Plan!!"
Wow! He absorbed all the energy!
What a guy! You must be superhuman!
He has overcome Magellan's poison! I can't believe it!
He recovered after only 20 hours!
This must be a miracle!
Miracle? It's something far greater than that!
You did it! You did it! You did it! You did it!
You did it! You did it!
I'm so glad!
Oh, Bon-chan! I'm so happy you survived!
What?! Are you kidding?! Gimme a break!
You're the one that made me worry....
Bon-chan! Hey!
You alright?! Hey!
What happened to you? Hey!
He's just exhausted! But it's not because of his wounds!
Oh, Ivan-chan!
Ivan-chan?!
I made it! Thank you for helping both of us!
If you wanna thank someone, you better thank Mr. 2 Bon boy, not me!
I only nudged you along with my powers.
But him,
he was struggling alongside you for hours and hours and hours here!
He lost his voice and spewed up blood but he didn't stop!
He kept shouting "Hang in there!" "You have to live!" to you!
I think it somehow affected your recovery!
I see.
--What's wrong with him?
--Is he naked?!
Straw-chan, I come to rescue you!
In the name of friendship!
Who the hell is this guy all covered in blood?!
Earlier, I was...
I'm sorry that I ran!
How do you know this guy?
I'm his friend!
Straw-chan! I'm not gonna let you die!
Bon-chan, thank you! I'm really grateful!
Here are your hat and clothes. But you're not ready yet.
You need to rest for several days to be fully recovered.
I don't have time! I've already wasted too much!
Sorry, but can you look after Bon-chan? I'll be back for him later!
--Hey, hey!
--See? You're not completely well yet!
The paper is still pointing down! Ace must be downstairs!
By the way, where am I now?
What's that?
It's a Vivre Card, isn't it?
You're on a floor between level 5 and 6.
I bet that since you've recovered,
you wanna go to rescue your brother no matter what.
Well, it's your life! You can do whatever you want!
What about you, Ivan-chan? Are you gonna break out?
Bon-chan thought he'd help your butt get out of here.
Your butt?!
Can you guide me to Ace on your way out?
What did you just say? Bon boy came here to save me?
Oh, I didn't know that. That's really sweet of him.
But I don't need to be saved.
It's not time to break out yet!
I know what's going on in the world now.
The world is about to change with the Navy and the Whitebeard Pirates as major players!
But he's not gonna make a move yet!
He's the mastermind of all revolutionaries in the world and my comrade!
The revolutionary--Dragon!
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
Yes. When your father makes a move with his army,
then I'll reappear and enter the world again!
If I escaped now, I'd just end up on countless wanted lists around the world!
D-D-D-D... Dad?!
Did he say "my dad?!"
What?!
Dragon is...
...your dad?!
D-D-D-Don't be ridiculous!
You're a son of Dragon?! He has a son?!
Oh! I shouldn't have said anything.
I guess it's okay. Grandpa didn't keep it a secret.
Your father's name is...
...Monkey D. Dragon! He's a revolutionary!
I don't really know about him. I've never even seen his face.
What?!
This seems legitimate!
He doesn't seem to be the kind to lie and he's a new star in the world of pirates!
And I've just seen his extraordinary vital force!
He's not a normal man! So it's believable!
Where did you come from?!
I'm from the East Blue!
Dragon.
Whenever you go for some air,
you always face towards the same direction no matter where you are!
Do I? Why would you be so curious about such a thing?
I've never noticed.
Then, it must be a homing instinct like animals have.
Is your home in that direction?
You're thinking about your family in the east,
aren't you?
Don't be so inquisitive about my past, Ivan!
I'm sorry.
Oh no! If Straw boy is a son of Dragon for real, that means...
Inazuma, check to see when they'll take Ace boy away!
Yes, right away!
There isn't much time!
But the Vivre Card was pointing down which means that he's still here!
I'm gonna go to level 6 with Straw boy now!
What? Are you gonna show me the way?!
But, did you just say "level 6?" Isn't it 5?
It can't be! You're on level 5.5!
Whatever. Alright, let's go!
I wasn't paying attention! It didn't even occur to me!
If Straw boy is Dragon's son, so is Ace!
Is this why the Navy captured Ace?!
No, it can't be! There would be no point in it!
They don't wanna fight Whitebeard and Dragon at the same time!
What does the government truly want?!
In any case, it's time to make a move!
Okay, Bon-chan! I'll be back!
Straw boy!
Don't tell anyone casually about your birth!
Yeah, that's what I thought.
I'm a friend of your dad and one of the commanders of the Revolutionaries army!
That's why I was arrested!
So it's my duty to support you whether you like it or not!
I can't let my friend's son die before my eyes!
Tell all the people in the New Kama Land!
We're going to rescue Ace boy and try to break out of the prison!
--What are you saying all of the sudden?
--Isn't this a bit hasty?
Decisions must always be sudden!
If you wanna come with me, get ready to die,
prepare for action and wait for us here!
Alright! Let's do it!
I'll follow you, Ivan-sama, to the end!
It's a new beginning for New Kama!
Alright! Wait for me, Ace!
I'm coming for you!
What?!
His pulse...
...is fine!
That was a joke?!
Because the treatment has just shortened his life,
he must be exhausted still on some level!
Emporio...
...Energy Hormone!
It's a matter of adrenaline!
Now you have enough energy for a day!
You'll feel the after effects in several days but I guess it won't matter much at that point!
Vice Warden! Warden won't like it if he hears that you've been sitting there!
We'll be sure to tell him later!
You guys are so mean!
Mr. 2, Mr. 3, Buggy the Clown...
Are you sure that they got onto level 5?
Yes, his disguise was perfect!
But the only thing that they found on level 5 was the headdress covered in blood.
We assume that they took Straw Hat out of the cell
but ended up being eaten by the wolves.
I see.
I never thought that I'd wear this special order thing before I became the warden.
I still haven't brought down Magellan!
Don't say it so plainly!
If we get duped or beaten again,
both yours and the Warden's jobs are on the line!
My position, too?!
--Of course!
The Staircase to level 3 must be close!
Level 4 is a breeze!
I haven't seen any jailers at all! They're totally gone!
Let's make a game of it! It's the Buggy and 3 Adventures!
Don't stop suddenly!
Wait a minute!
It's a Surveillance Transponder Snail!
If it finds us, all our efforts will go to waste!
Thank you for noticing it, partner!
Let's go carefully from now on!
What is this?!
M-My eyes are itchy!
This must be Magellan's poison!
That poison that he used against Straw Hat is still in the air here!
Oh no!
The guards will see us through it!
--That was close.
THE ELEVATOR TO LEVEL 6
You were too late!
You're so strict, Domino.
You need to do your business quickly from now on!
That's impossible!
Here it comes again!
Just hold it!
No way!
We need to hand them the prisoner 9 am sharp at the front gate!
That's our mission!
If we can't make it, we'll ruin the honor of Impel Down!
THE FRONT GATE OF IMPEL DOWN
Listen! We'll take Portgaz D. Ace from here and get to...
...the Marineford--Navy Headquarters.
Until the very moment that we hand over the prisoner,
--I need you to pay full attention!
--Yes, sir!
To be prepared for any possibility, we'll convey him strictly with 5 ships...
...under the direction of 5 vice admirals! Do not fail!
Yes, sir!
I dunno why but I'm full of energy!
We gotta hurry! We don't wanna waste even a second!
There's no security here! So we can just run out in the open!
Nothing can stop us now!
What's that?!
Who are they?!
T-That looks like Ivankov! I thought that he was dead!
No way!
Outta my way!
Don't mess with me!
Death...
...Wink!
Inazuma, open it!
Okay!
They'll be monitoring us from now on!
Come and get me if you want!
We have an intruder!
They're at the staircase between level 5 and 6!
Oh! I know this big guy!
He was the king of queers--Ivankov who went missing years ago!
How could this be possible?!
How did he survive all these years?!
And this is the invader from yesterday
I thought that he was killed by the Warden!
And he's another missing prisoner!
A revolutionary from South Blue--Inazuma!
What's going on here?!
They're heading straight to level 6!
They want to save "Fire Fist" Ace!
Domino-san and Warden Magellan are also heading to level 6 now!
They'll bump into each other!
They are all alive?!
Vice Warden!
Activate passageway traps now!
Call jailers on level 6 and have them clear for action!
They need to hold on until Sadie-chan and the demon guards get there!
And report this to Warden Magellan and all floors!
--That's all! Hurry up!
--Yes, sir!
I've never seen Vice Warden getting so serious!
Maybe it's an imposter again!
We have to get them!
My job is on the line!
No, he's the real one!
We can make it! We can make it!
I'll be there right away, Ace!
Alright, Portgaz D. Ace!
We will take you to Marineford...
...where the execution ground is!
The public execution of Ace is in...
...6 hours!
Luffy finally makes it to the
lowest level of Impel Down, level 6.
However, Ace has already been taken away,
and the cell is empty.
Luffy tries to follow Ace but he's held up by Hannyabal's traps!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ace's Convoy Begins!
Battle on the Lowest Floor Level 6!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!