Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in
which a winner will get the Flare-Flare Fruit
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
as the prize - and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law who's
been captured by Doflamingo.
Special Attack: Green Star - Platanus...
...Shuriken!
"A Fateful Encounter!
Kyros and King Riku!"
Usoland!
Usoland!!
I-I did it!
There's only one girl left to beat!
I don't wanna go rough on a little girl
but I've got no choice!
I have to put the Tatababasco grape
into Sugar's mouth somehow!
Trebol.
I can't believe you got
beaten by a guy like him.
You idiot. Drop dead.
I'm not dead yet, you little shit!
Wh-What's with this guy?!
Hey, hey! If you'd just kept running,
you might have survived!
But you took the trouble
to come back to be killed!
THE ROYAL PALACE 2ND FLOOR - THE SUIT CHAMBER
There was a report that you,
sir, were on the 1st floor!
Huh? What're you talking about?
Does it mean somebody who
looked like him was there?
Have you ever seen anybody
who looks like me in the palace?
King Riku-sama!
This sword looks good.
If I can turn back into a human,
I wanna use this!
My father was fighting
in the Colosseum today.
What? Is it true?
I couldn't believe Doflamingo's abdication
was a false report.
It was just this morning
and we all lost patience.
King Riku-sama was fighting
in the Colosseum?!
A boy committed a murder!
Two people got killed in a squabble in the slum!
The boy is now...
Stop resisting!
A BOY IN THE SLUM - KYROS (15 YEARS OLD)
How can he move like that?!
We have no choice but to shoot him!
--No way! He's just a boy!
--But...
King Riku-sama!
King Riku-sama! What are you doing?!
It's dangerous!
Although he's just a boy,
he's an infamous thug!
I don't care if you're the king or not!
Whoever approaches me will...
The king is in danger! Open fire!
Wait! Don't shoot!
Put your guns down!
B-But...
I heard you fought dozens of hooligans
on your own.
And more than the half of them got injured
and two of them got killed.
They ganged up on my best friend
and killed him!
So I was just getting revenge for him!
Are you a beast?
Say whatever you like!
A royal person like you can't understand!
He was the only person I trusted
in the whole world!
He was like a brother to me!
Your name is Kyros, isn't it?
Stay away from him, King Riku-sama!
King Riku-sama!
Come with me!
A 15-year-old murderer - Kyros!
He's gonna fight against an experienced gladiator!
This Colosseum is a sacred place!
A murderer like you doesn't belong here!
Teach him a lesson!
The battle starts!
Are you gonna keep looking
at the sword, brat?
The sword's blade may be blunt,
but prepare to get some of your limbs broken!
I-I can't believe it! Kyros wins!
The winner is the 15-year-old
murderer - Kyros!
--It's not over yet!
--That's enough! Stop!
He's so talented!
If the blade wasn't blunt, he
would've killed his opponent!
Barbarism looks a lot
like a talent here, huh?
How is Kyros doing?
He nearly killed all the convict
gladiators in his room.
He hasn't eaten for six days
and just keeps shouting "Call King Riku."
Dammit!
What's wrong, Kyros?
King Riku! What are you gonna do with me?!
If you're gonna execute me, do it already!
Shoot me or hang me or whatever you like!
Do you want to die so badly?
Or are you regretting what you did?
Regret? I thought you were different
and you understood me!
Kill me! Just kill me!
The gladiatorial contest that
you fought in the other day
wasn't just a deadly competition or a show.
It has been going on for several centuries
in this country.
It's a sacred event in which
fighters discipline their mind
and hone their sword skill.
Do you want to become a gladiator?
A gladiator? Me?
King Riku-sama is planning
to release you on parole
once you win 100 matches in
as much time as it takes.
FOUR MONTHS LATER
Kick the murderer's ass!
Bring down Kyros!
Kyros wins 20 consecutive matches!
He's unbelievably strong!
Kyros wins 50 consecutive matches!
Kyros wins 100 out of 100 matches!
Even the star gladiator couldn't do anything!
He finally won his freedom
in such a short period of time!
How could anyone be that strong?!
Don't come out, murderer!
--Hey!
--Think about it!
If someone like him gets released,
he may kill more people again!
--She's right.
--Uh-huh.
Yeah! Don't come back
on the street, murderer!
--Don't release him!
--Keep fighting until you die!
You're gonna stay?
I won't go out where people don't want me.
Since when did you want to become
the person other people wanted?
Shut up!
People like beasts...
...as long as they stay...
...in a cage!
Even if...
...I get out of the cage,
there is no place...
...for me to go back!
There is nowhere for me to belong out there!
His 200th win!
--Somebody, bring down Kyros!
--Defeat Kyros!
His 300th win!
Nobody can stop Kyros!
The heroes have been brought
down one after another!
Finally!
Finally - an unprecedented 1000th victory!
HIS 4TH YEAR AT THE COLOSSEUM
Kyros-sama!
Way to go, Kyros!
The ire of the crowd
turned to adulation before I knew it.
However...
You're here again.
--Kyros.
--Go away!
You don't understand!
No matter where I go,
I'll be a beast...
...who killed men for the rest of my life!
I wish...
...everybody would forget about me!
A mysterious tough man who
came into sudden prominence,
going by "Ricky", is fighting Kyros!
Go, Kyros!
The odds are for Kyros who will mark
his 3000th win if he wins this match
but Ricky isn't giving up an inch!
Whoa! Ricky landed a blow against Kyros!
Kyros has never taken a single hit
from an opponent before!
Kyros wins!
He won 3000 out of 3000 in nine years!
He's never lost!
The living legend - Kyros!
The word "invincible" truly only fits to this man!
Yeah, Kyros!
Why did you enter secretly,
King Riku-sama?!
I became quite strong after you
taught me how to fight, didn't I?
But you lowered your guard
when you noticed it was me.
You're not such a "beast" after all.
Isn't that enough now?
You've spent your life locked away
in this "cage" for nine years.
You need to leave now.
There's something I need you to do.
Kyros.
Rather than regretting
what you did in the past,
you can save many lives from now on.
That's one way for you to live.
Yes, sir!
Kyros! We'll be counting on you!
A YEAR LATER
Kyros! Thank you always for your service!
THE COMMANDER OF THE DRESSROSA KING RIKU ARMY
KYROS (25 YEARS OLD)
Oh! Kyros-sama!
Protect me!
Girls love you so much, huh?!
Kyros-sama!
But you're a murderer!
I don't understand why Father-sama
lets you in to the palace!
P-Princess-sama!
Big Sis, don't!
You can't bring up his old pain!
I can't believe he even assigned you
to be the commander of the righteous army!
Big Sis!
Even if you can fool the whole
nation, you can't fool me!
THE PRINCESS OF DRESSROSA
- SCARLET (15 YEARS OLD)
You'll reveal your true colors someday!
Don't come near me and my sister!
Don't touch us!
Understood?!
But Big Sis, he's kind of...
THE SECOND PRINCESS (THE YOUNGER SISTER) -
VIOLA (10 YEARS OLD)
Hey! Don't look into his mind!
His mind is corrupted!
But I'm responsible for protecting you two!
No thanks!
--Lady Scarlet has been kidnapped!
--They were pirates!
--What happened to her bodyguards?!
--They all got beaten up!
--What?!
--What should we do?!
--Just calm down!
--Don't touch me!
Nobody's gonna come rescue you!
How about we get a lot of
money from King Riku as ransom
and just sell her?!
That's a good idea! She's a real princess!
We can make a good price!
Lady Scarlet!
Kyros!
Who are you?!
Stay close behind me!
You bastards!
Are you all right, Lady Scarlet?
I-I'm sorry!
I-I touched you!
Kyros! I was scared!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
Big Sis is cooking something!
What's gotten into her?!
Oh no!
What did you say?!
You wanna resign as my daughters' bodyguard?!
Why're you saying that all of a sudden?!
Oh, well... I mean...
Don't tell me you're in love with Scarlet?
What?!
N-No, I'm not! I swear...
Kyros!
I am, sir.
The greatest hero in the
history of the Colosseum
and the commander of the
army. And the princess.
I know each individual will
celebrate your marriage
but social constraints
won't allow your criminal record.
That's how public life works.
Father-sama!
If I can't marry him, I'd rather die!
Lady Scarlet...
It was a sudden illness.
I'm sure she would've become
a great queen someday.
Scarlet. As of today,
you're not a member of the royal family.
People think you're dead.
Yes.
It feels like I'm repaying your kindness
with ingratitude, King Riku-sama.
It's unforgivable!
If it were anyone else but you.
Kyros! I've never heard a story like this!
Thank you, sir!
Her name is Rebecca.
Kyros, hold her in your arms.
She's your daughter!
I shouldn't touch such an innocent thing!
My hands are tainted!
I don't wanna taint her!
Your father is a strange man, Rebecca.
You're like an angel, Rebecca!
I'll be watching over you!
I'll always be by your side!
Peek-a-boo! Your grandpa is here!
Grandpa!
Rebecca! You got big again!
Father-sama, take off your disguise!
Kyros!
Gloves, gloves!
How cute she is! How cute she is!
You're crying again!
I'd never expected that
I could have such happiness.
But it didn't last long.
That was 10 years ago...
What's going on?!
King Riku-sama!
10 years ago, the Toy Soldier was tragically torn
from his loved ones!
Shouldering the burden of
everybody's expectations,
Usopp fights Trebol to the full extent of his power!
Will he bring a miracle?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Operation Failed! Usoland the Hero Dies?!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!