Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago.
And in order to go on to the
next stage - the New World,
they set sail for the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level!
You guys!
Set sail!!
I give you an option.
Do you wanna enlist under our
banner - the New Fish-Man Pirates?
Or do you refuse?
If you refuse, we'll sink you.
No way! Stupid!
Here we go! Coup de Burst!
The bubble here is a double structure!
We're gonna run into one
more bubble! Hold on tight!
Water?!
The current is strong!
Help... me...
Can't breathe...
We have 4 Devil Fruit eaters but...
Reach...
...out!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Damn! I can't swim against the current!
Where am I?
Oh, Luffy-chin!
I'm glad that you're okay!
This is a coral apartment in the sea.
The dorm is at the very
bottom so the rent is cheap.
We're here, on the surface!
Hey, Camie!
Everybody!
I found it!
This is my All Blue!
I see.
Straw Hat Luffy finally got this far.
What should we do, Boss?
Bring him...
...here!
"Excitement Blow-out!
Sanji's Life Under Threat!"
Even if the Straw Hats survived, they're humans,
they can't live in the water.
Then they must be somewhere above the water?
Let's just find them!
Now, what should I do?
It's hard to believe that
this place is in the deep sea.
Super!
Hey, Nami! I'm glad that you're okay!
I just thought I was gonna die because of you!
Robin!
Robin.
Nami?
Are you alright?
Where are we? The Fish-Man Island?
Yeah, probably. Franky is scouting it out now.
Oh, you're up, Robin!
--Thanks to you.
--Did you see Luffy and the others?
No, I can't find them.
We just got together again...
But there's no need to worry!
They wouldn't die so easily.
He's right.
We have to find the Sunny too
but first, should we check
with some inhabitants?
I found a town nearby.
Sanji-chan!
I'm on my way!
I'll...
...live...
...here!
Sanji-chan, you're so funny!
He seems to have recovered after all.
By his willpower alone?
I wanna swim like you guys.
Luffy-chin, you can swim with a bubble on.
Really?
Yeah, any craftsman in the city
can make one for you right away.
I'm glad because if he has a nosebleed now,
we don't have blood for a transfusion.
And Sanji's blood type is very rare.
Huh? That's not good, is it?
Hey, Camie.
There is somebody that I really
wanna see on the Fish-Man Island.
Who is it? The Mermaid Princess?
Nope.
It's Jimbei!
Boss Jimbei?
Hey Luffy, you mean Jimbei the Warlord?!
No, he resigned during the war so he's the former Warlord.
Yeah, he's my friend!
What's up with you?
You know the pirate empress, too.
When Ace died 2 years ago, I didn't lose heart...
...thanks to him!
You brat!
Can't you see things clearly now?!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
I still have my friends!
I wanna see Jimbei!
See you at the Fish-Man Island in 2 years!
I'm looking forward to the day
when you and your friends visit us!
We made a promise to meet
again on this island.
Oh yeah, I read in the newspaper
that you were with Jimbei.
Yoo-hoo!
Where's Jimbei?
Um, Boss is not on the island now.
Huh?
He resigned from the Warlords
during the war 2 years ago.
So the former members of the Fish-Man
Pirates could no longer stay here
and they left with Boss Jimbei.
What?! So I can't see him here?
It's a long story. But the war had a
lot of effects on this island too...
--Camie!
Camie!
--A ship is coming!
--It might be!
--The royal family's ship!
--Maybe no one's on it!
I'm sure somebody is!
Who's on it, Medaka-chin sisters?
We don't know yet.
--You don't often see the royal family's ship.
--They seldom come here.
Maybe they're coming to catch Luffy-chin
and the others for illegal entry!
So what?
What?
You guys need to hide!
Sanji-chan, this way!
Okay!
RYUGU PALACE
Is it the royal family's gondola?
You think so?
--It is!
--Maybe!
--I bet so!
--So what?
But it can't be somebody
from the royal family!
They don't bother coming all the
way to this corner of the island.
The Neptune 3 brothers-sama are here!
Hello, girls of the cove.
RYUGU KINGDOM THE NEPTUNE 3 BROTHERS
I want to ask something.
--Princes!
--What brought you here?
Princes?
No, Sanji-chan!
Hide here and stay still.
What is this? Marshmallow?
Ah, no, it's not.
The milky sweet smell.
Don't know why but it makes me feel comfortable.
Is it a fruit from the
Fish-Man Island? Sniff, sniff.
Hey, what is...
I received a report of an illegal entry.
FIRST SON - FUKABOSHI (SHARK MERMAN)
Didn't they come here?
If you've seen them, tell me-fa-so-la-ti-do!
SECOND SON - RYUBOSHI (OARFISH MERMAN)
If you haven't seen them, that's fine-mi-re-do!
Moonfish! Shake, shake!
THIRD SON - MANBOSHI (MOONFISH MERMAN)
I wanna stay here and play!
We haven't seen anybody.
Are they that important?
That you princes have
to come all the way here?
Well, I'm not sure if they're
who I think they are yet.
He's not sure-mi-re-do!
I can't hold it any longer!
Everybody, let's dance together!
What's going on?
Hey, look! They're the
princes of Neptune's army!
Why're they here?
What a pain in the ass. What should we do?
Let's see how things go.
Hmmm. Okay. Thank you very much.
We'll check somewhere else.
Sorry to bother you when you're having fun.
Let's dance another time!
Sorry for the bother-so-fa-mi-re-do!
Anytime!
Maybe the border guards
were just seeing things.
They're leaving.
Sniff, sniff!
Sniff!
--Sanji!
--What is that?!
Sanji-chan!
That was too much blood! He's in danger!
He couldn't hold it! All that
pent-up excitement exploded!
Sanji!
That's...
No mistaking him.
The pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
--Ammo Knights!
--Yes, sir!
Damn!
They look all the same!
Doesn't feel like I've advanced even a little!
Are you the Pirate Hunter
Zoro from the Straw Hats?
Yeah, so what?
There they are! Straw Hat and the others.
What should we do? They'll catch them first.
But we don't wanna cause any
trouble with Neptune's army.
Wait a minute!
We're sorry about the illegal entry!
But you can't arrest us now!
Can somebody donate blood now?!
If nothing is done,
our friend is gonna die within an hour!
His blood type is S RH negative.
It's rare but does anybody here share the same blood type?
Or are Fish-Men and Mermaids'
blood totally different?
Chopper-chin.
We don't have time! Anyone?!
This is... This is the dumbest way to die!
Somebody please! I beg you!
Give blood to Sanji!
Luffy-chin, Chopper-chin!
Mermaids and Fish-Men blood
are the same as humans so we can donate blood!
But...
Those humans are talking nonsense!
Those guys with sea monsters!
Prince Fukaboshi, that's Hammond
from the Fish-Man District.
There is nobody on this island who would
give blood to such lowly creatures as humans.
If somebody does,
he risks the Punishment of the Dark Night from human haters.
Punishment?
He can just keep losing
blood helplessly and die!
There is this old law in our kingdom.
Donating blood to humans is prohibited.
What?!
Make no mistake!
You humans set the rule first!
You people have a long history
of fearing us as monsters
and refused to get your blood mixed-up!
That's why Fisher Tiger,
the hero of the Fish-Man Island, died.
Fisher... Tiger?
He risked his own life to
free slaves of all races
but after a bloody war,
he lost his life although he could've
survived if he had a transfusion!
Those heartless humans
refused to give blood so he died!
Straw Hat, here is what I want you to do.
Just give up on your crewmember's life
and come to the Fish-Man District with us!
The captain of the New Fish-Man Pirates
- Hordy Jones is expecting you guys.
Shut up!
Hey, I don't know about the law but please!
Isn't there anyone with S RH negative?!
I'll do anything to repay you!
Just as long as you save his life now!
I said "It's no use"!
Camie!
If you don't comply...
Second Gear!
...I'll take you by force!
Trawl Net!
I told you that we weren't gonna join you!
...Jet...
Pistol!
Luffy, a monster behind you!
Hammond and the others got...
The monster gave up without fighting!
Cool!
What was it? Luffy-chan's unbelievable!
Impressive.
Luffy-chin and everybody!
Bring Sanji-chin, too! Let's go to the town!
It's the Ryugu!
There are many humans at the
harbor of the town! Hurry up!
Okay!
Alright, we're ready! Camie, let's go!
Uh-huh! Please, Ryugu-chin,
take us to the town!
Mosu!
Hey you, wait! The Ryugu is Princes'...
I'm sorry! I'll bring it back to
you as soon as we save Sanji-chin!
They're leaving!
We don't have a ride home-fa-mi-re-do!
Hmm.
I'm sorry. If my blood type
matched, I wouldn't refuse.
You don't have to apologize.
It all started because of his lecherous feelings.
Look. He's still smiling a little.
...And at the same time, it's nice and bouncy...
Sanji, that's enough!
Don't think about anything!
You're in a delicate state!
You and Hachi were discriminated
against at Sabaody 2 years ago
so I guess it really runs deep.
I can't believe Sanji's dirty
mind caused such a big issue!
Yeah, and even if we get to the town,
I don't know if we can find a donor right away.
What?
We haven't had that many
human visitors for a month.
You guys are our first visitors in a while.
Why? I thought this was the famous scoop.
Yes, it is a famous spot.
We don't know why.
They say maybe somebody
is standing in the voyagers' way.
Somebody powerful is up to something
- that's the talk of the Kingdom.
That was no good, ladies.
Why were you hiding the pirates?
I'm sorry, Prince Fukaboshi.
They were Camie's friends.
And they were good people and we
didn't want them to be arrested.
I hope Sanji-chan will be fine.
You ladies mistook us.
He's a well-known pirate,
he didn't need to go through immigration.
Because we know his identity.
We were looking for them for
another reason-re-mi-fa!
Oh, is it so?
And we were unable to deliver
the message from Jimbei, as well.
Sanji's overexcitement has put him in danger.
Luffy and his crew follow Camie to the Mermaid Cafe
in search of a blood donor to save his life.
There, they meet a gifted psychic, Madam Sharley,
and she predicts a terrible future for Luffy's crew!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Fish-Man Island Will Be Annihilated?!
Sharley's Prophecy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!