Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
They freed the toys who had been forced to
labor as slaves
but Doflamingo trapped everybody in the country in the Birdcage.
Now, let's bring an end to everything.
I-It's started...!
I'll pay 100 million berries for each star rating!
And put prices on the heads of Luffy and 11 others.
Wait, Hajrudin! If you kill Straw Hat,
you'll get a lot of money!
That's just a pittance!
I almost had my pride stolen
but was saved by God Usopp!
I can truly win my pride back,
only by repaying my debt!
--I will take down Doflamingo!
--No, I will!
--No, it's me!
--No, me!
I said "Go away"!
I will kick Mingo's ass!
It's massive! We're finished!
We have nowhere to run!
Gum-Gum...
...Grizzly Magnum!
What?! That's the stone man?!
This is the first time we've seen him
in a human-like figure!
I'll see you later!
Yeah, leave it up to me!
Our captain has no business with
a worthless rock like you!
I'm all you've got. Live with it!
You soprano-voiced dumb-ass!
"A Shocking Confession!
Law's Soulful Vow!"
Pica-sama stopped moving
after his head fell off!
What happened?!
Hey! The monster stopped moving! Is he dead?!
No, I don't think so.
But, whatever happened to him,
if he's not gonna throw those annoying punches,
now is the chance!
I will bring down Doflamingo!
--It's me!
--No, me!
Those jerks are coming again!
Stop them!
Don't let them get to the Palace!
Bring out more worthwhile guys to fight!
I-It's impossible.
We can't stop the group of fighters from the Colosseum.
Oh! How vigorous they are!
I can't believe they still wanna mess with the Young Master!
So reckless-in!
That's right! Groups of Navy soldiers led by
Fujitora are coming together in front of the Palace!
"G"roups of Navy soldiers! There's the "G"!
Bastille's unit will join us soon.
Half of all Navy soldiers are already
in front of the Palace!
I knew it was Straw Hat and the others
that stopped Pica-sama.
There are four different groups or individuals
approaching the Palace.
First, the group of tough men from around the New World,
who fought in the Colosseum.
Second, the former commander of the King Riku Army and...
...the strongest man in the history of the Colosseum - Kyros.
Just give yourself up, Kyros!
It's only a matter of time
before we're all dead
if we don't catch you all!
We need you 12 criminals to
sacrifice yourselves!
And, third, No.2 of the Straw Hats - Pirate Hunter Zoro!
Fourth, Straw Hat Luffy and the traitor - Law!
That's it! Keep going, Moocy!
--Yeah! Go, bull!
--Bull!
Guys, how much longer are you gonna stay on?!
Just get off!
I know you're kidding, Straw Hat-san!
I don't see Señor anywhere.
He was with us just a while ago.
I think he went to look for that pervert-in!
Pervert?
Alright, here I am!
Per...
...vert!
SMILE factory! Ow!
Now, break open, door to the factory!
Radical Bea...
I know that crappy attack won't even harm the factory but...
...I just came to finish up my business with you.
I still have to fight an enemy?!
That's what men do, boy.
Oh! Señor!
Please, Kyros!
Come on out and surrender yourself!
We're gonna come get you if you don't!
We're not doing this for money!
If nothing is done, we all have to kill each other until no one's left!
We have no choice!
We just wanna bring an end to this nightmare
as soon as possible!
You want to bring an end to this fight!
I don't blame you for your decision but...
...that means I need to get going even faster!
--Shoot!
--Don't let him get away!
There's something that I need to do, too!
You're doing great, Moocy! You're amazing!
We'll get to Mingo before anyone else like this!
Wait for me, Mingo!
I'm not gonna let them do it!
I'm gonna beat the hell out of you!
What are you guys looking at?
Straw Hat-san, your friend...
He stayed all by himself to
fight such a monster...
How manly!
Oh, you mean Zoro?
He'll be alright! He's not gonna lose!
What?!
I'm gonna kill you, you bastard!
Boy, your voice is so squeaky and annoying.
It makes my ears tickle.
Damn you!
Go to hell!
What are you doing, soprano-voiced old man?
He made a vow! He'll never be defeated!
At any cost!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya.
I know the only way for us to survive now is to kill him.
I've made up my mind, too.
The plan that I suggested to you guys was
to take down Doflamingo indirectly.
But, to be honest, I...
...want to hurt him directly, too!
I was beaten earlier but I won't be this time!
13 years ago, there was a person I adored
and Doflamingo killed him!
His name is Corazon.
The former top executive of
the Doflamingo Family!
What?! Was he a member of his clan?
Yes, he was.
He also saved my life and was...
...Doflamingo's...
...biological young brother!
Luffy-senpai!
Luffy-senpai! Where are you?
Huh? Luffy-senpai's not here!
Of course, he's not.
What do you mean "Of course"?!
Luffy wouldn't stay in the same place
even for five minutes.
Oh! Freedom! Whew!
That's how the King of the Pirates should be!
What is that stone monster?!
King Riku-sama!
Why is the Royal Palace up there?!
I found it!
Oh! Viola-san!
Viola.
I found it, Father-sama!
The key to Trafalgar Law's handcuffs!
I finally found it with my Clairvoyance!
I have to deliver it to them somehow!
Wait, Viola!
Why are they so important to you?!
They're pirates!
Yes, they're unlawful men - who will break
this country's deceptive peace!
Father-sama, I decided to trust them,
the Straw Hat Pirates!
The World Government gave him the title of the Warlord
and that pirate Doflamingo reigned this country with terror,
causing us so much pain!
I don't want the help of the Navy, that was supposed to be
supporting justice, or the Government after all these years!
They can't hear them!
The voices of the people who fell victim because of them!
The angry voices of this country!
People in authority often only hear
what they want to!
At least, the words of Straw Hat and the others are humane
and they take actions
out of the goodness of their hearts!
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
So stay with my friends!
Take a good look at this country!
If I stop now, what's gonna happen to it?!
King Riku-sama! King Riku-sama!
Take a look at him!
You're the Five-star man, aren't you?!
That's right!
His name is Usoland aka God Usopp!
This man risked his life
and broke the spell of toys
that had been
overshadowing this country for a decade!
He's our hero!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Usoland! Usoland!
His bravery moved us to tears!
Really, really, really,
we were so touched by it!
He's a superhero!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
And Luffyland is the superhero's captain!
King Riku-sama!
The Straw Hats aka Usolanders are Dressrosa's hope!
Even though they're pirates,
we're gonna trust them to the end!
This is great!
It's the Straw Hats' unforgettable moving scene!
How lucky I am to be here!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Look, Viola-san,
can I go deliver the key to Lucy?!
Rebecca!
I can't just stay here and wait!
Let me do it!
Rebecca...
Alright, let's do it!
Let's go see Luffy-senpai!
I'm coming with you, of course! Count on me!
Rebecca! You're a criminal in Doflamingo's game!
If you go down to the town,
--they won't leave you alone!
--I'm gonna be okay!
All right. Just be careful.
Uh-huh!
--Cub-san!
--Yeah!
Everybody!
You guys?!
If you are planning on going,
let's use the rooftops!
Cub-san and I will go along with you!
So don't worry!
--Rooftops?!
--Yes!
Inhel, can I leave the factory in your hands?
No problem!
According to the scouting unit,
Fraland is fighting Señor Pink now!
Along with Fraland, we Tontattas will all work together
to take back Princess Mancherie and our people!
Uh-huh!
I'll see you guys later!
Everybody! We don't have that much time!
I'll see you all again here on the King's Plateau!
Let's go now!
Yeah!
Straw Hat Luffy... What a strange man.
Even in this desperate situation,
everyone finds hope in the Straw Hats without them realizing.
Pirates, huh?
--Straw Hat-san, we're almost at the first level!
--There are so many enemies there!
--That's…
--Something's coming this way!
Yeah! We're the first to arrive!
No one's here yet!
Well done, Moocy!
--It's Straw Hat Luffy!
--Shoot! Shoot!
Gum-Gum...
...Fire Salute!
All right! Keep up the pace, Moocy!
Let's go!
Luffy and the others keep making smooth progress!
But the Navy led by Fujitora starts chasing,
and when they close in on Luffy and the others,
one man stands in the Navy's way on his own!
The strongest forces of the Revolutionary Army
and the Navy finally face off!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Big Collision! Chief of Staff - Sabo vs. Admiral Fujitora!”
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!