Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Well... you wanted to see me...
right, pirate lad?
I came to hear the truth!
Last night, I saw Nico Robin with my own eyes.
And... she is one of you.
That's the truth.
Was it really Robin?!
Don't say a word.
Your words no longer mean anything.
I called you in here...
...because I have a favor to ask.
Let me see Nico Robin again now!
Extra! Extra!
The culprits for Mr. Iceberg's
attack were the Straw Hat pirates!
We, Water-Water Newspaper, will buy
any information on their sightings!
I'll say it again. Let me see Nico Robin.
That's not possible.
We don't know where she is.
Gunfire!
It came from the bedroom!
Iceberg-san!
Y-You're okay...
Yeah...
I bet on a silly hope that I might
be able to get closer to the truth.
Capture... all the Straw Hats!
Of course!
Hey, Luffy...
Were you able to talk to
Iceberg-san by any chance?
Yeah. He said he really saw Robin.
Can't be...! Why would Robin
do something like that?
I refuse to believe it!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Eternal Farewell? Nico Robin,
the Woman Who Draws Darkness"
We're here! We're here!
Grandma Kokoro! Hurry! Hurry!
Don't get carried away.
Water Seven... It's been a while...
Grandma! Hurry! Hurry!
Okay, okay.
Wearing a mask is prohibited today
when you get on board the sea train.
Please show me your ticket and your face.
This is my own face! My own face!
Hm?
Hey, you...
Oh! Kokoro-san! Hello!
What's all the fuss about?
Yes... We're after the
Straw Hats who're the culprits
in Iceberg-san's attempted assassination.
Iceberg's assassination? Hm?
What's the matter? Ah...
These people...
N... Nooo!!
I'm falling! I'm falling!
I'm falling!
All right! We've landed!
Boy, I'm exhausted.
Don't "We've landed" me! I thought I'd die!
What else could we have done?!
It was you who said that
we couldn't use the elevator
because we didn't want them to find us!
Even so, you didn't have to jump off!
We're not that shipwright with a square nose!
I... I'm sorry.
Well, fine. At least it did get us down.
If it was okay, then don't hit me!
But... this may be kinda bad.
Bad? What's bad?
This island's geography and the weather.
With this much wind blowing,
if the atmospheric pressure drops,
a typhoon might come through here tonight.
This town is called the City of Water.
In other words, it can be a weak point
that could easily lead to flood damage.
So? What about it?
Well... It bothers me a little,
so I'll check into it later.
Anyway, let's go back to the inn.
Oh, welcome.
Yow! How's it going, Blueno?!
Is it going super?!
I think we're doing good.
What do you mean, "I think"?!
You sure are an indecisive guy!
Give me the usual! Fill them up!
You got money?
Just refill them! Cola!
To think that you run a bar
with such a stingy notion
that you take money from your customers...!
We've got money.
We've got a million Berries
left over from shopping.
What?!
We've got that much money from yesterday?!
How shameful! How uncool!
To think that I didn't spend it all yesterday...!
Now, give it to me!
Yow! You guys! You're lucky!
All your alcohol is on me!
Drink as much as you like!
Whoa! That's our Franky! You're generous!
You're the man! The face of the
Water Seven underworld! Thanks!
Whoa! Awesome!
Hey, there's more on the floor over there!
Hey, Blueno! Where's my cola?!
Hurry up, already!
Looks like you're doing well, Franky.
Hm?
Old hag Kokoro! That was you?!
I thought it was a statue of a monster!
Hey, is it okay to get a
refill for my juice, Franky?!
This is a bar. It's not a place for kids!
You're doing well, right?
Huh?! Okay, then. Suit yourself.
All right! Juice!
Well, I'm doing well, but I'm
feeling gloomy. I feel terrible.
I'm feeling terrible this week,
thanks to that damn pirate!
Here's the refilled cola! Thanks for waiting!
Yeah, took you long enough!
Fuel! Fuel!
Here it comes! Here it comes! Oh, yeah!
Super!
I've revived! That jerk! Next time
I see him, I'll beat him up!
By the way, old hag, why are you here?
Aqua Laguna is coming.
Oh? Is that right? No wonder the wind is strong.
Are you done getting your house ready?
Well, my house is gone.
I've got nothing that could sink,
so I have no worries.
I was going to have a drink with Iceberg,
but I heard he got shot.
Yeah, sounds like it.
They say it was the pirates' doing.
Galley-La and the townspeople
are furious right now.
Pirates' doing?
Do you seriously think that's the case?
You sound like you know something.
Don't say whatever comes to mind, old hag.
Iceberg has been getting nagged all this
time by the World Government, right?
Huh? Then, what? Are you saying
that official, Corgy, did it?
That tubby isn't an assassin type!
No... Shadowy incidents are the work of CP9.
Do you know about it, Blueno?
Just heard some rumors.
Geez... Common folk sure do like to believe
rumors of things like nonexistent organizations.
How foolish... It does exist.
But they never show themselves, since their
unit works secretly in the shadows.
Where's that confidence coming from?
Do you know something?
I heard about it over there.
Hey, that's just a rumor, then!
Don't mess with--
It always being a rumor is the scary part.
They eliminate people without anyone noticing.
If you meddle with them, you're dead meat.
Thanks. The job we had
to do yesterday went well.
Well done, Nico Robin...
That was a piece of cake.
Although naturally you're now
being pursued by the whole town.
Yeah.
But that's just temporary.
What's important is... tonight.
We'll infiltrate Iceberg's
residence one more time.
If worst comes to worst, it's okay
to eliminate all the evidence.
Among the disciples of this
Tom guy who originally had it,
Iceberg is the only one currently alive.
No matter how much he plays innocent,
in the name of CP9, we'll take
it away tonight for sure.
Bear in mind that this is a mission for justice.
Following the Aqua Laguna warning
issued for the entire island,
all the shipbuilding factory docks
on the shipbuilding island
will be opened as evacuation centers.
Large crowds are expected,
so please evacuate ahead of time.
In addition, since Dock #1 is
currently in a dangerous state...
Okay, I'll put the iron board on.
You guys have everything you need?
Yes, we do. Let's evacuate to the shipyard.
Daddy, hurry up!
Hurry up!
Well, hold on a bit. I'd better
fill the gap good with hempen.
If the inside of our house gets flooded,
everything will be ruined.
Hey, tie that side, too!
Hey, the wind is starting to get strong!
Get ready for waves soon!
Guys! If we're taking our time,
assassin pirates will show up too this time!
That's scary!
Where did he disappear to?!
I'm pretty sure he came this way.
He should still be around!
Okay, you guys go search over there.
Got it!
What the hell is going on?
Why am I being chased after? I don't get it!
So this is the reason they've
been chasing after me!
Assassination culprits?
This bites. I can't even go
back to the inn like this.
Ah... Who is it over there?!
This way! I found a suspicious guy here!
Are you sure, landlord?
Yes. Those pirates have been
staying at this inn since last night.
They were there until just a bit ago.
They were here?!
Yes. Since they've still got a
lot of luggage in their room,
they might come back.
Okay, then! You guys, stay here.
The rest of you, let's go
search this area together!
Listen, make sure you leave
no stone unturned to find them!
Yeah!
Hey, there's no one here!
Is this really their ship?
There's no mistake about it! Look!
That's the Straw Hats' pirate flag.
I bet they've already abandoned it.
This ship is all beat up.
How was it? Did you find them?
No, they aren't here!
There isn't much stuff left inside the ship.
This ship definitely is abandoned.
Let's go look someplace else.
Who were they?
Is something happening in town?
--Did you find them?
--No.
Dammit! Where are they?!
Hey, Luffy.
Hm? What is it, Nami?
Do you think everyone's okay?
Craftsmen are everywhere in town.
I think Chopper and Sanji-kun are okay,
since their faces are still unknown, but...
At any rate, let's hurry!
Yeah.
The sea train is still in service...
Looks like the afternoon train has already left,
but there's another one that
departs at night in this bad weather?
11 PM, leaving for Enies Lobby...
The sea train is pretty impressive.
Hey! Any information on the pirates?!
No. We've got nothing.
If we capture even one of those three
whose faces are known and squeeze him,
the rest of the gang will be identified.
Hurry up! Before the waves get high!
I wonder if Robin got on the sea train.
If she did, things can't get any worse.
When Water Seven is
already too big to handle...
I wonder if... I did something
to upset her at the bookstore.
You dummy... There's no way that's the case.
Oh, hey, excuse me.
Have you seen a pretty woman like her?
Oh, that... The pretty woman who's 20
years older than in that picture, right?
If I had, I would've told either the paper
company or Galley-La immediately.
But to think she's an assassin...
What a surprise, huh?
Well, it's fine if you wanna look for
the culprits, but you should evacuate soon.
Or you'll be swallowed by Aqua Laguna.
Well then, see ya.
Things are going wrong for all of us, too...
I wonder if Luffy and the others are okay.
Luffy's fine. The one I'm
worried about is Nami-san.
At any rate, the town is becoming quite empty.
The wind is gradually getting stronger, too.
People have started evacuating.
Dammit...
Hey, Robin-chan! Where'd you go?!
This scent... Could it be...?
Chopper, what's the matter?!
Hey, Chopper?!
Hey! Wait!
It's close!
Hey! I said wait! What's the matter?!
She's here.
Hey, Chopper! Chopper!
Whoa! Oops!
H-Hey, are you okay?!
Chopper! Are you okay?!
Are you hurt?
Geez, don't be reckless!
What on earth is going on...
Starting to run so sudden... ly...
I knew she'd be here.
--Robin!
--Robin-chan!
Wh-Where have you been?!
We looked all over for you!
Everyone's worried about you!
Now, let's go back to the inn together.
Well, a lot has happened while you've
been gone. I'll explain in detail.
But this distance is annoying.
Hold on! I'll be right over there!
No, that's okay. Stay there.
What?
I won't... return to you guys.
We're parting ways here... in this town...
Wh-What're you saying, Robin-chan?
Oh, I get it. You're thinking about the
newspaper, right? Don't worry about it!
None of us believe it,
and being falsely accused of a
crime often happens to pirates!
Yeah...
I'm sorry for pinning an
unreasonable crime on you guys.
But the article is telling the truth.
It really was me who infiltrated
the mayor's residence last night.
What?
No...
I carry a darkness within me
that you guys don't know about.
This darkness will destroy you someday.
The organizations Nico Robin had
something to do with up until today
all got annihilated... except for her.
As a matter of fact, I'm pinning this
crime on you and planning to run away.
The situation will get worse.
What do you mean?! Why are you--
Why I'm doing it... It's something
you don't need to know.
Robin-chan! I don't get what you're saying!
What happened to you?!
Robin! Let's go back together!
Although I only spent a short
time with you, after today...
...I'll never see you again.
Thank you for being nice to a person like me.
Goodbye.
Wait...
Hey... wait...
I can't...
...accept this.
Hey...
Wait!
Stop joking!
Wait! Robin-chan!
Robin-chan!
Wait! Robin-chan! Robin-chan!
Robin!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Isn't it time to settle
whether Robin is friend or foe?
Hold on a sec!
She's suddenly changed because
of the masked man she was with!
That's right! That man is
making her do bad things!
That would be fortune.
If this guy is Robin's real friend,
then that would be misfortune.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Capture Robin!
The Determination of the Straw Hats"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!