Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen
and were held captive,
by Caesar Clown who rules the island
and were exposed to Shinokuni,
a weapon of mass destruction.
But they broke out thanks to their ally
a Warlord - Trafalgar Law's
tactful maneuvers
and now they are heading
for R Building - gate 66.
However, Caesar has let
Shinokuni flow into the laboratory.
You've got to be kidding!
Run! Run!
What're you doing?!
Hurry up!
Get me down!
Tashigi-chan!
That's enough!
You have to survive!
Goodbye!
Smoker-san told me...
...to help them!
--No, Captain-chan, it's too late!
--There's... There's no time!
Don't be ridiculous!
Your colleagues are still
outside of the gate!
Outta my way!
No means no!
Captain Tashigi!
Well done, guys!
We certainly got our beloved
Captain-chan in our hands!
"The Treacherous Vice Admiral!
Demon Bamboo Vergo!"
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
I can't believe he broke
the wall of the lab
and let the gas in.
That Caesar guy does
such bizarre things.
We got away for now
but it's not safe yet.
You're right.
We have to find the children
and head to R Building--gate 66 in hurry!
And then from this annoying lab,
we can escape.
Hey, go faster!
You people!
When did all of you get on?!
Now it's too heavy even for me.
I'm so sorry.
But you have to hang on.
We have no choice.
What?
Is there a compelling reason?
Yeah, we are...
...too tired and we don't want to run!
That's the worst reason!
Get off of me!
Your name...
is Brownbeard, isn't it?
I'm sorry
but I want to rescue
my son Momonosuke
as soon as possible!
R-Rescue your son?!
However,
since I ran a lot already
I just don't want to run anymore!
Get off, you fools!
I'm pretty hot with my coat on.
You can hang it here.
Great.
I'm gonna take mine off, too.
Don't get comfortable on my back!
If you're not hurt,
why don't you run yourselves?!
I'm hungry.
I'm a samurai -
I don't get hungry.
Brownbeard-san,
do you have anything I can eat?
Shut up!
When we get to a soldiers' post,
I will buck you all off!
THE PASSAGE BETWEEN BUILDING A AND B
Captain-chan!
Captain-chan, are you listening?
Let's go ahead!
So he was making such a
deadly weapon on Punk Hazard
while the island was
believed to be closed.
If nothing is done, the damage
will spread around the world!
Let's get out of here
and make a report to Navy HQ!
What's the matter, Captain-chan?!
If we can't escape from here alive,
what did those guys who
saved your life died for?!
I'm sorry.
Let's go!
Yeah!
Wait a minute!
What's that noise?
There is something on the ceiling!
What is that creature?!
I think that thing came here
along with the Straw Hats!
Is it a lizard or something?
I heard that there was a
dragon on Punk Hazard!
It's a mythical animal
that Dr. Vegapunk created
for the security of the island.
It didn't look so scary before.
It's coming!
He dodged them!
H-He's chewing on steel!
If you get bitten by such strong jaws...
Everybody!
Run to B Building!
He flies, breathes fire,
and chews up steel!
What a creature!
What happened?
He's flying away.
Is he trying to escape?
He looked upset.
Did he get intimidated
by Captain Tashigi?
He was very scared.
Captain Tashigi,
you're gonna love this!
Reinforcements have arrived!
The Vice Admiral came to help!
Vergo!
Vice Admiral Smo-yan
and Vice Admiral Vergo!
We have both key figures of the G-5 here!
We're invincible now!
No...
Yeah! Now we're safe!
Run, everybody...
Run!
V-Vice Admiral Vergo,
did they do something wrong?!
Even if they needed to be punished,
your Finger Pistol could kill them...
Welcome.
I've heard about you,
Commodore Smoker.
Nice to meet you.
The soldiers of the G-5 are
rough and not very smart
but once you get to know them,
they're not as bad as people say.
Soon, you'll see
that they're very loyal.
Where is Vice Admiral Vergo?
He's not here.
Where did he go?
Don't worry.
Vice Admiral Vergo has to go home
suddenly sometimes.
His younger sister's sick.
Vice Admiral!
Stop it!
That's not what
Navy soldiers would say!
I don't think your house collapsed
because of our bombardment...
What do you mean by that?!
I'm sorry.
I'm responsible for their actions.
Oh yeah?
Then I want you
to take full responsibility!
You...
Don't get carried away!
I understand.
We will do anything
to make you satisfied.
Vice Admiral Vergo.
About the report on the kidnapped
child from the other day...
Oh...
I told some soldiers to look into it
but it was an accident at sea,
as I suspected.
So it was a false report.
A false report?
It's hard for any parent to
accept his or her child's death.
So they try to keep thinking
that their child was kidnapped
to keep their hope alive.
You will see
when you become
a mother someday.
Is that how it is?
Yes, that's how it is.
Everybody, back away!
He is not the man
that you used to know!
For a long time, he has been...
Captain-chan!
He's an impostor!
Vergo-san wouldn't do such
a thing to Captain-chan!
He's right!
Are you in disguise
or a Devil Fruit eater?
Stop mocking Vice Admiral Vergo!
Vice Admiral Vergo...
...always defends us
misfit Navy soldiers!
He's a man of humanity and justice!
Stop mocking him!
I'll kick your ass,
you impostor!
Go to hell!
You're unforgivable,
you impostor!
I've lost my voice!
Please stop!
Help us, Smoker-san!
A lady is...
Who is it?!
...in need!
Is that...
O-One of the Straw Hats?
Why is a pirate helping us?
I heard the sound of...
...a woman's tears falling.
INSIDE OF B BUILDING
Sanji has taken off somewhere
making a serious face!
I felt a mysterious presence back there.
Forget about him.
Something is coming!
Is that...
That's the dragon-san from earlier!
He looks a little different.
Different? How?
The look in his eyes.
The sedatives have
worn off as I thought.
Sedatives?
Yeah, he's violent by nature.
It's hard to handle him
without sedatives.
Plus, he's one of the smaller ones
that are newer and more advanced.
They're faster and
much more resilient!
Let's just run for now!
Run faster!
A STAIRCASE IN THE MIDDLE OF B BUILDING
Damn!
I don't wanna fall behind!
Straw Hat,
where are you heading?
I'm gonna catch Caesar!
What about you?!
I'm gonna sort things out with Vergo.
Is he with Caesar?
I think so.
Don't get in my way!
Wait, you bastard!
B BUILDING - THE GAS BALLOON LANDING PAD
Help!
I'm scared!
Get me out of here!
Help me!
Hey, stay away from the door.
Let's go back with everybody!
You can have a sweet candy
with your friends.
So let's go back to the Biscuit Room!
Brothers!
Sisters!
Help me!
In any case, I have to
get out of here first
to go rescue the children!
Let me out!
Oh?
What is a child doing here?
Let me out!
Be quiet!
If you don't stop,
I'll shoot you!
Weight Boost!
Stop it!
Who is it?!
I'll shoot you!
Don't move!
Are you okay?!
A monster!
Help!
It must be withdrawal symptoms.
Calm down!
No!
Oh yeah!
The sedatives!
This will ease your pain.
I'm gonna help you now.
Help!
Good girl!
It's done!
It's gonna work soon.
What was I doing?
You were pounding on the door.
Oh yeah,
I was trying to get out of here.
Hey, we took you out of here earlier -
why are you back here?
We came back here in
the Flying Gas Balloon
that the Master picked us up with.
But...
…big brother and sister
told us not to go back.
Of course!
What about the other kids?
Everybody's going to the Biscuit Room
because they have the candies there.
What?!
No!
You shouldn't eat the candy!
What?
This is bad!
Hey, could you take me
to the Biscuit Room?!
Okay! I know a shortcut
to the Biscuit Room!
Follow me!
CAESAR'S LABORATORY
What the hell is Vergo doing?!
The G-5 are my test subjects!
It'll be a total waste if I don't kill
them with Shinokuni!
That fool!
I have no choice.
Block off the passage ahead of them
and let the gas flow in
from the gate behind them!
But Vergo is still there.
I don't care if that idiot lives or dies!
Just do it!
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - NEAR THE BISCUIT ROOM
The Biscuit Room is down this way!
Let's go!
The Biscuit Room is this way!
Can I have the candy?!
Oh no! Those are the children?!
We can't let them go beyond this door!
Mocha!
If you wanna save your friends,
you have to help me!
Okay!
Mocha, hold the door!
What are you doing, Mocha?!
Open up!
I wanna go to the Biscuit Room!
Listen!
Don't let them get to the Biscuit Room!
Uh-huh!
Open it!
Hey!
Why shouldn't we...
...eat the candy?
Because...
Ready?
No!
Wait a second!
You...
I've been running so fast that
the friction has burned the floor!
But that was...
...not fair!
You were gliding on smoke!
Okay, ready?
Wait!
I told you to wait!
I'll say "Okay" when I'm ready!
I'm catching my breath now.
Hey, I didn't say "Okay"!
Listen,
Vergo is my enemy!
I know!
My enemy is Caesar!
Keep your hands off of him!
Oh, it's my enemy!
I won't let you get away this time!
Caesar!
The showdown with Caesar begins!
As Caesar uses his Gas Gas Fruit abilities that previously defeated the Straw Hats...
...Luffy launches a mighty offensive of his own!
The battle...
...grows more intense than ever!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Fierce Battle Gets Heated!
Luffy vs. Caesar!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!