Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Gum-Gum...
Now, Usopp!
Special Attack! Special Oil Star!
Three Chamber Shot!
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
Super Fencing!
Cien Fleurs!
Big Tree!
Wh-What's that?
Clutch!
Whoa, this is dangerous!
I'm gonna fall! I'm about to fall!
Skywalk!
Let's get a move on, Chopper!
Yeah!
Super Frapper Gong!
Bad Manner...
...Kick...
...Course!
Bottoms up!
We just scored our first knockdown.
"The Silent Assault!!
The Mysterious Visitor, 'Tyrant' Kuma!"
Eep! Th-That's one nasty woman!
She's like a demon! She's a demonic pirate!
What is the meaning of this?
Would you care to explain?
My lips are totally sealed!
Put me down!
Let's cut her to shreds!
You're so dead!
Do you think I'm going to
plop over dead and let the
treasure slip through my fingers?
I'll do whatever it takes to make you squeal!
Sh-Shut up!
Die!
Thunder Charge!
Swing Arm!
No!
We squealed! We told her
absolutely everything.
But Perona-sama loves treasure.
True! She won't let that woman steal it.
But we even told her about the shortcut.
We really blew it. Ploink!
Of all the nerve! They're loading
Sunny with all the treasure,
including ours, so she can
kiss this place goodbye!
But I won't let her get away with it!
I've got to hurry back to Sunny!
But what's up with this bridge?
Why is this part so narrow?
It's odd how well made it is...
You're a bunch of meanies!
Now I'm ticked!
I'm gonna send all of you flying!
Isn't that...?
But shouldn't I prioritize things
in order of importance?
I'll... pass on this!
I didn't see a thing!
You'd better say your prayers!
I'm gonna flatten you guys like pancakes!
You won't have a bone left in your body!
He's spitting mad!
Crap! Shoot!
Here he comes!
I'm stuck! My horns are stuck!
Drat! My horns are stuck
deep into the ground.
Gleam!
Twinkle!
Huh? You can't pull your horns out?
Hey, could that be...?
It sounds like Oars is screaming...
I'm telling you, that's just not possible!
He's the ultimate Special Zombie!
Give it a rest!
Retreat!
Yeah!
You guys are like devils!
Even flinging the guy didn't cut it!
It looks like we need to regroup.
So, what's our next strategy?
To stand a chance against that monster...
...Tactics #15 really is our only hope!
I'm willing to give it another shot!
Yeah! I'm confident it would
have worked earlier if Robin
had gone along with it!
Don't ask me to do that again!
You stupid idiots!
There is no way Robin-chan
could ever do something that humiliating!
It's so--huh? Wait...
I might want to see
Robin-chan dock after all!
K-Kidding! I'm just kidding, Robin-chan!
If you want to do it so badly,
you can do it by your--
Let's do it!
Enter standby, men!
Pirates Docking: Three!
We're not giant, but we're the Robot Warrior!
Docking: Complete!
Hey, Curly! Lend me a hand--
er, scratch that! Lend me a leg!
Sanji!
Do it, Sanji!
I like your drive! You've got it!
Go! Armée de l'Air Robot Shoot!
Man, it's only three of you?
Don't sound so disappointed!
We're a small, elite force, jerk!
Eat this!
Pirates Robot Attack!
Jerk! Jerk! Jerk!
Jerk! Jerk! Jerk! Jerk! Jerk! Jerk!
Jerk! Jerk! Grrr! Jerk!
Do they honestly consider
that a legitimate attack?
That's rather unimpressive.
Damn it! I'm disappointed in you,
Pirates Docking: Three!
That tickles! Stop it!
Now it's show time!
We'll make you taste the terror
of Pirates Docking: Three!
Huh?
I heard you boasted big time that you were
gonna become the King of the Pirates.
Aside from your big body,
you'll never be big!
Yeah, you heard him!
What was that?!
Who was crying like a baby
after we pummeled him?
Talk about a pathetic loser!
I didn't cry like a baby,
you darn puny pirates!
Now!
Sweet!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Well? How does it feel to have
your own punch rattle your brain?
Nice!
Did you see that, Robin-chan?
It went just as I had planned!
Well done, Pirates Docking: Three!
Since when was that all part
of your plan, stupid cook?
All right! Fall over!
Our second knockdown!
I-I'm not going down, jerks!
Robot Warrior, retreat!
We were so close!
We almost had him.
Dang, he can really take a licking!
While he's tying us up, Nami-san is...!
Wait, Sanji. I have an idea.
I've had enough of your tricks.
Hear me out!
It looks like he hasn't completely
lost all of Luffy's memories.
But he said that he doesn't know us.
He even called himself Moria's servant.
Regardless...!
Hey! What's keeping you, Nico Robin?!
Dock onto my left arm already!
Robin, hurry!
Come, Robin! Copy what I'm doing!
No.
That would hurt my human pride.
So you're not going to dock onto him?
Why do you sound so shocked?
Poopy! You got me worked up for nothing!
Didn't his reaction and the way
he whined remind you of Luffy?
It did!
So what do you have in mind?
When you get down to it,
he shares all of Luffy's weaknesses.
Oh, look! There is a mountain of meat!
What?! Meat?! Where?
Wow, he's right! It looks yummy!
Where? Where?!
Knee Crush!
Does knocking him to his knees
count as a knockdown?
Even if we had a set of rules,
I doubt anyone would obey them.
Sweet! We made his knees buckle!
--Yay! We did it! His knees buckled!
--Yay! Yay! Yay!
--We made his knees give out!
--That was embarrassing.
We're not done yet!
We just have to hang in there
until Straw Hat kicks Moria's butt.
Hurry and get your shadow back, Straw Hat!
Why do we have to wait on him?
All we have to do is take the lug down.
What?!
Whoa, wait! Weren't we just
keeping this monster busy so he
doesn't get in Straw Hat's way?
Do you seriously think you can defeat it?
There isn't any meat,
and I got knocked to my knees...
I'm simply accepting the fight he picked!
But not only is he huge, he's a zombie!
The only way to win is to purify him!
Right, Zoro! Work on buying time!
If you don't like it, start running!
I don't plan on waiting for Luffy.
Aw, man!
It looks like there is no stopping them.
Gum-Gum...
Supposedly it won't bend a millimeter,
even if a dinosaur steps on it...
I've heard that the black blade
is known for its "strength."
Once, a legendary samurai
wielded the great sword, Shusui.
I am sure this katana would be
happy to have you as its master.
I just obtained the O-Wazamono, Shusui...
This is the perfect chance
to test its strength!
No, wait! Luffy is gonna
take out Moria for us.
Damn that jerk Moria! Where did he go?
I can't find him anywhere!
I know!
Gum-Gum Rocket!
Found him!
All right!
Hey, you!
Who's that?
It's one of the pirate women!
What are you doing with the
treasure I was supposed to take?
And Sunny for that matter!
If it isn't the pirate woman.
Is your wedding ceremony
with Absalom over already?
Like I'm gonna marry that
perverted invisible beast man!
So you managed to get away?
He really is a stupid man.
So what are you going to do?
It's true that I intend to
leave the island on your ship.
If you want to stop me, I'm up for a fight!
My Mini-Hollow Corps will
blow a weakling like you to bits!
My nemesis is Mr. Negative
Nose and him alone!
Who is that?
Perona-sama, please run for it!
Who the heck are you?!
I have no idea who he is, but he's an enemy!
Just a second ago, he made my brothers
vanish without a trace
right before my very eyes!
He's no pushover! He's trouble!
Anyway, he's rottin' dangerous!
They vanished...?
No kidding, guys...
Of course he's not a pushover!
This is...
...one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
He's the "Tyrant" Bartholomew Kuma!
This man used to be the
epitome of cruelty as a pirate!
Eh?!
No way! He's one of the Seven Warlords?!
That's insane! He's as
powerful as Moria-sama?!
What brought him to Thriller Bark?
I can't believe it...
Are you Moria's subordinate?
M-Moria-sama--er, Gecko Moria
and I have cut ties!
Y-You caught me when I was
about to flee from this island.
This looks bad!
What is that monster
going to do to Perona-sama?!
If you were to go on a trip,
where would you like to go?
--Shock!
--What?! Small talk?!
Why do you care?!
But if I could go on a vacation,
I'd like to stay at a dark, damp
old castle oozing with malice,
where I could spend my time
singing incantations.
She answered him!
And the answer was most
befitting for our Ghost Princess!
Jeez! Pull yourself together, Perona-sama!
You made me march to the beat of your drum!
Of all the stupid...! I nearly let
the weight of your title crush me.
What a dreadful man!
Everyone falls to their knees
after I hit them with my attack!
Were you listening to me?!
I bet your shadow is
pretty darn strong, Kuma!
I'll take you down and give you
to Moria-sama as a parting gift!
Negative Ghost!
And Special Hollow!
Wow, there it is!
It's Perona-sama's ultimate combo!
I can't ask Moria's whereabouts
when you're being belligerent.
Where'd she go?
Where are you, Perona-sama?!
Perona-sama!
Hey, what just happened?!
Perona-sama vanished!
Jerk! What did you do to our princess?!
I won't forgive you for this!
Yeah, that was unforgiveable!
I'll never forgive you!
--Perona-sama!
--I'll never forgive you!
But he's rottin' scary!
Run for it!
Aren't you the Cat Burglar?
You're part of the Straw Hat Crew!
Is it true that Monkey D. Luffy
has an older brother?
Eh?!
What gives?! He got up there
in the blink of an eye!
Did he warp...?
Of course he does! Isn't his name Ace?
What of it?
I see... So it was true.
What gives?! Are you after Luffy?
What do you want?
Are you really one of the Seven Warlords?
I am free to do as I will.
That guy is trouble!
Is he after Luffy? I've got to let him know!
I've got ya, Moria!
You aren't getting away this time, jerk face!
Now fight me!
Give back everyone's shadows!
Gum-Gum...!
The shadow? I've been chasing after the--
Sh-Shoot! He pulled a fast one on me!
It's almost time for the sun to rise!
You'll run out of hiding
places if you dilly dally.
Moria, where are you hiding?!
Look carefully! I'm right here.
What?! Moria is inside of Oars' stomach!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Oars + Moria! The Most Heinous
Combination of Brains and Brawn!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!