Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map
has been verified,
it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
You bastard...
Are you mocking me?
Whoa... I'd expect no less from you.
If you're in that much of a hurry,
I'll show you...
...my new powers.
It's collapsing!
Oh, shoot!
I was gonna stop the transformation
when I reached my human-beast form,
but I became a giraffe!
A talking giraffe is falling towards us!
Kaku!
That power of yours is too cool!
A wolf?!
What is this place?! A zoo?!
How dare you all...?
Experience the fighting
power of a power holder...!
Tempest Kick!
Whoa! What's that?!
He's gonna do something!
Sky Slicer!
This isn't good.
Duck, Usopp!
"I Won't Kick Even If It Costs
Me My Life! Sanji's Chivalry!"
I see...
The point is the length--
in other words, the reach.
With the power coming from that huge
body in addition to centrifugal force,
his attack is deeper
and sharper than before.
Wh-What the heck?!
Hey, I don't see any damage.
Look at the ceiling.
Huh? The ceiling?
Oh?
I can see the blue sky.
Whoa...
I wonder why... Hm...?
Don't tell me the Tower
of Law has been cut in two!
Hey, hey, hey, hey...!
This is dangerous!
How shameful!
To think that you showed
your emotions in a battle!
Shut up.
I like being a giraffe.
I love giraffes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Even if your attacks are sharp,
that's not threatening to me at all.
S-Stop it, Zoro!
That hurts! What're you doing?!
Why are you pulling my arm?!
Huh...? Pulling my arm?
Whoa! It's locked tight!
Yeah, it is.
Hey! What're you doing?!
It's not my fault, is it?!
This happened because you charged at me!
I did that because you were standing
there in a daze when he attacked!
Just unlock these handcuffs!
What're those guys doing?
Beats me.
To put it simply,
this means that we're
in the same situation as Robin is.
Then, the key is...
...in the hands of one
of the CP9 members.
We have no choice but to get
the key by defeating them.
Don't be unreasonable!
There's no way we can fight like this!
Our prey got connected.
Okay then, Jabra.
Just stay back
and leave those two to me.
What?! Are you trying to steal my prey?!
Then, do you want us to work
together and fight them?
Even if it costs me my life,
the answer is no.
Me, neither.
Hey, you two!
Tell us the number on those handcuffs.
Number?
The handcuffs and the keys have numbers
so that we know which key
unlocks which handcuffs.
If those handcuffs can be unlocked
by one of the keys we have,
we'll unlock them right away.
What?! Really?!
The number... Where's the number?
Here it is! It's 2!
Unlock these!
Not the right one.
Mine isn't, either.
Sorry.
What?! You got my hopes up, you jerks!
Dammit!
Then, it means one of the other three
CP9 members has the right one, huh?
It can't be helped.
The early bird gets to kill the worm.
Seems like that's the only way.
What?!
Whoa! What's with these stairs?!
They're sliced in two and shifted.
The impact from earlier...
As I suspected,
something must've happened.
Is this building okay?
Hey! Are you okay?!
Ah! Zoro! Sogeking!
Ah! Hey! Chopper!
What's going on? They're waving to me.
It looks kinda fun.
H-Hey, guys!
Idiot!
Pay attention to these handcuffs!
Find the key for handcuffs #2!
Huh? A key?
What the hell is this?!
I just assumed that there'd
be a bridge or something.
What crazy huge swirls!
I can see the Gates of Justice now,
but is it possible to go
there on a regular boat?
I don't have much time anyway.
I guess I'll try something.
Here we go!
Just wait, Robin!
Yaay! Yaay!
I've found the path to those gates!
I'm gonna tell everyone!
Ooops!
That was close!
What's this?
Stare...
Th-This is...
Don't tell me...
Click.
Ahhh! What's going on?!
All right!
I found another secret passage!
Yaay!
Where are we?!
Whoa! Pirate guy!
What're you doing?!
I see.
So the handcuffs and the keys
have numbers on them.
What?!
That's what's happening here?
Then I'll fight those guys!
Don't be ridiculous!
There are
two of them! If you get taken out,
with these handcuffs on, we won't
be able to do anything but get killed!
Please! You're our only hope!
Hope?
It's not like I'm
happy to hear that, you jerk!
Sanji, Nami, and Franky...
If any of them
get the #2 key, bring it here right away!
We're counting on you!
The one who's likely to get
the key first is... Maybe Sanji?
I'll go look for Sanji.
I'm their only hope!
Now...
...I've caught you!
Let me go!
Yoyoi!
Just...
give up!
Die!
I'm no match for him at all!
Franky...
Iron Body!
...Boxing!
Shave!
What's with your punches?
You're no ordinary human!
No matter how much you harden
your body to make it like iron,
my fists are real iron.
N-No!
This is no time for having tea!
Witchcraft!
I was drawn in by your witchcraft!
I almost got swept up in a
high tide called "love trap"!
You've already had three cups.
Shut up, witch!
I'm not gonna
be caught in a trap again!
CP9 insulted Robin-chan
terribly on the sea train.
I'm not gonna forget about it.
Now...
give me the key!
That's too bad...
It seems like you're in a hurry.
Go ahead and take the key.
Where is it?
Well...
Where on my body do you think I hid it?
Why don't you try finding it?
I'd be happy to!
That was a bad start, huh?
You stupid Sanji.
Nico Robin is steadily
approaching the Gates of Justice
while we're here fighting like this.
Or maybe should I say that from
her perspective, she's approaching hell?
I know that.
That's right.
Robin-chan's life is at stake!
If you're gonna be in my way,
I won't go easy on you,
even if you are a woman!
Hand over that key to me
before you get hurt!
Even if you shout,
the key won't turn up.
You don't have to treat me
like I'm a woman.
I don't live in such a delicate world.
Since we've got an annihilation order,
I'll just take your life,
that's all.
I won't let you take my life.
What I want is...
...the key to Robin-chan's handcuffs.
Then I guess teatime is over?
Shave!
Your power is indeed
that of a superhuman.
An opening!
I landed a blow.
Ow!
Hey! How could you?!
Isn't that what you call
"landing a blow"?
How dare you...? You little...
Moon Walk!
He's fast!
I've just stomped you.
That means you lost!
Now, give the key to...
Finger Pistol!
Tempest Kick!
What a disappointing guy.
You're a pirate...
...and yet, you're quite the coward!
Hey, shut up!
Give me the key!
I've had enough of your
transparent threats.
Shall I try something fun on you?
Unless you fight back,
you won't survive.
He's not coming after me...
Good!
If I had gotten caught again,
I would've been killed.
I'll just run and...
Life Return!
Yoyoi! Yoi! Yoi! Yoyoi!
Oh, shoot!
Now, shall I...
...pierce you to death
or choke you to death?!
In this life, a cold wintry wind blows.
You will die here peacefully
before the spring comes.
I'll at least let you bloom
in lovely bright red petals
one more time
before you fall!
That's my compassion!
When you arrive in the afterlife,
please tell my late mother...
...that I'm... I'm doing fine...
killing people!
Now, die!
Now... Now... Now!
No!
Song of Spring Feeling!
Hoofprint... Roseo!
Nami! Are you okay?!
Chopper...
Thanks. You saved me.
What's with that guy?
Is he a power holder?
I don't know.
His hair moves like
an octopus, so I can't do anything.
More importantly,
now is our chance, Chopper.
Let's get out of here right away.
Why?!
Unless we defeat him,
we can't get the key.
You mean this, right?
I stole the key without him noticing,
but I just couldn't get away from him.
Do you know what's going on
with the others?
Say, Nami.
What number does it have on it?
Number?
It says 3.
Wrong one.
What is this number?
Something fell down!
Is this... a doll?!
No...
Sanji!
Why does he look like this?!
Hey! What happened?!
Why is your body like this?!
Are you okay, Sanji-kun?!
Sanji!
Sorry... I lost.
I couldn't get the key.
Hold on a sec, Sanji.
I'll give you first aid.
I never thought that Sanji-kun
would get taken out...
Sanji-kun...
Were you really
not able to defeat her?
Did you really fight seriously?
It was that woman
who you fought, wasn't it?
You're soft with women.
I'm sorry about the key.
That's not it!
I'm saying that because
of that stupid chivalry,
you're gonna lose your life!
You're gonna stick to it even
after getting hurt like this?!
What're you gonna do if you die?!
It's not like...
I want to die.
But I grew up having the idea that
I shouldn't kick women beat into me.
So...
even if it costs me my life...
...I won't kick a woman!
You're a fool.
Fool!
Hey! What're you doing, Nami?!
If running away is also
against your chivalry,
at least ditch that chivalry!
It's not worth dying in vain over.
Leave that woman to me.
Also...
I think a little more of
your chivalry than I did before.
What?!
Did she just say
that she loves me more?
No, she didn't!
I'm not kind.
Neither am I.
Sounds like we can get along.
Hey! Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
Hurry up and get me the cola!
I haven't forgiven you yet!
Just do it already!
If I have cola, I can power up!
What kind of idiot actually
gets stronger with cola?!
Shut up! That'd be me!
Just watch.
I'll finish him off in an instant!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fukurou's Miscalculation!
My Cola Is the Water of Life"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!