Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After hearing that his brother Ace was
captured by the navy and is waiting to be executed,
Luffy stowed away on a navy ship
with the Snake Princess's help
and headed to the Great Prison - Impel Down!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! The Science
of Weather and the Mechanical Island!"
If you were to take a trip,
where would you want to go?
Zoro!
Brook!
Usopp!
Sanji!
Franky!
Nami!
Chopper!
Robin!
Luffy?
It was just a dream.
You were screaming.
I saw my friends.
I see.
What can I say to cheer him up?
Luffy.
Don't worry.
You have to think first
about saving your brother.
You have faith in your friends.
Don't you?
You...
Plus,
you are not alone now.
I am here for you.
Hancock!
How foolish I've been!
I didn't notice there's
been a goddess on my side!
Luffy!
Hancock!
...And that's how it'd all play out!
--No, I can't do it! Yes, I want to! No, I can't!
--What're you doing, Hammock?
Meanwhile, a few days ago...
W-What happened?
Silently...
Where am...
Are you up?!
What? Who the heck are you?!
Where am I?
You're in my house. Now, calm down...
Don't mess with me!
Oh! You're scaring me.
It's not good to move around
so much. You're in bad shape.
--And the weather is...
--Stay away!
Bad shape or not, I'm getting out of here!
If I'm not there, they can't go anywhere.
--Quietly...
--Get lost!
Forgive me.
--I can't help wanting to help you.
--I said get lost!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, little girl.
Little girl, who flew through
the sky to get here.
I heard you the first time. What do you want?
Are you calmed down a bit now?
Are you sure you're not
going to flip out again?
Yeah.
This is good!
No wonder. You were sleeping for
two days since you crashed here.
For that long?
Yes. You must have had a rough time, huh?
Ta-dah!
Let me show you something! These
are tightly tied Wind Knots!
If I untie one...
there is a gentle breeze.
If I untie two...
there is a strong wind.
If I untie three...
it really starts blowing!
What're you doing?!
I thought it might cheer you up.
Yeah, I'm really cheery now! Thank
you so much! I'm outta here!
Where are you going? It's
impossible, young girl!
This isn't so bad!
I'm okay!
Looks like a huge cyclone is on its way!
Oh no, I told you!
You're covered in dirt.
Come in and take a shower!
In the meantime, I will
wash and dry your clothes.
Grandpa.
What?
This is not just a rain!
An enormous cyclone's approaching!
What? What did you say?
I'm telling you that a storm
is coming! A gigantic one!
Oh yeah, this is true.
Maybe somebody else will fall out of the sky.
God! He's so irritating!
Whatever happens, I don't care!
What? What's this?
If you turn the wheel,
hot water will come out.
T-The wheel?
Clouds raining hot water? What's going on?!
How's the water temperature?
If you push the wheel, hot air comes out.
I made some tea.
Oh, thank you!
It's good!
Wait! What? Why're we so relaxed?!
I said "a storm is coming"!
You should really give a crap!
You have to calm down!
Are we really gonna be alright?
It is about time.
I'll be back soon. You wait
here quietly, young girl.
What?! H-Hey!
Wait!
How can he walk smoothly in this wind?
Here it is!
Cool Ball!
Heat Ball!
Here I go!
Cyclone Burst!
Whoa...
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, young girl!
I heard you the first time.
What?
Oh, you only saw it the one time
but you already used the Wind Knot.
You are impressive!
It's easy!
Okay, I got to go!
Wh-What is this?
Where... am I?!
This is a small Sky Island - Weatheria,
where scientific studies
of the weather are conducted.
S-Sky Island?!
That cyclone was going to be a good sample
but it suddenly disappeared.
I wonder who did such thing.
Nami was whisked away to
a small island in the sky.
Will she able to get back to her friends?
"A Winter Island on the Grand Line"
The storm's getting worse. Let's
take a break somewhere, Kitton.
Okay.
What's wrong, Taroimo?
--It's big!
--Kitton, back off!
W-Wait! Stop, Taroimo!
Wait!
He's human!
What do we do?!
E-Excuse me! Are you all right?
He thought that you were
something we were hunting.
Yeah, I'm fine!
How is that possible?!
Ah, so you are fine.
That's good, right? Taroimo.
But, damn!
How far did I come?
Oh, it's so cold! Is this the arctic?!
Franky!
Oh no! He's only in his
underwear in all this snow.
Have you been robbed?
Put this fur pelt on.
Fur pelts?! You got to be kidding! No thanks!
If I wore crap like that...
Aw! Nah, man, it wouldn't be
fitting for a pervert! Aw!
Hey, follow my lead!
Shake your hip to the right!
Right hand on your waist!
Stick out your left hand!
Slide and left!
Right! Left! Right! Left!
Repeat! Aw!
One! Two! One! Two!
Right! Left! Right! Left!
One! Two! One! Two! One! Two! One! Two!
Aw! One! Two! One! Two!
Ha!
Super!
Woo-hee! Great!
I'm still pretty cold! Where
the hell is this place?!
What?! You don't know where you are?
Why the hell would I know this place?!
You're on Mechanical Island,
Future Land Baldimore,
the birthplace of the genius.
--Degenerate?
--The genius.
The... Degenerate?
The genius.
Mister!
Geek! I mean, god!
Let's take him to the hospital, Kitton!
Okay.
"OPERATION IN PROGRESS"
So he is a cyborg.
I can't believe that his
energy source is cola.
What should we do?
We don't have any cola here.
There's no time to lose. Let's just begin.
Okay.
Mister!
Mister?
Hello! You're the boy from earlier, right?
I'm sorry to keep you waiting!
S-Something's different about you.
Yes! Unfortunately, they don't
have any cola here so...
...they used tea instead.
It's Darjeeling!
Tea?
It has a super flavor!
It makes me super relaxed!
M-Mister!
Oops! I'm sorry!
Here you go!
Be careful, it's hot.
No no! That's not what I was gonna say!
Mister! You were funnier
before and I miss it!
Oh yeah? What was I like?
Like this!
Super!
Kid.
--Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
--How can you even say something like that?
Franky becomes a gentleman
on Mechanical Island!
Will he ever be the same again?!
And what will happen to
the separated Straw Hats?!
Chopper awakens on an island
to find himself perpetually under attack
by giant birds and brawny natives,
landing him in a nasty crisis.
Meanwhile, Sanji awakens
on Peachy Island, the island of dreams,
where he has an encounter with
someone truly frightening.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! An Island
of Giant Birds and a Pink Paradise!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!