Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
So you're gonna join our crew now, right?
I promised one of my comrades something.
I must tend to that first
or I will lose face!
Yeah. You're talking
about Laboon, aren't you?
I know all about it.
Franky and Robin told me.
Huh? Oh, that's right.
Laboon! That is the name of the whale.
He is at a certain cape--
Listen, Brook! We met Laboon
at Twin Cape. Honest!
J-Just a moment, please!
I'm shocked! This is so sudden.
Is it true? Did you actually meet Laboon?
Yup.
Is that right?
He's doing well?
I have never been this happy in my life!
"Brook's Past! A Sad Farewell
with His Cheerful Comrade!"
Laboon...
"Rumbar Pirates
Musician & Swordsman"
Hi, everyone! I hope you're doing well.
"Brook
(50 years ago - Age: 38)"
It's morning!
Let's start the day with a song!
Eh... This week, Power
Tune will be presenting
the famous song, "The Black
Handkerchief of Happiness."
Everyone, feel free to join in!
♪ White handkerchief, ♪
♪ don't let him find you ♪
♪ Run for it ♪
♪ White handkerchief, ♪
♪ Don't let the octopus catch you ♪
♪ That's a stain ♪
--♪ And now a squid is coming ♪
--S-Stop it! Not so loud in the morning!
--♪ There is another stain ♪
--I'll get up! I'll get up, Brook!
--♪ White handkerchief ♪
--I'm up! I'm wide awake!
♪ Covered in stains, you're
the black handkerchief of happiness ♪
Hey, Brook. Play that one
song--ballad version.
Roger! That's your favorite, Captain!
It's a whale!
It's the one from yesterday...
You're still here? Go look for your pod!
Isn't it adorable?
Hey, how long are you gonna follow us?
I bet your mama's worried.
Here! Eat up, Laboon!
Oh, man! When did you name him?
We're under attack!
Are you two okay?
P-Please help us! He's severely wounded!
Captain, an injured man fell overboard!
Toss him a life preserver!
We'll save him later.
It's not like I can swim...
I guess that's all I can do.
You're a lifesaver, Laboon!
Hey, we're okay!
Laboon!
Shhh! No, no, Laboon.
Don't wake everyone up.
I'll sing for you when the sun rises.
All right! Everyone, sing that song!
Laboon, are you cold?
Treasure! We found treasure, Laboon!
We're gonna party today!
Sea monster sighting!
What?!
Protect Laboon!
Yeah!
We won't go easy on anyone
who picks on Laboon!
Yay!
Laboon!
Laboon, are you all right?
Thank goodness!
I'm so glad!
That's not an option, Laboon.
Please hang tight and wait here.
Be a good boy, okay?
I think like he likes you best, Brook.
No kidding!
It's because Laboon loves music!
Nope! The shape of your head
makes him think you're kin.
Huh?
Is that right?
Could you try to reason with him?
We tried to talk to him,
but he wasn't willing to listen to us.
You understand, don't you?
We aren't strong enough to
protect him from here on out.
He's still a child.
There is no way we could
take him to the Grand Line.
Please hear me out.
Now, now! The music will have to wait.
It's true that we're comrades,
but you're a whale and--
The Grand Line is dangerous! Honest!
Maybe you could come if you were an adult.
But there will be ferocious beasts unlike
anything we've seen in the West Blue!
Laboon, listen to--
Nope. He wouldn't listen to a word I said.
He wouldn't?
Maybe we should sing that song for a while.
That would have the opposite effect!
Captain!
Forget it! I know it's hard,
but avoid eye contact with him.
You are not allowed to sing or play your
instruments until Laboon leaves our ship.
Laboon...
The sails are about to rip, Captain!
The rudder isn't responding!
Keep the rudder steady! Pull up the sails!
We'll ride the storm!
The entrance to the Grand Line
awaits us on the other side!
Captain, there's light! Light dead ahead!
Look! The guiding light points
to the Grand Line's entrance.
Sweet!
Yay!
Captain, it's time!
Does anyone see Laboon?
No, I haven't seen hide
nor hair of him for a week.
I feel bad for him, but
it was for his own good.
With any luck, he can return to his pod.
Men, are you mentally ready for this?
Yeah! We're ready when you are!
Let's go to the greatest ocean in the world!
Yeah!
I am Crocus, the lighthouse keeper.
Congratulations on crossing Reverse Mountain.
Welcome to the Pirates' Graveyard.
Oh, ouch! Don't jinx us, man!
I'm the captain of the
Rumbar Pirates, Yorkie.
In the West Blue, I've made a bit of a
reputation for myself as "Calico" Yorkie.
Sorry, Crocus-san, but our ship
took a pretty bad beating...
You're welcome to stay as long as you like,
but provide my meals while you're here!
Dang! You want to sponge
off a bunch of pirates?
Okay, cool! Please celebrate with us.
We're going to throw a party today!
By the way, is the whale
that came with you a pet?
Geh!!
Laboon!
You came with us? That was--
Brook!
Laboon, thank you! This
is great! I'm so happy!
You're injured?! I can't believe
you braved those stormy waters!
That was nuts, Laboon!
Hey, Brook! Let's sing that song.
Captain, you sure love that song.
You bet! It's perfect for pirates!
Laboon, you like it too, don't you?
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho... ♪
♪ Yo-ho ho ho, yo-ho ho ho ♪
♪ We're on our way... ♪
♪ ...to deliver Bink's booze ♪
♪ Sail leisurely with the sea breeze ♪
♪ Sail with the waves ♪
♪ The setting sun romps about
on the other side of the tide ♪
--♪ A ring of birds in the sky sing ♪
--Crocus-san, would you like to make a request?
Brook, you can play anything, can't you?
♪ Bid farewell to the port
of the weaving village ♪
--♪ As we set sail, we shall sing heartily ♪
--Pirates love to sing!
♪ Silver and gold waves
turn into ocean spray ♪
♪ We are off, bound for
the ends of the ocean ♪
Please understand. You can't
repeat what you did last time.
The Grand Line is too dangerous.
I'm afraid that you are simply
too small to take with us!
Listen to me.
We have no idea what to
expect from here on out.
Now what do you think everyone would do
if harm should come your way?
We wouldn't hesitate to save you.
We'd try, even if that spelled
the end of the Rumbar Pirates!
Please understand! I'm begging you.
I don't want to leave you, either.
You don't know how hard
it was for me last time!
But... But...!
We aren't leaving him.
Captain!
Laboon! Wait for us!
We're going to travel straight--
just straight--across this ocean!
And you know what, Laboon?
Amazingly enough, our ship will return
to the other side of the Red Line.
We'll cross the wall again
and return to this cape.
Please wait for us!
You just have to hang tight
for two or three years.
Then you'll get to see everyone again!
Captain!
Isn't that right, Brook?
Yes! I swear that we will come back for you.
By then, you should be big and strong.
--Later!
--See ya, Laboon!
Take care!
Laboon, let's go on adventures
together all across the ocean!
We're buddies!
--Thank you!
--Goodbye!
--Laboon!
I'm so glad you understand!
Thank you, Laboon!
Laboon! We'll now go into the
Grand Line and travel around the world.
But you wait for us here.
"Three Years Later"
"Florian Triangle"
I will deliver this. I swear it!
It holds the song that Laboon,
the captain, and the rest of us loved!
I promised my crewmates
that I would take it to him.
It has the choral number of a lifetime
performed by the Rumbar Pirates,
who make crying children laugh!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Bink's Booze! The Song that
Connects the Past with the Present!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!