Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
Luffy finally freed Ace!
However, Admiral Akainu landed
a fatal blow against Ace
and Ace died in Luffy's arms!
The man that Roger is waiting for...
...is not you, Teach, at any rate!
Forgive me, my sons.
I raised such a ridiculous fool.
You guys gave me everything.
I have deep appreciation.
Goodbye, my sons!
"The Show Begins! Blackbeard's
Plot is Revealed!"
Head Office! Head Office!
There's big news out of Marineford!
Is it true?!
Is Whitebeard really...?! Are you sure?!
Can't believe that Whitebeard is...!
The news has spread around
the world like wildfire!
"The Whitebeards failed to
rescue Roger's son Ace!"
"And the death of Whitebeard,
the legendary pirate captain."
Extra! Get ready to issue an extra!
Here is the breaking news!
Whitebeard died shortly after
"Fire Fist" Ace! I repeat!
--At Marineford...
--Whitebeard is...
...Dead!
Then this is it for the Whitebeard Pirates!
--The war will be over soon!
--We can live in peace finally!
People who witnessed with their own eyes
the historic event which is being reported...
...stand transfixed, words
frozen on their lips.
So Whitebeard's gone now...
He was 72 years old.
He stood even against the King
of the Pirates in his day.
He was the captain of the Whitebeard Pirates
and was the great pirate Edward Newgate...
...aka Whitebeard.
He died in the decisive war at
the bay of Marineford between...
...the Whitebeard Pirates
and the Navy Headquarters
and their ally The Seven Warlords.
This is great!
Things are really gonna change in the world!
But even before that,
I don't think that things will
settle down that easily here!
With the most heinous criminals and
the jail manager of Impel Down,
I wonder what Blackbeard is up to.
What's gonna happen?
Is this really the end of the war?
Also, the thing that Whitebeard
said before he died...
The One Piece...
...is real!!
It's a matter of time before
the world finds out!
I wonder how the pirates will react!
But even before that, can we
say this war is really over?
Why did Blackbeard come to Marineford?
That bastard!
Marco! Everybody feels the same!
But you better hold your tongue for now!
I know, Vista!
Hurry up and get on the ship! Don't
you remember our captain's last order?
--Ace!
--Pops!
Jimbei! Bring Ace's brother, hurry!
Okay!
Ace-san! Good old man!
I couldn't do anything to help you two!
I want to help Luffy-kun at least!
--Don't let the pirates get away!
--Kill them all!
Captain Buggy, where're you going?!
Are you stupid?! I'm getting out of here!
I can't kill Whitebeard - he's already dead!
Captain Buggy!
I couldn't do it!
Black Hole!
--Captain Buggy, now is your chance!
--Hurry and kill Whitebeard!
I know that you can make it over the crack!
Stop telling me what to do! It
wouldn't be smart to just jump him!
I'm waiting for the right time!
--They think that it's easy!
--Vortex!
You can't create earthquakes anymore!
Oh yeah! Captain Buggy knew
it and waited for this moment!
--Let us help you!
--Oh no, wait...
--Here you go, Captain Buggy!
--Wait, wait, wait! Wait a minute, guys!
Ouch! Damn!
I-Is that what a dying
old man is capable of?!
N-No! That's what makes
him the legend Whitebeard!
I was scared and I couldn't
even approach him!
Whitebeard was scary!
The man at the top is
scary, even if he is dead!
I don't care if you think that I'm
hopeless! I say goodbye to you fools!
Captain Buggy!
He's crying... Captain Buggy...
I know why! "Yesterday's
enemy could be today's d!"
He felt pity for his rival Whitebeard
as a human without even noticing!
He could've killed that guy!
And now he's trying to leave
us  without making excuses!
Son of a gun! He showed us something
more important than killing Whitebeard!
I can't believe that he chose
to have pity on the instead of
all the fame he was surely going to get!
He is one man in a million
as we knew all along!
You're way too cool, Captain Buggy!
--Wait, Captain Buggy!
--Let us come with you!
Captain!
He was so tenacious! Good to
see him drop dead finally!
It's going as we planned so
far. Now is the time, Captain.
Alright, let's begin!
They're up to something again!
--Teach, that bastard!
--What is he gonna do to Pops now?!
I'm gonna put on a show!
It's a show that will shake the whole world!
What is that black cloth?!
Blackbeard got inside of it
with the body of Whitebeard!
Now, please don't trespass for a while!
What do you think you're doing?!
He's someone who deceived us by joining
the Warlords only to betray us!
Stay alert!
I can't wait!
Are we gonna disband if we fail?
Hurry up! To the sea!
Luffy-kun!
Stay with me!
You have to carry on in this
world where Ace-san is no longer lives...
...tomorrow and the day after!
Fire!
You have to live strong!
Jimbei, if I don't escape death...
I'm sorry but could you
look after my brother?
I'm sorry to contradict you, Ace-san,
but you can't overrate me. I'm
not as good-natured as you think.
Even if he's your brother,
we're in the pirates' world.
I only help or protect the ones
who I have a high regard for!
My feelings haven't changed at all, Ace-san!
I'm not helping him because
he is your brother!
I have a high regard for
Luffy-kun! That is why...!
Hurry up, Jimbei! Give Luffy treatment!
Pacifista! Kill Straw Hat!
Although he's a Warlord,
Jimbei is our enemy now!
We're allowed to kill him!
Perfume Femur!
Boa Hancock! Are you gonna
stand in our way again?!
"Fire Fist" Ace and Whitebeard
are dead already!
I don't like persistent men!
Jimbei! Please take good care of Luffy!
Jimbei! Get on this ship!
Okay!
What's this?!
--Damn! He froze the sea!
--We can't leave!
Hurry up and do something!
It's Admiral Aokiji!
Stop Aokiji!
I have no choice! I'll look for another way!
When I say that I won't let you get away,
why don't you give up your life, you fool!
Hand Dragon's son over to me!
--Akainu! He isn't dead!
--I thought he was beaten by Pops!
--He traveled underground...
--...By making a path with lava!
Jimbei!
I cannot do that! Because I've
already made up my mind...
...to save his life even if it means death!
Alright then, I won't ask you again!
Coby! Akainu-san wants to
kill Straw Hat at any cost!
Once he sees you as a target,
you can't get away from him!
Luffy-san...
--We're gonna protect Ace's brother!
--That's also what Pops wanted!
Yeah! Ace's family is our family, too!
"Family"? Don't be ridiculous!
You guys just left "Fire Fist" Ace
and your "father" Whitebeard
to their fate and ran!
--What did you say?!
--Take this!
I-It doesn't work at all!
Outta my way, you cowards!
Move aside, Jimbei!
Emporio Face Growth Synthesis!
Ivan-san, let me assist you!
Great Scissors!
Keep your hands off of Straw boy!
I'll kill Dragon's son for sure!
Hell...
...Wink!
Since Impel Down, Straw boy
has been under assault...
...physically and mentally and it's
pushing him beyond his capacity!
If I let something happen to him,
I wouldn't be able to face...
...my comrade Dragon for the rest of my life!
I agree!
I have no time to play
with you guys right now!
So back off, you two!
Bring it on!
I'm burning way hotter than you right now!
Looks like he's all set now!
Let me see it already, Captain!
Alright, everybody, thank you for waiting!
It's the greatest show in the world
presented by Captain Teach
of the Blackbeard Pirates!
Please enjoy it!
B-Blackbeard!
What was he doing in there?!
Nothing has changed on Whitebeard's body!
And neither has Blackbeard's!
Navy!
I'll show you what I'm capable of!
We'll turn against each other again!
Black Hole!
What's going on?!
That's my Dark-Dark Fruit power!
And now...
...this is...!
That pose is...!
That's...
...the power of Tremor-Tremor Fruit!
W-Why does he possess the
late Whitebeard's power?!
You did it, Captain!
We're not gonna disband then?
It looks like I made the right
choice by teaming up with them!
Pops' tremor power?!
What did he do, that bastard Teach!
The gravity of darkness
brings total annihilation!
And the power of tremor destroys everything!
I possess them both! No one
can compete with me now!
I'm the strongest man in the world!
I don't know how he did it but...
he acquired Whitebeard's power!
How is it possible?!
That means we still have to fear
the power of Tremor-Tremor Fruit?!
If I'm correct, it's impossible to have
two Devil Fruit powers at the same time!
It's impossible for average
people, that's for sure.
But Teach is a little
different, as you guys know.
His body structure is irregular
compared to common people's.
That's why he was able to do it!
Hey, did you guys see that?!
Tell all the people in the world!
The boring people who love peace,
Navy soldiers, the World
Government, and pirates!
This must be a bad dream!
The future of this world is determined!
Yes, here comes the era that I conquer!
I thought that Whitebeard
died and the Navy won!
I can't believe that he now
has two Devil Fruit powers!
Who the hell is Blackbeard?!
I thought that the war would be over soon!
Then why is this happening?! Hey, Coby!
Although Luffy-san's brother and Whitebeard
died, this war is still not over?!
Blackbeard freely uses the power he
stole from Whitebeard to wreak havoc.
Meanwhile, Akainu and the rest of the Navy
chase down the pirates
in the name of justice.
The battle shows no sign of coming to an end,
but only increases in intensity!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Insatiable Akainu!
Lava Fists Pummel Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!