Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago
to go on to the next stage - the New World.
Rise to the top!
You guys!
I've got a lot of things that I want
to share with you but in any case,
thank you for going along with
my selfish decision for 2 years!
Set sail!!
"A Surprising Fact!
The Man Who Guarded the Sunny!"
Brother, it's hard to dig!
SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO
That's because this island is
made mostly out of tree roots.
Please forgive us, don't bury us!
I'll do anything, just don't kill me!
The captain, Black, forced us to do it!
Once we joined them, we thought...
...we could kill the Straw Hats...
...with high bounties...
...easily from within, as we like!
Drip!
Hey, stop! He's gonna die!
Are you a Devil Fruit eater?
Don't do it!
Yes! I got him...
Huh? What's going on here? Logia?!
But, look what happened!
I thought he just looked different
because I hadn't seen him for 2 years.
The pirate - Straw Hat...
No wonder! He was just a fake.
Do you think the gods
will forgive them, Coribou?
I dig! I dig!
That's right! Let's bury them!
Oh gods! Let us bury these fools!
Don't! Please don't kill us!
But I saw the real Straw
Hat Luffy for myself!
I told you that I had no choice!
THE PLACE WHERE "THE FAKE
STRAW HATS" ASSEMBLED
Dark King Rayleigh stood in our way!
He could even fight Uncle Kizaru equally
- what would you expect us to do?
The Caribou brothers and their crew
and some of the fake Straw Hats...
...got away successfully.
We caught all the others
but 2 Pacifistas were severely
damaged by the real Straw Hats.
One of them was the prototype that
cornered the Straw Hats 2 years ago.
Of course, his strength hasn't changed.
So they must have gotten stronger!
They've improved themselves
in last 2 years, big time!
Make sure to tell the
Navy HQ in the New World.
The Straw Hats are completely revived!
They're gone before you know it.
Monkey-chan and everybody,
they all got stronger.
--Were you watching?
--Yes, I'm a fan of theirs.
You're thinking about
something, aren't you, Ray-san?
Hmm? Well... Yeah...
Hey, that's a nice ship!
I stole it. My house burned
down so I'm living here.
Yeah? And what's your name?
Rayleigh.
I'm Roger! I think we were
destined to meet, Rayleigh!
Destined?
Do you wanna turn the
world upside down with me?
Huh? The world?
Who are you and where you from? Go away!
Your ship is small but it looks like it
can endure storms if you handle it right.
It's perfect for us to set sail in!
Us? Set sail? Don't decide for me.
Why should I join you?
Like I said, to turn the world upside
down! Alright, let's set sail, Rayleigh!
Maybe nothing in this
world happens by accident.
As everything happens for a reason,
our destiny slowly takes form.
At any rate, Luffy looks great in that hat,
better than ever.
Maybe I want to live a little longer.
UNDER THE SEA NEAR SABAODY ARCHIPELAGO
The surface is far up there already.
What a view!
Submarines can't have windows this wide!
We're sinking and sinking!
I can't stop worrying about flooding!
Feels like we're leaving the
inhabited world. It makes me nervous!
C-C-Can we go back on the
surface again for sure?
I-It's not like I'm scared but...
It's beautiful down here!
Look at that!
Trees... No, roots!
Oh yeah! Come to think of it,
Sabaody Archipelago consists of giant mangroves!
I'm overwhelmed by the beauty of nature!
I'm so surprised - my eyes could pop out!
I don't have eyes though!
I've seen this already.
Yeah, because you got on the wrong ship!
Shut up! Everybody's having a great time!
I can't believe these roots are
running down to the sea bottom!
They're enormous and magnificent!
I can't hold it any longer!
Hey, Chopper...
There's something behind that tree!
What?
Wow, it's huge!
How exciting! An underwater
adventure! It's like a dream come true!
Oh, fish!
I think I can catch them!
The fish here look delicious too.
Stop it, you fools!
What if the bubble pops!
Don't ever do that again or I kill you!
Nami-san, give us some dos and
don'ts on the coated ship
before they do something stupid.
Okay, Sanji-kun! Rayleigh-san gave me a note.
Alright, everyone, listen...
She's moving! A real, beautiful woman!
Sanji!
--It's gonna pop! It's gonna pop!
--How can you fly that far with nosebleed!
What?!
Sanji flew out into the water!
It's amazing.
The bubble doesn't break even under
tremendous pressure in this deep water
but things can pass through it like that.
Sanji! Come back!
I feel weak in the water...
Hang in there!
What happened to you, Sanji?!
You've become even more susceptible to women!
This isn't like you!
I feel sorry for him... What happened to this
ladies' man - Sanji-san in the past 2 years?
At this rate, he's gonna
bleed to death once he meets
the Mermaids
that he's longing to see.
I can't help worrying.
We'll have to call for blood
donations at the Fish-Man Island.
I wonder if Fish-Men and Mermaids
have the same blood as humans.
The bubble that coats the
Sunny has the same quality...
...as the bubbles at Sabaody
Archipelago as we just saw.
Stop analyzing the bubble
in such a calm manner!
Yes, Robin's right.
Basically, they're the same.
It stretches to a certain point and beyond
that, it allows things to get through.
Which means if we fire a gun or a
cannon at a creature that attacks us,
the bubble won't break.
Huh? Then, on what occasion
will it break instead?
As you can imagine, when there are too many
holes at once, it'll break. For example,
if we are bitten by a Sea
Kings' fangs, it'll be trouble.
It's coming from behind!
They're fighting... We're safe!
Or if the ship itself breaks up by
crashing into a rock or a trench,
the broken mast or planking will break
the bubble and that also spells danger.
So we have to be careful with
creatures and obstacles in the sea.
As long as we don't do anything
foolish from inside, it'll be fine.
I see! It's tougher than I thought!
But 70% of ships that head
for the Fish-Man Island...
...end up sinking. So be cautious.
What's gonna happen?!
With my Gatling, I can catch
a whole school of fish!
Then let's see which of
us can catch more fish!
Weren't you guys listening to what Nami said?!
"Too many holes" is no good!
Don't ever try it again or I'll kill you!
Damn! Hachi said he'd show us
the way to the Fish-Man Island
so I thought it was gonna be a safe trip!
Oh yeah!
They gave me a lot of lunches!
Since Sanji is sick,
let's eat these, everybody!
I'm so starved!
My bones are starved!
Nami, the ship is gonna
be stable for a while?
Don't we have to do anything?
Nope. We just have to ride
this big sea current for now.
So, yeah, we can continue
on like this for a while.
We don't have much to do until later.
Then we have a little time, huh?
There's something that I
have to tell you all about.
Could it be about...
...The robot's secrets?!
You have more secrets?!
What can you transform into?!
Or you have a secret weapon?!
Tell us, robot brother!
Super Armored Me!
No, I'm afraid...
I'm afraid it's not about that-robo.
Wow, cool! He speaks Robotese!
This is what I wanna tell you about.
Go ahead and eat while you're listening.
Hachi told us that he would show
us the way to the Fish-Man Island
but he got severely injured at Sabaody and
he's under medical care at Fish-Man Island.
He got injured for the same reason as Duval.
He had been protecting the Thousand Sunny.
Around a year ago, the Navy
found out about the Sunny
and those two both faced fierce battles
and were taken out of commission.
Huh? Then how did the ship
remain undamaged after that?
There was someone else who fought for it.
There was someone else?
He's the one who separated us 2 years ago.
The big Warlord - Bartholomew Kuma!
I couldn't believe my eyes when
I got to the Sunny a few days ago...
I've been expecting you.
What are you doing here?!
Mission accomplished.
There isn't even a scratch on the Sunny.
And Rayleigh told me later...
I work for the Revolutionaries army.
Since I have a connection with them,
I wanna let them get away from here.
I think you guys half expected that.
He saved our lives!
And after we vanished from the island,
Kuma-san visited Rayleigh and told him...
I don't have much time left.
I don't know what made him obey the Navy
but he agreed to be a guinea pig and let
his body be modified into a cyborg
piece by piece and he somehow
lost his personality before the War of the Best.
But I don't think he could guess what
each of us would do after we get separated!
Even so he waited for us at the
ship without his personality?
He made Dr. Vegapunk, who modified him,
agree to program a mission into his mind.
"Defend the pirate ship until the day that one of the
Straw Hats comes back to the ship."
That's why, for the past 2
years, without his own memory,
he had been carrying out his own
orders, as a human weapon, waiting for us.
That's insane.
Why did he do such a thing for us?
Terms like "connection,"
"Revolutionaries army,"
remind me about Luffy's father - the
leader of the Revolutionaries army.
I don't know my father that well.
But that bear-like guy was a good guy, huh?
Kuma...
There is no mistake that he's the one
who gave us the past 2 worthwhile years.
We can't even ask him why he
did it but just remember that.
Bartholomew Kuma turned out
to be one of our greatest allies.
But even if we meet him again,
Kuma is now a heartless human weapon.
That's all I have to say.
I appreciate what he did but
there are still some mysteries.
I hope we can find out his motive one day.
Ally?
--Oh, you woke up, Sanji.
--Eat lunch! It's from the Maiden Island!
Maiden Island? Is that
Kuma guy really an ally?
Don't you realize where
I was for the past 2 years?
What kind of training were you doing
at the dream island full of women, Luffy?
Whoa, whoa, Sanji-san, I don't
know what you've been through
but let's enjoy the voyage now!
Do you wanna sing with me?
Stop trying to cheer me up! I feel pathetic!
Brother, there he is. Straw Hat.
I can see that, you fool!
I'm gonna join them this time for sure!
How deeply are we submerged now?
It's getting darker and darker.
We went through the euphotic zone and
we're at the bottom of the twilight zone.
It must be more than 1000 meters below.
It's really quiet.
It feels different from submersibles.
It feels like flying in the sky.
The sky, huh?
I have to start using what
I studied on Weatheria for 2 years.
Whale! There is a whale!
--Laboon! Laboon!
--No, that's old man Whitebeard!
Hey, hey, there is no time
to relax and watch whales.
70% will sink! 70%! I can't just sit around!
I can't believe we have less than a 50%
chance to get to the Fish-Man Island.
I don't see any creatures or Sea Kings
or obstacles that look dangerous yet.
There's something at 6
o'clock! Is it a creature? No...
Are you guys all ready?!
--Yes, brother!
--Yes, yes!
The target is right there!
It's easier to just destroy their
ship and let it be swallowed by the sea
but that's no good because they
won't know who did it to them.
We gotta cut their heads
off and bring them back
to show the world what Caribou is capable of!
Yes!
They're not ready to fight!
It's a complete surprise attack!
Don't make a mistake, guys!
--Yes!
--Yes! Yes!
Hey, guys! There is a ship kind
of thing coming from behind!
--What?
--A ship?
It's coming towards us!
Charge!
--It's a pirate ship!
--They're pushing against us!
Go away! The bubble is gonna pop!
No! They're gonna come through the bubble!
Who are they?
Along with the attacking Caribou Pirates,
the Sunny sinks to greater depths.
They reach the giant
submarine waterfall Plume.
But there, the bane of the high seas,
the Kraken, is living.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Deadly Combat under the Sea!
The Demon of the Ocean Strikes!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!