Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New
World, the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After landing on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen,
they learned about the hideous experiments
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate
but as things got going,
they came to form an alliance with the
Heart Pirates led by Trafalgar Law.
Do as we discussed.
Yeah. While you're taking Caesar
and that woman somewhere else,
I'm gonna find out about the drug.
And Luffy is now headed to
see the Master Caesar Clown.
You will all experience it!
The chemical weapon explosion that
happened four years ago on Punk Hazard!
A world of death in which no one can survive!
And you will learn!
Just how powerful my weapon is,
that it can destroy an island!
And the greatness of the world's best
scientist who created the weapon!
It's me--Master Caesar Clown!
I got you!
"An Intense Battle!
Caesar Exercises His True Power!"
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND--THE
MIDDLE LAKE ZORO'S GROUP
Is that a Slime?
A Slime?
Yes. I was once reading a
book that had a monster...
...that looks exactly like
this one called a "Slime."
I couldn't stop reading it.
The Slime liked to attack women
and its body fluids would only
melt what the women were wearing!
SLIMY, SLIMY
It was such a dirty monster!
NO!!
What?! That's too convenient!
C-Can I borrow that book sometime?!
Me, too!
Fools! Look carefully.
Pinky promise! Huh?
I don't know if it melts your clothes
but you might not wanna touch it.
The fish are dying from the fluid
that it dropped into the lake.
It's like it's made of toxins.
If nothing is done, the poison
will spread all over the lake.
Poison?
Then, samurai-san's torso will...
D-Don't tell me you're going in, Sanji-san?!
Do I have a choice? It's my personal mission!
I'm Sanji, I'm a man! I've got to do it!
Sanji-san!
Do something about the Slimes behind you.
What? Behind me?
Copies of the Slime?!
When did they get here?!
Sorry, Nami-san.
I'm better at swimming than anyone else.
I'll try to get out of the water before
it causes damage to your beautiful body!
Please be careful!
He's risking his life for me
and going into the poisonous lake!
Th-The water is ice-cold!
Where is his torso?
The Slimes are coming toward us!
What should we do about them?
Yeah, what should we do?
Just Monet in the room.
This is the chance.
The Master is not here.
Yeah? Where did he go?
I don't know.
Being such a hideous person, he's
probably watching the fight outside.
I've seen pretty much everything
what I wanted to see on the island.
I'm thinking about leaving here soon.
Oh, we'll miss you.
There is something I could
use your help with though.
Could you come with me?
Are you asking me out? How sweet!
You're such an unfriendly person. What is it?
You'll see.
Alright. I was bored anyway.
Is that the bird woman that
Usopp was talking about?
What?!
CAESAR'S LABORATORY--THE FRONT DOOR
LUFFY'S GROUP
S-Straw Hat caught the Master!
Way to go, Luffy!
Dammit! That bastard!
Straw Hat!
Let go of me, you fool!
No!
That's what Haki can do? I can't
believe Luffy can do that.
He's grabbing a Logia eater!
Straw Hat! Stay away from the Master!
Let's save the Master!
I won't let you guys do that!
Clutch!
Outta my way!
Since Luffy became so strong, I
bet he can easily beat that guy!
We don't know that yet.
What?
With Armament Haki,
it's possible to strike Logia eaters
who you can't even touch normally.
However, unlike the sea or Sea Prism Stone,
it doesn't drain their powers.
We don't really know the extent
of the Gas-Gas Fruit's power.
Don't get carried away!
Armament Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
Gas Robe!
The smoke!
Damn! Gas Robe!
What is this?
I can't shake it off!
Luffy, hold your breath!
The guy who got it is...
Shit! It's poison gas!
Fool! It's no use doing that!
Once you get wrapped up in the Gas Robe,
you can't get away from
it no matter what you do!
How much longer can you hold your breath?!
Just breathe deeply
and drop dead!
--Luffy!
--Dammit!
After countless experiments,
I finally discovered the deadliest gas!
Now, suffer and die!
I have front row seats!
Is he going crazy?!
He's sucking the Master's
poison gas up voluntarily!
--He inhaled it all!
--He'll be dead soon!
I've never seen an idiot like that!
Go to hell!
What?!
Poisons don't work so well
against me now, I guess.
Thanks to Magellan.
Magellan?! The venomous
fool from Impel Down?!
I'm not like that pathetic Paramecia eater!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Mace!
Master!
Yeah!
How could he do that to our Master?!
I'll kill him!
Attack Straw Hat!
Yeah!
Stay out of it, weaklings!
W-Weaklings?
Did he call us "weaklings"?
Or did we hear him wrong?
That fool!
I'll show him my Gas-Gas Fruit power!
Armament Hardening!
Gum-Gum...
Come on!
...Gatling!
Gastanet!
What?
Luffy!
That's our Master!
Now, I'm gonna finish you off!
Smilies, wake up!
Smilies?
What?! All of a sudden, they're moving...
Smilies, cling onto Straw Hat!
Jump!
Why are they listening to the Master?!
Luffy, watch out! They'll explode!
Luffy!
Go away!
Gastanet!
Luffy!
Straw Hat's gone!
That was a huge explosion! I don't
think there is even a hair left!
He wasn't strong enough to fight against
our Master, the savior, in the first place!
No... Luffy!
You've got to be kidding!
I'm the greatest scientist in the
world, eater of the Gas-Gas Fruit!
You shouldn't have made me mad!
Master! Master!
Master! Master! Master...
You didn't know who you were messing with!
Oh, that was close!
What?!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
M-Master!
That was a big explosion.
That fool! Did he avoid the
explosion? How fast can he move?!
What a relief.
--S-Straw Hat?!
--Is he invincible?
All right!
How dare you do that to our Master?!
Move out of my way!
Okay, I really got you this time!
Master!
Robin! Franky! Is there anything
that I can put him in?
He's a Logia eater so
tying him up won't do it.
Isn't there a barrel or something?
Whoa-whoa, hold on, Straw Hat!
We, the Navy G-5, are taking him into
custody and putting you guys under arrest!
Fools, be ready for it!
Smoker-san, Straw Hat and
his crew caught Caesar!
Dammit, those fools!
Smoker-san!
Let's go, guys!
Follow Smo-yan and Captain-chan!
Yeah!
You can't escape, Straw Hat!
Straw Hat?
Luffy?
You shouldn't underestimate me.
Luffy!
Oh no!
Robin! I'll draw their attention to me!
You go and save Luffy!
Be careful! That guy's really tough!
What did you do to Luffy?!
Get out of my way!
Strong...
Right!
You're next!
Franky Radical...
...Beam!
Wing!
Luffy!
Robin!
She passed out all of a sudden!
What happened to her?!
Everyone, get out of here now!
Tashigi!
Captain-chan!
Robin, are you alright?!
Robin, stay with me!
Luffy!
You bastard!
Strong...
Ri...
Damn! What's going on here?!
I have them all now!
CAESAR'S LABORATORY LAW'S GROUP
Law?
Who is it?
What's wrong?
Oh no. You look like you're in pain.
Who is there?!
It's me.
Why are you...
...here?!
It's been years.
You've grown up.
Law.
Sanji manages to make it out
of the poisonous lake safely,
but there's little time to rejoice.
They end up surrounded by Smileys,
and are unable to escape from this crisis.
It's in this hopeless situation,
where the samurai reveals his true power.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Samurai Who Can Cut Fire!
Foxfire Kin'emon!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!