Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
While breaking out, Luffy and others
ran into the Warlord--Blackbeard...
...at the staircase in level 4!
I'm gonna save Ace at any cost!
Yeah, I'm not gonna say that it's a waste!
Anything is possible in this world!
I told you that the Sky Island exists!
And so does the One Piece!
It certainly exists!
You all should look forward to this!
In a few hours, we're going to...
...put on a show that's
gonna shake the whole world!
Don't stop, Luffy-kun!
Keep going!
To level 3!
Are you Magellan?!
So you're Blackbeard?!
Yes, indeed!
Hydra!
Ouch! What is this?!
Straw Hat! How did you survive
after I poisoned you?!
He's probably the one who
caused this situation!
I must take his life for sure this time!
Straw Hat!
That poison bastard!
I will never let you get out of this prison!
"Stop Magellan! Ivan-san's
Esoteric Technique Explodes!"
Straw-chan! Don't look back! Keep running!
I won't let you get away!
Hurry up!
Hurry! Magellan's right there!
Let's go all the way to level 2!
This is the last group!
Behind these ones, no one is...
...left standing!
Inazuma!
Alright!
Great Scissors!
Inazuma-san!
Why did you cut the staircase?!
Ivan-sama hasn't come up yet!
Don't worry! Just keep moving!
Ivan-san!
Please be safe!
What are you trying to do here?
What am I trying to do?
If you really can't tell
what I'm trying to do...
...you must be very...
...stupid!
Death Wink!
Heehaw!
Now things are getting serious!
Even if you buy yourself some time,
Straw Hat and others can't get out of here!
"Buy some time?"
So you think that you can beat me?
Kamabakka style - New Kama Kempo!
Feast your eyes on this!
Kama!
Heehaw!
Hey hey! Come on now!
Long underpants!
Chemise!
It's odd! The poison bastard
was right behind us while ago!
I saw Ivan-san and Inazuma
stopped in the lower level!
What?!
So they're fighting the poison
bastard! Let's go back!
Gimme a break!
If they're fighting, we gotta keep moving!
You have to believe in the
power of the miracle-worker!
Spin, spin!
What's wrong with this floor?
They can't be this lax.
It's strange! I don't see
any prisoners in the cells!
And all the doors are open!
I wonder who released them!
Come on, get out! Let's
get back on the street!
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
Yes! I'm so glad!
I'm out!
You gotta do your part!
--Here you go!
--Thanks!
Take this!
Shoot! Shoot!
Keep going! Keep it up!
Come on, get out! Let's
get back on the street!
Thank you, Captain Buggy!
Yes! I'm so glad!
I'm out!
You gotta do your part!
--Here you go!
--Thanks!
Take this!
Keep going! Keep it up!
Luckily getting out of level 2
blocked by Magellan's poison,
Captain Buggy and merry prisoners
are heading to the main entrance.
They're on level 1.
Running through level 4--the Burning Heat
Hell and level 3--the Starving Hell,
the mob of New Kamas led by Straw Hat
Luffy and the assembled freed prisoners...
...are now running through
level 2 - the Wild Beast Hell.
And Warden Magellan who was on their tail...
...is fighting with the queen
of queers Ivankov in level 3!
M-My spine has... mmm... got hurt!
D-Damn Ivankov!
Heehaw!
That's unforgivable!
Get them right now!
How long... mmm... are
you gonna keep sleeping?!
And the 4 demon guards who have been
beaten but come back repeatedly...
...are heading to level 1 by elevator.
Jail Manager Shiryu who switched
sides cut all communication lines
so no one would find out the
situation inside the prison.
Those unprecedented dramatic events keep
expanding literally behind closed doors.
Navy ships and prison ships are
anchored around the prison!
If we're able to steal one of them, we can
get to Marineford before Ace-san's execution!
Great! Wait for me, Ace!
Ace's imminent public execution is...
...in 4 and a half hours!
My face... My face is gonna melt!
My face... My face...
My face... My face... My face is...
...gonna melt... melt... melt...
...Or not! Because I've
got so much make up on!
"It's not gonna melt?!" Heehaw!
"You got me there!" Heehaw!
Heehaw!
Death Wink!
Wink! Wink!
Death Wink! Wink! Wink!
Wink! Wink! Wink!
Wink! Wink!
Venom Blowfish!
The lace... My bootlace...
...came loose... loose...
...loose... loose... loose...
...Or not! Because they're laceless!
Heehaw!
"There's no lace?!" Heehaw!
"You got me there!" Heehaw!
This is foolish.
What?
It's foolish of you trying to gain some time!
You think so? I'm having so much fun!
Alright then, let's get it over with.
Between you...
...and me!
New Kama Kempo: 44 - Aesthetic Technique!
Hair Removal Fist!
Ivan-san!
Venom Road!
Oh no...
Keep Out!
Are you here to stall me, too?
Here they are!
The 4 demon guards all
together after all this time!
Run!
It's over! Let's go back!
We can't fight them!
Let's just forget about breaking out!
What?!
Hey, are you okay?
You bastard! What are you...
...dile?!
B-B-B-B-Boss!
Huh?
Oh, it's you, Mr. 3.
What are you doing here, you useless trash?
W-Who released this pain in the butt?!
C-Captain Buggy!
They KO'd the demon guards!
What?!
S-S-Straw Hat?!
T-That's the Warlord Jimbei!
Good! You guys are okay!
GOOD! YOU GUYS ARE OKAY!
It breaks...
...My heart!
Captain Buggy!
A bunch of prisoners and perverts
are
coming up one after another from level 2!
Perverts, too?! What the hell?!
Who are you calling perverts?!
You two! This is for walking
out on us back there!
You're here, too, Mr. 2!
What're you doing to Captain Buggy?!
This is no good!
These level 4 prisoners
came all the way up here at last!
They managed to get away
from Warden Magellan?!
Jeez! We allowed two riots at the same time!
Where's Warden now?!
Hydra!
Magellan's here, too!
What's going on on this floor?!
What?! Then Ivan-chan and Crab-chan are...
Finally, Magellan catches up to Luffy and the others.
Luffy, in order to help the others off level 1,
holds Magellan at bay with the aid of Mr. 3.
Meanwhile, Jinbei makes it to the entrance with the prisoners,
but Magellan has one more thing up his sleeve!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Magellan's Tricky Move!
A Foiled Escape Plan!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!