Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition -
in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize -
and won the first round.
Meanwhile, Usopp and the others
learned about the nightmare
in Dressrosa a decade ago...
...from a toy soldier who is looking to
take down Doflamingo.
Please stop!
If there's no preventing me
hurting the citizens...
Somebody, please kill me!
We're here to save this country!
My name is Don Quixote Doflamingo!
The country fell into the hands
of Doflamingo in just one night.
We believed that King Riku went crazy
at that time, too,
so we got in touch with the new king Doflamingo
and ended up like this.
I'm so ashamed of myself
for distrusting King Riku!
I see! It's really too bad!
You let the innocent king that you
all admired so much die for nothing.
No, he's still alive!
There were soldiers who got killed
and who surrendered.
But when you sum it up,
it doesn't add up to a
whole army for a country!
In addition, they must've been feeling angry
since Doflamingo turned them into toys.
That unknown number of those poor people
is the key to our plan!
"A Showdown Between the Warlords!
Law vs. Doflamingo!"
Hey! I'm here!
--Zoro! Kin'emon!
--Luffy!
Don't shout, idiot!
Somebody's gonna find us!
--Shh! Shh! Please!
--Oh, sorry!
But I'm glad to see you!
I wasn't so sure about that man
who talks so weirdly
but it seems like
he did what he had to do.
Where is he?
He collapsed on our way here.
Really? What is wrong with that guy?
I don't know.
There you are.
Straw Hat!
Joker wants me to kill Straw Hat?
Finish it up before the competition's over.
Then, you'll get promoted to be...
...an executive of the Family.
I'm sorry, Straw Hat. But I...
I wanna get on board Doflamingo's ship!
Hey, Bellamy! Don't give up!
I'm not holding a grudge
against you anymore.
I'm done picking on you.
Yeah, and then
he suddenly collapsed...
Hey, Luffy. What's wrong?
Nothing.
Then, I got lost.
I didn't know which way to go, so...
Ah! There you are, Bellamy!
Hey, have you killed him already?
You haven't, have you?!
What do you want, Dellinger?!
DELLINGER - A COMBATANT
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE DIAMANTE ARMY)
Well, I thought you were gonna mess it up.
The assassination of Straw Hat.
What?!
Well, what can you do?
He's a strong guy.
But it doesn't matter
if you can get it done or not.
What do you mean?
I mean he wasn't that serious
about the assassination.
He doesn't want you to follow him about
so he told me to finish you off here.
That's Young Master-sama's order.
No way...
I shouldn't have told you that!
Oh no! Sorry!
You've got to be kidding!
No more...
...chitchatting.
Prepare to die!
ON THE IRON BRIDGE CLOSE TO DRESSROSA
Room!
What's the matter, Law?
I thought that you wanted to kill me!
Room!
Takt!
Scalpel!
Law, that fool!
He looks exhausted!
You can't get away from me, brat!
Room!
Shambles!
What the hell?!
The power of the Op-Op Fruit, huh?
How annoying.
But if I'm correct,
your power has a limit, doesn't it?
You've dealt with the meteorite that Fujitora
brought down and fought me once
and then rescued Black Foot.
I wonder how much longer it'll last.
Bullet String!
Room!
What are you gonna do now, Law?
Dressrosa is right there.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Hey, Doffy.
Diamante.
Oh, sorry.
Are you in the middle of something?
No, it's okay. Go on.
Violet betrayed us.
Black Foot was here
so I thought something was wrong.
We were gonna find out what the
Straw Hats were up to
with her Glare-Glare Fruit power
but we still don't know.
Oh, don't worry about it.
Diamante.
Deploy Lao G. and others
at the entrance to the SMILE factory.
Whoa-whoa, no way!
They have to fight in the finals
and make the people happy.
I'm sure you can handle it
by yourself.
Stop! You make it sound like
I'm some kind of genius.
Only you can do it.
Like I said, you make it sound like I'm...
Admit it. You are a genius.
Okay, I'll do it if you insist!
Clank!
Doflamingo... You bastard!
Law.
While you're drawing my attention as a decoy,
other members of the Straw Hats
are planning to destroy the factory.
Even if you die here,
as long as the factory is destroyed,
Kaido will kill me once
I lose all the SMILEs.
Isn't it how your little scenario goes?
But you can't buy time as you'd hoped
and the Straw Hats aren't doing so well.
You said you were just using them
but if you didn't trust them,
you couldn't plan something like that.
How can you trust...
...Straw Hat so much?!
Because I know
the "D" will blow up a storm again!
And what do you want, Zoro?
You fool! Why didn't you tell me
there was this kinda competition?!
Sorry, sorry!
You were having fun while I
was running around the town!
Hey, that's not what we're here for!
How could you let that old man beat you?!
What were you doing?!
I didn't get beaten!
--Didn't you see my Gum-Gum Thor Elephant Gun?!
--That's... No mistake!
Vice Admiral Bastille!
That was the "Pirate Hunter" as I thought!
And the guy in the Colosseum is...
...probably Straw Hat Luffy!
"SHARK SLICER" BASTILLE - A NAVY VICE ADMIRAL
So he was the winner of Block C, huh? Lucy?
No wonder he was so strong-dara.
As Smoker said, they are in this country.
Should we catch them?
No, leave them at large for now.
There are a bunch of
infamous pirates, highly-skilled
bounty hunters and mercenaries...
...from the New World
gathered in the Colosseum now-dara.
If we try to catch the Straw Hats
and make a scene,
they'll know that we're here-dara.
We're gonna catch every one of these badasses
as they come out of the Colosseum.
We wanna catch them
in one fell swoop-dara.
The ones that already got eliminated are
Don Chin Jao from Block C and...
Sai? Boo? Abdullah?
Why did I write down these names
that I don't even know?
Do you know any of these pirates?
What the hell are you talking about-dara?!
They've messed around the New World!
They're very troublesome...
What were those names again-dara?
Oh, yes. Sai, Boo, and Abdullah.
--Sai? Boo?
--Abdullah?
Who are they?
I've never heard those names-dara.
Oh? Who were we here to catch?
Huh?!
Ring, ring, ring...
Is this how you use it?
What are you doing?
Sanji-dono told me to call
once we see Luffy-dono.
Yeah?
Oh yeah, Luffy!
The Colosseum has been besieged
by the Navy.
You don't care?!
That was what we came here for!
OFF THE COAST OF DRESSROSA
Ring, ring, ring...
Sanji! The Snail is ringing!
Must be Kin'emon.
--Really?! I'm gonna get it then!
--Oh no, you can't!
This is the Sunny.
Sanji? It's me!
Luffy!
Alright, Chopper. Call
Usopp with the other one.
Okay!
There!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Clank.
--This is Usopp!
Connected!
Okay, now we have everybody
except Law on the line.
This is Sanji on the Sunny.
We have Nami-san, Chopper, Brook,
Momonosuke, and Caesar here.
Tell me your situation.
This is Kin'emon.
I'm in front of the Colosseum
with Luffy-dono and Zoro-dono.
Okay. What about you, Usopp?
This is Uso...
--This is Franky! I'm with Usopp and Robin!
--What are you doing?!
Listen, guys.
We are currently with...
...the King Riku Army, an anti-Doflamingo
coalition in this country.
--An army?
--Of Little People.
Little People?
Usoland, what are you doing?
This is a meeting for heroes only.
Don't listen!
Yes, sir!
Excuse us!
Hey, Luffy, do you remember?
We met the strange toy soldier
outside of the Colosseum.
Uh-huh. Who are the Little People?
He was actually
the commander of this army.
Oh! The commander of the Little People?!
And all the people here are looking to...
...take down Doflamingo this very day!
Huh? A soldier?
He is willing to sacrifice his life
to destroy this kingdom!
Oh, that's it! The "Toy Soldier"!
Rebecca wants to stop him!
--Franky, stop the army!
--No way!
I was thinking the exact opposite!
Have you talked to that girl Rebecca?!
Uh-huh! She is a really nice girl!
She didn't have much money
but she bought me three lunch boxes!
Despite that, once she entered in the ring,
the audience jeered at her!
I couldn't agree more.
Luffy, I...
I can't follow Tra-guy's plan!
What're you saying, Franky?!
This is how I remember his plan.
After destroying the SMILE factory,
we'll keep Doflamingo alive and
use him to take down Kaido.
But then,
what's gonna happen to these people
who're looking to bring
down Doflamingo today?!
We can't stop these Little People.
It seems like everybody's happy at first
but this country has a very dark side.
They're...
...getting ready to fight a deadly battle
to get rid of that dark side!
They're pretty small
but they have big balls!
This brave, little army is going to challenge
their filthy, monstrous enemy!
I can't...
...let them down!
Do you still think it's better for us
if Doflamingo wins the battle?!
Luffy!
No matter what you say...
I'm gonna fight with them!
Franky...
Soldier-san's gonna die.
Franky!
You're free to go all out!
We'll be there as soon as possible!
Thanks!
All right.
Let's go back!
What?!
I thought you were gonna say that!
What's that?!
What's happening there?!
Issho-san, there is a big fight in the town!
We gotta hurry!
What's that? I heard something
loud from your side!
--What's going on?! The town is...
--It's coming this way!
What the hell?! I can't see a thing!
What's going on?!
What the...
Vice Admiral Bastille! Is that...
Let's go-dara!
What's going on here-dara?
Doflamingo!
Tra-guy!
Stupid brat!
Hey, Tra-guy! Why are you with Doflamingo...
You've pushed it too far!
Cora-san...
Tra-guy!!