Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Let me tell you just one thing.
Slow-Slow Beam!
Huh?!
Remember this good, Straw Hat!
I am Silver Fox Foxy, a man
who obtains whatever he wants.
I'll take the 160 million Berries
along with the gold.
This time for sure, I'll show you
that we, the Foxy Pirates,
are the strongest pirates!
"Fox"
"The Guy Who's the Closest to Invincible?
And the Most Dangerous Man!"
Boss!
Porche!
Hamburg!
Those five all fell.
Boss, what're we gonna do now?
What else?! We're gonna
clear up the humiliation
of the Davy Back Fight by
defeating the Straw Hats.
Porche! Hamburg!
We're gonna go with Operation D!
It sounds fun over there.
I wonder if they're still partying...
Why don't you go, too, Doctor?
I can watch our ship by myself.
I-I'm in charge of watching the ship, too!
I'm also studying. I don't wanna go at all.
Dammit! How dare you trick me?!
Come out, Split-Head!
Hey, cool down a bit, Luffy.
That afro is getting you all worked up...
Yeah, no doubt about it.
The afro boosts your spirits.
Like I said, what's with the afro?!
After we went through
the trouble of saving them...
To think that he returned
our kindness with malice...
Yeah! And he's trying to take
our gold, too?! That's unforgivable!
At any rate, that guy is too optimistic.
If we get serious and go on a rampage,
a ship like this will be shattered
into pieces in an instant...
If the five of us do it...
If the four of you do it...
Anyway, for now, we have to
figure out how to get out of here.
Considering how that Boss is,
I bet he's up to something sneaky!
It seems like we can get out from here.
What?!
What the hell is this room?
Choppy!
Where is Choppy?
Where're you hiding?!
Geez... If you don't come out,
you... will... be... punished!
Is something wrong, Doctor?
Nothing.
You jerk! I hate this kind of joke the mos--
Wait, Sanji!
Luffy...
Hey, you!
Yes?
Where's Split-Head?
Huh?!
Oh, I don't know.
--Oh, you don't know?
--His cluelessness knows no bounds.
--Oh, no! Where did Boss go?!
--Why can't he see it?
--Well, if he's not around, he's not around.
I guess I'll go look somewhere else.
--Even for Luffy, this really takes the cake.
Looks like he's not here.
Luffy!
Hm? What happened?
Luffy, take a close look at the face.
What about the face?
Are you... Split-Head's little sister?!
Argh! Enough with the disguises!
Ahh! You're Split-Head! I got fooled again.
I don't even feel like making a comment.
Take this, Straw Hat! Slow-Slow Beam!
Don't you guys get it?! No one
can escape the Slow-Slow Beam!
Seriously, that beam's a real pain.
Yeah, seriously.
Slow-Slow Beam!
--Nami!
--What?!
Hey, you bastard!
Idiot! Don't come this way!
Sanji-kun! Zoro!
Oh, shoot! It hit them!
Hmph! You dodged it well,
Straw Hat! You play dirty!
Hold it, you jerk!
Does he know what "dirty" means?
Hey, Nami! Let's go!
Okay!
Both of you, be patient for 30 seconds!
What?! Hold on a sec!
N-Nami-san!
--What?!
--There's something on the door!
Let's see... From here on,
women aren't allowed. It's a man's path.
What does this mean?
Beats me. In any case,
let's be careful moving forward.
Is something wrong, Doctor?
Nothing.
That was close.
Yeah, you got that right.
It looks like an ordinary passage.
Yeah.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
What's the deal with these guys?
Oh, I see. Underneath this
passage must be a jail,
and they probably got locked up there
for making blunders or something.
I-I can go through a place
like this with no problem!
Hey...
A-A woman!
--All right!
--It's been so long!
I can't do it! I can't stand being treated like this!
Leave it to me, Nami.
Usopp...
Since they've been locked up in
this dimly lit place all this time,
they must be vulnerable to light.
So if we use this flash ball,
they won't be able to see for a while.
We'll use that chance to
make a break for it, huh?
That's right. Close your eyes, Nami!
All right! Now, Nami!
Okay!
--N-Nami!
--All right! I got her!
Usopp!
--Ahh! Hey! H-Help!
--Let me touch her, too!
Got it! You're saying I should go on
ahead and not worry about you, right?!
--Ahhh! Hey! Hey!
--Ah, the smooth leg of a woman!
--Nooo!
--It's been a while...
--How soft...
Is something wrong, Doctor?
No, nothing.
That was close!
Hm?
Wh-What is this place?
Hey, Nami!
Hm...? Luffy!
What took you so long?
What're you doing in a place like this?!
What am I doing? I'm eating
rice crackers and having some tea.
I can tell that much!
I'm impressed you've gotten this far.
I'll give you credit for that!
However...
Well, however, having Straw Hat stranded here
and you reaching here
are all according to my plan!
Why me?!
That's because you're a navigator as
well as an excellent strategy advisor!
If we eliminate you and Straw Hat,
the Straw Hat Pirates are practically wiped out.
Oh, I see.
Well then, shall we start now?
That's the spirit, huh, brother?
Oh, wow! We can finally beat up Straw Hat?
What are they?
I don't know what that is,
but this one is Gorilla Pants.
N-No, it's not "pants"!
It's the Gorilla Puncher 13!
Here I come, Straw Hat! Gorilla Punch!
Go hide, Nami.
--Okay!
--Gum-Gum...
You haven't forgotten, have you, Straw Hat...?
That when your punch touches these...
...Pistol!
...it'll burn...
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
So you have?!
Luffy!
You should pay attention!
You are the prey of Mr. Donkey Kicker 18.
Hey, Nami!
Water! Water!
Oh, I see... I get it!
Oh, wow.
She's trying to get Boss to forgive them
by humoring Boss with magic tricks.
Are you ready, Luffy?!
The weather forecast is thunderstorm!
Thunderstorm Tempo!
You fool! You thought you could break
the Gorilla Puncher 13 with lightning?!
You really don't get it, do you?!
There's no way you can break something
with rain if it can even withstand lightning!
We'll see about that.
You still don't get it?
Your punches don't work with this guy.
Gorilla Punch Golden Hits!
Fire can be put out with water!
Oh, no! What's he doing?!
Oh? Oh?
Gum-Gum...
...Spinning Top!
Boss! Please don't come this way!
Holy smoke!
Oh, no!
What happened?
That's Boss!
Boss won!
Guys...!
I lost.
See? You took so long
that we missed all the action.
It was because you got lost!
Hey, Straw Hat!
I lost in a fight between pirates,
so I won't whine.
Do what you want with us!
Yeah... Then... why don't you
let them be your crew again?
What? After they tainted the pride of pirates?!
You don't want to?
Straw Hat... You're such a...
Okay, then! For Straw Hat's sake,
you go scot-free!
B-Boss...
Now, go talk to them.
Thanks, Straw Hat.
Will you guys work for me again?
Boss!
Boss!!
At least, his charisma is something else.
Boss!
--It pisses me off for some reason.
--Boss!
What do you think you're doing, Sanji-kun?
Just kidding. I was just kidding.
Take care, Straw Hat!
You take care, too!
Oh, yeah!
--Ah, yeah!
--Stop it already!
You came around, Usopp?
Chopper... Why am I...? Ahhh!
Nami, you jerk! How dare you
desert me and go like that?!
You got it wrong, Usopp. The truth is...
Oh, I see... So that's what happened.
To think that he outwitted my plan...
He's our enemy, but I admit, he's brilliant.
Boss, what are we going to do now?
Are we going to find another opponent
to challenge to a Davy Back Fight?
What do you think?
Boss is cooking up a scheme again.
Listen, guys. Unless we defeat them,
"Fox"
we'll have to keep flying this
ugly pirate symbol forever.
If that's the case, there's only
one place we're headed, right?
Yeah!
I won't let you get away, Straw Hat.
Guys! I see an island!
Hmm...
Looks like it's an uninhabited island.
Ready the anchor! We'll land on the island!
Well then, go find some foodstuffs.
Yeah!
Listen. No rats or frogs, okay?
How self-centered you are. Once it's
in your stomach, it's all the same.
Hey, Sanji!
We got fish, shellfish, fruits...
We got a good catch!
Thanks!
Cheers!
Yummy!
Hey, Luffy! Don't stuff your mouth like that!
You snacked a lot earlier. I can't
believe you're still eating so much!
This still isn't enough!
With this amount of food,
we're gonna run out quickly.
Robin, you should eat now or it'll all be gone.
I'm almost done, so...
No! If you're always reading,
you'll become a worm!
They call it a bookworm, right?!
There you are, Straw Hat!
Guys, are you ready?
Yes, Boss.
We're ready.
Boss, they're all looking this way.
Don't be flustered. Any way you
look at it, this is an ordinary crab.
It's so obvious, it's unnatural.
Don't tell me it's them again.
They never learn, do they?
I wish they'd stop.
Okay. We're gonna destroy their ship!
What the heck?!
This looks yummy!
Hey, don't tell me...
Yeah, he thinks it's a real one.
Argh! Let it go, Straw Hat!
Oh? It's trying to run away!
Dammit. Take this!
Now's our chance! Crab-Crab Punch!
This is finally the end of Straw Hat.
You're just a crab! How dare
you make me get serious?!
Take this!
Oh? Did you guys get eaten
by this crab? How pathetic...
Oh, just get a clue already!
Now, let's leave those guys alone
and continue with our BBQ!
All that activity made me hungrier.
Hey, that one isn't done yet.
Well, I like this way the best.
Oh, no! Boss, I'm hungry.
You idiot! You're hungry?!
And you call yourself one
of the proud Foxy Pira--
Thanks for waiting, Mademoiselle!
This is today's special lunch.
Oh, wow! It looks good!
Please go ahead.
Oh, wow! This is scrumptious!
Please come to our ship, Mr. Cook!
Oh, no! If you ask me that,
Porche-chan, I'll have to consider it!
You should definitely go. I'm begging you, too.
"Fox"
Hello. This is the communications room.
Hi, it's me. Boss is knocked out,
so please come and get us.
Don't worry. He's alive. Well then, see ya.
Mr. Cook! Goodbye! Your food
was very delicious! I was so moved!
You take care, Porche-chan!
Are you really sure you don't have to go?
Don't be ridiculous. If I'm gone,
who's gonna be in charge of
Nami-san and Robin-chan's meals?
Right, Nami-san?
Sanji-kun! Zoro! Let's go find
foodstuffs for emergency stocks!
Okay, Nami-san!
Hey, Chopper. Were you able
to find any medicinal herbs?
Yep. I've collected most of them,
but there may be even rarer ones on this island.
More importantly, something's
been bugging me for a while.
I wonder what this weird groove
is that runs down this path...
Come to think of it, yeah, I wonder what it is.
It looks as if a bicycle passed by.
Hey, hey. This is an uninhabited island, right?
This can't be a trace of a bicycle
when there's no one here.
That's true.
Hey, we're almost through the jungle!
We're suddenly out in a large open space.
Ahh!
What's with Chopper?
He's headed to that rock.
Is there something there?
Ahh!
That darn Chopper!
He must be trying to have that
huge mushroom all to himself!
Hold it!
What's the matter, Chopper?!
Looks like something happened. Let's go!
Ow, ow, ow... Hm?
Whoa! What the heck is this?!
Ahh... Hmm?
A raccoon dog?
I'm a reindeer! See? I've got antlers!
Are you okay, Chopper?!
Who the heck is this?!
What happened?!
What's going on, Luffy?!
What's with you guys?
What's with you?!
Wh-Who's that huge guy?
Who's that guy?!
Robin!
What's wrong, Robin-chan?!
Wh... Why are you frozen?
Robin...
Oh-ho-ho?
Now, now. Don't be so bloodthirsty, guys.
It's not like I'm here on orders.
Since it's a nice day, I took a stroll here.
Orders?! From what organization?!
He's a marine. And he's one of the people
known as the World Government's
ultimate powerhouses.
This guy is?!
Yes... An Admiral at
Navy Headquarters... Aokiji.
Oh, my, my, you've turned
into a good-looking woman...
...Nico Robin...
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
What's wrong?
There're only three officers in the Navy
who hold the position of Admiral.
He's one of the World Government's
ultimate powerhouses.
Huh? Well, yeah, that's about it.
I finally found you, Nico Robin.
What're you doing to Robin?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Navy Headquarters Admiral Aokiji!
The Ferocity of an Ultimate Powerhouse"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!