Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After capturing Caesar,
along with their pirate ally - Trafalgar Law,
they finally arrived at their
next destination - Dressrosa.
"Explore!
A Kingdom of Love and Passion - Dressrosa!"
We made it! Dressrosa!
I said you're too loud, Luffy!
We're in their territory now!
Boy...
This week, I'm...
...super!
I'm gonna find the factory right away
and ka-boom!
I said you guys are being too loud!
We should just go to the town, right?
Yes.
Listen, don't let your guard down.
If we fail to destroy the factory,
it'll mess up our whole plan.
Oh yeah!
I just had a good idea!
Momo!
Alright, go Momo!
To the town without stopping!
Fly!
You're too heavy! Get off of me!
I can't fly and I'm not
gonna enter the island!
My father told me not to!
You can't fly?! What are you talking about?!
I saw you flying!
I don't know what you're talking about!
I said I can't!
I really saw him flying!
But he doesn't have wings.
See? I told you!
I don't remember flying!
E-Even if I did fly...
What's your name?
I-I'll never do such a dreadful thing again!
I'm not gonna fly in the sky!
Huh? Are you scared of heights?
You bastard!
Ouch!
Don't disrespect me!
We warriors don't get scared of anything!
Ow, ow, ow... You!
Stop it, you fool!
What do you think you're doing?!
Ow, ow, ow...
You're unforgivable!
What the hell are they doing?
Luffy-san, he's an eight-year old...
Cut the "warrior" crap!
I'm gonna become the King
of the Pirates someday!
Idiot!
I'm gonna become the shogun
of the Wano Kingdom someday!
Fool!
What did you say?! You eel!
You're so arrogant! You monkey!
Who did you call "monkey"?!
You're being rude to a monkey!
Enough, Momonosuke!
He saved us!
I'm sorry, Luffy-dono. Please forgive him.
Even though he's a child,
he's a proud warrior of the Wano Kingdom.
Having said that,
I can't believe you take an
eight-year old so seriously!
I don't like cowards! Idiot!
You...
I said "Enough"!
Dammit!
--Oh, Nami!
--Yes, yes! Momo-chan, come here!
That monkey is...
I know, I know.
You...
...Damn...
...Brat!
Get off of her!
What's their problem?
Like father, like son!
I didn't know warriors were so sick!
He's right! I wanna call you people "pervs"
instead of "warriors"!
H-How dare you say that!
Hey, Kin'emon! Let's go to the town already!
How should we pervert...
I mean, how should we change
our clothes for a disguise?
Oh yeah!
Dress shirts for men!
Let-it-all-hang-out for women!
This is how people dress in Dressrosa.
Let me change you all so you can fit in!
Dressrosa is the best!
Yeah!
Stop lying!
N-Nami...
Hey.
I want you to keep this.
Is this a Vivre Card?
Yes. It'll point toward an island called Zou
that I talked about earlier.
After handing over Caesar
and destroying the SMILE factory,
I was gonna head for Zou.
My crew is there.
But if anything happens
to us, go straight there!
W-Wait a second!
What do you mean "Anything happens"?
Nothing will happen, right?
Who knows.
What's that?
This is a map that my crewmember drew.
Wow! So terribly drawn!
We're here now, at the
west coast of Dressrosa.
Doflamingo's palace is at
the center of Dressrosa.
The SMILE manufacturing factory must be
somewhere on the island.
We don't have much time.
The Factory Destroying Team must move quickly.
What's this smell?
We, the Caesar Handover Team, will...
...go across Dressrosa and
cross the very long bridge to north
and get to Green Bit.
Why do we have to go across Dressrosa?
We can just take the ship!
All of us together!
I heard it's impossible to travel by water.
Oh, that sounds interesting.
P-Please get me there safely!
CAESAR HANDOVER TEAM
Oh no. I have a Fear-of-Dressrosa-itis.
Kanjuro... I hope he's still alive.
And you all, the Sunny's Security Team,
should watch out for the enemy's attack.
Don't let them take the ship!
--What?! What do you mean by that?!
Are they gonna attack us?!
What?! I thought guarding
the ship was the safest!
Guys, we're in the enemy's stronghold.
But we're with Sanji so...
THE SUNNY'S SECURITY TEAM
Huh?! Sanji's not here!
I mean, Luffy and the others are gone, too!
They're the key to this plan!
Where did they go?!
Hey! Who's gonna protect us?!
Visitors to this kingdom are fascinated
by a number of things.
First, by the fragrantly-scented flowers
and the delicious smell of local food.
Smells good!
Second,
the tireless, passionate
dancing of the local women.
Smells lovely!
And another thing...
Hey! Wait! Give it back!
Huh?!
Wait! Mario! Hey!
Give me back my arm!
Boy! You're a bad dog!
The cotton's gonna fall out!
Wait!
No!
I got a side stitch!
Although there's only cotton inside!
S-Stuffed toys?!
A shocking surprise for all
visitors to this kingdom.
Hello!
I am a soldier!
Oh? Have we met before?
Your faces look familiar.
Oh, yeah!
You were in the paper this morning...
Ouch!
Oh no! The strings got tangled up! Help me!
What's this?! A toy?!
Hey, Luffy! Look at that!
Everywhere you look,
blending in with the town
and living side-by-side with humans.
They are living toys.
THE FACTORY DESTROYING & SUMURAI RESCUE TEAM
This is a kingdom of love
and passion and toys.
The port town - Acacia.
A man has been stabbed!
Oh, again?
What do you mean "Again"?
Is there a phantom slasher or something?
No. Women in this country are passionate
about love and most are the jealous type.
So when a man cheats on a woman,
things can get pretty violent.
How scary!
The more beautiful they are,
the more likely to stab a man!
Toys are moving by themselves
but that's okay!
Let's eat!
Hey! Wait, wait!
All right! We're in disguise!
I'm hungry!
Let's go this way!
Hey! Let's eat here!
Excuse me.
I heard there is a gambling
house around here.
Do you know where it is?
I'm sorry, old man.
This is my first visit to this town.
Why don't you ask someone in that restaurant?
Oh, I see. Thank you for your kindness.
What're you doing?!
I don't have time to fool around like this!
I need to look for Kanjuro
as soon as possible!
Whoa-whoa, relax.
I know we need to hurry
but it's better to get some information
rather than just run everywhere.
Isn't it strange?
Their king just abdicated from the throne
this morning.
I thought there would be more confusion.
Maybe, they don't know yet.
No way.
Let's ask. Hey, pops!
Don't!
What's your problem?!
You were on the front page of
the newspaper this morning!
Here's your order.
Thank you for waiting...
...or not!
Here it comes!
I couldn't wait any longer!
Dress Shrimp Paella!
Rose Squid Ink Pasta!
And Fairy Pumpkin Gazpacho!
Everything looks yummy!
Let's eat!
Yum-yum!
What's "Fairy Pumpkin"?
Um, that's... In this country,
we still believe in a myth about fairies!
Or not!
What kind of myth?
Well, people claim to see fairies! Or not!
Seeing fairies?
Yes! Isn't it interesting?
For centuries!
Even though most of us haven't
seen them, they do exist.
People call those fairies...
..."guardian deities of Dressrosa"!
Or not!
Ah, shut up!
Well, you travelers, please
take care of yourselves.
Or not!
Boy...
They are stranger than fairies.
He got it right again! 14 times in a row!
What's going on?
It's a little noisy back there.
It's a roulette game.
Some blind man is on a winning streak.
A blind man?
Place your bets!
I've made up my mind.
Black, please.
Did you hear it? It's black!
--I bet on black!
--Me, too!
Me, too, of course!
No more bets!
It's black 29!
Oh, it's black!
I can't believe it! That
was 15 times in a row!
Thank you! Really, thank you!
We became very rich thanks to you!
Boy, what should I say?
I was just lucky.
It's not that much but
keep it. It's a present!
This is from me! Go for more!
--This is from me!
You are quite a gambler, huh?
Let's play just me and you! What do you say?
What? Just you and me?
That's right!
I wanna play a game against
such a very lucky guy!
Don't tell me you're gonna quit now.
No, I got chips from everybody as you see
so I'm going to play a lot more.
Good! I like you, old man!
So everybody else, please
go to the room in the back
to exchange your chips.
Now, place your bets.
White, please.
Oh, okay.
Then, I bet on black.
How does it go? What is it?
I'm sorry! It's black!
You were off!
Oh, did I? Then I'll get it right this time!
Okay, white!
Let's see.
You've missed it again. It's black 20!
It should be white this time!
It's black again!
White!
It's black!
Black!
White!
I'm sorry!
It's black!
That's awful!
They're a disgrace to Don Quixote!
What's the matter with them?
Okay, say goodbye to your bets!
We can make a lot of money
when Buffalo-san isn't here.
Right.
I guess I'm running out
of luck. This is no good.
What do you wanna do? Do you wanna quit?
No.
One last time.
I bet everything!
Great!
Then I'm gonna bet everything
on whichever color you don't pick.
Let's play it like real men!
Everything? Really?
Yeah.
Alright, let's do it.
Place your bets!
I've made up my mind.
White, please!