Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After landing on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one
burning, the other frozen,
the Straw Hats learned about
the hideous experiments
performed by Caesar Clown, the Master,
and headed off to investigate.
What?
An alliance?
I have a plan...
...to bring down one of the Four Emperors!
"Formed! Luffy and Law's Pirate Alliance!"
An alliance?
Are you saying that if we work together,
we can take down an Emperor?
How absurd!
I don't know what he wants but don't
listen to this jerk's fast-talk, Luffy!
I'm not saying we can beat
the Emperor straight away.
All I'm saying is we'd get a chance
if we advance the plan step by step.
What do you say, Straw Hat-ya?
Which of the Four Emperors
are you talking about?
Hey Luffy, why are you interested?!
We can't trust this guy!
The Emperor's name is...
I see.
Okay, let's do it!
What?!
What?!!
THE STRAW HATS' ENCAMPMENT
What?!
We're gonna form an alliance
with the Heart Pirates?!
You just went out to reclaim Nami!
So how did you come back with
such an eccentric idea?!
Listen...
If we ally ourselves with this
creep who gives me the chills,
I won't be able to sleep in peace at night!
See, Luffy? Everybody's against it.
Let's not do it. It's too risky.
We wanna travel at our own pace.
She's right, Luffy!
Besides, it's too early to even
think about the Four Emperors!
We can't fight them yet!
Hey, treat this racoon.
Forget about some racoon now!
Huh?
What?!
It's me!
Z-Zuber...
What happened?! My body!
Luffy.
I'm gonna go along with your decision
but alliances between pirates
are often marked by betrayal.
Maybe it's dangerous for you
since you are so trusting.
Huh? Are you gonna betray me?
No.
Hey, have at least a little doubt!
Anyhow, a pirate alliance
sounds like fun, doesn't it?
I think Tra-guy is a good man but...
...even if he isn't, don't worry!
Because I have you guys who spent
the last two years training!
What?!
Luffy, you're...
D-Don't mention it! Luffy,
you're making me blush!
Yeah, I know we're zuper dependable but...
We just do what we got to do!
You're not flattering me, you fool!
A-Alright, Luffy! You can count on us!
If Zoro and the others wimp
out, I'll convince them!
I'm counting on you guys!
Room.
Shambles.
I got it back! My great body!
I knew I liked myself the best when I'm me!
Super!
I'm happy for you, Franky!
Don't ever take Chopper's body again. Ever.
I'm...
...back to myself, too, but...
Why are there cuts and
bruises all over my body?!
What did you guys do to it?!
--I'm sorry. It's his fault.
Why?! You went out of
control in Chopper's body
so I had no choice but to stop you!
But you didn't have to use
the same technique you used
to beat the Kraken!
I blame both of you!
--I'm sorry!
You should be happy just being
back to yourself, Chopper.
Why do I have to be in
someone else's body again?
First, it was Franky and now, Sanji-kun!
Nami became Sanji!
You're looking good!
It wouldn't be funny if it happened to you!
It can't be helped.
Chopper and Franky could
go back to themselves because
their bodies were here
but since Sanji went out looking
for the samurai in Nami's body,
you have no choice but take Sanji's body.
Can't you do something about it?!
I can't do anything without your body here.
These are the children?
Yeah, I wanna help them.
I'm giving them this drug candy everyday.
They're such a pain - just forget about them.
I heard they're drugged.
We know! Because I tested them!
I just wanna take them home
but it'll take a while for them to recover
and most importantly, they are so big.
Boy, I can't believe somebody's
doing such a horrendous experiment.
Turning people into giants is a
project that has been underway for
hundreds of years by the World Government.
The Government? For what purpose?
Military might, probably.
If they can produce an infinite
amount of giant soldiers,
they'll become invincible.
Caesar wants to achieve the goal first
and outsmart the Government and Vegapunk
but I don't think it's that easy.
Do you really wanna help them?
You don't even know who they are.
Yes, I do. Although I don't know them well,
they asked me to help
with tears in their eyes.
It seems like the Master tricked
them and brought them here
but they already know there is
something wrong with this place.
Until I know that they are safe,
I won't leave this island!
Are you willing to stay here alone?
I'm not gonna leave my friend behind.
If that's what Nami and
Chopper want, I want it, too.
And Sanji wants to stick the
samurai's body together.
You got to help us if you
wanna team up with us!
I thought so. You have no idea.
You think an alliance is...
...a cooperative relationship just
for some common goal, don't you?
Of course, I do.
Listen. Luffy's idea of an alliance
is a little different from yours.
It's like being friends, isn't it?
If you're thinking of taking control,
it won't be that easy, either.
That's what they say.
Once he feels sure about
something, he won't back down.
It's a pain in the ass!
His selfishness is as formidable
as the Four Emperors.
That must be hard.
But what your friends want has
nothing to do with us at all...
Hey! Don't throw your booger at me, fool!
Oh, sorry!
I can't move right now!
Sorry, sorry!
Okay, I understand. There is not much time.
You guys have to take care of the samurai.
I'll look into the drug
that the kids were taking.
Who is your ship's doctor?
He's got to come with me and help
me research it behind Caesar's back.
Okay, this is good.
I'm sorry but I can't walk
right now so, thanks!
D-Don't drop him, Tra-guy!
Sorry! I shouldn't laugh! But...
Super cute!
Good luck, Chopper.
Count on me!
THE BURNING LANDS
1, 2, 3!
Alright, it's unlocked!
What do they keep in this warehouse?
What's that?
I can't see. It's too dark.
What happened?
Are you mad?
As you can tell from the assassins earlier,
Caesar-ya wants to get rid of you
guys and White Chase-ya's G-5
and take back those children.
Until he gets what he wants,
he won't stop attacking.
He is a former Government scientist,
who became a criminal four years ago.
If the fact somebody is here on
this restricted island leaks out,
he will lose this perfect hiding place.
That's why he'll try to
kill you all at any cost.
A 300 million berry bounty.
A Logia-type Gas-Gas Fruit eater who owns
weapons of mass destruction.
That's who Caesar Clown is.
300 million?
Those of you who can't use
Haki, stay away from him.
He's not just a scientist.
Those who can use Haki among
us are me and Zoro and Sanji.
And you.
I think that's enough.
I'm gonna go back to the lab now.
So what we're gonna do is
kidnap the Master, right?
Yes, that's it.
But why should we kidnap him?
Money? I thought the
Master guy is their boss.
Who else can pay us a ransom?
We're not gonna do it for
money. Just to raise havoc.
--Havoc?
--What do you mean?
There's no point to tell you
what lies ahead before we
even kidnap him successfully.
Focus on capturing Caesar Clown for now.
It's not gonna be easy.
Uh-huh. Uh-huh.
I'll tell you all the details
of my plan after that. However,
when we kidnap Caesar successfully,
things will start moving
whether you like it or not.
There will be no turning back.
This is the last chance
for you to reconsider.
That's okay. We're with you.
Then, I will go along with
what you guys want to do.
You need to convince the rest of your crew.
Yeah, I got it!
CAESAR CLOWN'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT
You bastard! Damn you creature!
"Rebar" Smoothie!
Fen Bock of the Gourd!
"Rope-Tugging" Chappe!
Smoker-san! They are former
prisoners as we thought!
Just looking a little different.
What's going on here?
Then why did they say none of the
prisoners survived four years ago?!
Smo-san, what are those people?!
How should I know?!
In any case, just hold them back!
We have to put the ship to sea...
...to make a report!
Shoot! Shoot!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Master, the Transponder Snail is ringing.
You don't have to take it.
They probably want to report
they opened the door.
"And something came out."
"It attacked our comrades. Help us."
They'll just go on like that. Quite annoying.
We don't often have this many visitors here.
You can stop gathering test subjects now.
What?
Hello?! Master?! Hello?!
Please come in!
We're in the Burning Lands! We
opened the door as you said!
No good! The Master is not picking up!
It's coming! What is that?!
It came out of the building!
It killed all of our comrades! Just run!
--Wh-Which way?!
--Th-This way!
What is that thing?! It's
bigger than a mountain!
It's coming! Help me!
Master!
Let me tell you about my pet.
It's a very rare slime-type creature.
Master...
No one...
...can leave this island!
How does it feel to be loose after so long,
Smiley?!
The ultimate weapon that Caesar created...
While its identity is slowly coming to light,
the Straw Hats make their move to capture Caesar.
However, Luffy's actions cause the
situation to go in an unexpected direction.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Capture M!
The Pirate Alliance's Operation Launches!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!