Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're gonna make you rue the
day you picked a fight with us!
Gecko Moria, we're taking back
twice the amount of food you stole!
And before dawn!
Yeah!
This spells trouble! I need to
hurry and inform the master.
What?!
The people we stole shadows from
couldn't possibly be awake!
I-It looks like their friends
whacked them awake!
Come to think of it,
where the heck is Absalom?!
Uh, about that...
His wedding ceremony is about to start...
The majority of the General Zombies
are attending his wedding.
This incident doesn't call for that beast.
What?
I'm going back to my room.
Come on, Kumacy.
Okay! I'm coming.
I'm going to stay here for a while.
I want to play with Oars.
Then I have a favor to ask of you.
Where is Moria?!
Stay away!
Give my food back!
Huh?
We're falling!
Usopp! Sanji!
The whole lot of them fell
when the stairs gave out.
Forget about those two
who came hurtling down.
What the hell is that?
It came out of nowhere
and it's blocking our path!
What is this wall?!
This isn't made out of stone...
No! What the heck are you two doing?!
That is Luffy's zombie!
"Usopp's the Strongest?
Leave Anything Negative to Him!"
"Moria's Dance Hall"
"Perona's Room"
Usopp and Sanji fell downstairs.
Aren't we going after them?
Nah! Those two should be fine!
We need to make our way to Moria
and pluck that giant shallot
before it gets up and moves!
Got it! That's the quickest way
to solve all of our problems.
That entrance leads to the dance hall
where he stole your shadow, Luffy!
Beyond there is a giant freezer.
That's the last place we saw Moria!
All right!
Didn't Perona take you down?!
Hogback...!
Who is that reindeer?
So that is Dr. Hogback...
He was with Moria!
May I give him a sound beating?
H-Hold your horses!
Wait, Luffy.
Could you leave him to me?
See that doorway in the back?
It leads to the freezer. Go on ahead!
Okay, you got it!
You can't skip straight to Moria-sama!
Learn some manners!
Cindry-chan, get him!
Certainly.
One!
Two!
What was that? A plate?
Looking good, Cindry-chan!
I won't miss again.
Three!
What's the matter, Cindry-chan?
What's that?!
Feel free to go ahead, Luffy.
'Kay! Thanks, Robin!
Wait, dammit! Straw Hat!
Hogback!
You've disappointed me!
I refuse to consider you a doctor!
I didn't recognize you, Dr. Chopper!
You were a Zoan type power holder?
No wonder I thought you were
such a peculiar creature...
I don't know how you escaped
on your way to Perona's garden,
but that won't happen again
now that I've run into you!
I will get your shadow!
Nah. How about I kill you
and use your body as a mario?
They'll do the dirty work!
That penguin...!
Sanji's shadow is inside of it!
Huh? Then what about the other one?
That's right! If the zombies act just like us,
then I saw your zombie, Zoro.
What was he like?
No different from you.
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame!
They aren't anything alike!
Indeed not.
Go! Wipe the floor with them!
Okay, Hogback-sama.
Who should we take out first?
That damn reindeer.
This hallway is surprisingly long!
Sweet! I finally reached the end!
Now where am I?
Found ya!
Hey! If it isn't you.
Wh-What...?
Wh-Why is he so freakishly big?!
What is he, some demon lord?!
I've never seen a giant this big before!
Isn't he a zombie?
This is...
Luffy's...?
Crap! We're doomed!
He's here to kill us!
Eek! Gulp!
What's he gonna do now?!
No!
I like this!
Sweet! Now I feel the part!
I'm gonna become the
rottin' King of the Pirates!
Man, I totally freaked out
when the building collapsed.
Wh-What gives?
Didn't he notice us?
He really sounded just like Luffy.
That body with Luffy's fighting
abilities might be a problem!
Why don't we give up on your shadows?
No way!
Even if you convinced me to,
I'd still want to save Nami-san!
Pull yourself together!
The lack of stairs is going to be a problem.
It looks like Usopp and I got knocked
down along with the entire stairway.
Even if we switched to this path,
the bridge here is also toast.
All of the paths leading to the mansion
by the mast have been cut off.
And none of us could make that jump.
There goes our shortcut...
There'll be gobs of zombies
along the long way...
Just give me thirty seconds!
Something about this design
doesn't seem right...
You built a bridge!
I could make a bridge or two easy with
all this wood and debris everywhere!
But didn't you go a bit overboard with
the details for a makeshift bridge...?
Are you telling me to do a half-assed job?
Hardly! This was a huge help!
Anyway, you were a lifesaver! Now, let's go!
What's with this room?
Isn't this room rather ostentatious?
I had planned on sacrificing you to the
zombies on the stairs and the bridge.
I never expected Oars to come crashing down.
He just had to interfere!
Those ghosts...!
I never would have suspected
that she was controlling them.
What the heck are they?!
You already know just how
terrifying these ghosts can be!
Having eaten the Hollow-Hollow Fruit,
I am an incorporeal human
capable of creating ghosts at will.
These ghosts are my clones.
They make people's hearts feel hollow.
You've reached the end of the line!
I can't believe that cutie is the mastermind
behind those annoying ghosts!
Save that for later!
If her attack hits us, we'll be goners in no time!
Our only option is to flee!
I can't fight ghosts!
Run for it!
Negative Hollow!
Mackerel... I'm worse than mackerel...
Yeah! I want a feral dog to step on me!
I'm sorry for walking on the same earth...
...as everyone else!
It's over! It's all over!
Apprehend them.
Yes, ma'am!
That was too easy.
Now to deal with the group upstairs.
Wild Shot: Salt Star!
Who did that?!
I won't let you...
...hurt my crew!
Shoot! He only pretended
to get hit by my attack!
I'll finish you off for real this time.
Negative Hollow!
What?!
My name is Captain Usopp.
Why?! Why aren't you falling to your knees?!
My ghost clearly hit you!
How did you counter it?
I didn't do anything to counter it.
I've always been negative!
What?!
He held out against the ghost's negative power!
This man is incredible!
Perona-sama!
That's absurd!
No one in the world could possibly
be immune to my Negative Hollow...!
Perona-sama!
People are alive...
That alone should be enough to
keep us looking forward with hope!
But this man...!
Hang in there...
--Hang in there!
Hang in there!
Hang in there! Hang in there! Hang in there!
"Live!!" "Hang in there!!!" "Fight!!"
--Hang in there! Hang in there!
--Don't try to cheer me up!
Snap out of it, guys!
You've gotta hurry and rescue Nami and Brook!
You guys--your abilities--
are powerless before this chick.
I'll take her on!
Dude...!
Why does he seem so dependable?
That didn't work on him?
Curse you!
But take out all of these
zombies before you go!
I can't defeat them! I'm sure I'd die if--
I'll let you handle things here!
Eh? Uh, no! That's not what I meant!
No! Hold up!
Wait!
I'm done going easy on you.
Do you, Absalom, take Nami
to be your wedded wife?
To have and to hold in sickness and
in health, to love for all eternity?
Yeah, I do!
Do you, Nami, swear to love
Absalom for all eternity?
Yes, I rottin' do! I love Absalom-sama!
Then you may kiss the bride.
What's this?
When I pull it, the whole
ship moves. This is fun!
Let's go starboard next!
Which way is starboard again?
I can't remember!
Meatboard! I'll go wherever there is meat!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The General Zombies Are Down in a Flash!!
Oars Feels Like an Adventure!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!