Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
You're going to kick my butt?
Yeah, you heard me!
But considering your level of strength,
you couldn't even lay a hand on me!
Brick Bat.
Gatling!
Damn it! He's blocking all of my punches.
Ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Don't follow me!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
Stop him, Kumacy!
Don't mess with Perona-sama!
I had no idea that stuffed animal
was so nimble and powerful!
And here he can't even reach
the zipper on his back!
Why, you...!
Skip! Skip! Skip!
Nami-san!
Get your grubby hands off her!
Sorry to have kept your waiting,
Nami-san. Your knight is here.
I'm in a foul mood right now.
I don't have time to deal with weaklings like--
Shut up, Fur Face!
Absalom-sama!
Basses Côte!
You said that you were in a foul mood?
That doesn't begin to describe mine.
I'm so mad I feel like my body could explode!
And unfortunately for you, there is bad
blood between us over one other thing!
"A Clear-Clear History? Sanji's Stolen Dream"
A-Absalom-sama...
You... and I... have bad blood?
That's right. You are the man
who stole one of my dreams!
A-A dream...?
Doesn't ring any bells.
There must be some sort of misunderstanding.
You and I...
...met for the first time today!
I'm going to send you flying...
...with my Hands of the Dead!
Take them off.
I said to drop the bazookas
attached to your arms.
Wha--?!
Do I need to spell it out?
If Nami-san gets hurt
because you went overboard,
no one will be able to tell you were ever
alive by the time I'm through with you!
He couldn't possibly know
what I've got up my sleeves!
I said to lose the bazookas!
Wow! A bazooka magically materialized!
Yeah, that's about what I thought.
It seemed like the type of attack
you would come up with.
You can make yourself invisible.
While in that state, you can make
anything you touch go invisible as well.
That is your current ability.
Invisible man born of the Clear-Clear Fruit,
I know every possible move you could make!
Who the hell are you...?!
Has that man met Absalom-sama
somewhere before?
Why does he know his powers inside and out?
What could this "bad blood" possibly be?
Back when I was a kid, I read an
encyclopedia on the Devil Fruit.
I had no interest in a shady object that
would make the ocean grow to hate you.
But there was one and one
alone that caught my interest.
I decided that in the unlikely
event I came across that Fruit,
I would eat it, even if it meant
losing the ability to swim!
But there aren't two identical
Devil Fruits at the same time!
If I ran into someone with that ability,
my dream would go up in smoke!
Now do you get it? I wanted
to become an invisible man!
That's why I said that you've
crushed one of my dreams,
since you ate the Clear-Clear Fruit!
He's venting?!
I put a lot of thought into my dream!
If I ate the Fruit, I'd use my
abilities to watch women bathe!
No! Just think of all the things I could
use it for. I could... watch women bathe!
No! Just imagine how I could help others.
I could... watch women bathe!
All you're really thinking about is
how you could watch women bathe!
Shut up! After long years
of imagining what I'd do,
I am fully aware of what I could see--
no, what I could accomplish with that ability!
Between this and endangering Nami-san,
you have compounded
transgression upon transgression,
making it impossible to forgive you!
Prepare to wave goodbye to watching
women bathe--no, to your life!
I was wondering what your problem was!
You're picking a fight over the stupidest thing!
Y-Your complaint is beyond absurd!
It certainly is.
You're a freaking pervert!
You're not one to talk!
He has a point!
But they're equally bad!
Have it your way!
I will throw your sudden claim of
bad blood and rage right back at you!
The lion muzzle wasn't my only transplant!
Elephant skin!
300kg of compact bear and gorilla muscle!
Dr. Hogback has conducted one
transplant after the next on this body,
allowing me to become the
ultimate beastly masterpiece!
The Clear-Clear Fruit's ability is a mere bonus.
Next to my strength, it's nothing
more than an accessory.
Get it?
But...
You still peeped!
You're absolutely right!
If a normal person kicked me,
my body would break his leg...
But he's kicking me like I'm a normal man...!
Regardless, I will be the last one laughing!
I have claimed the power you so desired!
And the woman you longed to
protect is about to become my wife!
I could not imagine a more bitter defeat!
When he abducted her,
Nami vanished with him.
We lost his trail after that!
You wanna make Nami-san go invisible!
But you can't have her!
Where do you think you're looking?
You're wasting your energy!
It's time I showed you...
...the power of a Phantom!
What's this? You're going to
sacrifice yourself for that woman?
Protect her! Assuming you've got what it takes!
Phantom Hand!
Phantom Leg!
I wouldn't drop that woman if I were you!
Damn beast!
Sorry, Nami-san...
You dropped her! I guess you didn't
value her as much as your own life.
I'm sorry...
I can't soil your pure
white dress with my blood...
Damn invisible man, sneaking around!
I'm totally over my dream now!
I don't care if I can't turn invisible anymore!
I'll peep without any special powers!
You're still going to peep?!
Let go, bastard!
Unhand me!
I'm not about to let go, you sick beast!
If you're a mix of a bunch of animals,
I bet you'll make lovely mincemeat!
Shut up, jerk!
Let go of me!
Extra Haché!
Absalom-sama!
A beast should be satisfied
with watching women bathe--
Scratch that! With a beastly bride.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow, ow!
Let go of me!
Ow, that hurts!
--Ow, ow, ow! L-Let go!
--Don't worry. They won't suck your blood.
What was that about
kicking my butt? What a joke!
Get away from me!
Your lack of experience is going
to make you humiliate yourself
when you underestimate others, greenhorn.
Damn it! Gum-Gum...
Brick Bat!
Ow, ow, ow! Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Ow, ow, ow, ow!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
You jerk! Now I'm ticked!
Gum-Gum...
Why did you jump over the rail?
Trying to run away?
...Stamp!
That hurt, brat!
Take that! So much for me not being
able to touch you, Giant Shallot!
He's still in hot pursuit!
If he was out of the picture,
I could take down the other pirates!
Stupid Mr. Negative Nose!
He's still chasing after me!
If he was out of the picture, I could
take down that Horo-Horo Chick!
Stupid bear zombie!
Wait!
Stay away!
Wait, Horo-Horo Chick!
Stay away! Kumacy, hurry and finish him off!
Wait!
Horo-Horo Chick!
Kumacy!
Don't you dare harm Perona-sama!
That was close! Too close!
Perona-sama!
Scary!
No!
Sweet!
Why is that stuffed animal
so freakishly strong?!
Wait! Wait!
Oh, yeah!
Eat this! Special Attack! Flame Ball!
Yikes, this is bad! It's fire!
Fire!
It worked! It totally worked!
A zombie is still a zombie!
And with this oil, I'll cast the
"You Cannot Cross This Point" spell!
What?!
Dumbbear! Now you can't come after me.
This makes me invincible.
If I don't have to worry about you,
that Horo-Horo Chick will be a pushover!
I, like, rule!
Now then, I think I might teach
that Horo-Horo Chick a lesson,
since she's weaker than me!
Huh? Where did she go?
Over here, Mr. Negative Nose.
Huh? I don't see you.
Could she be outside?
No, she couldn't be out there...
We're up on a really high fl--whoa!
D-Dang! Why are you flying?!
I thought you could only control ghosts!
Wh-What exactly is your power?!
Don't underestimate the power
of the Ghost Princess, moron!
I just figured out how I'm
going to take you down.
Once I knock you off,
the others will be easy pickings!
Wait a sec! This is not what I was expecting!
What's wrong? You haven't
landed a single attack on me.
Just a sec! See, I can attack
by sniping, being negative,
bluffing, and, uh, using my 8,000 subordinates!
Man, I'm screwed! Why doesn't any
of it work on that Horo-Horo Chick?
What should I do? What now?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save Me, Hero!! My Enemy
Is the Immortal Princess!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!