Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Perona-sama!
Moria-sama is summoning the Three Phantoms.
The master beckons? Whatever for?
I've heard that Straw Hat
Luffy has been captured!
He wants to make a show
out of reanimating No. 900!
Absalom!
What are you doing here? This is my room.
Welcome back, Perona-sama.
Zip it, Kumacy! How many times
must I tell you not to talk?!
I see you're as harsh on Kumacy as ever.
You're beary harsh.
More importantly, have you heard?
The master is summoning us.
They still haven't found us,
if you can believe that.
It's a miracle!
Why did we hide here in the first place?
We didn't have much choice!
Who knew Beast Man was
gonna catch up so soon?
And I didn't realize this was a zombie!
Let's look for a chance to make
a break for it. Sound good?
Absalom-sama!
So this is where you went!
I have something that I'd like to tell you.
What is it?
It looks like we have one more
intruder on top of the pirates.
An intruder?
It's the Humming Swordsman!
What?!
Weapons Left!
Nico Robin!
They've never failed to catch
our prey, not even once!
We hung out quietly in the ceiling
and snatched your friends up.
Now we'll take you to the same
place we took your friends!
Brace yourselves!
♪ Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho... ♪
Who is it?! Who's singing that song?!
♪ Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho ♪
Goodness, I see everyone really
did disembark onto this island.
How did you get up here?
I jumped.
I'm light!
Seeing as you're here, I suppose
you've left me with no other choice.
I shall tell you everything
about this island.
Hey! Who the hell are you?!
You aren't a zombie, are you?
I bet you're with these pirates!
Hey, Skeleton!
Yes, yes. Not to worry.
The fight is already over.
Huh?
Three-Pace Hum...
...Notch Slash!
"Luffy's Emergency Situation!
The Ultimate Shadow's Destination!"
The fight's not over!
Swords don't work on zombies!
He's gonna pop back up!
Curse you...!
Wait a sec...
I've seen you somewhere before!
Not to worry! I've already dealt with that.
How?
Even zombies have weaknesses!
What's that?!
It's the zombie's "soul."
His soul?! But I can see it leaving his body!
C-Captain!
It's high time you returned...
...to your rightful master!
Captain Tararan!
Captain! He took out the captain!
Captain!
He isn't budging an inch...
What did you do?!
I purified him.
You what?
Look! He's definitely the
"Humming Swordsman"!
Five years ago, he wreaked
havoc on Thriller Bark.
We've gotta tell the master!
Hurry! Hurry! Hurry!
That spider web is strong
against physical attacks,
but weak against fire.
What?
You're right! It melts right off!
They got Straw Hat and the others.
Y'know, you seem mighty
knowledgeable about this island...
I am, but I don't know where to begin.
If they've been caught,
we're probably too late.
What?! It's too late?!
P-Please don't yell at me!
It makes me jump under my skin!
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have any skin!
It's my skull humor!
Don't bother. He's already dead.
Anyway, please put the
joking aside and hear me out.
Don't bother! He's already dead.
As I already told you,
without a working rudder,
I spent decades wandering these seas alone.
Even if I wanted to escape
from the Devil's Sea,
I was at the mercy of the tide
because of my broken rudder.
Now let's go back to about five years ago.
Much like you and your crewmates,
I was "invited" to Thriller Bark.
Desperate to leave the Florian Triangle,
I walked around this island in hopes
of finding the parts I
needed to fix my rudder.
I wonder if anything is down here... Nope.
What is that?! Crap! Crap! Crap! Crap!
Scary! Help me!
Freaky! I hate ghosts!
All I found were monsters and zombies.
In the end, they caught me and
brought me here to this building.
Inside, I saw...
...a martial arts dancer who
they caught before me...
...and a type of corpse covered
in stitches called a "mario."
A ghastly giant appeared before them!
It was incredible!
He peeled the man's shadow off the ground...
...and snip, snip!
He cut the man's shadow off?
I questioned my eyes!
Not
that I have any eyes.
You're asking for a knuckle sandwich!
Feel free to let him have it.
Shortly thereafter, I suffered the same fate.
The man who lost his shadow
collapsed on the spot.
His severed shadow was stuffed
into the inanimate mario.
Now what do you think happened?
The "mario" corpse got
up and started to move!
How's that work?
Shadows are our "second souls" that are
always with us, moving as we dictate.
That is true of your shadows as well.
Normally, these "souls" always stay with you,
following your every moment from
the moment you're born until you die.
There is a giant of a man who captures
them and makes them do his bidding!
He is one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea, Gecko Moria!
He has eaten the Shadow-Shadow Fruit!
A Devil Fruit, huh?
Is he the one who stole your shadow?
A certain man stole my
shadow a few years ago.
Your shadow?
Does that sorta thing actually happen?
Yes, it does.
And having lost my shadow, I am no
longer able to exist in the world of light.
I cannot live under the light of the sun.
What would happen if you
were hit by the sunlight?
If I was directly hit by sunlight, my body...
...would be obliterated!
As long as he has a corpse, he can use
a shadow to turn it into a zombie.
The real problem is that his cohort
is the genius surgeon, Dr. Hogback.
He can reconstruct the body,
making it stronger than before!
Sometimes he uses his medical
expertise to revive the flesh
of legendary warriors from around the world.
And he has a tremendous collection of mario
currently preserved in his lab freezer.
Dr. Hogback...
I didn't realize the renowned
doctor has been here
assisting a pirate ever
since he went missing.
So those zombies are reanimated corpses,
but it's not like he actually
revived the dead, huh?
Exactly!
The shadow provides their
personality and fighting abilities.
The power of their body depends on
the physical ability of their mario.
If you combine a strong body
with a strong shadow,
it will create an even stronger zombie!
That is why Moria is eager to get
his hands on wanted men's shadows!
I getcha! No wonder he came after us.
So that's the deal with Thriller Bark.
Moria's favorite aspect about
zombies could be their obedience.
Generally, it's a challenge to
keep powerful warriors in line.
Right, but our shadows possess
the same abilities as us.
Once he has our shadows,
he can toss us troublemakers out.
The powerful are quickly returned to
the sea while they're still unconscious.
In that case, they're in trouble!
I wouldn't worry yet.
We still have time.
I will tell you the best way to handle this.
Please believe me and do as I instruct.
What?! You want us to believe you?!
Good sir, I'm shocked to the skull!
Actually, I haven't bickered like
this in decades, so I'm eating it up!
We'll hear you out, so get talking!
Certainly!
Master!
Moria-sama!
The Three Phantoms have gathered together!
That was quick! Enter!
Please come in.
Oh, you're here!
Turn me into the King of the Pirates!
We're on it!
You can't become the King of the Pirates!
The future King of the Pirates...
...is me!
Hey! Untie this rope, you oversized shallot!
Give Usopp, Nami, Chopper,
Sanji, and Zoro back!
Where'd you hide them, shallot head?!
This one has lot of fight in him.
So this is Straw Hat Luffy, eh?
I have a hard time believing this is the man
who picked a fight with the World Government.
Why is he wearing General Zombie armor?
Don't you get it? This is every guy's dream!
You got captured, so don't
lecture me about dreams!
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy! You've made
a pretty big name for yourself,
but you're only our third catch so far.
We've got Pirate Hunter Zoro and some
blond guy who didn't have a wanted poster.
Huh? Sanji's the only blond in my crew...
What?! Hey, it sounds like
they caught Zoro and Sanji.
No way! And they even have Luffy.
Wh-Why did the three monsters
have to be the first to get caught?
I have no idea who these guys are,
but they're definitely bad news!
By the way, what happened
to that trio, Perona?
I recall handing them over
to the Risky Brothers.
But Kumacy never got them.
You sure they didn't
escape on their way over?
Bingo!
They're talking about us.
The casket popped open!
Huh?
Jerks!
Usopp! Nami!
Hey, hang in there! Wake up!
Shush! Dude, don't say a thing!
--Actually--
--I keep telling you to keep that mouth shut!
You're too harsh on Kumacy.
You're beary harsh.
But the trio that includes my bride caused
quite the commotion in your courtyard.
Hey, wait a second...
Now that I think about
it... Hogback, you pig!
This means you've raised your
hand against my future bride!
I warned you not to touch her!
You'll never get married.
Say what?! Cindry!
Now, now, Cindry-chan!
You're only adding fuel to the fire!
And why are you standing in front of me?
You won't get married, either.
You're killing me! That
was a nasty stray bullet!
What are they going to do with
Luffy now that they've caught him?
And what's happened to Sanji and Zoro?
We're in pretty deep doo-doo ourselves!
But there is no way Luffy's
gonna stay in that cage!
What?!
Jerk!
Good, good! Keep nice and quiet.
No matter what anyone says,
my mind is made up!
That woman will be my blushing bride!
You will never get married.
Shut up!
Come on, Cindry-chan!
Why don't you just ignore Absalom?
Don't expect to get married... ever!
That's two stray bullets in a row!
She said I'll never get married!
Cut it out! Knock it off!
I can't stand all your fussing!
If those pirates got away,
you can deal with it later!
I had you gather so we could celebrate
the commemorative creation
of a powerful ally!
He's insane!
Master, the pirate chewed
through the cage and is escaping!
He chewed...
...through the cage?!
Why did you capture me?!
--Luffy!
--Sweet!
He's going to prove dependable!
Don't, Absalom! We're indoors.
I'll stop him.
You can't catch me, dummy!
Negative Hollow!
Those are...!
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!...
They're multiplying as they dance! Awesome!
I'll catch them and keep them as pets!
Fresh Fire!
Shoot! It didn't work.
That was an epic fail.
I'm such a loser this week.
I can hear the whole world booing me!
Okay! I've got the punk!
If I could be reborn, I'd like to be a clam.
I suck!
That won't work on me a second time!
If I could be reborn,
I'd like to be a sea cucumber...
Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive! Ne-ga-tive!
To fall from the King of the
Pirates to a sea cucumber...
Brutal!
Damn it! Let go of me!
Hit him with the light!
What the heck are you doing?!
Jerk, I'll get you for this!
What is that?! My shadow?
Hey, don't do it!
I've obtained 300 million
Berries' worth of might!
Now I can complete the greatest
Special Zombie in history!
Luffy!
This is the moment of the
century, Cindry-chan!
When I saw his corpse in the Land of Ice,
my body wouldn't stop trembling.
Cindry-chan, that's my line!
I was so close to the famous giant known
as the legendary "Continent Puller."
That's mine, too!
I'm gonna be King of the--
That's a far cry from your line!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Warrior Known as the 'Devil'!!
The Moment of Oars' Revival!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!