Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Stop! Stop! I said stop!
It's dangerous ahead of here!
Water is rushing towards us!
C-Can't you guys hear the sound of water?!
Listen, if the water flows into
an underground passage like this,
we'll have no choice but to drown.
Zoro-kun, can't you hear the sound of water?!
Hmm, it's true that
something doesn't feel right.
Then let's stop, you guys!
There's no other passage. We have
no choice but to keep on this path!
I knew it!
Granny and the others
are being chased by water!
Ah! Pirate guys!
Guys! Do something about this water!
Ahh! It's here!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
What is it this time?!
Something came out!
That won't work! The Bone Balloon is tough!
Gum-Gum... Giant Axe!
Gum-Gum... Giant Whip!
Finger Pistol...! Pick!
Tempest Kick... Victory Bird!
The iron outer shell got cracked...!
This ship won't last long!
That was close. I almost got split in two.
Fire!
"A Mystical Mermaid Appears?
As Consciousness Fades Away..."
I'm shrinking!
That was close!
Why did they fire at their
own battleship? Are they idiots?!
But in any case, I got shrunk again.
Third Gear is such an interesting
idea and it's really powerful,
but how my body reacts is a problem.
Since I was pumped up for about a minute,
I'll probably stay shrunk for about a minute.
I'd better hide until I go
back to normal or I'll be killed!
I can't tell if he's serious or fooling around...
But in the end, he's still alive.
Well, it'd be disappointing if he died from
a small cannon attack like that anyway.
We can now see the main island front gate!
We're almost there!
Hurry!
Franky, the one you love so much,
has been taken away just like Tom-san was.
Do you wanna come along?
Ribbit!
Straw Hat was going on a rampage
on that battleship just a bit ago,
but now he's been blown to pieces!
Serves you guys right! Your captain has died!
Hey, hey... They fired at the ship
while their own men were on it.
This is the power of a Buster Call,
the attack I set in motion!
This is justice, Cutty Flam!
Now, hand Nico Robin over to us.
In return, I could make your charges go away.
Why do you have to protect
that woman in the first place?
You're not even a pirate.
Are you saying you'd trust that dangerous
woman who carries Ohara blood in her veins
over the World Government that
protects you ordinary people every day?!
If you disobey us,
just like Tom, you'll end up dy...
M-My face can't get any more swollen!
Can it! I've heard enough of your crap!
He drew the elephant sword, Funkfreed!
That thing is powerful!
Listen, Funkfreed. To ensure they
won't be able to resist any longer,
we'll fatally wound Nico Robin,
whose guard is down right now.
Take this! Elephant Chop!
Bastard!
He stopped it...!
He's so pathetic in every respect.
Funkfreed! You're an elephant!
You shouldn't be losing to him!
Go crazy and cut them up!
Put your nose back to normal, elephant,
unless you want me to shoot
you right between the eyes.
All right. That's good. You're smart.
Nico Robin, will Straw Hat
and the others come here?
Everyone will... for sure.
Spandam, I thought I told you that
I'm betting everything on them.
What?
I never thought a day like this would come.
If I had had power on that day...
I'm changing the charges.
For the charge of building the pirate ship
for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates,
we'll take shipbuilding
engineer Tom to Enies Lobby.
That is all.
What got into that old geezer?
Oh, well. I don't have
business with his disciples.
Release those two disciples!
Tom-san can no longer be saved.
If it's the World Government we're
up against, there's nothing we can do!
Bear it. Tom-san saved you two!
If you make an enemy of them,
no matter how many lives
you have, it's not enough!
Enies Lobby is the judicial island
owned by the Government.
No criminals taken there...
...have ever returned!
Is he stupid or what?
What should we do?
Are you stupid, too?!
Just keep going; give him what he wants.
Don't be concerned about him!
Y-Yes, sir.
Stop, Puffing Tom!
Where are you taking your creator to?!
Ribbit, ribbit...!
I won't let you pass here!
Give Tom-san back to us!
I wanted to get Tom-san back at any cost.
Those who know the myth of
the impregnable Enies Lobby...
Those who know the power
of the World Government...
The Straw Hats overturn their
common sense and advance.
In order to rescue one friend,
they make the world into their
enemy without a second thought.
It's exhilarating.
Up to this very day, I've never once
forgotten about Tom-san's death.
The stupid face of that official...
Every time it went through my mind...
...I hoped...
I hoped that...
Hey, stop it, you idiot! Stop it! Hey!
...one day I'd be able to crush him...!
...like this.
Thanks to them, my wish came true.
Weapons Left!
I'm someone who once died in the past.
If it enables the Straw Hats
to leave this place alive,
I don't mind sacrificing my life!
Hand over the escort ship to us!
I'll prepare an escape route for them!
I'll fight, too. I'm okay now.
Run with all your might!
You'll die if you stay on the island!
Sail out on my raft!
What about you, Saul?
This is it for me. I got caught.
Go!
No! There's no one on the sea!
Listen carefully, Robin!
You're alone now, but you'll
meet friends someday for sure!
Friends?
Right. The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
No one is born into this world to be alone!
Run, Robin! Don't look back!
Live together with them.
This is different from Ohara... From that time.
There's nothing to be afraid of...
...because... I'm not... alone anymore!
Hurry!
The entrance to Enies Lobby...
The main gate is around the corner!
We're almost there!
Go! Giants!
Leave it to us!
We'll be able to get off the island!
We'll be able to escape!
All right!
There, we did it!
So how about it--were you
impressed by our giant guts?!
What?!
Oh, no...
Three battleships!
They arrived here ahead of us!
Look! They really came!
I'm sure we tied them up in the courthouse!
How did they do it?
Vice Admiral!
Yeah...
--Aim at them.
--Yes, sir!
After stating your unit and marine code
and showing your picture ID,
you may board the battleship!
Okay. Go.
What a relief. I thought we were gonna
get eliminated along with the island.
Resisting is futile, pirates.
Make one move, and we'll fire
our guns and cannons at you.
This is bad!
It sure doesn't seem like
they're gonna let us get away.
Behind us is a harbor and an island on fire.
There's no place to escape, either.
In front of us are guns and cannons...
What're you thinking about right now, Paulie?
Memories of my past.
Don't say something like that.
Or...
Or...?
The hell that we're headed to now...
Ribbit!
We finished retrieving marines and officials.
To all battleships.
Maintain a distance from the main gate.
What're they trying to do?!
Th-This is...
H-He found me!
That's quite an unbalanced
combat power you've got.
You should willingly accept it,
if that's the price you pay
for the power you used earlier.
Life Return. Paper Art. Fighting Form.
Finger Pistol!
After all, your ridiculous attacks wouldn't...
I-I got stuck!
This is bad!
Sorry, but die in that stupid state, Straw Hat!
Finger Pistol! Spots!
Go back to normal, body!
Hurry! Hurry! I'm gonna be killed!
The damage I took earlier is affecting my legs!
Oh? I'm going back...!
I'm going back to normal!
See? My attacks...
...did a number on you after all.
Is there anything we can do?
We have to do something...! Or we'll all drown!
When we still haven't really
gotten Robin-chan back yet...!
Is this it? My life...
...was quite fun... Hey!
I haven't lived long enough!
Besides, it wouldn't even be funny
if the great Usopp, brave warrior
of the sea, died from drowning!
I can't hold my breath any longer!
I can't breathe...! Everything's going dark!
Help!
You'll be fine. Get ahold of yourselves!
I'm not gonna let you die!
What?! What's going on?!
My body is being pulled by something!
Oh... Am I dreaming?
I must be...!
Several sailors are drowning in the sea...
As their consciousness fades away,
they see an elegant tail fin...
When they look up, they see
long hair swaying in the sea...
She's so beautiful.
This is the mermaid legend...
It's like we're seeing a fantasy...
If I'm dreaming... please don't let me...
...wake...
I'm gonna go super express!
Make sure you hold your breath tight!
Du...
--Du...
Du... A dugong?!
What on earth... is this Buster Call thing?!
Hey! Hurry up, Straw Hat!
Your friends... Your friends...
are waiting for you here!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Cannon Fire Sinks the Island!
Franky's Lamentation"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!