Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Isn't it about time for us to settle this matter...
...as to whether that woman is... foe or friend?
By the way, why did you put up Nico
Robin's wanted poster in your room?
Are you curious?
A little.
It's better if you don't know.
She is... a devil.
Tonight, we'll infiltrate Iceberg's
residence one more time.
Among the disciples of this
Tom guy who originally had it,
Iceberg is the only one currently alive.
No matter how much he plays innocent,
in the name of CP9, we'll take
it away tonight for sure.
Bear in mind that this is a mission for justice.
If something is to happen,
it'll be tonight. Are we going?
We are.
What's our goal?
We'll capture Robin.
Otherwise, we won't know anything.
True. Thinking about it is a waste of time.
If we wanna know the truth,
that's the only way.
Okay, I'll do my best, too!
Well then, let's go...
...to Galley-La Company!
Everyone, be on your guard!
Yeah!
If we allow those pirates to infiltrate
with so many of us on guard,
it'll be an embarrassment
to Galley-La! Don't let them in!
Protect Iceberg-san!
Don't let the assassins get away with this!
What about the back door?
Back door? We're surrounding
the entire main office building!
There's no blind spot!
Bring it on! We'll take care
of all the Straw Hat Pirates!
Yeah!
How is it, Chopper? Does it look
like something is happening?
For now, nothing.
But...
...they're all carrying weapons,
and they look strong.
I wouldn't be surprised.
The shipwrights here beat even pirates.
We should be careful and take
action when the time is right.
Yeah, if we carelessly plunge in,
we'll be in big trouble.
Look who's talking! He jumped in
without any plan this afternoon.
Chopper, we don't know what'll happen.
Don't miss even the slightest movement.
Yeah.
If you see any movement,
let us know immediately.
Yep. Got it.
It's gonna be a long night,
but don't let your guard down.
If we miss our chance tonight,
we'll have to say goodbye
without knowing what happened.
Think that we won't have a way
to go after Robin anymore.
This is where we find out what we're made of.
Yeah... We'll definitely capture Robin.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Cannon Fire Is the Signal!
CP9 Goes into Action"
Kalifa...
Yes, Iceberg-san.
Sorry, but could you step outside for a while?
Okay.
Also...
...please send Paulie in here.
Yes, sir.
--Paulie...
--Hm?
Iceberg-san says he has something
important to discuss with you.
With me?
Yes, just you.
I'll be in the secretary's office,
so if anything happens, just call me.
Yeah...
Taking the trouble to have a
talk alone at a time like this...
What on earth could it be about?
Beats me.
A will?!
She said it was something important.
Get in there and talk to him already.
Y-Yeah...
Shall we stay a little ways away from the door?
Yeah.
I wonder what he needs to talk to Paulie about!
It's Iceberg-san we're talking about.
It must be very important.
More importantly, our current
problem is those pirates.
Yeah.
According to Kalifa's investigation,
there're seven of them. Coo coo!
The captain, Straw Hat Luffy.
Pirate hunter Zoro and Nico Robin...
In addition, the young woman who
came to Dock #1 this afternoon
and the round long-nosed guy.
Yeah. There're two others besides those.
That's everyone. Coo coo!
Their purpose is the least of our problems.
When they make their entry here,
that will be the end of them.
We'll bring them all down together. Coo coo!
Yeah!
Okay... understood.
This could be very risky.
I thought about it hard, but you're
the only one I can ask this.
Will you do it for me?
You're acting like I'm a stranger.
Please leave it to me.
You have my gratitude.
Well then, I'll get on it immediately.
Yeah.
Coo coo... Are you guys done talking?
Something came up. Sorry, but I
have to leave for a bit. Is it okay?
That's fine. The four of us
will be more than enough.
I see.
Watch over Iceberg-san.
Listen, Paulie.
Right underneath the desk
in the president's office...
If you lift up the carpet, you'll find...
...a safe buried there.
This must be it.
I'll give you the combination, so listen carefully.
First, turn it right to 6...
Click.
Are you ready?
Yeah, we're ready.
Then I'll cause a disturbance.
The other four of you, please carry out
your own mission after the signal.
Understood. In the name of CP9...
Ready? Nico Robin?
Yes... anytime.
An explosion!
What was that explosion?!
Bring water, now!
Take the injured someplace safe!
Hurry! Put out the fire!
W-Was it cannon fire?
No, it didn't fly in!
It was set up to explode!
Put out the fire! Hurry up and put out the fire!
Someone! Give me a hand!
What a showy signal...
Let's go!
The explosion happened in the
north corner of the first floor!
Is everyone okay?!
At least half of you stay at your post!
We still haven't seen the enemy!
To prepare for an attack,
strengthen the defenses!
Don't let them come in the building!
Are you okay, Iceberg-san?!
Yeah... I was surprised.
I saw someone!
He's wearing a costume! Catch him!
Here they come!
Leave them to me!
I'll nail them!
Hey! Wait!
Geez...
Coo... coo...
This way! Catch him!
Don't let him get away!
He's just by himself! Corner him!
Come on! Assassin pirate!
He climbed to a higher floor using a whip!
You thought there'd be no one on the rooftop?
Don't underestimate Galley-La's craftsmen.
How dare you mock us by
attempting an assassination?!
Prepare yourself, pirate!
We're definitely not gonna
forgive you bastards!
You'd better not try anything.
You're no match for me.
There're two here!
They're headed to the back door!
Don't let them get away!
We'll attack from both sides!
Don't let them inside the building!
Follow them! Capture them immediately!
You have the blueprints of his residence
in your head, right, Nico Robin?
Yes.
Ahh... The craftsmen are in a frenzy.
Yeah. It's gotten quite noisy.
What do we do? Shall we go in soon?
Hm? Where's Luffy?
Whaaat?!
Think thoroughly before you
take action! You dumbass captain!
Are you just realizing that?
The back door! They're headed
to the back door! Corner them!
Don't let them get away! Surround them!
How dare you show your faces
in front of all us guards?!
Don't make light of the craftsmen at Galley-La!
Your fate was already decided
when you hurt Iceberg-san!
Just give up!
You can no longer escape, pirates!
Give up and show your faces!
We're gonna drag out the rest of the
group using you two! Damn assassins!
He's gonna do something!
Shoot them!
They disappeared... No way...!
What's going on?
Where'd they go?
Hey, are you okay?
He's strong... What's with that whip man?
He ran... in the air.
No way...
He ran in the air?
Seriously, you people never listen, do you?
He jumped off!
Moon Walk!
He's doing it again!
He jumped, in the empty air!
Thorny Road!
I told you not to, didn't I?
Ahh! He's coming!
The courtyard! He landed in
the courtyard! Go around behind him!
Hey! He went that way! Go ahead of
him and hem him in from both sides!
Okay!
This must be it.
I see...
So that's the thing
Mr. Iceberg's been hiding, huh?
Give it to us.
You can't appreciate its value.
Who the hell are you bastards?
Where'd you come from?
The darkness.
However, we're a group that carries out justice.
We are Cipher Pol No. 9,
an undercover intelligence agency.
No matter where you slipped in from,
you must've encountered
our craftsmen without fail.
Did we?
We might have... or we might not have...
I don't really remember the details.
This is no longer something as
simple as an assassination, is it?
Well, I don't recall us calling it that.
In any case, please give us that
valuable item of Mr. Iceberg's,
and... since you've learned
something about it...
...we'd like you to die.
In the name of justice...
Right here... right now...
Did you find those two who
disappeared by the back door?!
No! We can't find them anywhere!
What about inside the residence?!
There're guards at every window and door!
There's no way they could infiltrate!
Dammit, pirates! Where'd they go?!
They definitely must be hiding nearby!
Look carefully one more time!
Capture them for sure! Got that?!
Yeah!
He's behind this wall.
Okay. Now, push me.
I'm shocked.
I knew you'd come sooner or later...
...but I never thought
you'd come through there.
Did you do the same last night?
I know there isn't any door there.
It's the power of the Door-Door Fruit.
No matter how hard the wall is,
the area I touch becomes a door.
As long as there's a wall,
I can go in and out anywhere.
What're you doing? We haven't
gotten the signal yet.
You can't call someone weakened
when he's got enough energy to talk.
Just like a good chef wouldn't neglect
to prepare the ingredients beforehand,
pros would be careful to restrain their victim
so that he wouldn't act unexpectedly
before the promised time.
So that's... CP9's way of doing things, huh?
You've got good insight... You're exactly right.
I did a bad turn to Straw Hat...
So, as I suspected, he had
nothing to do with this.
You don't have to feel bad, right?
You just told the truth
that you saw me last night.
That was also part of your plan?
That's right...
We kept you alive so that the crime
would be pinned on the pirates.
Besides, if we killed you suddenly,
we wouldn't know the whereabouts
of what we're after...
The blueprints of a certain ship.
It's something that has
been secretly passed down
from shipwright to disciple
shipwright for generations.
If you felt your life was in danger,
you'd try to entrust it with someone for sure.
And the one you chose was Paulie,
one of the foremen at Dock #1.
Our fellow members are with him right now.
So everything is going... as you planned, huh?
Make sure things are carried out flawlessly.
Okay.
I'll go deal with the
shipwrights outside the door.
Nico Robin, you finish off this man.
Once those two get the blueprints
from Paulie, they'll contact you.
Kill Iceberg at that time.
Our mission is accomplished once we kill Paulie,
who's come to know the truth.
After that, this crime will be
pinned entirely on the Straw Hats.
Seriously... why can't he
listen to people's advice?!
But that's nothing new.
But... Robin might be in that commotion, right?
What are we gonna do?!
We have to act carefully!
But depending on how you
look at it, we've lucked out.
When Luffy marches into enemy territory,
do you think he'd go around
to the back or the side?!
--Not a chance.
--No chance.
I bet by now he's marched in from the
front by either jumping in or running,
and now he's getting chased around
with no idea where to go, although he made
it inside the residence, don't you think?!
Yeah, sure do.
Yeah, definitely.
Right? From the shipwrights' perspective,
Luffy is the ringleader of the culprit group.
Once he jumps in, I bet everyone's
attention will go to him!
In other words, there's no doubt
that the guard in front of the
residence has lightened up for now!
So we'll be able to go across that opening
and mix in with the crowd of
shipwrights who're in an uproar!
I see. So thanks to Luffy, the best
chance to infiltrate is right now, huh?
That's convincing! Then, it should
be okay to jump in, huh?
Looks like we can jump over that fence!
Are you guys ready?!
Okay, we're gonna go in!
Follow Luffy!
What part of this is light?!
Dammit... I can't get out.
I wanted to jump into
the building, fast and furious...
...but I'm stuck and can't move!
I can't get out...
I have to hurry...
Just wait... Robin!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Nico Robin... I was finally able to see you.
I wonder if we're connected by a thread of fate.
We're alike, so...
What do you mean?
My belongings and your existence
will destroy the world, so...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"CP9 Takes Off Their Masks!
Their Shocking True Faces"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!