Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
I don't know the answer yet
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
Wicked rain will get in my way
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
But his struggle ended in vain
as the war came to a close.
Ace is really dead, isn't he?!
Yes, he is dead!
Ace!!
"Luffy and Ace! The Story
of How the Brothers Met!"
The War of the Best in Marineford
left a scar in many people's mind.
10 years ago, in the East Blue,
there was a small village called Windmill
Village where people lived peacefully
but not far from it was Mt. Corvo
where people seldom stepped foot.
Only the strong could survive there and
the weak who entered were doomed to die.
What I'm saying is, grandpa...
I'll become the King of the Pirates...
Cut the crap!
Let me... Let me go!
On top of eating the Devil
Fruit, you're talking nonsense!
Luffy! Both you and Ace have to become
MONKEY D. GARP [10 YEARS AGO]
the strongest Navy soldiers!
Ow, ow, ow, dammit!
MONKEY D. LUFFY [10 YEARS AGO]
My body is rubber but why is it painful?!
Let me go, grandpa!
It was a mistake to leave
you in the Windmill Village!
Of all things, you like
pirates?! What a fool!
You can't make friends
with "Red-Haired" Shanks!
I wanna become...
Ouch!
...a strong man like Shanks!
Hey!
What's this place?
Stop it!! Whoever you are,
do you wanna get killed?!
It's me.
G-Garp-san!
CURLY DADAN
A MOUNTAIN BANDIT: DOGRA
A MOUNTAIN BANDIT: MAGRA
You're looking good.
Give me a break! Please,
you gotta have mercy on me!
Ace is 10 years old now!
Oh yeah, already? How is he?
It's not funny!
We can't handle him anymore!
You have to take him!
--Putting that aside...
--Don't put it aside!
You're annoying, kid!
Look after him, too.
Hey, Luffy, say "hi" to them.
Yo!
Who is that kid?
He is my grandson.
What?
What?!
One more?!
He's Garp's... I mean, Garp-san's grandson?!
We can't!
Alright then, Here's your choice.
Do you wanna spend all your
life in prison or raise him?
There are many crimes you
committed that I've overlooked.
Come on!
Well, I don't wanna get arrested but...
Sometimes I think that maybe it's better
to be in prison than take care of Ace...
But you want us to look after your
grandson, too? I bet he's also a monster.
Crappy shack!
You wanna fight?!
Not listening!
Boss! Are you alright?!
What is it?! Ugh, spit! Gross!
Who did it?!
Hey, you!
Say "sorry"! It's gross!
Ace!
Are you back, Ace?
PORTGAS D. ACE [10 YEARS AGO]
Hey, say "sorry"!
Luffy, this is Ace. He's
3 years older than you.
You're gonna live here with them from today.
What?! You can't just do that!
Be nice!
Is it decided?!
Any problem with that?
We'll take him!
That's all from me. I'll
stop by when I have time.
--Um... What about some child support?
--Put it on my bill.
--This is not a bar...
--Huh?
--You're always welcome!
--Boss, we can't take care of one more kid!
--Shut up! Let's just eat first! Fix it!
--Okay!
Say "sorry"!
Wait!
I'll leave this hat with you.
Where did he go?
Who are you?
Let me go!
Give me your money or I'll kill you!
I don't have any!
Then tell your parents
to bring some money here!
--Grandpa is my only...
--That's fine. What's his name?
Garp-san.
Is this kid...?!
He's gonna live here with us.
--Why did you accept?!
--This is not a day-care!
Our boss has no guts!
Shut up you all!
It's time to eat!
--Give it to me, fool!
--It's my meat!
I want some meat!
--You already ate!
--I want more!
I'm not gonna give in to young people!
--You got to share!
--It's a dog-eat-dog world.
His arm stretches!
Dog?
It's your turn to wash dishes!
Can I have some more, pops!
I'm a woman!
Do you even know where you are now?!
No.
Then I'll tell you.
This is a den of the Dadan family,
mountain bandits that rule Mt. Corvo!
Mountain bandits? I hate mountain bandits!
Shut up, you little shit! We're
annoyed by having a kid like you!
If you don't wanna stay here, that's fine!
Go away and die like a dog somewhere!
Easy, easy, boss.
I wanna eat more...
I wanna have that meat, too.
These are all from a bison that Ace brought.
He gave us a cut of the
take so everybody can eat.
The mountain bandits' world is rough sailing.
You're gonna have to work
pretty hard from tomorrow!
Cleaning, laundry, polishing
shoes and weapons,
burglary, robbery, fraud, and murder!
Remember, you can't tell
Garp what we make you do!
One bowl of rice and one
glass of water for a day!
That's all I can guarantee you.
You gotta get everything else by
yourself and grow up on your own.
Okay!
"Okay"?! Why don't you cry or something?
I'm fine because grandpa
threw me into a jungle once
and there was water to drink and frogs,
snakes, and mushrooms to eat in the forest!
Plus, I'll become a pirate someday so...
...I must be strong like that!
--Boss!
--Are you alright?!
What're you doing?!
Here we go!
Where is he going?!
Where are you going?!
Did you just say "pirate"?
He's not listening!
Hey!
See? He's too tough!
That's why I didn't wanna
take care of Garp's grandson!
Easy, easy, boss.
Hey!
Wait for me!
My name is Luffy! I'm not mad
about you spitting on me anymore!
Why are you laughing?!
He only spilled some booze on me.
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
It's nothing worth getting mad
over. Let's become friends!
Are you going somewhere?!
It's a dead end!
Hey! Ace is back!
Food!
Ace, did you come back alone?
Where is Luffy? I thought
that you were with him.
I don't know.
That fool, where is he and what is he doing?
Maybe he's dead already.
We are dead if Garp finds out about this.
Boss must be pretty worried I bet!
--Get hold of yourself, boss!
--What did you say?!
I said it's not good that we
lost him on the first day!
Who cares! if he dies, he dies!
Garp is gonna kill us.
First of all, why should we
look after Garp's grandson?!
We're not nannies! He has to
take care of his own grandson!
--Why don't you say it to him?
--You have a problem?!
What if Gold Roger had a child?
Of course I know what'd happen to him!
He'd get his head cut off for sure!
I want to hear from him as he dies:
"I'm sorry I was born! I'm
just a piece of trash!"
I'm already giving up on Ace, too!
I don't care if he dies or not. I'll
just tell Garp it was an accident.
It's true that "the devil's
children have the devil's luck"!
He's the devil's son!
If the Government finds out about this,
what do you think they'd do to us?!
Easy, easy, boss.
You're drinking too much!
ONE WEEK LATER
One week later...
How annoying!
Why don't you shut up?
Boss! Boss Dadan!
Who is it?
--You!
--Luffy came back!
You fool! You're alive! You...!
Easy, easy, boss.
Where were you?!
Easy, easy. Where were you
and what were you doing?
I've been chased by wolves
at the bottom of the valley.
What were you doing at
the bottom of the valley?
--Anyway, it's nice that you're okay.
--Yeah.
It's not okay! The pest came back!
Why don't you go to bed tonight?
You gotta work from tomorrow!
Already?
What's up?
Are you gonna go somewhere today, Ace?
Take me with you! Let's become friends!
Wait for me!
Boss! He's going after Ace again!
Hey! You gotta do chores around the house!
No thank you!
You little shit! You're out of control!
Easy, easy, boss.
--Bring him back right now!
--Yes, ma'am.
Hey!
Ace!
Ace! Let's become friends!
The 8th day...
Ace!
Wait for me!
Boss!
Work, you little shit!
It's no use...
--Bring him back!
--Yes, ma'am.
I'm not gonna lose you today!
I can do that!
Let's become friends!
10 days have passed...
--Luffy!
--He's gone already...
Look for him!
He kept going after Ace and losing him.
But it went on everyday.
Ace!
1 month...
2 months...
Ace!
No matter if it rained and was windy...
Luffy kept going after Ace desperately.
Luffy is chasing Ace again?!
How does he never learn after
getting hurt so many times?
Damn! He has to stop making me worry!
So you're worrying.
N-No way! Stop talking nonsense!
A bee-hive fell on me.
Who are you?
Ace!
Ace! Hey!
I can't believe he's coming
this far. He's so persistent.
Oh crap!
Damn! I lost him again! Ace runs so fast!
Is it Ace?!
That's the beast of Mt.
Corvo! No one can beat it!
Why is he not running?! It's gonna eat him!
I-I feel weak at the knees!
That fool!
Now, Luffy had been chasing Ace for 3
months with cuts and bruises all over...
It's the end of the forest.
What is this place?
Discarded junk lies around everywhere,
and smoke fills the air.
This is Gray Terminal, a town of outlaws.
Ace once took charge of the thugs here,
amassing funds in order to
become a pirate someday.
Along with one other friend...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Here Comes Sabo! The Boy
at the Gray Terminal!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!