Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and were drawn into a climactic
battle on Punk Hazard
which ended with Caesar's capture.
Then, they headed out for
their next destination
along with their pirate ally
- the Warlord - Trafalgar Law.
We made it! Dressrosa!
Luffy and the others arrived at Dressrosa -
a kingdom ruled by Doflamingo,
and divided into three teams.
The first team will head for
Green Bit to hand over Caesar.
The second team will stay at
the Sunny to guard the ship.
The third team will...
...destroy the SMILE factory
and rescue a samurai.
Luffy and the others entered
a port town - Acacia
where they came across living toys.
Then, they walked into a bar to eat something.
However...
Let's go this way!
How does it go? What is it?
I'm sorry! It's black!
You were off!
Okay, white!
Let's see.
You've missed it again. It's black 20!
It should be white this time!
It's black!
White!
I'm sorry!
It's black!
I guess I'm running out
of luck. This is no good.
What do you wanna do? Do you wanna quit?
No.
One last time.
I bet everything!
Great!
Then I'm gonna bet everything
on whichever color you don't pick.
Let's play it like real men!
Everything? Really?
Yeah.
Alright, let's do it.
Place your bets!
I've made up my mind.
White, please!
"Full of Enthusiasm!
The Corrida Colosseum!"
If you pick white, I bet on black, of course!
Okay.
Come on, white! White!
It's gonna be black! Black!
Which is it?!
You're not saying anything. That means...
...it's white, isn't it?!
I'm sorry, old man!
What?! That means it's...
Yes!
--It's bl...
--White!
Ah?! Who the hell are you?!
Look carefully! It's black, idiot!
It's white.
Old man, you win!
What?!
You bastard! Stay out of it!
That's right!
Do you wanna get your ass kicked?!
Who is he?
Doesn't he have any idea who they are?!
He got himself involved, as usual!
How annoying!
He looks so calm and composed!
D-Do I really win?!
Yeah, you win.
I don't know who you are
but thank you for your kindness!
Don't mention it. I just said what I saw.
I'm happy for you.
But, old man, you look so strong...
What you're doing is so senseless, you brat!
When we say "It's black," it's black!
He can't see anyway so it doesn't matter!
You're so annoying!
Go away!
Oh no, did I trip a big boar or something?
If so, I'm sorry.
Y-You fool!
This is no good.
Young man, could you step aside a little bit?
I'm going to send those people to hell.
Kill him!
What?!
It's heavy! So heavy...
I-I'm going to get crushed!
What?! What's wrong with him?!
What did he do?!
Wow! It left a hole!
It's not too bad to be blind.
I know there are many hideous things
that are better unseen.
Okay, excuse me.
Who is he?
Is he a Devil Fruit eater?
What kind of Devil Fruit is that?
Excuse me, mister.
You can send a bill for the repairs here.
O-Okay...
Wh-What?! Don't tell me you're...
Goodbye.
Old man, you're so strong! Who are you?
I should not tell you that
for the sake of both of us.
Hey, are you blind?!
I-I'm sorry. Did you get hurt?
"For the sake of both of us"?
Is he extraordinarily infamous or something?
Whoever he is, he is not an ordinary man.
--Oh, my bag is gone!
--So is my watch!
I can't find my wallet!
Oh no! My jacket got stolen, too!
In broad daylight,
while there was dust everywhere...
That old man was a thief?
There are only two!
What's the matter?
One of my swords is missing!
My Shusui that was here a minute ago!
What?! The national treasure
of the Wano Kingdom?!
Damn! My Shusui...
Where did it go?!
What are you gonna do?!
They stole from everybody.
It was fairies who took your stuff.
What are you talking about?!
Is that the name of a group of thieves?!
Fairies are fairies.
All you can do is laugh it off and let it go.
How can I laugh it off?!
Those invisible fairies are
the guardian deities of
Dressrosa from ancient times.
We have to turn a blind
eye to whatever they do.
Well, if fairies did it...
We should just forget about it!
I can't just let it go!
He's right!
The sword is the national
treasure of the Wano Kingdom!
That's my sword!
It's not yours!
I told you! Somebody gave it to me!
I'll have to challenge you
to a duel at some point
and win the Shusui back for the Wano Kingdom!
Yeah, I'll accept it and defeat you!
You got too greedy, fairy!
You can't get away!
Hey, Zoro! Where are you going?!
Wait, wait!
We don't have time to let you wander!
Sounds like fun!
Wait, Luffy!
Did you find the thief?!
I'm not gonna let anybody
have the national treasure!
Hey, let go of me! We should go, too!
I have an idea.
An idea?
I understand now.
When there are only these guys around,
I have to take charge.
Boy, they're all out to get attention?!
Leave everything up to this big brother.
There it is! Wait, you fool!
You wait, you idiot!
Give me back the national treasure of
the Wano Kingdom!
Wait!
You wait!
Give me back the national treasure of
the Wano Kingdom!
Look! He has a strange hairstyle!
What did you say?! How rude!
I didn't know my topknot was exposed!
Oh no! I'm not a child but...
...I'm lost!
You're working under Doflamingo, aren't you?
Yeah. So what?
Super that's what we thought!
Yeah.
Do you guys think
you can mess with the Young Master-sama
in Dressrosa and get away with it?
That's not gonna work for us.
Old buddy, why don't you spit it all out -
everything we just asked you...
I-I told you!
I remember going after a couple of samurai
but I don't know how one got captured
and where he is now.
And I don't know what SMILE is.
You don't even know a bit about SMILE?
Yeah, and I don't know the
factory you're talking about.
Who are you people?!
I can't believe this.
Even his man doesn't know about it.
Then tell us where people of higher rank are.
This guy is too low in rank maybe.
Everyone's too busy today -
I don't know where they are.
I've been summoned to the Colosseum, too.
Look!
All the people in this kingdom
are heading to the Colosseum today.
What Colosseum?
It's the Corrida Colosseum.
If you wanna see high-ranked
officials, go there!
Why are they going there?
There will be a very big event today.
All the executives of our
family should be there.
The very big event that you're talking about is
that super event?
For whatever reason, Young Master-sama
offered an unbelievable prize!
Oh, it was so surprising!
Everyone wants it!
D-Don't tell me it's...
...that delicious meat
that Mingo was talking about!
Huh?
He said he has something that you will want.
Then what is the prize?
Prepare yourself for the shock...
The prize is...
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Ouch!
Here he comes! The Lightning Soldier!
You hurt me!
We want to see it, too!
Let us in!
It is not for kids to watch!
People will kill each other! Go home!
That's the wanted toy soldier!
He just won't give up!
You can't shoot me!
Jet Walk!
Ladies and gentlemen and toys!
What you will see today is...
...one hell of an event!
The king entrusted us
with an extraordinary prize...
...for today's event!
There was a man who died
in the War of the Best
in Marineford two years ago.
What?! He means...
He was a 2nd division commander of
the legendary Whitebeard Pirates
and a son of the King of the Pirates -
his name was Ace!
--What?!
--Ace?!
Flame Commandment!
Fire Pillar!
They say he could smash through a warship
with his Fire Fist
and could burn down a town,
turning it into hell!
That tremendous power is now
reproduced as a Devil Fruit!
--R-Reproduced?!
--For real?!
Look!
The winner will get this forbidden fruit!
It's Logia, the most powerful
type of Devil Fruit!
--No way!
--That's...
It's the Flare-Flare Fruit!
--Wow!
--I can't believe it!
Is it a real one?
Young Master-sama won't lie about this!
Ace's...
...Flare-Flare Fruit?!