Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law who's been
captured by Doflamingo.
Count on us to destroy the factory!
All of you, be safe!
Roger that!
Tra-guy's life...
Rebecca's wish...
He holds the key to all of that!
We're gonna head for the palace!
And beat the hell out of Doflamingo!
At the Colosseum, the final round
of the competition started.
Meanwhile,
the Tontattas' Operation SOP is...
Cyborg Franky has been silenced!
U-Usopp! I know you can do it!
Set off the panic already!
Don't worry, Young Master.
He's not even conscious now.
Usoland!
You can have this poison grape back.
--Oh, the Tatababasco grape!
--Our only hope!
You eat this.
Drop dead.
"The Legend is Back!
Kyros' All-out Blow!"
When Sugar passes out,
that's when all the toys in the country will
turn back into Big Humans!
All his evildoing will be revealed
and the pirate - Doflamingo
- will show his true colors!
What will Doflamingo do?
What action the Navy will take?
What will the people in this country think
and do?
Will they go crazy and riot?
Or will they give up and surrender?
Or will they...
...fight together with us?!
S... S...
Sugar has passed out!!
I've turned back!
What?!
This is...
What is going on?!
They're transforming one after another!
The toys are...
...Getting bigger and bigger!
I've turned back!
What's going on?!
You bastard!
Thank you for pushing
me around all this time!
Brother, don't use violence!
Oops, I've held the wrong one!
You son of a bitch!
Flapper?!
Leo!
Leo! I'm so relieved!
Finally!
We accomplished Operation SOP!
Sugar! Hey, wake up! Sugar!
Hey! Hey!
This is no good!
What's going on?!
What is it?
What is happening here-dara?
What the...!
He's turned into a weird old man!
What's going on?
I've turned back!
Wait!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank.
S-Sugar has...
I'm sorry, Doffy!
You're too loud, Trebol!
What happened to Sugar?
P... P...
Passed out!
She has passed out!
--What? What happened?
--Sugar has passed out?!
Hey...
Is this some kind of joke?!
The servants that we've been
collecting for a decade
are turning back into humans!
The spell of the Hobby-Hobby
Fruit is being removed!
The Tontattas' operation must've
been pulled off!
See? I told you
Usopp would take care of it!
Young Master, look at the Colosseum!
I've turned back!
--Honey!
--I remember now!
Wh-What is going on here?
Oh! Um...
What is happening here?!
The toys are...
The toys are turning into humans!
Not just humans!
Don't tell me Sugar has...
A decade of our hard work...
Sugar must've been beaten
by somebody-in!
How pathetic that shitty little tramp is!
But...
...I hope she's not hurt.
Boy!
You said such an unkind thing but...
...you actually care about her!
So hard-boiled!
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Palace, please answer!
We keep getting emergency reports!
This is an emergency call
from Sevio in the south!
The toys working at the port
suddenly turned into pirates!
--Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--This is Carta in the east!
The toys turned into old Dressrosa soldiers!
They turned into gov't officials!
Navy soldiers and
senior officials from abroad!
Wild animals! This is Primula District!
Are they real?!
Young Master!
I've turned back into a human!
I'm so glad!
--Stay with me, Usopp!
--Usoland!
Usoland!
Me and everybody else, we all turned
back into humans thanks to you!
--Usoland!
You did it!
Operation SOP has been accomplished!
Everybody turned back into a human
and they're all happy!
What's the matter, Onepoko?
Hey Mom, Onepoko is acting strange!
What?! Onepoko!
One...poko? One...poko?
One... No! My darling!
I-I've turned back!
Honey!
D-Dad! You're not Onepoko!
--Yes, I'm your dad!
--Dad!
Why have we forgotten about you
all this time?!
That's how the spell worked!
I thought I was gonna live as a toy forever!
--Hey Dad! Can you lift me up high?!
--Alright!
There you go!
Damn! You're quiet again?
Where did you go, stone guy!
Usopp... Little People...
Operation Sugar Oversurprised
and Panic went...
...super well, I guess.
--Usopp, stay with me!
--Usoland!
I think... I can't... carry on...
anymore...
Usoland! Please wake up!
--Don't die!
--I don't want you to die!
Usoland has died!
Guys!
Excuse me...
I'm... still alive.
Usolan...d?
The hero's still alive!
Usopp!
Usoland! Thank you for everything!
Everything... went as planned!
So cool!!
Leave the rest... to my friends.
The battle has...
...just begun.
Okay!
Help!
What?
Run!
Hm? You!
Huh? Who are you?!
I'm Onepoko, the dog you've
been pushing around!
Just carry it, Onepoko!
What?! You are?!
How dare you boss me around...
...Like I was your slave!
I can forgive everyone else but you!
Palace! Send some backup ASAP!
The pirates are out of...
Hey!
It's not enough yet!
Guys!
Beat the hell out of Doflamingo's men!
Hey! What's wrong?! Answer me! Hey!
How could you treat me so violently?!
You bastard!
Esta!
--Oh yeah!
--What?
--I have a boyfriend!
--Huh?!
You cheated on me!
I'm sorry! I forgot about you!
I was forgotten for a decade!
I hate Doflamingo!
Take down Doflamingo!
We were fooled by Doflamingo!
What are you talking about?
He's a good king.
You just don't know who he really is!
He's... a devil!
Kill Doflamingo!
Come on out, Doflamingo!
I've gotta pay you back
10 years' worth of pain!
Issho-san, what is happening here-dara?
I guess the tides have changed.
The darkness of this country must be
much deeper than I thought.
The darkness-dara?
--Kill Doflamingo's men!
--Let them all shed their blood!
Beautiful!
Let's take our country back!
Bring down Doflamingo!
Damn those pieces of shit!
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
I had been forgetting everything!
I'm Kyros! King Riku-sama!
--Kyros?
--Yes!
I'm sorry. It doesn't ring a bell.
Now, I remember clearly!
What?!
Who is he?!
Brother Kyros!
Even I lost my memories of him!
What are you talking about?!
What do you mean?!
Oh? Where did the soldier go?!
--It's him.
--Huh? That's a human!
The toys were originally humans
but they were erased from our memories!
Since the Devil Fruit eater Sugar
passed out now,
we got our memories back!
He's the former commander of
the King Riku Army - Kyros!
The strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum!
That's the old man the statue is of!
Yes, that's him!
And he's also...
...Rebecca's biological father!
What?! She said she didn't know him!
When people forget about you,
there's nothing you can do
to make them remember you!
That's why he's just been watching over
his beloved daughter for a decade!
He has always been by her side,
day after day, as a toy soldier!
Hey, who the hell are you?!
You are...!
You're Kyros, aren't you?!
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry to keep you waiting
for a decade!
Now, I'm here to save you!
I'm here to take back the real Dressrosa!
Kyros takes down Doflamingo!
This sends unprecedented shock
waves throughout the Royal Palace
and at the same time, the fight
at the Colosseum is about to
reach its dramatic climax!
The battle for the Flare-Flare Fruit
finally comes to an end!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Fire Fist Strikes!
The Flare-Flare Fruit Power Returns!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!