Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Pirate guys!
Straw Hat!
What brought you guys here?
Big Bro Franky asked us to bring you guys!
The dream ship has been completed!
They built an incredible ship!
What?! It's already done?!
That was really quick!
Five top-notch shipwrights
worked on it day and night!
Yeah, they did!
All right! Let's head there right away!
Yeah!
Straw Hat...!
Straw Hat!
Franky Family...
What're you guys running that
frantically for? You're out of breath.
To tell you the truth, we came
to ask you a huge favor.
Did you see the wanted posters?!
Wanted posters?
Straw Hat, the bounty on
your head has gotten crazy!
And all the others, too, are wanted in addition!
Me, too?! All right!
Me, too...?!
Me, too?!
Instead of having me explain,
just take a look at these.
All seven of you now have
bounties on your heads!
Straw Hat Luffy, 300-million-Berry bounty.
All right! It went up!
Pirate Hunter Zoro, 120-million-Berry bounty.
Cat Burglar Nami, 16-million-Berry bounty.
Oh, no...
Cotton Candy Lover Chopper,
the gang's pet, 50-Berry bounty.
Fifty...?
Devil's Child Nico Robin,
80-million-Berry bounty.
Who's this...?
Black Foot Sanji, failed to obtained
a picture, 77-million-Berry bounty.
Hey, Sogeking's got a bounty, too.
Fifty...?
W-Well, we sympathize with you, or, well...
I'm sure you wanna say all sorts
of things, but, well... please wait.
The favor we're talking about
has something to do with this!
Please take a look at this!
Franky!
Cyborg Franky, 44-million-Berry bounty.
Oh, no! Bro's got a bounty on his head!
Oh, no!
That's right. We somehow
were able to get off the hook,
but Bro had no such luck.
If he stays in Water Seven,
his life will be in danger.
If he gets caught again, we're not
strong enough to rescue him!
But he probably will try to stay on this
island because he's worried about us.
So we got together and discussed it.
Straw Hat, please! You can
do it by force if you have to.
Please take Bro out to sea.
He's a pirate's son to start with!
Straw Hat!
This is how we all feel!
Please consider it!
You guys didn't have to ask me that.
I decided a long time ago that he's the
only person I'd accept as our shipwright.
Seriously?!
A-Are you guys all okay with that?!
--Who's this...?
--I-I guess...
Of course.
Looks like you have your answer.
I... I'm relieved!
Now that we know how they feel,
we'd better get going.
Okay, let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Where're you guys going?
The scrap heap island is this way!
Sorry... but we're not going to see him off.
Seeing him would make it
hard for us to say goodbye.
Mozu! Kiwi!
Tell him that we wish him all the best!
"The King of Animals that Overlooks the Sea!
The Dream Ship Magnificently Completed!"
You guys are prepared for the
worst regarding Usopp, aren't you?
Zoro...
This is how it should be.
Right.
Now, hey, you guys! Just how
long do you have to feel down?
Shut up! Why does mine have to
be the only one that's a drawing?!
People don't usually start off
with a bounty that large.
Huh? Just how does this
picture look like me?! Well?!
--How could they think this is me?!
--You look like that, you know.
Use real words. I don't
understand what you're saying.
I'll be the laughing stock... of all
the ladies throughout the world.
I was tricked...
He said he was a reporter from
one of the local magazines.
At least he did manage to
get a cute pic of me, but...
I've finally gotten a bounty myself...
I'm a pirate, too! I fought hard like a man!
I wanna file a complaint
about my 50-Berry bounty!
Well, there's always next time.
Straw Hat! What're you doing?!
Let's hurry. Bro's waiting for you!
Sorry!
Don't forget anything.
We're gonna get the ship
and Franky and set sail!
Luffy, Sanji isn't moving.
Just leave Twirly-brows be.
Huh?! Hey, wait!
Are you pirate ladies and guys already leaving?
Chimney, Gonbe, thanks for everything.
"Navy"
This is indeed an incredibly rare case.
Few though they may be,
to think that they all have a bounty...
Furthermore, their bounties
total over 600 million Berries.
By the way, this "Black Foot" guy...
why isn't there any picture of him?
Yes, sir, well... I am certain
that I took his picture,
but I was shocked when I
saw the developed picture.
This is the picture.
This is indeed something
right out of a horror story!
Did you take off... the lens cover?
Eh?
Bro!
We brought them!
Bro! Where are you?!
They're here.
Whoa! There's something huge!
Is that it?!
Hey! We're here, Franky! Give us the ship!
Oh, Ice pops!
So you're here.
Where's Franky?
Unfortunately, he had to go somewhere.
But the ship is completed.
I'll show it to you in place of Franky.
Yeah.
This ship is incredible!
When I saw its blueprints,
my eyes opened wide in surprise.
It can sail any kind of sea!
With this ship, going to the end
of the world isn't a mere dream.
Hurry up and show it to us!
Hurry up!
Here is Franky's message to you, Straw Hat.
If you're going to be
King of the Pirates someday...
...board this King of Animals ship!
Incredible!
This is...
--What a spectacle!
--Well, well...
Whoa! It's huge! It's so cool!
It looks like it has all sorts of things flying out!
Whoa! He's gonna give this to us?
I see... This is at least twice as big as Merry.
What a big fore-and-aft sail! Is this a sloop?
Let me see the kitchen! The kitchen!
What a fine ship!
I wonder what kind of
flower the figurehead is...
--Well, I think it's, of course, the mane of a lion.
--Whoa! The interior is incredible, too!
It's a deck with a lawn! It feels good!
A slide! Whoa!
Looks like we can do gardening, too.
What a good view it has!
Hey, where's the kitchen?!
That big gaffsail seems
to have a lot of mobility!
It's called brigantine.
Sloop boats sail as people's
imagination dictates.
The navigator's skills
determine the sail's usefulness.
I can hardly wait! I'll do my best!
I'm gonna go check out the ship, too!
Whoa! My dream fridge! One with a
lock on it! There's a huge oven, too!
Thank you, Franky! This ship is awesome!
Hey, Ice pops. Where's Franky?
We'd like to say thanks.
It seems he has no intention
of seeing you guys again.
What?
Straw Hat...
Are you going to ask him to
join you guys as a shipwright?
Yeah. How'd you know?
I've decided that he's our shipwright.
He seems to have realized it.
Then he doesn't want to?
It's the opposite.
He's not sure if he can turn you
down if you ask him face to face.
That's why he went and hid.
But, well, his honest wish is...
He wants to set sail with you guys.
That he's entrusting this dream ship that
he's been planning all this time to you
is proof enough, isn't it?
Whoa! There's an aquarium here!
Hey, you're right! Amazing!
Franky has come to genuinely like you guys.
But he's imposing a duty upon himself
to stay on this island forever.
A duty?
It's a stupid persistence, if you ask me.
If you really intend to take him with you...
...do whatever it takes.
Take him by force!
That's the only way to free him!
By force?
Those guys said the same thing,
too, but is that really okay?
This is the start of Bro's new life.
We mustn't show tears. Smile!
But... they're coming down
on their own. What can I... Ah!
Bro! What are you doing back here?!
Huh? Why do I need a reason?!
This is Franky House! It's my house!
But...
I'm gonna come right out and say it, Bro!
You want to go with the Straw Hats, right?!
Huh? Don't be silly!
There's no way I would, is there...?!
Look at this! With your skills, you guys
can't even properly build a single house!
We just went to see them...
...to ask them to take you out to sea!
You fools! Mind your own business!
B-But he had already made up his mind
to ask you to be their shipwright!
Why do I have to become a pirate?
It doesn't take a genius to see it.
We had never seen you building a ship before.
But I thought, "Wow, I never
knew he could look this happy."
I've never seen you having
that much fun before.
Bro...
You know the Straw Hats are looking
for a shipwright, don't you...?
You ran away on purpose, didn't you...?!
Look at this, Bro!
My wanted poster!
So they put it out, as I thought.
You shouldn't stay with us any longer!
We don't wanna be a hindrance to you!
Look at this, Bro!
My wanted poster!
So they put it out, as I thought.
You shouldn't stay with us any longer!
We don't wanna be a hindrance to you!
Don't talk so cocky! The hell with the Navy!
I took you all in when you were about
to die like dogs on the backstreets!
That might be true...
...but...!
You guys can't even live
without me, and... Whoa!
I got his swimsuit off of him!
Swimsuit? Why'd you do that...
Ah, wait! I get it!
--Good job!
--Pass it around!
Don't give it back to him, no matter what!
Give me my swimsuit back! Hey!
That's my best swimsuit!
Scatter! Let's go!
Fine by me!
He's coming after us!
You'd better know that you can't defeat me,
even if you all gang up on me at once!
Just one survivor would do!
Deliver his swimsuit to Straw Hat!
Bring it to the scrap heap island!
Strong Right!
Give me my swimsuit back!
Sorry! I don't have it!
I'm sure I saw you had it! Enough of...
Hey, brother! Take this!
Dammit! A fake-out!
Run to the southeast!
Hm? What's this fuss about?
The perv is... Franky is going on a rampage!
Not again!
The town will be destroyed!
He's coming this way!
Hold it, you bastards!
Hey! He's not wearing anything down below!
Ah! Ding-don...
Take the children inside!
Don't let them see the perv!
Strong Right!
Dammit!
You're committing indecent exposure!
You're under arrest!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
D-Deliver... Deliver the swimsuit!
We'll go ahead of him by Yagara and wait!
Okay! Go!
The backstreets... have become a battlefield!
Dammit! My legs...
Oh, no... Is this it?
Hey! Pass it to me! This way!
Throw it to me!
Straw Hat...!
Straw Hat!
Package receipt confirmed!
You bastard!
Straw Hat!
Did you like the ship?!
Yeah!
I've never seen such an incredible ship! Thanks!
You perv! Go away!
--Have some shame!
--You perverted bastard!
Of course it is! In addition to my super design,
everything you guys requested was added!
Did you see the soldier
dock system I invented yet?!
No, not yet!
It's the biggest showpiece! I bet you'll like it!
He's coming this way!
What about the fish tank?!
I saw it!
If you put the fish you catch in the fish tank,
you can view and enjoy them
through the big tank downstairs!
It's a room that's like an aquarium!
You can have meals there with the others!
You can always have fresh fish!
I'm looking forward to it!
That ship is the ultimate dream ship
to you guys as well as to me!
So why are you...?
Give me my swimsuit back!
Chopper!
Yep!
H-He's coming! Roronoa-san!
Sanji-san! We're counting on you!
Leave it to us!
Get in!
Aim at the scrap heap island!
What're you guys doing?!
Franky Family's specialty!
Anything Cannon! Fire!
H-Hey, you guys! Enough with your jokes!
What?! He's flying there before
his swimsuit even gets there!
Hang on to me, Chopper!
Huh?
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Wh-What the heck is that?
Is that some sort of a curse?!
You dummy! It's just a perv!
--We can see everything!
We can see everything!
--B-Bro...
Well...
What the hell is going on?
Franky!
Thanks for the ship!
It's the best ship ever!
We'll take good care of it!
Yeah! I wish you a safe journey!
If you want me to give
this swimsuit back to you,
then join us!
Those idiots... They know they
can't do anything without me.
How cocky of them to say that!
To me, this town is...
You guys all are...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Goodbye My Dear Underlings!
Franky Departs!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!