Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
So where do you guys wanna go?
Since we've got our own ship,
we won't take the train.
We'll just follow the log.
I see. Then it must be Water Seven.
Water Seven?
Above all, it's a city that made
a name for itself with its shipyard.
Their technology is No. 1 in the world!
All right! I've decided!
We're gonna go there and get a
shipwright to join our crew for sure!
What the hell is this?!
This area should be okay, don't you think?
Holy crap! The Going Merry
has gotten this rickety?
Take this with you.
A map?
This'll be helpful! Thanks!
That's perfect. Once we get the money,
we can go to the shipyard right away.
Yeah. We can finally have
the Going Merry repaired!
All right! Go! Yagara!
Thanks for your business! Be careful!
Dash to the shipyard!
Yahoo!
"Adventure in the City on the Water!
Head to the Mammoth Shipbuilding Plant"
This is great!
Hey! I'm counting on you!
It's amazing that such a convenient
creature exists in this world.
It doesn't rock much. It's comfortable!
To the right! Right!
--The ball is headed your way!
--Here we go!
Ah! Stop the ball!
--Pass the ball! Pass the ball!
--This is neato!
This area seems to be a residential area.
This town really is built around canals.
Hey, mister!
Hey, pops!
Where are you going? Sightseeing?
To the shipyard! We're gonna
have our ship repaired!
Then go to the backstreet
shopping district first!
Checkmate.
Thanks!
S-Sure...
Backstreet shopping district...
We'll turn right ahead of here.
Oh, my beautiful mademoiselle!
How about dinner with me tonight?
Huh?
Ow! Ow, ow, ow!
Don't worry about him. The guys
around here say that like it's a greeting.
O-Okay.
Hey! Hurry up and go to work already!
I know, I know. Stop nagging.
At any rate, people in this
town are generous to outsiders--
or should I say they're overly friendly?
Hey! You with the long nose!
--Huh?
--Nothing. I was just saying hey, that's all.
Want a fist in your face, pops?!
Hm?
Ah, a hill is coming up. We're gonna
go against the flow. Is that okay?
Can we go up?
Wait! Wrong way! Go right! Right!
So it doesn't matter even if the
water is running downhill, huh?
Not bad, you guys!
The canals even go above the rooftops!
But we're going the wrong way!
We have to go to the shopping district first!
Oh, don't be so hasty.
This is a rare opportunity.
Let's stroll through the canals.
--Hm?
H-Hey! L-Look! Look ahead!
Oh, that's right! We're at the top of the hill!
Which means...
This is fun!
This is fun but scary!
Nooo!
Sorry!
Arrrrgh! We went flying!
We're falling. We're falling.
We're falling. We're falling. We're falling...
We're falling!
Don't get full of yourself!
Hm?
Miss! Our stuff is cheap!
How about taking a look at our products?
We've got lots of superb
items that are hard to find!
We're now starting our 50%-off sale!
Wow! Things have gotten lively!
Oh? We ended up in the shopping district!
Could it be that you took a shortcut?
I'm sorry. You guys are actually smart, huh?
I've never been to such an
energetic shopping district!
Hey, look at that! That's a huge bull!
Whoa! Hey, it's coming this way!
This guy is scary!
It's like he's about to eat us!
Considering its size, I wonder if this is a King.
Hm? What the heck is that?
Masks...
Wow, they're pretty. They're gorgeous.
I wonder if there's a party or something.
What? What's going on?
Here! These are freshly made
water-water octopus dumplings!
Two water-water croquettes?
Both look yummy! Yagara, go over there.
Hey, where're you going?!
Hey, Luffy! Where're you going?!
Ask the Yagara!
Welcome! What would you like?
Oh, so you were hungry.
Water-water meat is the Yagara's
favorite food, although it's human food.
Water-water? Then give me ten of them.
They're so good that the cooks from the gourmet
town would secretly come to purchase them.
It captivates your body and soul, doesn't it?
They... are... so... soft...!
--Yummy!
--What?! Is it that good?
Hey, Luffy! Give me one!
No! Buy it yourself!
Hm?
Hey, Nami! Pull the boat over to that shop!
More masks... Now that I look closer,
they seem to be everywhere in town.
Nami!
Those people with masks...
Hey, Nami!
Hey! Some pirates started
causing a ruckus at Dock #1!
What?! Is that true?!
We'd better get there right away!
I don't understand what you're saying.
Well, actually...
I thought about it carefully.
I thought about it really carefully.
Well, it's true that you guys repaired our ship,
but no matter how I looked at it,
I thought the fee was too high.
You're interrupting our work.
So... I decided not to pay--
not even a single Berry.
Thanks for the perfect repairs!
On top of that, it was free!
Well... Kalifa, what's going on over there?
Yes, Iceberg-san.
They're the customers for Dock #1.
Now that the work has been completed,
they're saying they won't pay.
That's sexual harassment.
Well... That is sexual harassment.
Sir, it'd be wise not to tease craftsmen like that.
B-Boss!
Boss!
Oh, pardon me.
You son of a bitch!
Watch carefully where you're going!
Oh, pardon me.
Y-You bastards! Are you picking a fight?!
Who do you think we are?!
Hey, have you test fired the cannon?
Oh, not yet, sir.
Dammit! Who the hell are you guys?!
We'll remember this!
The pirate way of doing things doesn't
work on craftsmen's turf, now, does it?
Now... We're finally going to
go to the shipbuilding island
by using a water gate elevator.
A water gate elevator?
That tower-like thing is the one.
Please come in!
The elevator will go to the shipbuilding island,
shipbuilding plant, and downtown Water Seven!
Please hurry inside the gate!
One minute until the gate gets closed!
What'll happen inside?
Whoa! The water gate is now closed!
We're going up!
We're going up! We're going up!
I see. That happens. Then, this happens.
And then, they do this and that.
So that's why it's a water gate elevator.
Whoa! Water Seven is interesting!
So they use water for all sorts of things!
Hey!
Who're you calling Moss Head?
Hey, Zoro.
--Huh?
--Where's Robin-chan? She isn't on the ship.
Hm?
Right, she isn't. She went
out with Chopper earlier.
--What?!
--She said she was going shopping.
What the hell?! Then are you
the only one on the ship?
What a boring environment!
You got that right.
All right, then. I'll go grocery shopping, too.
So make sure you watch the ship good.
Geez, he's already asleep.
Well, fine. I'll leave the ship to you.
We're here!
So this is the world's No. 1 shipyard!
Downtown Water Seven!
As expected, I see more ground around here.
Things are huge all over!
I've never seen a huge town like this!
Seeing that fountain up close
makes it look especially big!
Hm?
What's with that crowd?
Aren't they watching the shipyard?
Let's go see it! Go, Yagara!
Hey, look over there!
It's Lucci-san! He's so handsome!
Isn't Paulie here?
Lulu's here! How refined he is!
He's truly a man's man.
Who's manlier than Tilestone?
--Hey, pops.
--Hm?
Did something happen?
Yeah. It seems that some pirates
caused a ruckus at this here Dock #1.
But, well, it ended when the
craftsmen knocked them down.
There's no end to those fools.
Shipwrights beat pirates up?
Oh, you must be a voyager.
That crowd is... well, in short, busybodies.
Those shipwrights at the Galley-La
Company are admired by all the residents.
They're strong...
...and skilled.
They're the pride of Water Seven.
Wow, I'm looking forward to meeting them!
Ahh...!
Hey, Luffy!
Hm?
Let's hurry up and go to
the money-changing shop.
We can come back here later.
Okay!
It says that we're in the
backstreet shopping district.
They call a place this lively the backstreet?
So they have places that
we can walk around, huh?
The water is clear and the town is beautiful.
Yeah.
Scary!
Wow!
What a beautiful lady!
Such beauty hasn't been
seen for the last 100 years!
Err...
This place is full of Sanjis...
Whoa! What's that?!
That's a mask shop.
I've noticed people are walking
around in town wearing those masks.
Oh, so they're wearing them, huh?
I thought those were weird faces.
It sounds like they're holding a
costume carnival every day right now
on San Faldo, an island you
take the sea train to get to.
What? How come you know that?
People walking by are talking about it.
I'm surprised that you can hear them.
It's a habit...
Since my childhood, I've lived by trying to judge
people's feelings and listening in on them.
You're amazing, Robin.
--Doctor...
--Hm?
Over there! There's a bookstore.
Really?!
Can we stop by here?!
Of course! Let's go inside.
All right!
CP9...
Robin! I'm gonna go on ahead and go in, okay?
If I'm in my human form... it may be okay.
Oh?
Wow, what a cool mask!
What're you dressed up as?
Y-Yeah... A human reindeer.
If you're having fun, that's what's important.
Oh?
Robin?
Hello?!
Robin?!
I thought we were attacking you in your sleep...
Who are you bastards?!
Identify yourselves!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Incredible! Usopp flew in the sky!
Yeah! Hm? Hey, I'm right here.
Come to think of it, that Usopp
has a square-ish nose.
--When it comes to guys,
nothing beats a round nose!
--Well, welcome, Straw Hat.
I'm Iceberg, the boss of this city.
Are you a big shot, pops?
Then please repair our ship!
--Sure.
--Whoa, that sounded frivolous!
Is it okay to be that frivolous?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Franky Family and Iceberg-san"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!