Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
People are terrified when they hear "zombie."
But what if I rephrase it
to "resurrecting the dead"?
Hasn't that been all mankind's eternal dream?
Everyone has a special someone or two
they'd like to see return from the dead.
But toying with human mortality is
unorthodox medicine that disrespects God!
That's why I slipped away
from the public eye--
so I could continue my
research on this island in secret!
S-So that's the story!
But I'm sure tons of people
around the world would be thrilled
if your research is a success!
I'll be rooting for you, Dr. Hogback!
You're rather open-minded!
Thank you, Dr. Chopper.
What?!
Sh-Shucks, Doctor! I'm not happy because
you thanked me or anything, you jerk!
May I have your autograph?
Why, certainly!
"To Dr. Chopper..."
To Dr. Chopper...
Could you show me your lab later?
By all means, steer clear of my laboratory!
"Nami's in a Major Pinch! The Zombie
Mansion and the Invisible Man!"
Man, Nami! I wish you could
take a bath by yourself!
Seriously! I wanted to talk
with Dr. Hogback some more.
Shut your traps and come with me!
Yes, ma'am!
I wanna take a peek...
What?! You do?! For real?!
I'm not interested in a naked human woman,
but I wish I could peek
inside Dr. Hogback's lab...
I don't wanna see it! I'm too scared!
Gosh darn it, Nami! Why do we have
to stand guard while you clean up?
Don't bathe if you're scared!
I'm amazed you don't care
that zombies touched you!
Nasty!
We're just gonna get dirty again. Right?
Right!
We're leaving as soon as night falls.
What?!
Whoa, there! Are you crazy, moron?!
Here.
He said we could spend the night!
Can't you see what'll happen if we
leave in the middle of the night?!
Anyway, we should try to stay put!
Luffy and the others are sure
to come save us. You hear me?
I'm with him! I don't wanna go outside again!
I'm not going back in
the forest or graveyard!
It's the same whether
we're inside or outside.
Have you paid close
attention to this mansion?
Y-You don't mean...
Yep! If my gut feeling was right,
the halls and rooms were
filled with people's auras.
This mansion is already teeming with zombies.
Wh-Where were they?!
And if they're inside, that makes Hogback
the most suspicious person here.
He's lying to us...
There is no way he could live in this
zombie-filled mansion or on this island
if he wasn't connected to
those zombies in some way!
Wh-What do you think, Chopper?
If her speculation is right...
She's wrong! Dr. Hogback would
never do anything like that!
At any rate, let's play ignorant.
Once it's night, we'll make our break.
You're a rather clever woman.
Huh? What was that?
Usopp? Chopper? Did you say something?
Huh? We didn't say anything.
Ah, I just farted!
Usopp, that stinks!
I'm Uso-P.U.!
Why, you--!
What's going on?!
I don't see anyone!
A beast...?
You're weaker than the woman
on the ship--more my type.
Someone's here?!
Usopp! Cho--
Woman, be my blushing bride!
Hey, Nami? Is there a problem?
Did Usopp's fart stink up the bathroom?
Thank you very much!
You just thanked her!
They're in the way...
Stupid! Help me...!
Take that!
Usopp! Chopper! Help me!
"Evil Be Gone"
Someone's in here!
Huh?!
She's right! I'm picking up an odor!
"Evil Be Gone"
Huh? Uh, sorry!
I don't mean your fart!
It smells like a person.
Hurry! He's escaping out the window!
Why did the window suddenly open?
What the heck is escaping?!
Special Attack! Exploding Star!
It couldn't be...
Has that bastard... done it again...?
Wh-What should I do? Fire another one?
No, he's gone now.
I can't smell him anymore.
I wonder if we'll make it out of here...
Nami, are you okay?!
He overheard our entire conversation...
H-Hey, Nami, what was that all about?
I'm really confused here...
He was here the whole time.
He was an invisible man.
It's no use. It doesn't matter
if we kick or whack it.
This massive spider web is here to stay.
I don't like this.
There is no point in staying here.
We should make looking for Nami-san
our top priority. Let's head on out!
Hey, Zoro! Come on, Zoro!
Not only did that skeleton's ghost ship
and Sunny get caught in the web,
it also snared the Mini-Merry that
Usopp and the others were riding.
And it almost feels contrived
how the island entrance
is right in front of us,
like it's inviting us in.
Sheesh! I can practically see
the ghosts inside waving us in.
What are you griping about, Zoro?
C'mon, you're joining us!
Do you want to fall for
that stupidly obvious trap
and have those idiots
treat you like a moron?!
Why not? There's nothing
to do if we stay here!
Now let's go!
I'll share my lunch with you!
Sheesh! Well, I guess it might be fun
to see what those idiots look like.
All right! Let's move out!
You took forever, Moss Head!
Shut it!
Why does it go right into a staircase down?!
This is the entrance, so there's
no point thinking about it.
Oh, the ground is covered in bones!
Hmm. Cerberus, huh?
He would have been safer in Hell.
My, how cute!
Hey, isn't he lookin' for a fight?
He doesn't know his place.
Think he's yummy?
Woof!
Woof, woof! Woof! Woof, woof, woof!
Woof, woof, woof, woof! Woof, woof, woof!
Hey, cool it...
Look. He's ready to fight.
Actually, he's found his
courage after getting cornered.
So it would seem.
Then I'll--
Nah, wait.
Let's try to tame him.
What?!
Stupid! He may be a dog, but he's
basically the boss of all dogs.
But a dog is still a dog.
Yeah, good dog. Good dog.
Paw!
And here you just warned him!
There, there. You're a good dog.
There, there. Good dog. That's right.
Now let go nice and slow.
Slowly now. You're such a good doggie.
Darn mutt!
Down!
No, not quite...
But don't those injuries look horrible?
I'm amazed he's even alive.
Before that, I think that
fox thrown in the mix
makes it one messed-up animal...
We found such a fun animal
as soon as we arrived.
I can't wait to see what
this island has in store!
You look blue, Cerberus-san.
Hey, don't show the defeated any sympathy.
It'll hurt his pride.
Nami-san!
Hey! Where are you, Nami-san?!
--Nami-san!
--So the outside of the trench
leads to a forest, huh?
This place is like a maze!
Hey, Nami-san!
Nami-san!
Between the weird layout and this fog,
my sense of distance is fried!
There is also the possibility
that we're walking in circles.
Nami-san!
Maybe we should have left
Moss Head behind after all...
Are you pinning the blame on me?! Well?!
Huh?
A-An elderly tree and a
unicorn are sharing a drink!
--Save me!
--Wait!
Wait! Wait, dammit!
--Gum-Gum Butterfly Net!
--Strong Right!
Caught ya!
Please let me go!
Oh, dearie me!
Hey, Luffy! What are you
going to do with that?
He wouldn't...
Guys, why don't you join my pirate--
Cut that out!
That was a close call.
Hey, Absalom! You're here, aren't you?
What was all that ruckus about?
Were you in the bath again, you pervert?
I was searching for my bride, Hogback.
That woman tickles my fancy.
I'm going to make her mine!
Just so you know, she is a wanted woman.
You can't have her.
What did you say?!
There are six of them this time.
One of them is worth over 100 million.
The captain is worth 300 million.
300 million?!
Don't take those numbers so lightly, Perona.
If the government put 300 million
on his head, he's no ordinary pirate.
If you understand that much,
dedicate all of your energy to
capturing your prey, Absalom.
We're going to be busy tonight.
There's no such thing as an invisible man!
But I'm sure he was back there!
Not if he doesn't exist!
It was a hallucination or illusion!
You scared yourself into
thinking you saw the impossible!
What are you talking about, Usopp?!
Didn't you see how somebody
was pinning me down?!
Uh, er, well...
Nope, I didn't see that!
Yes, you did!
Gah, you're leading the witness!
You're trying to make me admit that I saw
you naked so you can charge me for it!
What?! How greedy do you think I am?!
Although I'm still charging.
You are?!
Anyway, I refuse to believe anything I
see on this island! Including you naked!
You just imagined the invisible man!
The ghosts are just weird birds!
The zombies are just a unique tribe:
The Hollow Earth People!
They're what?
Sure, we met a skeleton that had died
and come back because of a Devil Fruit!
We did, but that was truly
the exception to the rule!
Two people can't possess the same power!
And there is no stinkin' way
the dead can come back to life!
Right, Chopper?
Don't you agree with me?
Isn't it natural to assume they
were something along those lines?
Well, from a medical perspective,
all of this has been impossible.
I think your logic makes more sense.
But Dr. Hogback has abandoned his
life of glory to delve into his research.
Just maybe, miracles of that scale
have been happening on this island!
Hey, a-are you serious...?
Aren't you putting a bit
too much faith in that man?
Dr. Hogback is a truly
wonderful man! I respect him!
You're the one being rude!
Don't accuse the doctor of conspiring with
zombies if you can't back up your claim!
Even if I can't, everything is
pointing in that direction!
The doctor is the Zombie King!
Knock it off, you two!
You're freaking me out!
Anyway, let me talk to the doctor.
Is that acceptable, Nami?
I hope Luffy and the guys save us soon...
It's true that I'm only
basing this on my intuition,
but everything about this place is creepy...
Usopp? Chopper?
What is it, Nami?
Isn't that the room we were in earlier?
Yeah... Whoa! Why is it pitch black?!
What?!
C-Cindry-chan...?
Doctor, where did you go?
I enjoyed the bath!
Ex-Excuse me!
D-Doctor!
Those two have already
turned in for the night.
Hildon?!
You jerk! How dare you
abandon us in that graveyard?!
My humblest apologies.
I left to attend some errands with the horses.
The moment I took my eyes off them--
You're a bag of lies!
Everyone on this island
is in cahoots with each other, right?!
P-Please don't make such vile accusations!
Come right this way.
I'll show you to your rooms.
You're at it again, trying to
"show us" somewhere!
I wonder if that's the real
entrance to the underworld.
Thanks for the offer, but we must be off now!
What?! Wait a sec! Let me talk
to the doctor a bit more!
She has spurned you, Hildon.
Wh-Who's there?! I don't see anyone...
Keep out of this! I'll be sure
to take them to their rooms.
Why don't we drop this charade?
They are already starting to grow suspicious.
Before we slip up and give
them a chance to escape...
Wh-Why...
...is the picture...
...t-t-ta...?!
You're trembling. How adorable!
You're so cute...
I won't let you leave, children!
No!
Ch-Chopper!
A zombie popped outta the picture!
Save me!
Chopper!
That's right! You get him, Nami!
Help me out!
You can do it, Nami!
I'm Oinkchuck-sama, the head hog
of the zombies in this room!
You'll be dead before you get so
much as a single foot out the door!
Th-The wall mount... talked!
N-Nami, did you see that?!
The wall mount was talking!
The wall mount--!
Ow, ow, ow...
Who was the jerk that
stabbed me in the back?!
It's just like Nami said!
This mansion is teeming with zombies!
Usopp!
Punk!
Take this, you darn bear rug!
Crap! It's a candle!
It's hot! It's rottin' hot!
Fire! It's terrifying!
Put it out!
Crap! He climbed up the chandelier!
Someone knock him back down!
I know what you're weak against!
I've got enough for everyone! Take this!
Eat this!
Darn you!
And you! And you!
Chopper! Nami! Head for the door!
We're leaving the mansion!
--Yeah!
--I'm leaving! I've had it!
Hurry and open the door! I don't
wanna spend another minute here!
What's keeping you, Nami?!
No!
D-Don't tell me...
It won't open! We're trapped in here!
What?!
Now you've made me mad!
I won't let you escape!
Now come on back!
No!
Chopper, I don't really wanna know,
but what's on that operating table...?
Do you really want to know?
You had to ask? So it's what I think it is?
Are you ready? I'm going to tell you now.
G-G-Give me a sec! I'm not ready for this!
--That's--
--I'm scared!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Zombie's Secret!
Hogback's Nightmarish Laboratory!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!