Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy finally made it to Marineford
to rescue his brother, Ace!
There, the Whitebeard Pirates
are trying to get to Ace
and the Navy is standing in their
way. The battle is heating up!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Rifle!
Ace!
"Hard Battles, One After Another! Devil
Fruit Eaters vs. Devil Fruit Eaters!"
He beat the Giant!
Awesome, Straw Hat! You beat
the Giant in one sweep!
I'm back!
Straw Hat, I think we caught their attention!
Don't let them advance any farther!
Don't let the rookie get the best of you!
Luffy!
Get them!
Let's launch a frontal attack
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
and join Pops inside the bay!
We gotta save Ace!
Drive the Navy out!
The Navy admirals! They're so strong!
But we can't stop!
We're gonna rescue Ace!
They're a bunch of fools!
Bazooka unit, fire at Whitebeard!
Pops!
Damn! Please don't do this!
Slash him to pieces!
Gum-Gum...
...Twin Pistol!
I'm gonna...
...rescue Ace! Don't get in my way!
Luffy! Why did you come?!
Why did any of them come?!
I deserve this! They don't have
to risk their lives for me!
We, the 2nd division of the Whitebeard
Pirates, will save our commander Ace!
Don't do this!
Everyone! Why are you
doing this for a guy like me?!
I'm your brother!
How stupid you are! Luffy! Pops!
Become my son!
What's wrong?
I'm ready...
...to accept anything
that's gonna happen to me.
I'll hold a helping hand.
I'll take the blade of punishment.
I won't make a scene anymore.
Because I feel sorry for them.
Start firing!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
He's suddenly standing out in this battle!
Damn Straw Hat!
Captain Buggy, we need to
make a strong showing, too!
Let's beat Whitebeard now!
Alright! Let's do it!
Having said that, this war is crazy!
There're a
bunch of big-time pirates and the Navy soldiers!
I better keep quiet here...
Hey, you red nose!
What did you just call me?! I'm
gonna kick your ass, you bastard!
Huh?
Whitebeard!
I know you. You're the brat
who used to work under Roger.
It's been a while, huh? So you're alive.
Oh no! I drew his attention!
He's gonna kill me!
He's dead! He better run!
W-Whitebeard! That notorious Whitebeard is...
...talking to him! How cool!
I knew that you were a living legend!
Why're they so thrilled?! Must be
nice if it's not your own problem!
You're accompanied by so many prisoners...
Are you here to challenge me?
Yes, he is!
Oh, sorry. Captain had to say it.
Give it to him straight!
Dammit! I have no choice now!
Y-Yeah, at last we meet! Prepare yourself!
He's pushing his luck a bit too far!
Oh? I don't mind if you try to beat
me but what are you gonna do next?
There are more Navy soldiers
than you can handle.
In fact, they're more than I can handle, too.
Shouldn't we join ranks since we're
both pirates and knock the Navy down?
Then, you can beat me after that.
Oh my god! Whitebeard recognizes
you as a powerful man!
Like his equal!
No, Whitebeard called him a "brat!"
You can't fight against the Navy!
You think there's a chance to win?!
Yeah, if I go all out.
He's losing his grip on reality!
--You sure?!
--I got goose bumps!
I'm starting to think that
I can do it! I can do it!
I can see myself becoming
the King of this world!
Yeah, we can beat the Navy
if he and I join forces.
This is too great! I'll faint!
Alright, Whitebeard, I join
with you! If you insist!
Huh? Who does he think he is?!
Well, he's our Captain Buggy!
How many more things can
they take the wrong way?!
He is unbelievably easy to trick.
The red nose aside, the prisoners
behind him are something.
It's a pain to have them as our enemies.
And now, I must...
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
Ships in the back,
come forward and deploy the backup!
Our forces are superior!
I have a report!
The pirates in the
back are also heading this way!
It's about time.
Forward unit at the bay head,
change the formation as Fleet
Admiral Sengoku instructed
All units, keep fighting
back and back up slowly!
--Did they stop firing?!
--They're backing up, too!
--There is disarray among the Navy!
--One more push!
Navy ships are coming from either side!
--It's too late!
--Let's charge into the bay!
Alright! It's our chance to
join Pops inside the bay!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
This is Whitebeard.
Is Squard there?
Pops! Captain Squard... Oh?
He was in my sight a while ago
but it seems like he's gone.
That bastard.
He was all fired up to
strut his stuff to make Pops proud.
It can't be helped. Then,
DeCalvan Brothers...
--What is it, Pops?
--Pops, what is it?
Follow my lead and take
command of all pirates.
--Okay!
--Okay! And what's your lead?
Sink the Navy ships around you first.
What?! Pops, I think we can
make a frontal attack now!
Are you giving up?
I have a bad feeling about this situation.
I got it, Pops!
Pops, I got it! We'll tell the captains!
What?! Pops said that? Alright,
then I'll get the right side!
We'll take the left.
Okay, got it.
We'll take the right side.
If Pops says so.
I can head my ship in any direction.
Squard?! I haven't seen him. Really?!
I'll take the left side.
Fleet Admiral Sengoku! Pirates of
the New World changed their moves!
Yeah, they turned to the left and right.
They've started attacking Navy ships!
Good guess! Whitebeard must have sensed it.
He didn't fall for that cheap trick.
Maybe it was a bit too lame.
But he can't prevent a
thing just by sensing it!
Damn! There're too many enemies!
It's hard to break through!
Death Wink!
Heehaw!
Ivan-sama, you're alright!
Ivan-chan, I wanna clear the way to Ace!
Jimbei!
Fish-Man Karate!
Death...
Gum-Gum...
5000 Brick Fist!
...Wink!
...Bazooka!
Advance!
Ace!
Stop Straw Hat and the others!
Straw Hat! I won't let you get through!
Moria!
You've got to fight me, Moria!
Jimbei!
I can handle you on my own, Moria!
You wanna fight me, Jimbei?
Alright! I have to get rid of you
in order to use zombie soldiers!
Go ahead, Luffy-kun! Don't waste any time!
Thanks, Jimbei!
Pffft! It's a pity to think
that I'm letting Straw Hat go!
Jimbei, you think you can
beat me on the land?! Huh?!
I never thought that Jimbei
would become our enemy!
The Seven Warlords are our crucial
forces! We shouldn't fight each other!
--Huh?
--What's wrong?
There's something wrong with my shadow.
Now, fight for me, shadows
of the damned Navy soldiers!
Did you know that I get more powerful
by taking in the shadows of other people?
You have no chance to beat me, Jimbei!
You got bigger.
But getting stronger by
taking other people's power
doesn't make you any better, Moria!
Silence! I couldn't care less about
it! All that matters is winning!
Now, I'm gonna take your shadow!
Spend the rest of your life
in the dark undersea, Jimbei!
Let me have your shadow!
You're so quick for a hulking fellow!
You're the hulking fellow here!
Fish-Man Karate!
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
Shark Brick Fist!
You let go of the shadows
that you've taken in!
You need to train yourself more!
Now, you need to let me through, Moria!
I have to hurry forward!
Wait, you bastard! The fight is not...
Straw Hat!
Move, Tashigi!
Ouch! You are... Smokey!
I see you finally, Straw Hat!
Straw boy!
Kuma! You're so persistent!
Oh, no, no...!
Oh yeah, that jutte is tipped with
Sea Prism Stone! That bastard!
Second Gear!
I'm gonna take care of you!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
White Launcher!
You've got much stronger than before!
Straw Hat!
He disappeared!
That's fast! Where is he?
It seems like you became
stronger than before, as well!
Your power is not enough to beat me!
Commodore Smoker pinned Straw Hat!
Amazing!
Damn! Get your jutte off of me!
Now I know why Dragon...
...helped you at Loguetown, Straw Hat!
Dragon got in my way at that time but
this time I won't let you get away!
D-Damn!
You! Leave him alone!
She got me although my body is smoke!
Kicking shouldn't hurt him!
Th-That's...! The pirate
empress saved Straw Hat!
Hancock! What are you doing?! Are you
gonna resign from The Warlords, too?!
Shut up! I'm deafened by my own anger!
How could you hit and pin down my beloved?!
I won't let you survive! I have
never felt this much anger before!
I'm gonna cut you up and feed you to beasts!
That's the Haki of Kuja!
Hancock!
Yes!
You called me Hancock again!
Kuma! Kuma, that's enough!
It's me! Did you forget my face?!
If you don't stop, I'm gonna fight
back although I'm a gentle person!
I don't know how you know him
but you may as well give up!
It's no use talking to him, Emporio Ivankov,
commander of the Revolutionaries army!
You...! What do you mean?!
What's wrong with him?!
You're a friend of
Bartholomew Kuma I suppose.
He was once called Tyrant
Kuma and now he is...
...dead.
What are you talking...
Kuma is...
...dead?!
Ivankov and Bartholomew
Kuma were once comrades,
but despite Ivankov's desperate
cries, Kuma's cruel attacks persist.
Then Doflamingo shares the shocking
truth about what happened to Kuma.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Kuma's Transformation!
Ivan-san's Blow of Anger!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!