Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
But I won't walk away
nigedasanai kara
Oh
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Luffy and the Whitebeards are
trying to make it to the scaffold
but they have been walled in!
But with Jimbei's help,
Luffy was able to get over the wall
and finally make it to the plaza!
Luffy!
I'm on my way!
Ace!
Wh-What is that?!
We're enclosed!
What the hell is this?!
Do it, Akainu!
Meteor Volcano!
He's firing lava fists into the air!
They can't get away!
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
I'm sorry...
The plan is going well!
Now let's move on to...
...the execution of Portgaz D. Ace...
...immediately!
Jimbei!
I need you to do me a favor!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Oh no! You finally made it!
You're standing tall, Dragon's son!
It scares me! His youthfulness!
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp Gatling!
"Moving into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's Trump Card for Recovery!"
I can't believe that he's
attacking the 3 admirals openly!
He's a damn fool! They're gonna kill him!
Second Gear!
I don't have time to fight those guys!
He fooled us!
You're too slow!
Luffy-san!
I told you!
Damn!
Be ready!
Yes, sir!
Do it!
Ace!
Ace-san!
Ace!!
Who did this?!
You bastard!
I thought that it was to
our advantage to have you
since you hold a grudge against Whitebeard.
Crocodile!
That guy!
What is this? I thought this
was my chance to show off.
He was trying to kill the good old man before.
The winds have changed!
I can kill that old, dying buzzard later.
But before that,
I don't want to let you taste victory!
Hey, you, gator guy!
D-Doflamingo!
You turned me down and now,
you wanna team up with Whitebeard?
It makes me jealous.
I'm not gonna team up with anybody.
So that means you are still
giving me the cold shoulder.
Looks like it.
I don't know what this is
all about but it's helpful!
This is it, Straw Hat!
Die!
Don't get in...
...my way!
Stop, Straw Hat!
I won't let you go any further!
--Outta my way!
--Shave!
Moon Walk!
Iron Body...
...Smash!
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body!
...Bullet!
Stop Straw Hat!
Don't let him go any further!
Admiral Sakazuki!
That hurts! Dammit!
I owed a favor to your grandfather
but I have no choice!
Because you chose to risk your life!
You fool! I won't let you do that to Luffy...
Admiral!
That's...!
1st division commander--Marco!
Thanks! You saved me!
Don't mention it!
We've got three invaders in the plaza!
Devil Fruit eaters can fly over the walls!
Th... Three?
A-Am I one of the three
that they're talking about?
But when did they find out about me?!
I escaped Admiral Aokiji's attack by a hair
and survived so many deadly crises!
And finally I got this far!
But I'm not safe here either!
Isn't there any place safe?!
Someone's coming!
That was...
INSIDE THE BAY OF MARINEFORD
Go across the sea towards Oars!
Get to the plaza whatever it takes!
Fleet Admiral-dono!
The pirates inside the bay are acting strangely!
Go across the sea towards Oars!
Get to the plaza whatever it takes!
They are desperate.
Defend the open space in the wall!
Yes, sir!
They've gone crazy after losing their ships and the
ice they stood on, stupid pirates!
They're fair game for us! Shoot!
Don't hesitate! Keep going forward!
Head towards Oars!
Get to the plaza!
Wh-What's wrong with them?
How can they keep their
morale in this situation?!
Advance!
Everybody, get on board!
Hold on tight!
N-No way! It's a ship!
We have a problem!
Another coated ship is entering the bay!
Dammit! It must've been hidden
at the bottom of sea all this!
I don't remember saying that
that was all of our ships.
It's a paddle boat!
It's coming towards us at full speed!
What?!
Sink it like the Moby Dick!
No! Not the boat! Shoot at Oars!
Huh? Why Oars?
It's too late!
Get ready, everybody!
He pulled the boat out of water!
They broke the encircling walls!
We made it to the plaza!
Let's save Ace!
Let's burn down Navy HQ!
Wait for us, Ace!
They got us!
There was only a space the size of a rathole!
But they went for it wisely!
The walls could become
an obstacle for us this time!
Pops!
Whitebeard!
You still have your head, right, Ace?!
We did it!
Now we can save Ace-kun...
Oars!
Save Ace-kun at any cost...
Oars...
Whitebeard has descended to the plaza!
Stay back, my sons!
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
...destroy the Navy!!
Garp.
Yeah.
I don't think we can make it
through this unscathed!
I'm on my way, Ace!
At last, Whitebeard stands before Ace!
But he's faced with the two admirals Aokiji and Akainu,
and the conflict becomes a battle royal.
Amidst the chaos, Marco finds an opportunity
to make a dash toward Ace!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy at the End of His Tether!
An All-out Battle at the Oris Plaza!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!