Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has broken out of the
great prison - Impel Down
in order to rescue his brother, Ace!--
No! I know that you guys know about the
war between Whitebeard and the Navy!
--What'd you say?
--The Navy HQ?
We passed through the Gate of Justice.
That means our destination must be
either the Navy HQ or Enies Lobby.
The Tub Current that we're on
is exclusive to the Government.
It's a giant whirlpool that connects
the Government's 3 major facilities
We didn't know about this!
Buggy! Buggy!
Be quiet, you flashy fools!
You guys are all full of whim and fancy!
If you guys are real men, why don't
you live out a dream with me?!
Today...
I'll beat Whitebeard which means
that I'll conquer the world!
--I will follow you!
--I don't want a peaceful life!
That's right!
Let's go, guys! To Navy Headquarters!
Looks like it's over.
I hope they are having fun.
"The Friends' Whereabouts! The Weatheria
Report and the Cyborg Animals!"
I know that you are worried about Ace-san
but you need to take some rest.
The war that we are about to get involved in
is literally the decisive battle of our times!
Just as Impel Down is the
greatest prison in the world,
the Navy Headquarters is the
greatest fortress in the world!
Meanwhile, a short time ago at
the small Sky Island - Weatheria,
home to scientists who study the weather.
Hey, hey, hey, young girl!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey,
hey! Hey, young girl!
Hey! Hey!
Alright! What do you want?!
H-Hey, what's this?!
Do you like the taste of my cloud
candy? I've been working on it.
It was so hard to make it
taste like cotton candy.
What do you think?
Are you trying to kill me?!
Wait a minute, young girl! Violence won't do!
Honestly!
Oh, it's sweet! It does
taste like cotton candy!
That's what I thought!
Hm... So I guess that this island
is really full of wonder!
Oh, by the way, are you sure that we're
heading to the Sabaody Archipelago?!
Yes, I'm doing it for you as a special favor!
But it's been a while since I asked you.
When are we gonna get there?
What do you mean?
Huh?
Wasn't I clear enough?!
Weatheria travels on the wind.
If a
typhoon comes, it's gonna be really fast.
How far did we get yesterday?
Probably about 200 meters.
Honestly, if this weren't a Sky
Island, I would've left already!
But we're still too far away from the
Sabaody if you were to go down on the ground now.
If you stay here, we'll get there someday.
Look, I don't have that much time to spare.
Then, shall we go down?
I'm running out of research funds anyway.
Huh?
What do you mean "go down?"
I mean, on the ground.
Is that possible?!
You know, it takes a lot of
money to do this research.
So I go down from time to time to do some
business with my knowledge of the weather.
What is this?!
Young girl!
It's this way!
A ship?!
Wow, this ship... floats in the sky?!
No!
Let's go!
What?!
That's just the island
that I was looking for!
This island is...
...terrible!
Did you say that you can save this island?!
Yes.
It seems like you people are
in need of blessed rain.
I can make it rain with my
knowledge of the weather!
What did you just say?!
I can do this now for a special price...
...of 100 million berries!
100 million?!
I'm afraid we don't have that much money.
Is it too much?!
That's way too much!
No one can afford that!
Well...
--Then, 100 berries!
--Huh?!
What a deal!
You came down too much! You
have no sense for business!
Relax!
That aside, can you really do it?
Weren't you being too optimistic?
Believe in my knowledge of
the weather! Okay, ready?
Those are..
...soap bubbles!
There's something inside.
Young girl, could you generate
some wind with this?!
Oh, this is...
Do you want it full power?!
Yes!
Oh my god! I can't believe this!
--It's raining!
--Yeah!
We did it!
They're so pleased!
Yeah! Now, don't you think the
science of weather is useful?
Okay. So I guess this is
goodbye, right? Young girl.
I already asked the mayor
so he'll provide
you with what you need for your journey.
--I'm not going!
--What?
I'll stay with you.
I've become interested
in the science of weather a bit.
Really?
Can you teach me about it on our
way to the Sabaody Archipelago?
Of course!
You sure? Thank you!
Anyone who loves the weather is welcomed!
Is this from before? This is perfect!
Let me tell you about this soap
bubble with the thundercloud inside.
Oh no, this is not good!
Huh?
You...
What're you doing?!
S-S-Science exacts a price!
Am I the price?!
Help... Help me!
Meanwhile, on the Mechanical Island -
Future Land Baldimore, the
birthplace of the Genius.
It makes me super relaxed!
Oh no!
He was way funnier before!
Oh! What do you think we can
do to turn Franky back?!
The cola hasn't arrived yet so
we can't conduct an operation.
He has to take back his perversion...
I mean, wildness, in order to
get back to being himself again.
Wildness?
It's cold!
How did I get here?
Here is a scarf!
Oh?
What is going on here?!
"Keep Out?"
"This is an enclosed forest
of mechanical animals?"
Mission: The surprising
wake-up in the jungle!
Take back your wildness
through surviving, old man!
Don't try this at home, kids!
Hey guys, you better relax!
You all seem very frustrated.
Have you eaten breakfast?
It is not good for your mental health
if you don't eat it every day!
Oh I see! This is breakfast time!
What was I thinking?
Delicious! There is nothing like the
first cup of tea in the morning!
Do you guys want some?
It feels great to be alive!
It's not working!
Help us!
Good morning, boys!
Old man!
I'm not an old man! Call me Mr. Frank!
Violence is not...
I know you are at an age
when you want to be naughty...
If you let me talk...
You'll see...
Let's sort this out...
...in a gentlemanly manner!
Stop... Nothing good... comes... from war!
Mr. Frank!
Oh no, it's not working at all!
Relax...
Listen to what I say... Listen to what...
Listen to... Listen...
Lis...
To...
Listen... Lis... L...
Lis...
Super!
Who do you think I am?!
I am Franky-sama!
Yeah! You're back, old man!
Per... vert!
What's the matter?
I got cooled down a little
so I'm running out of steam!
Oh, geek! I mean, god!
Um... Um...
Oh yeah! We gotta go there!
Where are we going?
The house of Dr. Vegapunk!
Maybe we can find a machine
to make some cola!
Dr. Vegapunk?!
He's the standout genius
of Future Land
Baldimore known for its advanced technology!
The mechanical animals that you just
saw are all cyborgs that he created!
I heard that he was a weirdo and he
left the island with cyborgs running wild
but that he was also amazing!
Grandpa told me to keep away from here
because there are a lot of
dangerous creations inside!
Alright!
What the hell is this?!
Sanji is on the run from countless
pursuers of ambiguous gender.
After running and running to escape them,
he's met by a mysterious
queen, and a frilly dress.
Around that time,
a huge, round creature falls
to the ground behind Chopper!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! A Cheeper
of Giant Birds and a Pink Showdown!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!