Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
...head for the New World, the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle at the Fish-Man Island,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal, they landed on Punk Hazard Island.
It was a strange island divided into two parts; the Burning Lands and the Ice Lands.
I can't let them escape!
Room!
What is this?! It's like a thin film...
Shambles!
E-Everybody, calm down!
Let's do a roll call!
--Chopper!
--Here!
--Franky!
--Yeah!
Sanji-kun?
What?
Nami-san?
You're Nami... aren't you?
Uh-huh!
What is going on here?!
You stupid pirate, don't push your luck!
You ate the Op-Op Fruit and you're the Modification Man, I believe!
Stay out of his sword's reach!
You guys are in my way! Get out of the circle!
The circle?!
While you're in the circle he created,
you're like a patient on an operating table!
This is his operating room.
He has total control over it and can manipulate anything as he pleases!
He's the Surgeon of Death!
Don't do it, Tashigi!
Your Haki is not strong enough!
Captain-chan!
"A Collision! Law vs. Vice Admiral Smoker!"
THE LABORATORY - IN FRONT OF THE MAIN ENTRANCE
C-Captain-chan got cut in half!
--Hey, you're alive, aren't you?!
--Tashigi-chan!
How...
How dishonorable! I got sliced but I'm still breathing!
Why don't you just kill me, Trafalgar?!
You talk like a master swordsman.
Let me tell you something, Navy soldier girl.
The weak can't even pick their way to die!
You bastard!
You can't reach me with that sword.
I can chop you more if you liked it.
Damn you! Stop insulting our Captain-chan!
Captain-chan, don't worry!
We'll riddle that fool with bullets!
Bullets?!
How did the bullets get here?!
Where did the bullets that we shot go?!
Those are the bullets you shot.
I switched them with the snow falling over you.
Is he invincible?!
Get down! He's gonna cut everything again!
No one can stop his sword attack!
That bastard! Captain-chan, run!
Captain-chan!
Smo-yan!
The Surgeon of Death--Trafalgar Law!
You're just a pirate!
Stop messing with the Navy!
I feel an unpleasant energy.
You have Sea Prism Stone on the tip of your jitte, don't you?
Oh no! The recoil made the sword cut the artwork!
The ship's gonna fall onto us!
Let's run! He doesn't want us to be here anyway!
I don't care if you're a Warlord or not!
Just get out of my way!
Vice Admiral Smoker!
Captain-chan, let's get away!
--But...
--He's no match for us!
White Blow!
Run! Get out of the circle!
Th-They were strong... Too strong...
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew...
Damn! They took Boss Brownbeard with them!
W-We got to help the Boss!
They're cold-blooded pirates!
I don't know what they're gonna do to him!
Boss Brownbeard!
We have to let the Master know!
Follow me, those of you who can stand up!
THE ICE LANDS - LUFFY'S GROUP
I heard a huge noise. Was it Sanji and the others?
Hey, Alliga-taur!
You really don't know what happened to my crew?
Shut up! I won't tell you anything!
Fine. Then run faster! To the building that Brook saw!
We gotta save Nami and the others!
How humiliating to lose to such a squirt!
You robbed my people so cruelly of all they had, you cheap muggers!
Don't try to give us a bad name!
You guys attacked us first!
You're showing no sign of remorse, alligator guy.
Brook, I know you don't feel cold because you don't have flesh...
So why did you steal the coat?!
Because I felt like it.
I'm so happy to see you all again so I wanted to share in your feeling cold!
I feel bad that Nami and the others were abducted in those clothes.
I hope they don't get frostbite and lose their limbs.
Geez, Robin! Don't share those gruesome concerns!
Master, what should we do?
Mr. Law and Smoker are in a big battle.
What is he thinking?
I thought the plan was just to make them go away.
But those escaped pirates took the kids in the Biscuit Room with them
and ran into Law and the others at the front.
So the Navy saw the children?!
Yes.
That's what I feared the most.
Now they know something is going on on this island!
Even if we kill Smoker,
the Navy will become aware that something is wrong.
I thought so.
You just got back - what are you doing now, Monet?
It was them.
We should have paid better attention.
Oh yeah, I forgot to mention.
Vegapunk's dragon and
Brownbeard's Centaur Patrol Unit have been defeated.
--What?!
--Unbelievable!
Which means those pirates you kidnapped along with
their ship had other crew members
and they were in the Burning Lands already.
They made it across the lake and they'll be here in a matter of minutes.
They were so strong. Now look.
THE STRAW HATS ARE BACK
I'm sure it was them.
The Straw Hats...
I'm sure you have heard about them.
They're an unforgivable archenemy not just for the Navy
but for the World Government too.
The World Government, huh?
If they're so notorious, maybe it's good for us!
Whether it's the Straw Hats or Smoker,
we can get rid of all those troublemakers who are learning what's
going on on this island at once!
But Master, even if they're a group of misfits,
if we kill all the G-5 soldiers,
the Navy would be on the alert, wouldn't they?
Well, we can just suppress things that are going to
happen on the island from now on.
--Call Joker.
--Yes, sir!
A MOUNTAIN BEHIND THE LABORATORY SANJI'S GROUP
We made it out from the backdoor but what should we do now?!
Even with this strange transformation going on,
we have to keep running for now!
What's going on?! It's super confusing!
--Bros!
--W-We're gonna freeze to die!
Deadly cold? I don't give a damn!
The samurai and the brats? I don't give a damn anymore!
What?!
Isn't there a camera somewhere?!
I wanna take a picture before we return to normal!
What're you gonna take a picture of?!
And stop having nosebleeds in my body!
This is more important, Nami! Don't button up my aloha shirt!
Are you all okay?
I know it's cold but hang on a little bit longer!
The Spiral Bro is being kind! It's too creepy!
What happened? Did you get your bodies switched?
Looks like that's what happened.
Hang on, kids!
I'm being treated very differently from before.
I didn't know humans felt this cold!
Bros, stop!
It's cold...
This is it... I-I can't even move...
--Me too!
--I'm freezing too!
Damn! We shouldn't have taken them with us when
we didn't know where to go.
I don't feel cold at all with this body.
Pieces of the ship are falling like leaves off a tree!
Are you okay, Smo-yan?!
Captain-chan, how is your body? Did they stick together?
By the way, your right hand is my left foot!
My hands! Whose feet are these?!
Dammit! We're in big trouble!
We lost our means of communication and the ship!
I thought the Warlords were on our side! That bastard!
Hey hey, Captain-chan, don't try to move! Stay here!
Tashigi, keep this in mind.
Pirates will always be pirates!
Pirates will be pirates!
Why are you here?
No one, not even pirates or Government allies,
is allowed to be here on this island, Law!
That means you people are not allowed, either!
Law, why are you here on Punk Hazard?
I never understood why you joined the Warlords in the first place!
What are you up to?
What we need to do now is to achieve higher status.
Pirates all over the world have started to pay respect
to the Straw Hats because of the incident at Enies Lobby.
Yes.
I'll put all my pride on the line and kick their asses in the New World!
Whether it's the Straw Hats...
...or the Warlord who serves for the World Government - Trafalgar Law,
pirates will be pirates!
I've never trusted you Warlords.
Maybe that's the right thing to do.
Law!
What is this place to you?
Who's behind this?
What are you up to on this island?!
Why don't you answer first?!
What are you all up to?!
There are things that you can't see unless you change your standing, Smoker!
Scalpel!
My heart!
I don't have to tell you anything.
Smoker collapses after his heart is stolen.
With Law looking down coldly before them,
the rage of Tashigi and the G-5 reaches
its peak and they attempt an attack...
When Luffy suddenly appears!
The meeting between the two,
who share a deep bond from the great war,
causes the situation to drastically change!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Meeting Again After Two Years!
Luffy and Law!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!