Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace to take
back Law who's been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, Usopp and the others put
Operation SOP into action
along with the Tontattas
but their plot has been uncovered.
"The Last Light of Hope!
The Secret of Our Commander!"
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
Stick-Stickem...
...Meteora!
What?!
T-Trebol-sama is going crazy!
The Executive Tower has been destroyed!
THE ROYAL PALACE B-1
We keep getting blocked!
I told you! Pica can manipulate
this whole stone palace any way he likes!
Straw Hat!
Is he really going to be okay?!
You mean Zoro?
You don't have to worry about him!
He'll be fine no matter what!
What the...!
Rebecca has never made an attack
before but she just did it!
What kind of sword is that?
Its blade is blunt.
The ring is a place for killing.
If you can't cut anybody,
you'll have to shed your own blood!
It's what the people want to see!
Lock!
That's a direct hit!
The undefeated girl couldn't do anything!
Diamante!
Damn!
Hey, Musclemelon!
No, I'm Bartolomeo...
Protect her!
What?!
Rebecca, do you know
how your mother Scarlet died?
I'm gonna go buy something to eat.
The Toy Soldier cried like a baby.
He was so pathetic.
I'm sorry!
I couldn't protect your mother!
Our ship...
Why did Trebol-sama do this all of a sudden?
Usopp!
Usopp! Wake up!
What a relief!
--Robi...
--Shh!
Wh-What just happened?!
I saw a big duck falling from the ceiling!
I'll explain to you later. We have a problem!
Leo and the others got caught!
What?!
You prick!
Drop dead! Right now!
I'm not gonna die, you little shit!
We're having a serious conversation now!
Don't get in my way!
Stop lying!
I'm not gonna tell you!
I know someone is helping you - who is it?
Hey! Hey! What's his name?
I'll never tell!
Yeah! Never, ever tell!
Let's run while we can, Robin!
Even though he's actually my friend?
What?
If I remember correctly, his name is...
You mean Usoland?
Hey!
You idiot! He's not my friend!
Oh no! I've been fooled!
Is the one-legged soldier
your associate, too?
I-I'm not gonna tell you!
Well, I already know.
Oh, if you know, then it can't be helped!
He's our associate!
--I thought so!
--Oh no!
Now, we see some connections!
It doesn't matter anymore!
You people are finished!
Today is the decisive day!
We will pull off...
...this operation no matter what!
And we will...
...take back our friends at any cost!
Let me tell you something.
That sticky stuff is flammable!
What is it this time?!
Trebol-sama!
Hey!
Are you guys okay?!
Leo! Leo!
Everybody, are you okay?!
Stay with me! That was too reckless!
The operation is over! Let's run away!
I mean, you have to fall back!
You guys did all you can!
But you can't beat Trebol!
That's not an option!
We must complete Operation SOP...
...as soon as...
...possible.
Leo!
Then, the commander will...
...take down Doflamingo...
...for sure!
The commander is...
...waiting for us!
We must hurry!
Lao G, you bastard!
Lao G's "G"!
"G"!
DRESSROSA - THIS MORNING
DON QUIXOTE DOFLAMINGO
WITHDRAWS FROM THE SEVEN WARLORDS
Doflamingo-sama withdraws
from the Seven Warlords?!
I can't believe it!
Is he gonna step down
from the throne of Dressrosa?!
Yeah!
He's nothing but an ordinary pirate now!
He's gonna be chased by the Navy!
We're gonna be free!
Finally, we're free!
Commander, did you see the newspaper?!
It means we're gonna have our friends back,
doesn't it?!
We no longer have to fight Doflamingo!
That's great!
No.
It was a false report.
What?!
No one's coming back!
No way!
I'm so glad that it was just a mistake!
He's a great man!
He's not gonna abdicate the throne!
Doflamingo-sama!
I'm gonna enter today's competition
and win the Flare-Flare Fruit!
And I will take down Doflamingo!
Rebecca! Come to your senses!
I know you're angry!
So am I! But don't jump the gun!
We're gonna rise up! We're locked and loaded!
No! I'm not gonna wait!
Our hopes have been dropped
from heaven to the edge of hell.
No one here can take it anymore!
Their spirits are broken!
All there is left to do is
wait to be executed now.
We'll be released if we
can win a thousand times?
That's not hope!
That's a wall of despair!
The legendary gladiator Kyros won
3000 out of 3000 matches?!
Everybody knows that statue is
just make-believe!
Dying prisoners must have made up
their ideal warrior and that's Kyros!
They built the statue
wishing to be freed like him someday!
I'd rather not dream an impossible dream!
Today's competition is a
chance and I'll take it!
So...
It's not a chance!
It's impossible for you
to win that competition!
You're gonna die!
I won't allow you to enter it!
You're not thinking straight!
You're only 16!
Do you think of yourself
as an adult now, Rebecca?!
You're still a kid!
You must listen to what I say!
Oh, please! You're not even my parent!
You're the one who's not thinking straight!
What's your plan?!
You have no chance to beat Doflamingo!
Because you're...
...just a one-legged toy!
Yeah...
You're right!
N-No!
Sorry for being meddlesome
but I hope you're not gonna
enter the competition.
I didn't mean it! Soldier-san, don't go!
Please! Soldier-san!
I was just afraid that
you were gonna sacrifice yourself!
I'm sorry! Don't go, Soldier-san!
Soldier-san!!
It's shaking!
It must be Pica! What is he doing?!
You can't go after him!
Are you okay, Commander?!
Th-Thank you!
--Let's get going!
--Wait! They're gonna get beaten up!
Hey! Let go of me! You little bastards!
Stop looking back, Commander!
We were planning on
sacrificing ourselves from the beginning!
Don't be silly!
What will happen if you stop here?!
Even if Leo and the others
pulled off Operation SOP,
if we let Doflamingo walk away,
he'll turn everything back again!
You're the only one who can bring
down Doflamingo, Commander!
Why do you care about the commander, Leo?
Why do you guys count on him so much?!
C-Commander!
Even if only he makes it...
He's just a one-legged toy!
Normally, people who are turned into toys
are bound by the contract
and they will become
workers who can't disobey.
The commander was the first person
ever in this country to get turned into a toy
but the Hobby-Hobby Fruit eater, Sugar...
...made a mistake forgetting
to make a contract!
Just one mistake from ten
years ago made him...
...the only toy in this country who
can get back at...
...the Don Quixote Family!
That's why he's been fighting
on his own for a decade!
If it weren't for him,
toys would have no choice...
...but to put up with it!
We Tontattas wouldn't know anything
and we all would have been enslaved by them!
If we ignore his rallying cry,
there'll be no chance of saving this country!
He's worth betting everything on!
Nobody remembers him now
but everybody knew him once!
When he was a Big Human, his name was...
...Kyros!
He was the strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum!
That's who our commander is!
The Toy Soldier runs to reach Doflamingo
but a brutal enemy named Gladius stands
in his way!
When the Toy Soldierfs life is at stake
Due to Gladiusfs overwhelmingly
destructive power
Luffy rushes in like the wind!
On the next episode of One Piece
!
"The Rupture Human! Gladius Blows Up Big Time!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!