Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome treasure
at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King of
the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
The horizons everyone dreamed
of were separate at first
but now they can be seen through
a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny is
leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve your
dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
Where am I?
Oh, you shouldn't move yet.
Chief! The golden belfry...
We still have the duty
to protect it to the end!
Don't rush, Wyper.
Vearth, at least, is not refusing anyone.
Right... Right now, at
least,no one wants to fight.
It's party time!!
The long battle of 400 years had ended,
and all the citizens of Skypiea
continued their joyous party day after day.
"I Made It Here! The Yarn
the Poneglyphs Spin"
I... I... I can't drink any more...
There they are!
Hey!
What is it?
Nami, wake everyone up!
Why?
We're gonna steal the gold and run!
There's gold?!
Idiot! Not so loud!
What do you mean "idiot"?!You're
louder than I am!
Hey! I'm louder, you
say?!You're the louder one!
What?! You're calling me loud when
you're really super loud?!
Your voice is the one that's really
super-mega-ultra loud!!
There's no way that's true!!I'm
talking loud because you're loud!
You're the one who spoke loud first!
Shut up! I can't sleep!!
What?! You're the loud one!!
It wasn't me! It was you!
I'm a delicate woman! I wouldn't
yell with my mouth wide open, would I?!
What?! There's no way I'd
do something like that!
See? See?! Your mouth is wide open!
Geez, wake up, sleepyhead!
But you did hit me here!
Here! It's really true!!
Nami-san! Good morning!!
That's because you ticked me off!
Oh? It's not morning yet!
Yeah, yeah... Go ahead and be
feeble-minded like that.
Like I said, you don't have
to shout, you know!!
What do you mean, "feeble-minded"?!
Blue Sea people sure like
to party, don't they?
This is the fourth day in a
row.Their vitality isn't normal.
So, that's the plan.
Okay, guys! It's not often that we
get to visit a sky island!
Make it so that you'll have no regrets!
He's so cool!
This is getting exciting!
Chief! We found the golden bell!!
What?!
Hey, are you serious?!
Yeah. It's stuck on the fallen Giant Jack.
We're pulling it out right now.
Those who can help, come to the western
seashore! Hurry! Hurry up!!
Okay, guys! Gather everyone!!
Hurry to the western seashore!
The belfry was found!
Where?!
At the western seashore.
Okay!
Are you sure?!
Yeah! Hurry!
They said they found the
bell that fell in the sea!
Yeah. Those who can move,gather
at the western seashore!
The belfry was found!It's
at the western seashore!!
The belfry was?
One more time!!
One, two...!
Pull!!
Dammit! We still need more people.
It's the pride of our ancestors'
city,Shandora. We'll get it at any cost!
That's right!
Give it everything you got!!One
more time!! One, two...!
Pull harder!!
Rubber band?! So you call
this a rubber band?!
Yeah! My Usopp Rubber Band did 90%of
the work of taking Giant Jack down!
Whoa! Incredible!
Whoa!
I'm the only one in the world that has them.
Whoa! Amazing!
Whoa!
But... put that aside for now.I'd
like to show you this iron sheet!
Now, ladies and gentlemen!This
is no ordinary iron sheet!
I tore it off from the Going Merry,our
ship that endured very hard travels
on the Grand Line, as well as
Eneru's attacks! It's the "King of Iron Sheets"!
How about it?! You guys want iron, right?
Would you trade me dials for this?
No! I want this rubber band!I'll
trade you for this rubber band!
I want one, too! Is that okay?!
Me, too!
Whoa... Are they serious?!
Give me one, too!--Me, too!
Water, light, fire...
Things whose shape is transient...
Things with no form...
I cut them!!
Shells! I got shells! Oh, yeah!
Lucky, lucky! I got so lucky!
You're in a good mood, aren't you, Usopp?
Did the negotiation go well?
Hear that? I got lots of dials!
I press it and...
Just like that!
Good for you.
Good for me! With this many dials,I
can do many different things!
The Usopp factory'll be running full steam!
Hey, Zoro, if you make your
swords Flavor Swords
and store the smell of stuff
like melons in them,
you can enjoy your everyday training!
No thanks.
Oh...
Oh, yeah! I can make Nami's
Clima Takt stronger!
My slingshot will be incredible, too!
So, where are Robin, Luffy and the others?
Luffy and the others are still
inside.Robin went somewhere.
In any case... this snake's
really conked out.
He kept dancing day after day...
...though I don't know what
he was so happy about.
Anyhow, they'd better come out soon,
because if he wakes up,he could
give them a hard time again.
Huh? This good-tempered snake?
Idiot! You just don't knowhow
troublesome he can be!
This good-tempered snake?
Like I said, you can be so optimistic
because you didn't see
what a pain this snake can be.
This good-tempered snake?
Hey, now listen here, Usopp!
It was a Tone Dial!
Don't do stupid stuff like that!!
Yeah, it's stupid! It's really stupid!
What the heck?! What does this snake eat?
Are we there, yet, Luffy?
Look! There they are!!
Wow! Amazing!
This is the real thing!
It's pretty! It looks just like the
ones that we saw at the monkeys' house!
See? See? See?! There's all this!
Isn't it awesome?!
So this is gold...
How beautiful...
Incredible...
I didn't expect it to be this...
How magnificent.
But one of the side columns has been broken.
Yeah, but there isn't much we can do.
Hey! Look at that.
So this is... the Poneglyph...
The stone that our ancestors risked
the city's life to protect...!
Just what is written on it, Chief?
Something we're better off not knowing...
We just...
"Hold our true motive in
your hearts and speak not of it.
We are the ones who weave history...
...with the sounding of the grand belfry..."
How do you know those words?
They were carved on the Shandoran ruins.
So you were the keepers,entrusted
with this for generations.
Could it be... You can
read those characters?!
Poseidon, the "ancient
weapon"named after a God...
Its whereabouts...
What?! What's that?!
She said "ancient"!
Ancient weapon?
Why is it talking about something like that?!
Yeah...
Another weapon...
...separate from Pluton that
I read about in Alabasta...
I hear that one shot from Pluton will
completely destroy an island.
To think that there are such dangerous things
in this world waiting to be found...!
Just as I thought, this was a disappointment.
This isn't what I want to know.
Hey! Aren't those the same kind of characters
on that engraving next to it?!
What?!
"Gol D. Roger"...!
I made it here. I will guide
this text to the ends of the earth.
Pirate Gol D. Roger.
King of the Pirates...! Could this mean that
he came to this sky island, too?!
What on earth do these words mean?!
No, more importantly,why can
he use these characters?
So it says Roger?
You know him?!
He's a Blue Sea pirate who came to
this sky more than 20 years ago.
So his name is engraved there?
Yes. I don't know how he reached this bell,
but this sure is indelible proof that he did.
Come to think of it, there're
two kinds of Poneglyph stones.
Ones with information, and others that
indicate their whereabouts.
And this stone is one of the
ones with information.
"I made it here. I will guide
this text to the ends of the earth."
Guide this text... Guide...
It couldn't be...!Could
the Rio Poneglyph be...?!
Chief... This Poneglyphhas
already fulfilled its role!
It has?!
That's right. I bet those Poneglyphs
with information scattered around the world
will, when put together, become one text
that will fill the "Blank
History"for the first time.
In other words, the text completed
by connecting them...
That is the Rio Poneglyph,which
still does not exist.
Gol D. Roger, King of the Pirates,
definitely delivered this
text to its destination.
So it's no longer...
Then...
Hm?
...does that mean that our
duty has been fulfilled as well?
We...
We... don't have to... fight any longer?
I see... Our ancestors'
wish has been fulfilled, then?
Chief!
Are you all right?!
Good... Good... So our
duty has been fulfilled!
Yes.
Which means I, too,
have to guide the text on those Poneglyphs
that I read in the past...
...to the end of the Grand
Line... to Raftel...
Young lady, the feeling that straw hat
kid gives me is reminiscent of Roger.
Is it my imagination?
His name is Monkey D. Luffy.My
interest in him never fades.
D? I see. He's got the
same letter in his name.
Yes... and I'm sure it's a big issue that
has something to do with history.
By the way, young lady...You
guys wanted gold, right?
You said it's more valuable than
Vearth in the Blue Sea.
Yes.
How about taking the broken belfry column,
though we can't give you the bell...
That's a good idea!
Naturally, we have to show
our appreciation to you guys somehow.
That's right!
Don't hold back!
Are you sure?! They'll be happy to hear that!
Yeah!
Alright, then! Let's bring this
to the Blue Sea people!
Wrap it with cloths! It's hard to carry!
We'll give this to those who saved our land!
Man, this thing's huge...
What's Robin doing? She's late!
Darn! I'm hungry!
In any case, this place is so
empty. What's going on?
Where the heck did
the guerrillas and angels go?
Well, it's better they aren't here.If
they find us, they'll chase us around!
Since we're trying to steal this much gold
and run, they won't just let us go!
Well, Nami and Conis are preparing to
set sail, but we still have to hurry.
Before that, Sanji, do
you have something to eat?
Not until we get to the ship.
But you've gotta have something
to munch on, right?
What a pain!
Give me some!
We don't have to wait for that woman, do we?
I can't give you what
I don't have! Just give up!
I'm gonna go on ahead and get on board.
Idiot! Don't!
Idiot!
Idiot Moss Head!
Moss Head Idiot!
If you go into the forest alone, you
won't make it three steps without getting lost!
Hey, look! It's Robin!
Robin-chan!!
Yoo-hoo, Robin!! Hurry! Hurry up!We've
gotta run!! We stole some gold!
Idiot! Don't say that!Take
a good look behind her!!
They're all coming back here together!
There's tons of them!!
This is bad! This is bad! This is super bad!!
And what's that? A huge cannon?!
That's gotta be it!!
They all came back all at once!
Hurry to the ship! We can
no longer stay here!!
Check this out! We got a good
catch!The bag's stuffed! We're rich!
Hm? They all have bags on their back!
Don't tell me... Are they already leaving?!
Hey, stop, you guys!! Stop!!
Hey! Stop! Stop, you guys!
See?! They found us out!
Run!!
I'll strike a pose and say it!
You guys say, "Stop! Stop!" but...
Yeah! Tell them, Usopp!!
We risked our lives to come all
the way to this sky island!
That's right!
And we've found the legendary city of gold!
Robin-chan! Hurry up! We'll be caught!
How the heck can we, proud pirates,
just go back empty-handed?!
What?! Caught?! What's he talking about?
All we want to do is thank them!
Hey Miss, aren't you
guys gonna take this gold?
Looks like they don't need it!
What?!
Oh, no!
Run!!
Hey! Wait!
They're all after us! It's scary!
How was that?! Wasn't I cool?!
Yeah! Well done!
Robin-chan! Hurry!!
Hey! Come back!!
Guys! Keep running all the way
to the end of the sky!!
Yeah!!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens as you wander about
Just like the moon,you
keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection
wanes as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who
spend countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
Listen, everyone! We'll split the
treasure once we get back down, okay?!
I'll keep it safe, so don't worry.
Where?!
It's a secret.
There's no way I'll tell you where I
hide my secret stash, right?!
Hey!
Just kidding!
That's a lie! Her eyes say
she's telling the truth!
Alright, guys! We're going
back to the Blue Sea!!
Yeah!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Off to the Blue Sea!!
Finale Woven by Feelings"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!