Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,
one burning, the other frozen.
After learning about the ruler of
the island - Caesar Clown's motive,
and all while trying to escape Shinokuni,
along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Trafalgar Law,
they are on the move to kidnap Caesar,
save the children,
and escape from the island.
After falling into a garbage dump,
Luffy met a dragon named Momonosuke -
who has the same name as the boy that
the samurai Kin'emon was looking for.
Wh-What?!
Hey, wait!
We're... flying!
Wait, Mocha!
Don't do that.
Robin!
Oh!
You're Pirate Hunter Zoro
with a 120 million berry bounty!
She's a Logia-type.
I'll take care of her!
"A Deadly Fight in a Blizzard!
The Straw Hats vs. the Snow Woman!"
B BUILDING 3RD FLOOR - THE BISCUIT ROOM
Robin! Are you okay?
Yes,
it's just a scratch.
We must stop the children quickly.
Yeah.
Nami, please hurry!
The kids are gonna
leave the room soon!
Wait, Mocha!
I promised her that I will hold them
but I couldn't
and I put Mocha in danger!
Stop!
Give us the candy!
You can't have it!
Chopper-chan told me
what these candies do to us!
It's not fair!
Wait, Mocha! Give us the candy!
You shouldn't eat these candies!
Come to your senses, everybody!
Mocha, we have no choice.
We are sick.
Mommy!
Daddy!
They said we couldn't
see our parents now.
If adults get infected with the
disease we have, they'll die.
You don't want your mother
and father die, do you?
Let's get good treatment
for a year and get better!
Uh-huh!
I'm glad that you made it!
Good to see you!
My name is Caesar Clown.
Call me "Master."
You two are a part of my
first-generation of patients.
I'm looking forward
to working with you.
I bet you were scared and worried
when you heard
that you're sick out of the blue.
But everything is okay now.
You don't have to worry about anything.
I will treat you at any cost!
To tell you the truth,
I lost my only son to this disease.
I never wanna see another
child suffering from it!
Also, I don't wanna see another parent
lose their child and have to grieve like me!
Oh, I'm so sorry.
How embarrassing.
I shouldn't cry in front of you.
Are you okay, Master-san?
Thank you. You're very kind.
Oh yes! I must introduce you to them!
They're from other islands
but have the same disease.
Mocha!
Wait!
I'm Uzu. Nice to meet you!
Candy!
I'm Doran.
Wait! Mocha!
I'm Konbu.
Give me the candy!
We have some new friends here!
Teach them about this place, okay?
Okay!
Let's play over there!
Let's play!
Go ahead!
Uh-huh!
Everybody! Be nice to each other!
Let me know if you need any help!
Okay, Monet-san!
Monet-san was kind
but she was lying!
It was all lies!
This is a reward for
enduring with the treatment.
It's a candy from the Master.
Let's escape from here together!
Please!
Come to your senses now!
We gotta catch up with the children!
Yeah!
Where did she go?!
Hey you!
What are you doing?!
What?! Wait a sec!
Why is he coming this way?!
Wait, Nami! No!
You can't use me as a shield!
What a shame.
Why are you trying
to attack the weak ones?
It's strategic to finish off
easier foes first.
Zoro, move out of my way!
Heat Egg!
The heat worked, just as I thought!
Don't come after us!
Stay away!
Cat Burglar -
a 16 million berry bounty.
She hid herself in the snow again!
Don't you wanna fight me,
snow woman?!
The exit is...
Oh no!
Snow Fence!
Perpetual Snow!
Nami?!
The snow is...
It's cold! I can't move!
Nami!
She did it again!
Watch out, Chopper!
Cuatro Mano!
Spank!
Nami!
I was scared!
Robin! Thank you!
Oh please.
Those children are the Master's
precious test subjects.
And I'm responsible for protecting
Caesar and his experiment.
Who planted this rebellious
spirit in Mocha's mind?
What?!
Those kids asked for help on their own!
Move out of my way!
You go ahead!
We'd better hurry!
Uh-huh!
Mocha, please hang on!
You people are so uncool.
Every single day, we treat them nicely
and allow them to live in great comfort.
What you people are trying to do is
take away these "treasures"
from us "foster parents."
You people are like pirates.
So you have no problem with it, right?
I said it's uncool.
Stop interfering with my duty!
Sword Snow!
Skin Sword!
Great! We can get out of here like this!
Wh-What?!
What's the matter?!
I'm not hungry at all...
I'm not...
What is Monet doing?
The children are getting away!
But who cares?
We can always restock
guinea pigs through kidnapping.
Our priority now is providing
a showcase for Shinokuni
and getting rid of the Straw Hats.
Because the gas is
flowing into the building,
the situation is favorable for us.
B Building will be
filled up with gas soon.
They have no choice
but to head to R Building.
They're gonna be killed
by the gas anyway though.
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh no...
Oh no! Oh no!
Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh no! Oh no!
It's coming again!
How did the gas flow in?!
I thought the door was closed!
Is it leaking from somewhere?
Really?!
If so, this building is no longer safe!
We have no time!
Let's split up to look for the
Sea Prism Stone Handcuffs!
Again?!
But I guess we have no choice.
Brook, you go with Kin'emon!
We can't leave him alone -
he's too clumsy!
Alright!
Corpse-dono, thank you!
See you at R Building!
Okay!
You've been only defending yourself
without even trying to attack. Why is it?
Could it be what I think it is?
To be honest, I didn't think
I could beat you but...
...maybe I can.
There's another room!
Find the children and
take them out of here!
Hey, isn't it a little cold here?
The Navy?
Let's go through the door!
Yeah!
Everybody's trying to take
the children away from us!
I won't allow it!
Let's go!
Charge!
Why are you leading them?!
Brother! I don't see any children
but there's Pirate Hunter Zoro!
He's such a pain.
Alright, guys!
Stick out your lower lip
and make fun of him!
I hope they all slip on the snow,
hit their heads and die.
Hey, Nami and Robin went ahead.
Just go away already.
Oh! What good information
even from a fool!
Alright, let's go, guys...
But there's a cutie behind him!
Oh! She's so cute!
You people are so obnoxious!
Just go already!
Hey. But look!
Her appearance.
She's not a human.
A bird with a human face?
She's a harpy!
What?!
B-But...
...she's still cute!
Rather bewitchingly beautiful!
Yeah, so sexy!
You're enjoying this, aren't you?!
Hey, why is it snowing in here?
Oh yeah.
It's because of me.
It's getting stormy
all of a sudden!
No matter who you are,
I'm not gonna let anybody
take the children!
She's gone!
Where did she go?!
Hey! Are you alright?!
Wh-What happened to my shoulder?!
You bastard!
Sh-She's a Logia-type!
That bitch!
Damn!
A swordsman using Haki?!
Captain-chan!
We sealed off the door to the room
to prevent the gas from flowing in.
But we don't know
where it might start leaking again.
There's not much time!
Everybody, do all you can
to save the children!
What about you?
I'm gonna stay here!
What?!
What are you thinking?
I think you need my help here!
What?!
Monet attacks, using the powerful
Snow-Snow Fruit powers,
and Tashigi desperately fights
back by using her Haki.
But she is then caught by
Monet's monstrous fangs,
and just as her shoulder is
about to be torn to shreds,
Zoro's beast-like instincts cause him into action.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Showing Off His Techniques!
Zoro's Formidable One-Sword Style!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!