Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome treasure
at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King of
the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
The horizons everyone dreamed
of were separate at first
but now they can be seen through
a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny is
leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve your
dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
♪ The impregnable fortress, G8! ♪
♪ Pirates can't come near it! ♪
♪ With its 108 cannons jutting out, ♪
♪ it's a hedgehog that
protects the peace! ♪
♪ Our pride, G8! ♪
You know, though, I hear our fortress isn't
very popular lately within the Navy.
Yeah, I hear there're some people who call us
dim-witted hedgehogs made soft
by peace behind our back...
It's not surprising, since we've had
hardly any pirate attacks the past few years.
What'd you say?!
It wasn't me who said
that.It's a rumor! A rumor!
Tsk! What's their
problem?!Peace is wonderful!
What's wrong with peace?!
♪ The impregnable fortress, G8! ♪
Every day is a beautiful day.
Man, they really tore up this ship!
It'll probably take at
least a week to fix it.
Our orders are to fix it in three days.
Oh, man...
Did this ship climb a mountain or something?
Oh, it's you, Mechao-san.
That's a good way of putting it!
Yeah, it'd have to climb a mountain or
something to get this wrecked!
Well, you know, it
might've fallen from the sky.
It probably got caught around the sea
gate when entering the port.
Yeah, that area is very narrow,so
it's hard to pass through,
even for a navigator who's used to it.
Now, let's stop joking around and
get to work already!
Okay, okay...
Geez... Sailors these days don't have
enough love for their ships...
What's the matter, Mechao-san?!
"A State of Emergency Is Issued!A
Notorious Pirate Ship Has Infiltrated!"
We've got a problem!
I-It appears that we've been invaded by
a huge object from the sky!
An invasion from the sky?!
F-From the sky, you said?!
"Justice"
An unidentified mysterious object
has invaded the base!
Hurry up! Guard the sea gate!
You guys go watch the coast!
Sniper Unit! Move it!
But I'm sleepy...
Close the sea gate!!
Over there! 4 o'clock!
4 o'clock! All lights on the target!!
P-Pirate ship...
The pirate flag has... a
skull with a straw hat!
Th-The Straw Hat Pirates?!
Wh-What?!
Ready!
Target the Straw Hat Pirates' ship!!
Did somebody say "Straw Hat"?!
Lt. Commander Drake!
The ship that has invaded our base is
the Straw Hat Pirates' ship!
Straw Hat, you say?!Where's
Commander Jonathan?!
Well... we can't find him.
Honestly, that man's...!
I'll be damned... To think
that someone invaded from the sky...
Resistance is futile! We
have you completely surrounded!
"Full of Power!""Carbohydrates!""Navy
Dining Hall"
Don't you think it's been
pretty noisy outside?
Yeah, I wonder if there're intruders
or something...
Ouch!
No chit-chatting!
Look! We have to prepare meals
for 1,000 people!
In two hours, a bunch of boys from
the night shift will show up!
There's no time for fooling around!
But...
The siren from earlier...
Don't worry, lads!
The day this fortress falls is
the day the world falls.
Besides, when Jessica-sama blows
up, she's a lot scarier than...
Jessica-sama...
What is it?
Commander! Where have you been?!
I didn't catch anything today.
Again?!
But I had a large catch yesterday!
I'm not talking about that!Commander,
if you're always absent...
What's the big deal? Night fishing isn't
necessarily a waste, you know.
Commander, I have a report!According
to the watchmen,
as well as the maintenance men inside the
dock who saw the ship close by...
A-According to them...
What is it?
Spit it out already!
Yes... well... um...
They say they saw ghosts.
Like I said, something suddenly
fell from the sky!
A hairy monster appeared.It
jumped and then disappeared.
Hands... Hands...
What about hands?!
Hands grew out from my body, and
the next moment, everything went black!
That's right... they were
a girl's soft hands.
It's gotta be...
A ghost ship!!
Don't be ridiculous!
Yes, sir...
Without doubt, that is the Straw Hats' ship!
There's no way it's a ghost ship!
Moreover, of all things,to say
that it fell from the sky?!
Well... the part about it coming from
the sky, at least, is true.
I told you that it isn't a waste, didn't I?
Right, Lt. Commander?
I see...
A ghost ship, huh?
It smells good.
Commander! I found these in one of the rooms!
Ingots and a crown... Those are quite old.
They must've stolen them from
some ancient ruins.
Send them to the forensics lab!
Yes, sir!
Well then, let's explore inside, shall we?
Chirps?
That's the one. It's just an ordinary South
Bird. There's nothing to fear.
South Bird?
Yeah.
It's a funny bird valued highly by
old-time sailors because they always point south.
Hey, stop it!
Are you all right?!
So they're surprisingly violent.
They're well maintained.
Medical books and history books... huh?
I guess these ghosts study a lot.
Ghosts again? How ridiculous...
Thanks for your hard work. Continue the
investigation of this ghost ship.
Ghost ship, he says?
Got that?
Y-Yes, sir!
It appears that that ship stopped
by Jaya quite recently.
The coffee was tasty, wasn't it?
Yes...
The color and smell of
the coffee left on the deck...
That was definitely Jaya Coffee.
But you've got the courage to drink it
without investigating it well.
Um... Well...
And that South Bird... That's a
bird that inhabits the jungles of Jaya.
Did you know? A legend of gold remains
deeply entrenched there.
Commander, then that ship is...
I don't know about its crew's whereabouts,
but it's certain that it came from Jaya.
It's not some ghost ship.
Right! I've seen that ship
twice.It's the Straw Hats' ship!
But you, yourself, called it
a ghost ship earlier, Commander.
We have fresh recruits and
prisoners at this fortress.
If we tell everyone about the
Straw Hats' invasion
without knowing their true purpose,
it'll only cause confusion within
the fortress, right?
So let's just keep calling it
a ghost ship for now.
With all due respect, Commander,
we should organize a special investigation
unit right away
and search for them as soon as possible!
Please assign it to my unit!
Now, don't be so hasty.
But...
Building up our defense is the priority now.
You go reinforce security at the
coast as well as around the sea gate.
Yes, sir!
You go reinforce security at the ammunition
bunker, detention facilities
and the major passageways. I'll also grant
you authority to manage personnel.
Understood!
You look dissatisfied, Lt. Commander.
No, sir...
The night is still long.They
probably can't move around much.
Well, that goes for us, too.
Wait until morning, then take your unit
and thoroughly investigate places
where people gather.
Places where people gather, you say?
That's right!
It's hard to find green insects
since they live in green grassy places.
If the Straw Hats were
to wear our uniforms...
It's not that I don't
trust my men's abilities,
but it's very possible that
they'll take some of our uniforms.
Pirates are like stray
dogs...They're always hungry.
Why don't you start by checking the
dining hall once morning comes?
Yes, sir!
Where did everyone go?
What is this place?!
Crap!
Good thing we've got a waver.
Security is tight.
We'd better get out of here right away!
Don't tell me! This is...?!
Well, well... We've fallen to
a troublesome place.
I wonder if Nami-san and
Robin-chan were able to escape okay.
What's the matter?!
Well, I saw some sort of light in the tree.
You were probably seeing things.
I can't even smoke in peace!
Beef, pork, chicken, beef, fish, pork...
Meat! Meat! Meat!!
No matter how I look at it, I haven't eaten
since we left the sky island!
Well, that didn't help.
If Chopper were here, he would've caught
the smell of food for me!
Found them!
Damn... We can't even get close
to the Merry like that.
Oreja Fleurs!
After all that, we couldn't
find even a single crew member.
Even worse, the maintenance
guys said they saw monsters, right?
Yeah, and the Commander clearly admitted
that this is a ghost ship.
How mean... asking us to watch
a creepy ship like this.
I see. Apparently, the Navy thinks that
the Merry is a ghost ship.
A ghost ship?! How rude! I'm gonna sue!!
But it's better for us, as well as
for the Merry, if they think that way.
We can buy time.
Now that I know that...
I get it! They must've stolen cursed
gold from some ruins!
Cut it out! I touched that gold...
Gh-Ghost!!
Straw Hat Luffy and Pirate Hunter Zoro...
We can probably assume that the
woman with countless hands
and the hairy monster are
also part of the group.
In any case, there're seven of them.
Among them are...
A skilled cook...
A knowledgeable ship's doctor...There
may be a historian as well...
I heard a suspicious noise!
This way! Hurry!
I don't know what's going on! How
do these convoluted hallways work?!
I'm trapped! What am I gonna
do?!What am I gonna do?!
What am I gonna do?!What
the heck should I do?!
It's downstairs!
Okay, got it!
I'm saved!
Now... where should I head?
Just as I thought...It's surrounded
by land in all directions.
Does that mean we fell on
a huge lake with no way out?!
At any rate, obtaining the information we
need to escape is our top priority.
Let's be resolved... Long-nose.
I don't want to.
It was just my imagination.
That idiot! He's got no sense of tension!
What I don't know is their purpose.What
on earth did they come here for?
Well, at any rate, my fortress is
no laughing matter.
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,on
the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give
in,even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared
of,we can overcome it
Of all places, this is a Navy fortress?!
I'm starving!
We can't do anything until we
know the entire picture!
I'm starving!
Let me see your cook's spirit!
Are you talking to me?!
I said I'm starving!
Welcome to the fortress of Navarone!
Are you talking to me?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sanji the Cook! Proving His Merit
at the Navy Dining Hall!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!