Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
God Eneru and Luffy finally
clashed on the Ark Maxim.
What the hell... are you?!
I'm Luffy.
I'm a pirate and a rubber person.
Rubber?
Lightning has no effect
whatsoever on a rubber person.
Strong as Eneru is, he
felt threatened by Luffy.
Grom... Puddling!
Gum-Gum... Battle-Axe!!
As the battle intensified,
the golden Ark Maxim finally took off.
The circuit to this ark's ultimate feature
is already open and functioning.
Its name is Deathpiea.
It's despair, the savior of this world.
You think it's okay for a
god to destroy everything?!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!!
Gum-Gum...
...Rifle!!
"Luffy Falls!
God's Judgment and Nami's Wish!!"
Ahh! The ship is leaving the Vearth!
It's flying! What should we do?!
The ship's gonna fly away!
You did it! You did it!!
You defeated Eneru!!
B-But the ship is... the ship is flying away!
Don't tell me...! Is he still getting up?!
You fools!
I-Is that all you've got?
Once you're gone, the world will be mine!
Once again, everyone will fear me,
worship me, and revere me.
My world!!
Vermin like you are no match for me!
To me... nothing is impossible!!
I am the Almighty God!!
Get out of here!
Look! Something is floating
in the sky above Upper Yard!
A... A ship?!
That can't be! A flying ship...
I've never heard of such a thing!
So that ship's what caused
the sky to become dark?!
God is on that ship!
Hey!
Get out of here, now!
Board the ships!
Lots of ships are leaving Angel Island!
What on earth is going on?
Those dark clouds... What happened?!
Hm? Someone is coming this way!
Ahoy! Shandians!!
You should immediately
prepare your ships as well!
This nation is lost!
What?!
Escape!
To the Blue Sea!
T... To the Blue Sea?!
A ship...
God... Eneru...
Feast your eyes, rubber person...
...on the falling island's despair.
This will be the end of the sky island.
The lives of the angels will be terminated.
No one can stop it any longer.
Of course... that includes you!
Stop it!!
Grom...
The golden wall...!
How dare...
...Puddling!!
Ow! Ouch!
He melted it using the electric heat!
Dammit, it burns!! Ahh!!
Luffy!!
It doesn't come off! Dammit!
Rubber person from the Blue Sea...
...I don't have to fight you, you know.
Take this off! You bastard!!
After all, I couldn't stand taking
a hit while fighting you again.
So...
...why don't we part here?
In honor of the good fight
you put up, I'll give you...
...this gold!!
Luffy!!
Once I confine you, the world
will be mine, just as it was before.
There will be no one in
the world who can defeat me.
"In the world"?!
Are you stupid or what?
There are lots who can!
In the Blue Sea, there're
tons of monstrous fighters!
Someone like you is...
You sure are a talkative brat, aren't you?
Fall! Together with the sky island!
Someone like you is...!!
N-No!!
Luffy!!
Luffy...
Damn you!!
That's Luffy, Horsey-Bird! Luffy's falling!
That's... Aisa! Pierre!
So that's who it was...
that sly voice I've been hearing.
Fight me!!
Luffy! We're coming to save you!
How annoying! You're wasting your time!
Aisa! Pierre! Watch out! Dodge it!
Eneru!!
God's Judgment!
El Thor!!
Luffy!!
Aisa!! Pierre!!
"God"
Luffy... Aisa...
As tough as I am, that
still hit me pretty hard.
That rubber thing... was quite annoying.
However... this is the conclusion.
What a large ship...
So that's the ark that the
Divine Squad was forced to build.
Here, the northeast of the island.
After they get the gold, I'm meeting
up with them at this seashore.
Then, as soon as everyone
shows up, you can leave?
If necessary, I can go once
the treasure gets delivered.
N... Nami-san...
They're coming to the seashore in the
northeast... coming back to their ship.
I'll go there and wait...
for everyone to show.
And I have to guide them to the Blue Sea!
I'm the only one who can show them
the way to escape the sky island!
I have to hurry to the Going Merry!
I had a long dream...
Yes, it was a dream about you.
Oh, Nami-san, you and I ate a forbidden
fruit and wandered in a paradise.
I don't wanna wake up... Let us stay
forever in this beautiful dream.
Oh, Nami-san...
Hmmm... What is it?
No!
I want to stay in the dream with Nami-san.
Hm...? Nami-san?
Where's Nami-san?
Hm?!
Nami-san!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
Mellorine... Mellorine, Mellorine...
Mellorine, Mellorine,
Mellorine, Mellorine, Mello--
Nami-san!!
Oh, no!!
Hey! Wake up, Usopp!
It's no time to be in bed! Idiot!
What is it? Hm? What hap...
Never mind that, just get ready!
Huh? G-Get ready?
We're gonna rescue Nami-san!
Rescue? Res...
That's right! Now I remember!
God! God appeared!!
Oh, no...
God, God, God, God...
He isn't here anymore! He's long gone!
Tremble, tremble, tremble,
fumble, fumble, fumble...
Nami-san was kidnapped by him!
N-Nami was?!
Dammit! She was kidnapped
because we're so pathetic.
Since she's cute...
Well, she was kidnapped?
Where?
There!
What?!
What is that?! A forest?! A ship?!
Though it was just for a
second, I saw her for sure!
Nami-san is on that ship.
It doesn't matter what it is!
In any case, she wasn't wearing her T-shirt.
That really doesn't matter!
I don't get the situation at all. Where are
Conis, weird knight and the others?!
I don't know. Anyway, we have to hurry!
Hey, where're we going, Sanji?!
Where else?! That ship!
What?!
If we get any further behind,
we won't be able to board!
Now is our only chance!
Um, am I going, too,
by any chance? To that place?
Of course!! You have that thing, right?!
The rope that you shoot out from your belly!
Oh, you mean "Usopp Aa-aa-aa"?!
Then I'll let you use this,
so I'll wait down here!
Just hurry up!
I don't want to! W-Wait a sec!
Idiot! There's no time to waste!!
I'm coming for you!! Nami-san!!
Now that the Ark Maxim has been activated,
even if they cry or scream, there is
no way for this nation to be saved.
The sky island will fall from the sky
and I, the Almighty God,
will rise up to the land without end,
to the Endless Vearth...
on the golden ark, Maxim.
That's right. I shouldn't forget...
...to pick up that treasure
on my way up there.
The huge golden bell that
Shandora took pride in,
and the grand belfry for that bell...
I needed to see the belfry.
A golden bell...
A huge bell that's the most befitting
to me, who rules the heavens!
What's the matter? You're lucky
enough to have made it this far.
Abandon those who are incompetent.
You must have a future you wish for, right?
A future I wish for...
Yes, I do.
But if I just stay here and go with you,
it's the same as being alone.
Let's get this party goin'! It's the
night festival before gold-hunting!
Let's get the treasure!
Gold!
Where's the fun in gaining
what you want all by yourself?
There're actually a lot of things
I want and that I'd like to do,
but if I have to abandon those
guys and go with you like this...
...then I don't want anything anymore!!
You don't want anything?
That includes your life, right?
What's going on?! Hey, Suu?
Both Usopp-san and Sanji-san
aren't in shape to be moving around!
What happened?!
Why aren't they here? Where are those two?!
"Um..."
"Oh, yeah!"
"The guy with the cool
eyebrows woke up first..."
Sanji-san woke up...
...and woke Usopp-san up.
"...and he woke up the
dubious guy with a long nose."
"They ran very hard..."
And they both ran,
"...jumped using a weird gadget..."
and jumped... into the sky?
"...and went to that flying ship."
What?! Don't tell me...!
They went to that ship?!
Their bodies still aren't...
How reckless!
A-Are we really going to do it?!
Are we really, seriously, going
to do it in this strong wind?!
Ahh... My "Can't Go to
High Places" disease is...
Like I said, I'll let you use this,
so go by yourse...!
Stop rambling nonsense!!
Now!! Come on!
I won't be responsible for this!
Come on... reach it!!
That's not really a smart thing to say.
Now you've lost the means to survive.
If you don't want to be on this ship,
then there is only one fate for you.
Go to the afterlife.
Ahh! I don't like this! Come off! Come off!
Shut up!
Yes, sir.
Usopp! Don't swing, dummy!
You idiot!!
Usopp Aa... aa...! Hey...!
God or not, if someone
lays a finger on Nami-san...
...I will become a devil of the Blue Sea!!
Nami-san!!
I'll put my all into this. Even if it
takes all my energy and brainpower,
I will survive!
One more time... Yes, to sail out to
sea with everyone one more time!
Luffy... I'm gonna borrow your courage!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens
as you wander about
Just like the moon,
you keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection wanes
as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who spend
countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
How dare you kidnap Nami-san?!
Bastard! You won't get away with this!!
If I stay here, I'll die for sure!
I have to escape somehow!
There is no salvation for you at this point!
What are we gonna do against God?!
Go... to the afterlife!
Just hold on! I'll protect you
even if it costs me Usopp's life!
Um, mine?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Two Awaken! On the Front Lines
of the Burning Love Rescue!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!