Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
He repelled Zoro's attack with his bare hand!
Is that your ability?
I have the power to repel various things.
I am a paw man,
having eaten the Paw-Paw Fruit.
What is that supposed to be?
Air? Is he condensing the air with his paws?
The bubble is getting smaller!
He's applying pressure to
a large body
of air by repelling it with his paws!
That's making it shrink!
When all of that air depressurizes,
it will generate power!
The giant sonic blast it creates
will be like a bomb.
Wh-What?!
A bomb?
In other words, he's making a bomb?!
A... bomb?!
I will spare your lives.
In exchange, all you need to do is
hand over Straw Hat Luffy's head.
As long as I get his head,
the government will not complain.
You want us to sell out our friend?
Now then, give Straw Hat to me.
Forget it!
What a pity.
"The Pain of My Crewmates Is My Pain!
Zoro's Desperate Fight!"
Ursus Shock!
Lion Strike!
What... are you?!
Are you a cyborg like Franky?
No, you're stronger than tempered steel!
That melted... steel!
A cyborg...
Although an accurate description,
I am nothing like Cyborg Franky.
I am the government's
incomplete human weapon,
known as a "Pacifista."
A Pacifista?
My developer is the government's
genius scientist, Dr. Vegapunk.
He is the most brilliant man in the world.
It's said his scientific knowledge is
500 years ahead of the rest of mankind.
He gave you an incredible body...
and you're a power holder!
I feel like hope is fading away.
As you can imagine,
my body refuses to do as I tell it.
Are you absolutely insistent
on taking Luffy's head?
That is the most I can compromise.
All right. I'll give you a head.
However, instead of taking his...
...I would appreciate it if
you took my life instead!
My bounty isn't worth much yet,
but I was going to become the
greatest swordsman in the world!
This should be a fair trade.
Are you truly willing to die
for that man when you harbor
such great ambition?
Right now, it's the only way
to save my crewmates!
My ambition means nothing if
I can't protect my own captain.
Luffy will become the King of the Pirates!
Wait! Wait, you stinking idiot!
What good will come from your death?
What happened to your ambition, stupid?
Why, you...!
Hey, Colossus!
Whoa!
Instead of taking that moss head
swordsman's life, take mine!
The Marines still don't think much of me,
but before long, I'll be the most
dangerous member of this crew.
I'm Black Foot Sanji!
Why, that--!
Now kill me!
Don't take his life, take mine...
I've always been prepared to
sacrifice myself for the others.
This is where I'll die gloriously!
Hey, please give...
...my regards to the others.
Sorry, but you'll have to
search for another cook.
Y-You jerk!
I'm begging you!
If I harm Straw Hat now,
I will only bring shame upon myself.
I am in your debt.
Trust me not to bring him harm.
I am a man of my word.
In exchange, I will...
...show you hell.
What I just repelled from his
body was pain... and fatigue.
This is all of the damage that he
accumulated in his battle with Moria.
If you want to take his place,
take all of his pain and
suffering unto yourself.
It will be impossible for
you to survive when you are
already on the brink of death.
You will die.
Have a small taste.
Well?
Let me... do this somewhere else!
He has good companions.
I should have expected no less
from your son, Dragon.
Hey, is everyone still alive?!
That Kuma guy must have thought we died
in the blast and left! So much for that!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey, man! You've gotta be joking.
What's gotten into you?
Hey, look! My body feels light. Why is that?
Don't lie! That can't be true.
Perhaps he has taken so much
damage that it's given him a high.
Yeah, right! I don't buy it!
But it's true!
And I'm sayin' that's not possible!
Yahoo!
It's too hard to believe!
I'm light! Light!
There is no way everyone pulled through okay!
Where is that jerk?!
There he is.
Phew, you scared me!
Hey, where did that Warlord go?
Where did all of this blood come from?!
Hey, are you still alive?!
Where is he?!
What happened here?!
No...
Nothing happened...!
I've never seen Zoro this
severely injured before.
What could have happened?
I saw what went down!
Isn't it wonderful to have comrades?
I must fulfill the promise I
made to my dear comrades!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Promise from a Distant Day!
The Pirates' Song and a Small Whale!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!