Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Buggy and Mr. 3 who were
trying to get to level 3...
...have been captured by
Vice Warden Hannyabal, but...
Meanwhile, Luffy's battle
against Warden Magellan is...
This is your punishment.
There is no way to neutralize the
amount of poison you have absorbed!
You will agonize for 24 hours
and then pass...
...to the real hell!
"For his friend!
Bon Clay Goes to the Deadly Rescue!"
Warden Magellan! Great fight!
What should we do with the fallen Luffy?
He'll die soon but we don't
want him lying there.
Throw him into the Central Tower on level 5.
Yes, sir!
W-Warden Magellan!
We had a problem at the staircase to level 3!
That's Hannyabal's post! What happened?
I don't know the details!
Hey. Hey!
He's gone.
He's either dead or preserved for the future.
That's ridiculous!
My f-fingers!
I can't move them! I can't even feel them!
That's frostbite! You're history!
Damn, this is aggravating!
I can't even bite this bread!
Hey, look! Here's a newcomer!
Hey! What's your name?!
How much is your bounty?! Talk to us!
He's nearly dead!
He already got the poison punishment!
What's the meaning of all this?!
Hannyabal! I counted on you but all
of your guards have been beaten!
Wake up, Hannyabal! What happened here?!
W-Warden! Please let go of me!
I-I am very sorry! I was off-guard!
I-I don't want gomon (torture)!
Komon (anus) stinks!
Damn that queer! He abandoned us!
A queer who uses martial arts did all this!
How can I put this...
He caught us by surprise!
No excuse!
You let him get away and
he escaped to the upper levels, right?
That prisoner used to work for
Crocodile's Baroque Works.
He's the guy who used to call himself Mr. 2.
I mean, that queer!
That doesn't matter!
He was captured in level 3.
I'm sure that we'll catch him in time.
What happened to the riot on level 2?!
It's almost under control.
I want all guards gathered
on level 4 to go to level 3!
Unleash all demon guards
under Sadie-chan's command!
I'll leave the rest to you!
Okay! What about these two?
Do whatever you like!
Clean up all the mess now
and get things in order!
I'm going to head to my "private place."
Ouch!
"The runs"... as usual?
Hey you guys, get up and
look for the last escapee!
Yes, in a second!
E-Excuse me!
What do you wanna do with these two?
Oh! I want to ask them about something.
Get us an interview room.
I'll take charge of them.
Understood, sir.
Alright then, Vice Warden!
Yeah.
Now, what we'll do is...
We're safe now!
W-We escaped torture!
Okay, what should we do now?
You know what we're gonna do!
We better hurry and...
...rescue Straw-chan!
R-Rescue him?!
Did you hear them saying
that he's been poisoned
by Magellan and is on level 5?!
There's no hope for him to survive
and we'd die like dogs!
He's right! Why should we even try?!
I don't care if we die like dogs--or queers!
When I turned my back on
Straw-chan and Magellan,
I had already died!
I thought that I better run
than suffer the same fate.
And if there's a chance he'll survive,
then I'll be back to put my life
on the line and rescue him!
That's what I swore!
And I ran!
That's a very nice story,
but now you're free!
Why would you wanna go back
and risk your life again?!
Because I'm his friend!
I don't need any other reasons!
Friends?
We gotta deal with the poison
to save Straw-chan!
We need an antidote!
You think that we can get it?
It's too late anyway!
Shut up!
I must... I must do this!
Wait for me!
Don't die on me yet, Straw-chan!
No way?!
I mean, what do you mean that
you can't make an antidote!
No one ever survives after...
...challenging Warden Magellan and
receiving a heavy dose of his poison!
If it's just one kind, maybe we could
but we can't make an antidote...
...that works for various poisons!
And you people call yourselves
a medical team?!
Gimme a break!
Huh?
I mean... give me a break and do something!
We have to turn Straw Hat Luffy
over to the Navy!
But if we administer the medication
incorrectly, he'll die sooner!
I'm sorry to say this but
there's no way to keep him alive.
I told you! It's too late to save Straw Hat!
There is no antidote.
That means we can't do anything for him!
Now, give up on Straw Hat
and let's get out of this prison together!
He's right!
You need to know when to give up!
If we stay here any longer, we'll melt away!
To be honest with you,
no matter how hard you try,
Straw Hat is maybe already...
It was reckless to fight against
Magellan in the first place.
You can't survive a battle with him.
It'd take a miracle!
A miracle?
Oh yeah! He is in Impel Down!
The queen of queers--
Ivan-san!
He once saved both a patient
who was given up on by his doctor,
and a half-broken country!
There are a lot of legends about him!
He's the greatest star of all queers--Ivan-san!
We better find him now!
Who's... Ivan-san?
LEVEL 4--STAFF STAIRCASE
You wanna go to level 5?
Yes, I do.
These two have been
sentenced to freeze to death!
Why are we going to level 5?
We have no choice.
We can try to escape
but the security on level 3
must be tightened by Magellan's order.
We're safe for now as long as
we stay with the "Vice Warden."
I know that!
But his obsession with saving Straw Hat -
I don't know how long we're gonna be safe!
Yeah, but at least we are for now!
Keep walking!
I got to do this!
Wait for me, Straw-chan!
But this list of prisoners is confusing.
What is this about?
Emporio Ivancov--the real name
of Ivan-san has been crossed off!
Has he been released already?
Or has he been executed?!
Did we let this prisoner go free?
What?! Oh, Ivancov...
You-know-what happened
to him a few years ago...
You-know-what?
Don't you remember it, Vice Warden?
Oh!
Oh yeah! That! Yeah!
Do you know about That?! Explain it to me!
But there are prisoners here.
I don't care!
People have disappeared
occasionally in Impel Down.
They didn't break out because
some of them could barely move.
They just disappeared without a trace.
We call it "Demoning away!"
We all fear these unnatural
disappearances and assume...
...that they're pulled into the gate of hell.
That's why we call it "Demoning away!"
People disappear...?
I wish that I hadn't heard that.
Me, too.
Wow, it's cold already!
The door isn't even open yet!
And we're wearing heavy clothes!
We're here!
Be careful of the severe coldness
and Army Wolves!
Now, I'll take them as usual.
Huh? You take what?
Well, your weapons and coat.
What?!
We really can't imagine how you can do it!
How you always say
"I'll show the prisoners
the dignity of the Vice Warden!"
and go into the Freezing Hell
naked without any weapons.
We all admire you for doing so!
What?!
It's not appropriate to let prisoners wear coats
so we'll take them, naturally!
They'll take our coats, too!
What?!
Be careful!
Due to the temperature,
Transponder Snails don't work here!
Take care!
What?!
It's so... ugh!
U-Unlock my handcuffs now!
I-I can barely use my hand in this coldness!
It's too cold! The air hurts!
I-I almost got it!
It's unlocked!
Yes! You did it!
1, 2, 3... there're 4 of them!
Hey, don't tell me that they're Army Wolves!
Do you know why they're here instead
of the Floor of Wild Beasts from Hell?!
No. Why?
Oh, I know!
Because they would eat the
other beasts like the Basilisk or Sphinx!
Are you kidding me?!
So they're extra special savage!
Severe cold was enough
but now we got Army Wolves, too!
Another reason for my teeth to chatter!
Alright, let's just do this!
We're gonna rescue Straw-chan!
I don't wanna become their dinner!
You're running already?!
S-So strong!
Now I know why they're
demon guards on level 5!
But I can't die here like a dog or a queer!
I gotta save Straw-chan!
I'll show them my queer guts!
"Oh Come My Way" Kenpo...
Ha!
I-I can't move my body!
I told you!
It's not good for us to stay with that guy!
The situation is far worse than I expected!
We gotta find a way out, quick!
If we fool around here any longer,
The Army Wolves will find us!
The Burning Heat Hell to the Freezing Hell!
What a difference!
But this coldness is unusual...
Hey, don't stop running!
But I can feel that instead of
keeping myself warm by running,
it's drawing all my energy!
How cold can it get?!
Yeah!
Oh, I think that we can
avoid the wind over there!
W-W-Wait!
D-Dammit!
The wind isn't blowing here but
the floor froze my butt and my entire body!
If we stay here,
both of us will be frozen for real!
Alright, let's do it!
You got a plan?!
Do you remember that we formed
an alliance to breakout?!
Yeah, we huddled and decided to join forces...
We should huddle together now!
Good idea!
Alright, let's snuggle up and get warm!
Rub, rub, rub...
Hmm...
I'm not getting warm at all and...
Um. I feel kinda sick!
I feel sick, too!
They followed us!
And there's more now!
He tastes better than me! I guarantee!
What're you saying?!
I'm a wax man so I taste awful!
--He tastes better than me!
What a mess this is.
Do we have to see him dying?
Ouch!
I wanna go and rescue Ace!
You'll be like an ant blown into a storm.
You can just be flicked away
without even having done anything.
A... Ace!
Stop resisting!
You can't survive after
taking that much poison!
You've lost your sight, huh?
Can you hear me?
Be quiet and accept death!
No! I don't wanna die!
I'm not gonna die until I rescue Ace!
Do you wanna rescue somebody?
Even you have no hope for yourself?
Is it your friend?
How stupid!
You gotta save your own ass in a prison!
No one's gonna come to save you!
We're all alone!
In the sea of fire,
you'd step on someone
beside you in order to survive!
When you face the beasts,
you'd sacrifice someone near you to survive!
You'll die if you care about others!
So, cut the you-wanna-rescue-someone crap!
It makes me sick!
Look! Somebody's coming!
He's not a jailer or one of the staff!
What's wrong with him?
Is he naked!
Straw-chan, I come to rescue you!
In the name of friendship!
Bon Clay searches level 5 for the queen of queers--Iva-san.
However, under repeated attacks
from the Army Wolves and
fighting to withstand the
cold of the Freezing Hell,
he loses his strength and collapses.
Where is this queen of queers, exactly?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Paradise in Hell!
Impel Down Level 5.5!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!