Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fish-Man Pirates,
who were holding a grudge against humans
and looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom.
Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of
the New Fish-Man Pirates, in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
2 years ago at a Sky Island,
I read a Poneglyph indicating where
one of the ancient weapons is.
The Mermaid Princess who lived
around the same time as Joy Boy...
...was known by a specific name, wasn't she?
The ancient weapon...
...Poseidon!
"The Straw Hats Stunned! The
New Fleet Admiral of the Navy!"
I do not know their purpose
but a long time ago, there were powerful
entities that could destroy the world.
They were 3 Ancient Weapons
given the names of gods.
Pluton, Uranus, and Poseidon.
And she is one of them.
Indeed.
We can't let anyone know about this.
Every powerful group in the world would
want Princess Shirahoshi's power.
The Government--even pirates.
The Ancient Weapons?
They could destroy the world?!
I got all their treasure
and I was about to leave
but this is even bigger news!
I see. So that Mermaid Princess is...
Whew, I want seconds!
You already ate it all?!
It's so good--I could eat this forever!
Especially this candy!
It's as good as meat. I
want hundreds of them!
I-I'm afraid we are running out of that one.
We can bring other things if you want!
All right!
Let me ask you, Luffy.
What do you know about the
state of the world now?
Huh? What are you asking all of a sudden?
Looks like you know nothing. You're
out of the loop--that's not good.
Yeah?
Here's the food!
Let's go somewhere else to talk.
Okay. One sec.
I'll take a light snack.
Oh, you guys are here too!
I drank too much! I'm trying to sober up!
I ate too much!
Sanji Mermaid-ed too much.
It's like heaven! The Mermaid Island!
What?! Akainu and Aokiji had a big fight?!
That's what I thought.
You didn't even know about that, did you?
I didn't hear about anything
during my training.
Rayleigh is terrible.
I knew about it! I knew!
Are you serious?!
Right after the war 2 years ago,
Fleet Admiral Sengoku resigned.
Sengoku recommended Aokiji
to be his successor since he was
very popular among his own men
but a lot of people at the
highest level favored Akainu
and so he became a major contender.
Normally, Aokiji doesn't show his passion
but he hated the idea of Akainu
becoming a Fleet Admiral.
They stood against each other and the
first-ever feud between the Admirals...
...erupted into a battle
on an island somewhere.
Like the saying "Dead men tell no tales,"
whoever lost had to withdraw his candidacy.
The winner would lead the Navy.
As all the world now knows, their
deadly struggle lasted for 10 days.
They were comparable in their
strength but it came to an end.
Akainu won!
Sakazuki is the new Fleet Admiral.
Akainu!
I got you!
Did Aokiji die?
They were both severely wounded
and though Akainu is
pitiless, he showed mercy
to his former comrade
who couldn't even stand.
But Aokiji refused to work for Akainu
so he left the Navy.
He's not a Navy soldier now, is he?
No, he is not. I wonder where he
is and what he is thinking now.
It was a big loss for the Government, too.
Of course. The Admirals were
the Navy's greatest powers.
But what the Government
did to cover their loss...
...gave the Navy unexpected power.
Listen. You all need to know
the two biggest changes...
...which have occurred in the New World.
First, the Navy Headquarters
led by Sakazuki...
...has become an even more
powerful force for justice.
And second,
the Blackbeard Pirates have advanced.
Blackbeard?
We met them in Mock Town.
They destroyed my hometown once.
The new era they're talking about is crap!
The era where pirates have dreams
will be over, they say?! Huh?!
What's going on?
People's dreams... have no end!!
Isn't that right?!
So you're...
...Blackbeard?!
Oh yeah, I never gave you my name.
Long time no see, Straw Hat!
He was once a long-time member
of the Whitebeard Pirates.
He knows their territory very well
and he conquered it in an instant
after the good old man died.
Using the Tremor-Tremor Fruit power
that he got from the good old man.
The world already counts him among...
..."Red-Haired," Kaido,
and Big Mam,
and considers him as one
of the Four Emperors.
So he took Whitebeard's place successfully.
What a dirty rat!
Yes, he is annoying.
Rumor has it that they are  on
the hunt for Devil Fruit eaters.
They can somehow acquire a Devil Fruit
eater's power after killing them.
They keep looking for
stronger Devil Fruit powers.
Be careful!
They'll get me!
No one wants your Human-Human Fruit power.
What?!
Especially you, Luffy-kun.
There is a lot of bad blood between
you and Blackbeard--Teach.
So take extra care...
Luffy! Are you even listening?!
I thought you were the captain!
You have to know a little
bit of information at least!
Don't worry, Jimbei.
We were listening.
I thought captains normally
don't listen to other people!
Captains are responsible for their
crew's safety, aren't they, Luffy?!
Hey Jimbei, take it easy! I
like taking chances anyway!
It must be hard to work for him.
Yeah...
Luffy-chin!
There you are!
You shouldn't be here. You're
the life of the banquet.
Camie!
I haven't seen Yowahoshi.
Princess-sama said she's
tired and she wanted to rest
so she went to her room.
Hey, Zoro!
Sanji!
I think there is a wild animal
or something in this palace.
You're right.
I feel it, too.
THE HARD SHELL TOWER
I did not know it's such fun
to party with everybody!
Help!
Shhh!
Please stop! Who are you?!
Somebody! Help!
Don't look so resentful, Princess-san!
Don't worry! I'm not gonna
hurt you or make you suffer!
I was content with taking the treasure.
It became a pain to sell those Mermaids
but you're an exception!
I just need you to be
unconscious for a while!
I just got word from my
brother and the others
they've arrived at a port on this island!
Come to the New World with us!
Hey.
Come on! Why don't you laugh?
Nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, nyah, boo!
Hey!
What do you want, Straw Hat?
I'm having fun here so go away!
Nyah, nyah!
Nyah, nyah, nyah! Nyah, nyah, nyah... Nya...
What?
Straw Hat?!
Luffy-sama!
I didn't know he was still around.
It was scary!
You're so lucky, Luffy!
I should have kicked him!
He was the pirate that
we captured in the sea.
I haven't seen him since we
entered the Fish-Man Island.
I forgot about him.
That was close! Thank you again!
Don't mention it!
I can't believe the treasure
thief was still here.
We usually don't even let
a tiny fish into the palace
but the gate was left open in
the confusion of the battles.
Look! That tower on the right
has been sliced clean through.
I assume the thief did it
while we were not here.
No, this guy cut the tower.
When they escaped from the cage,
he cut bars, walls... everything!
Why did you have to tell him
that, you stupid starfish?!
What?! As they say, lying and
stealing are next-door neighbors!
Wait a minute, Minister of the Right-chan!
Chan?
Did you say "treasure thief"?
Yes, he stole all the
treasures in the palace.
What?! He did?!
I have a bad feeling!
Aren't they national treasures?
You're not gonna go after him?
After seeing my people's lives be
saved, treasures mean nothing to me.
No, they're worth something!
What if we get them back?!
You can keep them all.
It would be wonderful if people who
saved the country had them-jamon.
Are you sure?!
You fools! Why did you kick him out?!
Why didn't you just punch
him and tie him up here!
I love it even when you...
Go find him now!
K-King-sama!
Something wrong with Hordy and
the others! Their cuffs came off!
What?!
THE PRISON TOWER
Damn humans! Our grudge against
you will never go away...
Our time to avenge will come again...
Bring Straw Hat here! I'll kill him!
Am I drunk?
I feel pain in my joints!
I got old on purpose.
I'll get back at the Straw Hats-fosun...
We are the ones who will punish humans.
What is going on here?
Is that Hordy and his clan?
Don't think that you can keep me
in jail, you stupid royal family!
Th-These bars are nothing...
Captain Hordy!
What is going on here?!
I knew it! The Energy Steroid
that you guys were taking...
...was the legendary pill that
was kept in the Tamate Box!
Tamate Box?
It was national treasure that had been
passed down for generations-jamon.
10 years ago, somebody stole
the contents of the Tamate Box.
We couldn't find who did it
and by the King's decision,
we closed the case before
it became a scandal.
Come to think of it, that was
when you left the army, Hordy.
That's right! I stole it!
You idiots!
The legendary pill had unclear effects.
One explanation says it
gives you tremendous power.
Another explanation says
it just makes you old.
It is an odd national treasure.
I assumed they guarded the power drug closely
in order to seal off its dangerous effect.
You folk opened the box
that should not be opened
and dreamed a foolish dream
of gaining some power-jamon.
Shut up, Neptune!
Seems like they no longer get their revenge.
Shut up!
We're chosen avengers!
We will kill all humans...
...and you!!
I feel sorry for them now.
I will consider giving them clemency.
Wait, Neptune!
Fukaboshi, you're a dishonor to our race!
The Fish-Man Island will change.
You killed my mother but I will
not hold a grudge against you.
So please. Just shut your mouth!
I don't want the children
on the island to hear you.
Minister of the Left!
Mr. Pekoms and Baron Tamago
arrived at the Candy Factory!
They were sent by Big Mam.
This is not a good time!
Where are our sweets? Grr!
Mama is waiting for them-soir!
We don't have any sweets
to pay them for this month.
Hordy and the others destroyed the factory
and the undamaged sweets have
been sent to the banquet
since everybody wanted the
Straw Hats to have them!
I wonder if we can explain the situation.
She is like a monster who would
destroy a whole country for sweets!
One of the Four Emperors...
Big Mam!
Luffy and the others are caught up trying
to reclaim the treasure of Fish-Man Island.
The crew of Big Mam, one of
the Four Emperors, shows up.
Just as Fish-Man Island faces
destruction yet again...
...at the hands of one of the
overwhelmingly powerful Four Emperors...
...Luffy takes a stand!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"She Loves Sweets! Big Mam
of the Four Emperors!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!