Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set
sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Luffy accepted the Foxy Pirates' dare
and agreed to Davy Back rules.
However, his team lost the first-round
Donut Race, due to Foxy's trickery.
The first person I want is... you!
The ship doctor! Tony Tony Chopper!
All right! Do anything you like with me!
The team must now win the
second-round Groggy Ring
to get Chopper back, but...
--Seem like a good match?
--Yep.
"Round 2! Shoot It into the Groggy Ring"
Our mighty Groggy Ring
combatants have taken the field!
Opposing them...
...is the violent cook who kicked
the interference squads'
butt in Round #1: Sanji!
That's "first-rate cook."
And the pirate hunter with a bounty
of 60 million: Roronoa Zoro!
This is what they called us
out here for? What a laugh!
Right, Big Pan?
Huh?
He can't hear ya.
What's with these guys?
We'll start with a coin toss.
Tails.
--What do you choose?
--Heads, obviously!
Tails.
Field or ball?
Ball.
Our Groggy Monsters have chosen the ball!
The Straw Hat ball man will
enter the other team's mid-circle!
--Which side do you want?
--Doesn't matter.
During the game, there are two
"ball men" with a ball on their heads!
Knock your opponent's ball man into
your opponent's ring and you win!
Just get on with it!
Get in position, ball man!
Hey, now.
I don't care how pushy you are,
I still ain't gonna be the damn ball.
I refuse to wear this stupid thing!
Quit your whining!
--Oh! Looks good on you!
--I won't fall for that, moron!
Zoro! Sanji! It's up to you guys!
Win Chopper back! We can't lose now!
I'm really sorry! We're counting you!
Whoa, a wotan... I've never seen one before!
I guess they're not as large
as pureblooded giants.
Cheer them on all you
want; it's still no use!
Everyone on our team is a Groggy Ring expert!
What do you want, Split-Head?
He said it again...
Oh, Boss!
Now quit doing that, Straw Hat!
I doubt I'll need to
interfere with this game,
so I thought I'd watch too.
Got a problem with that?
Interference is allowed with this game too?!
Imbecile! It's allowed for every game!
It's just, some people will stoop
to anything to help their team win,
while others might insist on a
fair-and-square contest, you know?
So it depends on the situation.
But if you can't even
handle a little interference,
how can you hope to survive
as a seafaring pirate?
It's a question of character.
That's how you justify it?
What's with that team of yours, anyway?!
If you can even call it a team!
Talk all you want! Once the match starts,
you'll see what they can--!
You went too early just now!
Did not! I win!
At everything.
Don't be a smartass!
We're talking about rock-paper-scissors here!
No, you lost!
Just decide on a ball man already!
They haven't even agreed on that yet...
Sanji-kun! That ball looks nice on you!
I'll do it! I'm the ball
man! I'm the worthiest!
It does suit you. You look like a prince.
Of Moronica.
Just start the game!
Hold on! Weapons are against
the rules! Lose the swords!
Huh? Really?
Yes, this is a ball game!
It wouldn't be much of a game
if weapons were allowed!
I'm fine either way, to be honest!
Hey, you gonna be okay?
A master swordsman without swords is...
Is what?
...nothing but a worthless wimp.
Knock it off, you guys!
All right! It's now or never!
The Straw Hats' ball man, Sanji,
has entered the opponent's circle!
--Hey, cook. Hope you get trampled.
--Shut up!
Stomp 'im, Big Pan!
The crowd is all fired up!
Big Pan! Let's run-and-gun 'em!
Huh?
He can't hear ya!
U-Uhh...
C'mon, man...
Pay attention!
It's not that funny, is it?
The Groggy Monsters are as jolly as always!
Let's get this delightful show on the road!
There's no time limit,
and the first team to score wins!
So we win if we knock Jumbo's
head into the other ring...
And we lose if the cook's head
gets knocked into our ring...
Can Team Straw Hat win back
the reindeer they lost in Round 1?!
Crush 'em!
Or will Team Foxy swipe
another crew member?!
They're about to clash in Groggy Ring!
The whistle is about to sound!
Let the game begin!
What will ball man Sanji
do in enemy territory?!
Will he retreat or attack?!
Let's do it!
There goes "Tackle Machine" Pickles!
All right. I'll take care of this myself.
Sling Tackle!
I don't care about you!
I'm only after you!
All we gotta do to win is beat you down!
It's a ball man battle!
Collier...!
Wh-What the...?! His skin's all slimy!
Sanji the cook slips and slides
on Big Pan's outstretched arm!
It's only natural, though...
...for Big Pan is a slippery-skinned
wotan of loach origin!
What the heck are you doing?!
Run-and-gun!
You idiot!
Who are you calling an idiot?!
Punk Pass!
There it is! Big Pan's super-long pass!
Sanji!
Their leader, Hamburg,
makes for the landing point!
With Roronoa Zoro racing by his side!
I'll chop you up if they score a goal!
Shut up! Quit your whining!
Sweeping Tackle!
Pickles enters enemy territory!
Meanwhile, can Hamburg
catch Sanji in the air?!
Yes! And then...!
Gorilla Throw!
I got it! I got it!
Waiting for him now is Pickles!
Get back here! I'll teach you to...!
Roronoa moves to intercept, but...!
Spinning Tackle!
What?!
Ball man Sanji is sent flying skyward, too!
Sanji!
Bringing up the rear is Big Pan!
He rushes for the falling Hamburg!
Punk Receive!
Hamburg catches Sanji above
enemy territory! Incredible!
They're within range of the ring!
Stupid Eyebrows!
Here it comes! The Hamburger Dunk!
Wh-What are you--?!
Zoro! Sanji! Do something!
Is it about to end already?!
Don't need to tell me...!
I ain't gonna... let 'em score!
You ain't gonna score!
I'm still in tip-top shape!
I can't let that damn swordsman snub me...
...by saving...
...my hide!
No goal!
It looks like ball man Sanji isn't going
to pass through the goal so easily!
Mind your own damn business!
You get thrown around too easy, idiot!
A duo as powerful as the
Groggy Monsters has appeared!
We have an epic game on our hands!
This has never happened before!
This is unprecedented!
These behemoths were sent
flying through the air!
The crowd is stunned!
Team Straw Hat is formidable!
I don't need you to give me backup!
It's only 'cause I can't count on you!
--They're amazing!
--They actually threw Pickles!
They sent Hamburg-san flying!
--Who asked for your help?!
--You get tossed around too much!
Oh, no! What are you doing, Hamburg?!
Lose and you'll regret it!
Are you an idiot, Pervert Cook?!
I do things my way, Twirly Eyebrows!
You're nothing--
Just shut up and do what I say!
You're a real idiot for someone so green!
Oh, but Team Straw Hat is acting strangely!
Although the game is still going
with both ball men in bounds,
the two teammates are
arguing instead of playing!
They're funny!
Zoro! Sanji! You idiots!
What are you doing?! Now's your chance!
The other ball man's all alone!
Gang up on him and knock him into the ring!
Huh?
Big Pan goes in for a surprise attack!
Whoa...!
Too Bad Dance!
What are you running for?! He's the ball man!
Yeah, we know! But hang on,
he has blades under his shoes!
Hey, Ref!
What happened to "no weapons allowed"?!
Whoa! Can you be any more blatant?!
If he misses a play, it's out of his hands!
Quit screwing around, Ref!
Hold on, Sanji-kun!
You saw the whole thing!
Why are you sweatin' like a waterfall?!
I-I didn't s-see a th-thing...
Liar!
Hey, hold on! He's the ref, you know!
Yellow card to Sanji of Team Straw Hat!
Say what?!
W-Wait! Wait! Wait!
And there's the yellow warning card!
One more and Sanji the cook
will get a red ejection card!
I'll eject you!
I can't believe he's scummy
enough to attack the referee!
Shut up! I oughta knock you off!
He's a gangster!
We gotta do something about his weapons...
Hold on! You're allowing that now?!
--I just happen to be looking away...
--Look out there, Ref!
That idiot's using an axe now! An axe!
No! Stop! You can't afford to get ejected!
Are you kidding me?! I can't let
'em get away with this insanity!
Don't you see?! They want you to get mad!
--Just let it go!
--I won't!
Pull yourself together!
This is for Chopper's sake!
All right! Then I'll beat him up!
Don't go complicating things!
Sanji-kun! Just beat 'em!
"Pose of Love"
You got it!
You don't make any sense...
All right! Back to the game!
You didn't have to start with that again!
This is gettin' us nowhere!
But we can change our game plan
now that we know they've got weapons!
It's time to take him out!
Stay out of my way! I can handle him myself!
Work together! You're a team, you know!
And there they go!
All three are about to collide!
Can't attack where his skin
is exposed! He's too slippery!
That leaves his hands,
feet, mask, and trunks...
Loach Scooping Slide!
Crap!
Loach Racing Circus!
There it is! The Racing Circus acrobatics!
Both opponents slide across his wide back!
Ha! Won't work this time!
I can handle a little skating!
Now they can't escape!
--So dizzy...!
--Come on, you guys!
Meanwhile, the other two players
have gotten back into the game!
--Oh! They're back in it!
--Slaughter 'em!
Oh? Their attire is a little different now!
Hamburg, their leader, is wearing
iron knuckles and iron elbow guards!
Meanwhile, Pickles has donned
spiked shoulder protectors!
These clearly violate the "no weapons" rule!
Oh, but the referee just happens
to have his back turned right now
as he does some stretches!
Now I'm mad, Leader!
Here goes!
Loach Coaster!
Everything's spinning...!
Let's do it, Leader!
Yeah!
Spinning Tackle!
The recovered players counterattack!
But their target isn't the ball man--
it's the swordsman Roronoa!
They're sniping him with the iron knuckles!
Hamburger Hammer!
Zoro!
The attack isn't over yet! Big Pan
instantly takes an attack stance!
Hamburg prepares to use
his iron elbow guards!
--No way!
--It can't be...
This is truly dangerous! A horrifying combo!
He's almost like...
...an arrow!
Punk Attack!
Zoro!
It connects! Direct hit!
Note that deaths in Groggy Ring are
to be expected and are of no concern.
So... dizzy...
Team Foxy isn't ready to stop its attack yet!
Human...
Cannon!
Ugh... I feel sick...
The spiked shoulder protector draws near!
Sanji! Get out of the way!
Sling Tackle!
They're setting up Sanji the ball man now!
Size Attack: S!
Hamburg sends him flying back!
They're not preparing to score at all!
M!
L!
The Groggy Monsters unleash
a spectacular team attack!
Just terrible...
Zoro!
Sanji!
Looks like Team Straw Hat
isn't getting up from this!
Piece o' cake!
The opponents literally are "groggy"!
All that remains now is to stuff
the ball man into his ring coffin
and this will be two wins in a row!
The undefeated Groggy Monsters
are supremely powerful!
We win again!
Hey, cook...
Lend me a hand for ten seconds...
Sounds like... a reasonable length of time...
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless
sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Hold on! They're clearly using weapons now!
--Hey, Prince Moron!
--Come on, you wimpy swordsman!
--Ugh, I can't stand them!
--Forget it. This is the way men are.
They're funny!
Come on! This is for Chopper!
Pull yourselves together!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Barrage of Red Cards in Groggy Ring!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!