Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for a
fighting event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
Are you interested in that guy?
Who are you?
I'm Rebecca. A gladiator.
This man was a legend.
A legend? This old man?
He was the strongest
gladiator in the history
of the Corrida Colosseum, named Kyros.
The winner of the Block
A battle group emerged:
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates.
Now, the battle of Block B is about to start.
Meanwhile...
Hey.
I'm not blind.
No matter how you disguise yourself,
I can't help recognizing the face of the guy...
...who put a blot on my record!
You!
"The Fateful Reunion!
Bellamy the Hyena!"
SCENE-1
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
You...
...gave the diamond-head pops hell.
I'll be back by morning!
A city of gold? A sky island?!
The era of dreams is over,
you pathetic excuses for pirates!
Your name was...
...Maro.
-Bellamy!
Oh yeah, Bellamy!
Why are you here?!
No particular reason.
THE FORMER CAPTAIN OF THE BELLAMY PIRATES
I'm not a resident of Jaya.
BELLAMY THE HYENA
BOUNTY: 195 MILLION BERRIES
I can be wherever I want.
On top of that,
Doflamingo has been my pirate hero
since I was a kid.
I've no interest in the Flare-Flare Fruit
but I have my own reason to win this thing!
Well, then I'll have to just fight you again!
But I'm not the man I used to be.
Straw Hat.
I visited the Sky Island.
You mean Skypiea?!
I lost my crew but it turned my
view of the world upside down.
You didn't do anything to
the people there, did you?!
Maybe. Maybe not.
Anyway, I'm not holding a grudge
against you anymore.
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's
ship to ride through
the "wild wave" that will come soon or later.
I'm done picking on you.
Hey.
AT A CAFE IN THE NORTHEAST
SCENE-2
CAESAR HANDOVER TEAM
Green Bit?
I don't recommend you to go there.
Are you people researchers or explorers?
Yes, something like that.
You better not go
unless you have a purpose
that's worth risking your life.
That bridge looks very strong though...
Yes, it's made of iron.
But, look at the entrance.
Nobody's crossing it nowadays as you see.
A school of Fighting Fish inhabit
the area around Green Bit.
Before they came,
people used to come and go freely
but that was 200 years ago.
Mister, what's a Fighting Fish?
It's a savage fish with horns.
If you approach them by a ship,
they'll capsize you.
That's why they reinforced the bridge with iron
but it's no use.
No use?! What do you mean?!
Can they even tear down an iron bridge?!
Well, I don't know
the current condition of the bridge.
Only people who crossed it know
but I don't know anyone who came back.
What?!
Hey, Tra-guy!
You have to change the handing-over spot now!
He's right!
Think what it's like to be handed
over at such a place, fool!
You fool!
I'm not gonna change.
We're already here. Stop making a fuss.
More importantly,
I'm worried about the situation of this country.
Their king quit all of a sudden.
How come they are so calm?
We're in unexpected circumstances already.
That's what worries me!
What are you doing, Robin?
What's going on?
CP-0.
What?! "CP"?
The strongest intelligence
organization in the world.
Cipher Pol Aigis Zero!
D-Don't tell me they're related to CP9!
They're the greatest of
all of those organizations!
CP9 was fairly strong!
They are more formidable?!
When they're on the move,
nothing good happens.
Indeed.
SCENE-3
THE FAIRY AND ZORO
I won't let you get away, you thief-fairy!
Where did it go?
Is that it?!
There it is!
This is it!
I caught you!
Give me back my sword!
What?
Oh no!
Ow, ow, ow... This is no good!
I'm so dumb! This human will see me!
I have to run! Otherwise, the human will...
SCENE-4
STRAY KIN'EMON
Where are you, Kanjuro?!
Who are you people?
I'm just an old man passing by!
Don't lie! Isn't that a
topknot under your hat?
N...
No, it's a topknot-shaped hat!
Then, take it off for us!
I can't do it - for a good reason.
You're a samurai - Foxfire Kin'emon,
aren't you?!
I am not!
You must confuse me with someone else!
We saw you in the video from Punk Hazard.
And we figured a samurai like
you will come back here.
That's what samurai do, right?
If so, what are you gonna do?
Let me tell you something.
If you point your gun at a samurai,
you better prepare yourself for the worst!
Whoa, easy!
If you don't want Kanjuro
who you're obviously looking for, to die.
What?! Did you just say Kanjuro?!
Keep your hand away from
the sword, samurai-san.
You know where Kanjuro is, don't you?!
Of course, I do.
But if you don't listen to me,
I will kill both you and Kanjuro.
Now, the competitors of
Block B are entering the ring
one after another!
I gotta hurry! It's gonna start soon!
Oh, I have a good view from here!
How could you do such a
dirty thing, Navy-san?
You people sent in a rat to this competition
to arrest all the wanted pirates, didn't you?
What are you talking about?
You're good at playing dumb!
But I can't just let you go
after getting my dear subordinate beaten.
I guess I'd better silence you, Bartolomeo.
I can't believe how famous I became!
SCENE-5
SANJI IN LOVE
Violet-chan!
Yes?
No, I just wanted to call your name!
Oh my!
Sanji-san.
Yes?
I just wanted to call your name!
I got my sights on the target.
Violet-chan!
"Dear Nami-san and Robin-chan."
"How is the weather there?"
Yee-ha!
I can't believe it! You're very strong!
No no! Anybody can detect a sniper
at 16 meters above the ground!
It was nothing!
How dependable!
"I'm getting hit by a hurricane called love!"
"I'm...
...in love!"
I'm here for you!
SCENE-6
THE SUNNY'S SECURITY TEAM
No, you shouldn't drink it all up!
What?!
Listen! A poison tester's job is
to try the food for a shogunjust a little to see
if there isn't any poison in it!
Understood?!
Yes, sir!
Do it again!
Get me a cup of tea, Choppa'emon.
Yes, sir!
A VASSAL: CHOPPA'EMON
I'll bring it to you right away, sir!
A MAID: O-NAMI
Sir, how are you feeling now?
Ah, it's so comfortable.
I'm feeling great.
Yeah? That's good.
I'm feeling great, too!
Y-You hurt me, Nami-san!
Huh? I thought it was a
sleeping-in-your-lap party!
What kind of party is that?!
Brook.
He's playing shogun.
Playing shogun?
Whenever we leave Momo alone,
he looks very serious and depressed.
Maybe, he's thinking about dirty things.
No, he's not!
He's not gonna share it with us
but maybe he has had some kind
of trauma even at that young age.
What?!
I see. I didn't notice that.
But he tries to act cheerfully like that
because he doesn't want us to worry.
How touching.
Hey, Bone-kichi!
Yes?
Do something to warm the place up.
No way. I only take orders from Luffy-san...
Do it!
All right!
I'm gonna sing a song.
Ah, great!
Soul King!
Don't like it
I don't like it
Doesn't matter how many times we bury him
He's gonna come back
Yeah!
The Vitality Corpse
Come on!
Thank you, everybody!
--Huh?
--What?
I don't like it...
What?!
What's going on?
I thought there are only
four of us on the ship.
So did I... Then what's that noise?!
Creepy!
I'm scared!
O-Nami!
I don't like it... Honestly...
I-I-It's from the men's dormitory.
Oh, I don't like it!
There is somebody in there!
Who is it?
What the hell?!
What, what's going on?!
Chopper!
Bone-kichi!
Go look!
What?!
I think we don't have a choice.
Uh-huh.
Wh-What's going on in here?!
I can't believe this.
You're too weak and this
is like a joke, Navy-san!
Competitors of Block B! Is Capman here?!
And Bartolomeo?!
You're Bartolomeo, aren't you?
Block B's match will start soon!
Okay.
And did you see a competitor named Capman?
I don't think so.
Can I watch it with you, Lucy?
Of course, you can!
Now, the next competitor to enter is...
a latecomer!
He's in Block B, too!
It only took him a year to become infamous
and enter the New World!
An incomparably brutal and crazy rookie!
He roasted some pirates on a skewer
and shared the video!
And he also bombed some innocent civilians!
He ranked No.1 in the "most annoying pirate
who should just go away" competition!
A pirate -
Bartolomeo!
All of you!
Go to hell!