Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set
sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
The first round of the Davy
Back Fight is the Donut Race.
The Straw Hat team managed to
overcome various acts of sabotage...
...but Zoro and Chopper's boat
was knocked out of the race.
Only the Cutie Wagon,
Barrel Tiger, and It's a Raft remain!
The battle is between these three boats now!
"'Silver Fox' Foxy! The
Merciless Interference"
The race is really heating up!
The Long Coral Reef blocks
the course directly ahead!
In the lead is Porche-chan's Cutie Wagon!
The Straw Hats' Barrel Tiger
and It's a Raft desperately pursue!
Wow! They're like Chopper's antlers!
What is this long, protruding coral?
What kind of coral sticks out like that?
Look! It's causing strange-acting currents!
We can't just plunge in recklessly...
Yuck! I can't believe the
race has lasted this long...
Monda! We're counting on you!
But let's not forget there's someone
on land just hoping to interfere:
our boss, "Silver Fox" Foxy!
Just what does he have in store?!
--Get 'em, Boss!
--Yahoo! Just a matter o' time now!
Oh, what's this?! Both Straw Hat
boats have slowed a bit!
--C'mon, Nami! Paddle!
--Not yet!
But they're getting ahead!
I said not yet!
--Same goes for you, Sanji-kun!
--Your wish is my command!
The Cutie Wagon uses this
chance to continue forward
and plunge into the Long Coral Reef!
Let's go, Monda!
Wait! Oh, my! What's happening?!
Monda!
Oh... They came back.
Oh, my! The Cutie Wagon
has been sent backwards!
What in the world happened?!
No! Why?!
See? I knew something
was up with these currents.
Okay! Let's increase speed!
R-Right!
Follow us, Sanji-kun!
Aye-aye, Sir!
Try again, Monda!
This way!
What's this?! Both Straw Hat
boats have sped up!
All three boats are entering the
Long Coral Reef at the same time!
Hmm? The Barrel Tiger and
It's a Raft are staying inside!
Whoa! What the...?!
Ahh! There it is at last!
Devilish interference from you-know-who!
A smoke screen...!
What's that damn idiot doing?!
I can't see in front of us!
Oh, my!
It's too dangerous for the Straw Hat
boats to continue forward one bit!
Operation White Out is a great success!
Let's see you find your way
through this coral maze blind!
Success?
How in the...?!
They got through! With no
trouble at all! How did they do it?!
Just as I thought!
The Straw Hat boats slip through
the forest of coral with ease!
Meanwhile, the Cutie Wagon...
--Oh, no!
--...has been sent back again!
What's going on?!
The boat's moving on its own!
--This is a maze of sea currents.
--Of sea currents?
Yep. The whirlpool up ahead is
causing strange currents in this reef,
full of smaller whirlpools.
So we don't need to see ahead!
The currents will carry us through,
as long as we take the right entrance!
Awesome! That's the power of our navigator!
Hurray!
Way to go, Nami-san!
Curses!
But their joy is short-lived!
Beyond the coral forest is the Long Ring!
Huh?! It's just one "Long" after another!
Usopp! Quit freaking out and fire it!
--Fire what?!
--An Impact!
--I-I told you, we don't have it! Nope!
--Oh? Then what's this?
When did you...?!
Hurry! Before the whirlpool sucks us in!
What's with the smile...?
You've used it before!
You know using it can bust your shoulders...!
--That's okay! I don't mind!
--'Cause it's my shoulder!
--Good luck!
--Hey, now!
Hurry! There's no time!
No wonder you seemed so calm!
You had this in mind from the start...
Well, it's been a nice life...
Treinta Fleurs!
--Okay, Long-nose!
--"Okay," my butt...
Fine!
Oh! The Barrel Tiger and
It's a Raft have sped up together!
More than just that! They're flying!
They're leaping right over Long Cape!
Will they land back in the water?!
No, wait!
Huh? Huh?
Huh, huh, huh? Huh?!
It snapped off...
The It's a Raft crashes
into pieces on Long Cape!
It can't continue the race!
What a shame! The It's a Raft
is now out of the race!
Sorry, Nami-san! Don't worry
about us! Just keep going!
Right!
But the Barrel Tiger takes
a miraculously big lead!
Does this spell defeat for
the indomitable Cutie Wagon?!
We underestimated them a bit!
Hang on tight, Porche-chan!
We're counting on you!
Combine!
Two Fish Engine!
No! They haven't lost yet!
Their fishman muscle and shark fin
combo doubles their engine speed!
They zip through the coral and
turbulent waves to close the gap!
The race is half over!
Meanwhile, the Barrel Tiger
paddles desperately!
Get up, Usopp!
--Where am I?
--Just start paddling!
Your arm is twisted in an odd direction.
What's that?
--It's a course marker.
--It says to go right.
Okay! Right we go!
Like we'd fall for that!
Oh, my! Our boss's Ploy #18,
"Operation Lie to Them," has failed!
Truly formidable! Does this girl
not believe anything?!
Shut up, you!
She's foul-mouthed, too!
The race continues!
Barrel Tiger is still in the lead!
What are these columns of water?!
They also clear the long waves
that reach high into the sky!
Natural phenomenon?!
Granny...
Boss, err, Granny...
Yeah... I think I'm done for...
Our boss unleashes a third nasty trick!
Oh! You on the boat! Please save me!
Unbelievable! She completely
ignores a helpless, sick grandmother!
Is she heartless, or does she
only care about herself?!
Whatever the case,
Navigator Nami has a heart of ice!
Will you shut up already?!
I'd never fall for that crap!
She's foul-mouthed, too!
Look! It's the goal!
The finish is close at hand!
Not so fast!
The Cutie Wagon has caught up!
Who will be the winner of
Round #1's Donut Race?!
Who will be the winner?!
I told you...
Cut it out! You're annoying!
She even sees through "Operation Fake Goal"!
Formidable! Truly formidable!
I have a question for her now!
What does it mean to "believe"?
I don't care!
Oh, it's too late! Her heart's
already closed! She's a heathen!
The real goal is near, though.
--No more Impacts!
--Yeah, I know!
Meanwhile, Porche-chan's team has
tragically stopped at the fake goal!
--What happened to the race?
--Hey! Where is everyone?!
The purity of your heart is dazzling!
But you've been duped!
Pay attention, Porche-chan!
So many idiots!
I'll be too embarrassed to live
if we lose to these guys!
They'll take our crew too! That's even worse!
Oh, no! This goal is a fake!
What?! Who would be so evil?!
Eep!
The Barrel Tiger is finally
approaching Long Bamboo Cape!
The goal is just beyond it!
This is the homestretch!
He's right! There's the goal!
Wait!
But they're catching up to us!
We're no match for their speed!
That's it, Usopp! Can you
knock that bamboo down?!
The bamboo?!
All right!
--Like that?!
--Do more!
Full speed, Capote! Monda!
We have to sink them!
Take this! And this! And this!
Wow! Bingo!
Oh, no! Capote!
They'll pay for this!
Cutie Baton!
What's that? Flower magic?
Flower Shurikens!
Ah, they're throwing stars... Yikes!
Oh, no! We've sprung a leak!
It's okay! We can make it!
The goal's right there!
Let's make a run for it!
Round #1 of the Davy Back Fight,
the Donut Race,
is about to reach a conclusion!
Stay strong, Monda! We
can't let them beat us!
We'll lose if we don't do something!
Stay in line with them!
Right, Boss!
Which one is winning?!
--Made it in time!
--All right! Nami's team is winning!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
You speedy ladies are lovely!
Man, you guys almost won...
Huh? We are winning!
For now! But look!
--Our boss is there!
--So?! What can he do now?!
Our boss is just like you.
He has Devil Fruit powers.
Slow-Slow Beam!
And the winner is the Cutie Wagon!
Our idol, Porche-chan, has won the
first round of the Davy Back Fight!
All right! Way to go!
Oh! Thanks, everyone!
--You're the greatest, Porche-chan!
--It's only natural I won!
Now let's swipe us a crew member!
No one's a match for the Foxy Pirates!
Wha...?
All right! Time for you to
hand over a crew member!
Are you guys hurt?! Are you okay?!
Yes, we're all right.
What happened?
Beats us...
That's what we'd like to know!
Did we end up losing?
You were about to win, but then you
suddenly got slow and they passed you!
There's no need to be mystified!
It was caused by Slowmo Photons!
Hey! What did you do to Nami's team?!
Slowmo Photons...?
They're a type of particle
unlike anything currently known.
Whatever this light touches--
whether it's alive, a liquid, or even a gas--
physically loses a fixed amount of speed
while retaining all other energy.
I don't get it! Are you stupid or something?!
--He snapped at me...
--Oh, no! Boss!
But that sounds too ridiculous...
...to be real?
You surely know that such childish
claims have no merit in these waters!
Everything they touch slows down!
That's the power of Slowmo Photons!
Oh, now that makes sense!
After eating the Slow-Slow Fruit,
I became a "slow person"
capable of producing these
particles from my body!
Observe its power!
Yikes! He slowed a flying cannonball!
Slow-Slow Beam!
The effect lasts approximately 30 seconds.
It'll regain its original speed afterward,
as if nothing had happened.
Can't believe your eyes? This is--!
Boss!
Crap! So that's what happened to us?!
So this is the reason they're
strangely confident about the game.
What a joke of a power...
Do you get it now?! You lost!
Victory in Round #1's Donut Race...
goes to us!
Oh, my! You were so close, too!
That concludes Round #1!
Now for the long-awaited spoils of war!
It's time to call one member
of the opposing crew!
The first person I want is...
you!
The ship doctor! Tony Tony Chopper!
Me?!
Bring him here at once!
Oh, no! Chopper!
What a rare creature!
You're way softer than I imagined!
Oh, Boss! Let me touch him too!
Nauseatingly cute!
He's ours now!
Chopper!
So that creep was after Chopper?
Well, I guess he is the
rarest of rare animals...
He's into cute things?
Or furs, perhaps?
This is no time to chat!
This is serious!
They just took our friend!
Guys...
All right, Dr. Chopper.
You're a member of my crew now.
You need to pledge loyalty to me!
Now put on this mask...
Guys...!
I'm sorry we lost, Chopper...!
Damn!
This is a true rarity!
A talking reindeer! Amazing!
Let's be buddies!
Yo! Comrade!
Guys!
I only set sail so I could be with you guys!
No! I-I don't want this!
Luffy! I only set sail
because you invited me to!
I don't wanna go with these guys...!
No! I'm the Straw Hat Pirates'
ship doctor, Tony Tony Chopper!
I don't want this!
Quit your griping, Chopper!
You're being a poor sport!
Zoro...
You're the one who decided to set sail!
No one else is to blame if
you end up dying somewhere!
Only you are!
We agreed to this game.
Usopp, you, and everyone else did their best!
No one in the pirate world would
sympathize with your tears!
A real man...
...would roll up his sleeves and
watch the rest of the contest quietly!
How can you say that?!
Don't you know how he feels?!
All right! Do anything you like with me!
Chopper...
All right!
--Whoa!
--That swordsman is awesome!
All right! Teach 'em a lesson, Zoro!
Get Chopper back!
--Let's take him next, Boss!
--This reindeer's got guts!
Let's get the second round started.
So moving! I'm moved to tears!
Yeah. There's still two rounds left.
We're gonna take back our precious
emergency food... and then some.
Sanji! We're counting on you!
The exchange is finished
as the Davy Back Fight suddenly
explodes with excitement!
Huh? Wait, Chopper's in the second round.
--But they took him.
--You're right.
That's the real thrill of this game!
We told you!
You can't change your roster!
No replacements allowed!
In other words, only the other
two Straw Hat contestants
can participate in Round #2's Groggy Ring!
Team Foxy already has the advantage!
What?!
You can drop out too, if you want.
No, but you can, loser.
I find it hard to believe
they'll work as a team...
--Say what?!
--Stop that!
I'll now explain the rules of Groggy Ring!
There's a field, and two goals!
Knock the balls into them and you win!
However, the balls are no ordinary balls!
They're people!
Both teams, select someone to be a ball!
Which of you's gonna be the ball?!
Here's your ball mark!
Who made you boss?!
You be the ball, Moss Head!
Oh, there it is! Their entrance song!
It's the undefeated elites of Groggy Ring!
Yes! Defeat is impossible for them!
Crush 'em!
The famous Groggy Monsters
have just taken the field!
At the lead is "Full Dash" Hamburg!
He's followed by "Tackle Machine" Pickles!
Last but not least is Big Pan the wotan:
a half-fishman half-giant!
This is literally a monstrous march!
Now, then!
What is that?!
What is that giant fishman?!
They're putting the ball mark on him!
Let's see you win this!
Seem like a good match?
Yep.
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless
sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
--What are you doing?!
--Huh? Look who's talking!
I'll chop you up if they score a goal!
Shut up! Don't try anything funny!
You get thrown around too easy!
I don't need you to give me backup!
It's only 'cause I can't count on you!
They're funny! They're fighting
even during the match!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Round 2! Shoot It into the Groggy Ring"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!