Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
My axe! Hit Hordy!
The Noah is falling!
Just in time!
The Fish-Man Island...
...is in danger!
"Luffy Loses the Fight?!
Hordy's Long-Awaited Revenge!"
So he's dead finally!
Now, Vander Decken's
power became ineffective
and the Noah will crash
into the Fish-Man Island!
Go to hell, Straw Hats!
And all those people who stand
in the way of our vengeance!
--The Fish-Man Island...
--...Will be no more!
We have to stop the ship somehow!
Straw Hat!
You wanna stop the Noah, don't
you? Then you have to beat me.
Otherwise, you can't save
the Fish-Man Island!
You bastard!
If the Noah crashes into the Fish-Man
Island, it will be the end of everything.
Both the kingdom and the Noah's purpose
that has been protected
for hundreds of years!
Listen, my sons.
That ark - the Noah is not just
a relic from history-jamon.
Hundreds of years ago, a promise
was made to a great man
and that ship has been kept on the
seafloor until the appointed day comes.
The ship has not served
its purpose yet-jamon.
Now, we don't even know
how they made that ship.
The Noah cannot be damaged
until the day comes!
Understood, Father.
We will go and find out why
it moved and take care of it.
I have to save both the kingdom
and the Noah at any cost!
Straw Hat, you have neither
a strategy to stop the Noah
nor a chance to beat me!
What's the matter? If nothing is done,
your friends will have no choice
but to be swallowed by the sea,
along with the Fish-Man Island!
Were you fooling yourself when you said
you'd protect them all, Straw Hat?!
I will stop it!
I'm gonna break it to pieces
before it gets to the island!
You can't do that, Straw Hat!
Even if you could do so,
as I told you, the Noah has
a long history and will serve
a purpose in the future!
Then how can we save the island?!
We don't have time!
That's all I can think of!
Decken could still be alive.
If we can wake him up, maybe we
can change the course of the ship.
What if he's dead? Then what are
we gonna do? We gotta destroy it...
I said "Wait"!
Are you guys splitting? While you're arguing,
look, the Noah is falling towards the island!
Wait, Noah! There are people
who I love on the island!
Decken-sama! If you are alive,
please make it come after me!
Please don't harm the Fish-Man Island!
Drop dead now and watch it from beyond
the grave, as the Ryugu Kingdom falls!
Fish-Man Karate!
Shirahoshi!
Sea Drums!
Brother Mamboshi-sama!
Mamboshi!
It's your turn now!
Fish-Man Karate!
Hordy!
Straw Hat!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
Luffy-sama!
...Jet Pistol!
Damn! I can defend myself
with the Armament Haki
but my Haki is not good enough
for these kind of attacks yet!
I shouldn't be fighting in the water.
In order to beat him, I need...
He wants to fight on the
falling ship, doesn't he?
But what he really wants is...
...the air on its deck!
If I could get in there, I can
beat Hordy with a single blow!
I knew he was going to do it!
Those bubbles are susceptible
to large gashes!
Damn! The air on the deck is gone!
It's so easy to render you humans helpless!
You should realize you're
no better than us Fish-Men!
Not only can you not stop the
Noah but you can't even beat me!
Drop dead, Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Snake Shot!
Screw you!
Do you think I'm stupid enough
to get hit by the same attack twice?
I wonder which comes first - your friends
being shattered to death
along with the island
or your last breath! Can't wait to see!
Oh no! He's gonna break my bubble again!
You dullard!
Luffy-sama!
Shirahoshi!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Listen to me very carefully.
I want you to handle Straw Hat.
Handle Luffy-sama?
I'm going to stop Hordy at any cost!
You have to trust me no matter what
happens and stay close to the Noah!
No matter what happens! Understood?
Yes.
There's no way I can miss now!
Even with my eyes closed!
Oh no!
This is it!
Wh-What happened?
Luffy-sama.
I'm sorry.
Yowahoshi!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama asked me to do this.
Brother-hoshi!
Hordy! What's wrong with you?!
There are so many lives on
that island! How could you?
What's wrong with you?!
You three Princes are the
strongest in the Ryugu Kingdom?!
After all, you are sons
of that stupid Otohime.
She had no pride in being a
Fish-Man and died a dog's death
trying to become friendly with humans.
You three are worthless Princes who
can't even save your own country!
Brother-hoshi!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Even your power is fake,
I admit that I couldn't fight back
because I'm not strong enough.
But there is still hope!
Merman Combat!
Ultramarine!
Don't you get it?!
You can't beat me with
those crappy attacks now!
Why, Hordy?!
What is it that you want
badly enough to sacrifice
so many innocent fellowmen's lives?!
How can you do such a horrible thing?!
Hordy! Ultra...
Shark Slicer!
...Marine!
Go to hell!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
How pathetic, you piss-poor Prince!
This power is a gift from heaven!
Now, it's your turn, you two.
Damn!
You can't beat me with that fake power!
Drop dead already!
Hordy, what's with you?!
You petitioned for vengeance against
the humans to Fish-Men, but now
you're trying to take those fellow
Fish-Men's lives along with the island!
You even abandoned the ones you grew
up with in the Fish-Man District!
Don't you realize what you are doing?!
Or is your hatred for humans so
deep that makes you lose your mind?
What happened to you?
Did humans beat you?!
Did humans kill your loved
ones or someone dear to you?!
What did you go through in the past?!
Answer me, Hordy!
What did humans do to you?!
Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
That bastard!
Yowahoshi! Brother-hoshi
is in trouble! Let's go!
What are you doing?! Hey! Yowahoshi!
Where are you going, Yowahoshi?!
You have to trust me no matter what
happens and stay close to the Noah!
No matter what happens! Understood?
Yowahoshi...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Straw Hat Luffy-san, this is the
Air Tank. We met you a while ago.
Oh, it's you guys.
AIR TANK
We've been listening to what's
been going on out there.
And we see the Noah falling
towards the island.
CONTROL ROOM
We're getting ready as planned.
That's what Brother-hoshi was talking about.
You wanna go to the deck?
Hordy!
--Go after him!
--No, wait, Straw Hat!
Why?!
I'm sure you know it by now.
Hordy has an advantage in the
water since he is a Fish-Man.
--If nothing is done...
--What should we do?
I have an idea!
Hey, where are you going?! Brother-hoshi!
THE MAIN ENTRANCE OF THE FISH-MAN ISLAND
Prince Fukaboshi?
What brought you here, Prince?
Listen, we might need a
large amount of air soon.
Make preparations!
Yes, sir!
It's fine. There is some air on the deck.
Then I can beat him up there.
Aside from Decken,
do you think Hordy would leave the
bubble so you can fight there?
I want you to take this Baby
Transponder Snail just in case.
We need to be well-prepared. Let's go!
Luffy-sama! What should I do about the Noah?
Brother Fukaboshi-sama told me
to stay close to the Noah along
with Luffy-sama, no matter what happens!
So that's what Brother-hoshi...
H-Hey, hello?  How can we get air from you?
We can shoot all the air from the Air Tank.
What is the Air Tank?
It's an air conditioning facility that's
providing air to the Fish-Man Island.
If we make a bubble and shoot it,
maybe we can surround the Noah.
But the bubbles neutralize ascending forces
so it's not going to make the Noah float.
That means we can't stop it from falling.
On top of that, we have to use all the air
we have in order to engulf that giant ship.
In other words, there is only one chance.
If we don't shoot it at the exact moment
that the Noah comes right beside us,
there will be no second chance.
So basically, it's a hit-or-miss situation.
Y-Yes. And I'm afraid you'll
have to take it from there!
Again, I can't emphasize enough that...
Enough with the difficult
stuff and just do it!
I can handle anything
as long as there is air!
All right. We'll do our best!
Luffy-san, please save the island!
Straw Hat! Shirahoshi!
What can they accomplish by
swimming alongside the Noah?
They are only a human and a Mermaid Princess!
Shark Slicer!
Straw Hat!
Screw this!
Armament Hardening!
He's putting up quite a fight!
Hey, Human! Give it up, Human!
It makes me sick to my stomach
just looking at you people!
Even if it shortens my life and even
if it comes at the ultimate price,
I will execute my revenge on you humans!
That bastard!
Don't miss it! You don't
have a second chance!
If you miss it, the
Fish-Man Island will be...
Hey, Straw Hat. Can you hear me?
It's Brother Fukaboshi-sama!
Brother-hoshi, are you okay?!
Barely alive. Anyway, listen carefully.
About Hordy Jones...
I found out who he really is!
As the Noah once again draws near,
Fish-Man Island is in chaos
as the citizens evacuate.
The Straw Hats continue to
believe in Luffy and fight on.
Neptune's army finally
joins the battle, as well.
The battle at the Conchcorde
Plaza is unfolding rapidly,
as a new truth further
shakes up the citizens!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Shocking Fact! The
True Identity of Hordy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!