Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Laboon, I swear that we will come back!
Please be here waiting for us!
Laboon, if you have been waiting
there for the past fifty years,
could you give me just another year or two?
I take pride in being a pirate!
If you are facing the wall,
I want to greet you from the
front, just like I promised!
"A New Crewmate!
The Musician, Humming Brook!"
Hey, skeleton!
Are you done singing?
Sing another song! Just one more!
My crewmates and I poured
our lives into this song.
It is the Rumbar Pirates'
"Great Choral Number."
I listened to this countless
times while wandering
the dark, dark foggy seas
by myself for 50 years.
--Ha! Hi-ho! Hi-hi!
--Heehaw! Heehaw!
When I was all alone on that large ship,
this song was the only thing
that helped me feel alive.
But now that I bear new
determination in my heart,
today I shall seal this Tone Dial.
It's sealed!
Your head really is a storage unit?!
I learned that Laboon is
happily waiting for me!
I have my shadow back!
I'm out of the Devil's Sea!
The voices we recorded on this dial no
longer exist to help me recall the past.
I am supposed to take this song to Laboon!
Every single day was filled with pain.
To be honest, I couldn't see a ray of light.
But you know, Luffy-san...
I-I...
I'm glad to be alive!
I am truly glad to be alive!
Of course you are!
And it's all because of today!
Ah!
May I join your crew?
Yeah, sure.
What?! That was quick!
He joined!
Eh?!
But we're glad to have you!
Hurray for the musician!
The musician died and now
he's nothing but bones!
I've been wanting a musician!
The musician is extremely light!
And that is one of your charms!
It's one of your charms!
Yep! I'm as light as bones!
--I'm as light as bones! I'm as light as bones!
--He's hilarious!
--I get it already!
Our ship is going to grow even livelier.
Why do we always attract such a quirky crowd?
I'm not sure what happened,
but you guys seem happy, Namizo.
Yep! Thank you.
We don't know what the deal is, but...
Cheers!
We're totally lost, but...
45 degree angle!
What the heck?
Laboon...
I will not pull back.
We have always looked
straight ahead in our voyage.
That was the path that
would take us back to you.
As I travel around the world,
you're waiting at the goal!
Isn't that right?
That is why I will not pull back.
I swear that I will go to you.
Please wait for me!
Wait just a little longer...
Huh?
What's the matter, Laboon?
You're in an unusually good mood today.
Let me introduce myself anew!
A wanted poster? You're a wanted man?
I apologize for the late introduction.
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
I have a bounty.
I am known as the Humming Brook.
My bounty is for 33 million Berries.
A long time ago, I was the leader of
a certain kingdom's assault convoy.
After that, I was the acting
captain of the Rumbar Pirates.
I am a musician and a swordsman!
As of today, my life is in the hands
of Captain Straw Hat Luffy!
I will work myself to the bone
to avoid tripping everyone up.
All right! Let's have another drink!
"Two Days Later"
This is wonderful! Thank you,
Franky-san and Usopp-san!
It's cool, really! Don't
think anything of it.
My design won!
I picked the flowers.
Thank you so much, Chopper-san.
Stupid! That doesn't make me
the least bit happy, silly!
This is a truly wonderful grave.
I couldn't possibly put all of those
bones on that cute Lion-chan.
From now on, call her the Thousand Sunny.
Strangely enough, the island on Thriller Bark
came from the West Blue,
which is where we were from.
Perhaps they will find some rest
if they sleep on familiar soil.
Well, Brook, we're gonna head on back.
--See ya!
--Later!
All right.
Oh, you startled me.
Are you sure you should be up?
Yeah. I overslept a bit.
What is that?
My dead sword, Yubashiri.
Please let me lay it to rest here.
Luffy will become the King of the Pirates!
Excuse me...
N-No, it's nothing...
Oh, yes! I've joined your crew.
That right? Your luck really does bite.
Our crew is a handful.
So it would seem! I'll work myself to death!
Ah, but I'm already dead.
All right! Now that Zoro
is up, let's hit the seas!
Time to head out for our next adventure!
Yeah!
Huh? Zoro, did you remove
your bandages again?!
Yeah, they hampered my movement.
They were meant to keep
you from moving! Wait!
You seem awfully anxious to go.
Are you really setting sail?
You guys can have Brook's ship.
I fixed the rudder and sails.
Thank you.
You guys have been such
a big help in so many ways!
I owe you so much!
I couldn't begin to thank you.
I'd love to marry you.
You're a great catch, but unfortunately,
I'm just too cool. It wouldn't work out.
I hate to see you guys go!
Let's party for another two or three days.
Nope! Our next stop is Fishman Island.
I'm dying to get there!
I bet it's full of fascinating people!
I'll get to frolic with beautiful mermaids!
Would it be all right if I asked the
mermaids to show me their panties?
Hey, man! Don't be stupid!
Mermaids don't wear panties.
Mermaids are stinking gorgeous!
The Pirate Empress Hancock
is nothing compared to them!
Mermaid! Mermaid!
--Mermaid! Hurray!
--Doesn't their lower half look like a fish tail?
--Mermaids! Love them!
--How come you know so much about them?
--Mermaid! Mermaid! Oh, baby!
--Oh, we passed through on
our way here three years ago.
--Mermaid! They're wonderful!
--Fishman Island was incredible!
Lola, you went to the New World?
I didn't go there. That's where I was born.
My mama is a pirate.
Oh, yeah!
This is my mama's Vivre Card.
You may have a piece.
It's paper?
Wow, you're lucky! Captain Lola's
mama is an amazing pirate!
Take good care of that!
I'm sure it will come in handy later.
What is a Vivre Card?
Huh? You don't know?
Captain Lola, Vivre Cards are
only available in the New World!
Oh, really?
This isn't your typical sheet of paper.
Water and fire can't hurt it.
If you take your nail clippings to a shop,
they will make a special sheet
of paper that mixes them in.
It is known as the
"Paper of Life," the Vivre Card!
You can tear off a piece and give it
to family and friends who are leaving.
And then?
Just watch. This is the Vivre Card
that my mama gave to me.
Ah, it moved!
No matter where in the world you are,
the pieces will pull toward each other.
So I always know which
direction my mama is in!
Of course, it doesn't
indicate how far away she is.
Wow, that's amazing! Is the New World
filled with things like that?
Isn't it handy? I'll sign
my mama's Vivre Card,
so if you ever run into trouble,
use this to get to her.
When you see her, let her
know that I'm doing well.
Thank you, Lola!
I might have one of those.
That thought just occurred to me as well.
Isn't this identical to the white
paper that Ace gave to you?
That scrap of paper will bring you
and me together again sometime.
So that's what he meant...
This is it! Huh?
It's kinda burnt. And it's smaller now.
Let me see that right quick!
This is definitely a Vivre Card.
I hadn't told you this yet, but it
also reveals the owner's vitality.
Isn't this person dear to you?
Yeah! He's my big brother.
Lola...?
I hate to say this, but his life...
is burning out.
What?!
Hey!
--Take care!
--Hey!
Goodbye, guys!
I will never forget what you've done for us!
The sun! Thank you for
bringing the sun back to us!
Everyone, careful not to get wiped out!
Don't jinx them, jerk!
Lola, thank you for the
Vivre Card! Take care!
Say hi to Mama if you see her!
Let's meet again, Namizo!
We're off!
They're gone, aren't they?
They sure are.
The fog is rolling back in.
We'll set sail tomorrow!
No one knows what happens in the
Florian Triangle's mysterious waters.
Every year, over 100 ships
disappear in the fog.
That is an old mystery that began before
the giant pirate ship, Thriller Bark,
began to lurk in the shadows
of that sea ten years ago.
It just so happens that, once again today,
the dense, white fog is covering the
eerie face of the sea with its white vale.
Luffy!
Are you really sure?
Oh, you mean about Ace's paper?
It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Luffy-san, I don't mind.
We can take a detour.
By now, time is of little
consequence to me and Laboon.
"Live" and "Reunite." Those are my mottos!
Luffy, everyone is cool with taking a detour.
It's cool! It's cool!
Yeah! Let's go see your whale of a brother!
No, it's okay. Honest!
If he is in trouble, I doubt he'd want me
to worry every time this happens.
Ace hates it when people see him look weak.
Even if we went, he'd just yell at me.
When we meet, we will be enemy pirates.
Ace has adventures of his own.
That Vivre Card shrinks when
its owner is in a weakened state.
When he gets better,
it returns to its original size.
Yep! We won't meet until then.
That's why Ace gave this paper to me, right?
Come to think of it, Zoro,
you still haven't done this,
since you were asleep the whole time!
So, I'll take it from the top.
Let's drink to our new crewmate,
the musician, Brook!
Cheers!
Thank you for having me!
Okay! Pull up the sails!
Let's fly with a Coup de Burst!
Yeah!
Coup de Burst!
What is this?!
Blue waters and a shining sun! This is bliss!
There are a bunch of neat things here.
You're... Split-Head!
Who are you calling "Split-Head"?!
I'll put an end to your wisecracks
with my new technique!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Slow-Slow Menace!
'Silver Fox' Foxy Returns!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!