Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that
the prize for a fighting
event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
The first round is a battle royal
where only one can win.
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates won
the match of Block A.
Now, the battle of Block B has begun.
Let the battle...
...begin!
Oh shit! I'm gonna fall!
A school of Little Fighting Fish!
Oh, is this the place to watch the battle?
You're...
How is Garp-san doing?
Straw Hat Luffy-kun!
You know my grandpa?
What?!
I almost got killed by Garp-san once.
And I've made up my mind to carry the grudge
even against his children and grandchildren.
"Big Names Duke It Out!
The Heated Block B Battle!"
Garp was like a real demon
for us pirates back then.
It's been decades now
but my wound hasn't healed.
Hey, is it true?!
No, no, no... I just misheard it! I'm Lucy!
You don't mishear your own name!
I need you to pay for
what your grandfather did to me.
What my grandpa did is none of my business!
So you are Garp's grandson!
No, I'm not!
If you're the real Straw Hat Luffy,
I'm gonna chop you up now!
If I had found out about the existence of
Garp's son Dragon sooner,
you would have never been born.
Hey, what happened?!
Don Chinjao is going crazy!
That's not good!
Hey, wait a minute, old pops!
Take that beard off!
Stop! No! Let go of me! Let go!
You've got to be kidding!
Is he gonna attack again?!
I don't know how much weaker he's become
but his bounty was more than 500 million berries
at his peak!
I'm Lu...
Damn you Don Chinjao! Back off!
He's my enemy!
Cavendish drew his sword!
Is that it?!
One of the greatest swords
in the world - Durandal!
Here it goes! Head-Arms!
Beautiful Sword!
Blue Bird!
It's piercing his skull...
No, it isn't!
They're pushing against each other!
I can't stab him with Durandal!
A skull impervious to a sword!
The power to push back a giant!
They're both beyond human power!
I can't take him down without going all out!
You bastard!
I said "Stop"!
He knocked down Chinjao!
Who is that little bearded guy?!
Oh my...
Wow! It didn't work against him!
Maybe the legend about him is true!
They say he broke up the Ice Continent
with a head-butt!
The Ice Continent?!
It didn't work at all.
I thought I used enough strength.
Oh my...
It seems like you two are quite strong!
But you guys need more training!
Seeing how strong you are...
I'm now sure you're Straw Hat.
What do you want from me?
Leave me alone!
Being born as a grandson of the demon
and stealing other people's popularity -
you really incur everybody's hatred.
Neither of those things are my fault!
I'm Lucy, by the way.
If you keep standing in my way,
I'm gonna kill you, too, young knight!
Wait, wait, old man! That's enough!
If you cause trouble here,
they'll eliminate you!
It's Sai and Boo from the Kano Kingdom!
Let go of me, my dear grandsons!
No! I don't know what's going on
but you got to stop!
I finally found my sworn
enemy - Garp's grandson!
If we get eliminated here,
we can't fulfill the real purpose
that we entered for, grandpa!
Hey, you guys!
What's going on over there?!
We'll have to ask you to leave
if you're fighting outside of the ring!
The guards are coming.
I don't care if I get eliminated here or not!
I'm going to...
Where did he go?!
Old man, the guy with the fake beard
is in Block C so are we!
If you wanna kill him, do it in the match!
I'm not gonna let you get away, Straw Hat!
I'm gonna kill you before the match!
What a mess. What was that all about?
I heard someone said "Straw Hat."
It reminds me of the
pirate - Straw Hat Luffy.
Do you think he entered this competition?
No way!
Boy...
I promised Franky that
I wouldn't let anybody know who I am!
There are about 70 competitors
left in the ring now!
Already half of the competitors are gone!
We are coming to the moment of truth!
Hack, the master of the Fish-Man Karate,
has taken down his 17th opponent!
Hey you stupid Fish-Man!
Why are you participating in
a human competition, freak?!
Say something! Hey, fish!
Poor man.
Huh?!
I can't hear you!
You're like a puppet
who can't speak in words of its own.
Let's "communicate" with our fists at least!
That's a good idea!
I'm gonna smash your annoying fists!
Oh? It got stuck!
4000 Brick Fist!
That was awesome, Hack!
He beat his 18th opponent!
Like my friend and our
species' hope, Jimbei, does,
we can establish friendly relations
with our fists!
Hence, I'm gonna keep fighting!
Cool! Was that the famous Fish-Man Karate?!
And this man is runner-up!
An unknown gladiator who burst
into prominence - Ricky!
He may be the one everyone should
keep an eye on in Block B!
He did it! He cut down his 16th man!
--Hey!
--Huh?
There is a gladiator who
I've never seen before.
What are you saying?!
We're in the middle of a fight!
Look! That's the guy!
He's quite strong. Do you know him?
I've been fighting here as
a gladiator for a long time
but I've never seen him before!
Gladiators of this Colosseum
are trained to fight
with a sword and a shield!
But he just uses a sword!
Like a samurai from the Wano Kingdom!
Let's test his skill!\
Okay!
Too slow!
Now, Ricky beat the same
number of men as Hack!
Did you just see what the gladiator
with a skull on his cape did?
Yeah.
He's that strong but I don't
remember seeing him here before.
Well, I was gonna say...
I think I've seen him before.
A man who fought like that without a shield.
What was his name?
Abdullah!
Take this!
Jeet!
You're showing your back to me!
You cowards!
I can't believe it!
Jeet and Abdullah, a pair of evils,
beat 10 strong men at once!
"Cowards"?
I like the sound of that!
Let's kick that guy's ass next!
Alright!
He went over to Elizabello's
side, huh? Great!
Now, Blue Gilly is attacking
Elizabello II's clan!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow... Damn that bastard!
What the hell are you doing?!
He's just an unarmed, spindly man!
I-It doesn't matter
whether he's unarmed or spindly!
His legs are like iron whips!
Hey guys, come closer!
It's too boring when you're standing back like that!
He's just a guy from the Longfeet Tribe!
Why don't you try to attack his legs, then?!
It's impossible!
We can't approach him!
That movement!
I can't figure out where his
kick is gonna come from!
Damn! I don't care anymore!
That's a hell of a kick!
Blue Gilly kicked some guys' ass again!
I think you can't protect your king
with such weak soldiers.
Looks like he has spirit.
Oh, in the meantime,
Abdullah and Tank are facing each other!
What the...
I-I can't believe it!
They're taking down Tank!
The military captain of
Dressrosa's Self-Defense Army -
Tank Lepant got eliminated!
He fell a prey to the pair of evils -
Abdullah and Jeet!
They keep using dirty tricks!
Captain Tank!
Over a 100 competitors have been eliminated
and there are only 30 some
men left in the ring!
A little more to go.
It doesn't matter how tough
the remaining one will be
as long as we have the King Punch...
Competitors led by Dagama, the tactician,
are protecting Elizabello II,
the king of Prodence Kingdom!
When is he going to throw
the devastating King Punch?!
Who's next?!
Those who wish to bleed, come fight us!
The pair of evils - Abdullah and Jeet
who took down the strong man - Lepant,
are trying to provoke their next victim!
What?!
Bellamy!
Bellamy-sama!
"Atrocious"! "Evil"!
Those are the words only fitting to this man!
Is he the top contender to
beat Elizabello II after all?!
In the meantime,
the Jiaokungdo martial artist - Blue Gilly
and the mysterious gladiator - Ricky,
the two strong men are fighting each other!
That Fish-Man is so tough!
He's been knocking out all of his
opponents with a single blow!
That's so cool!
I'm so excited!
It seems like one of these competitors
is likely to win Block B!
Stop him!
Unbelievable!
How much more does Bartolomeo
want to offend other people?!
Why is nobody kicking his ass?!
In front of this huge audience,
he pulled it out and started peeing!
No one has ever done such a thing
in this Colosseum!
It feels so good!
Somebody, stop him!
Here comes that somebody!
Some of us are taking this
thing seriously, brat!
What?
You'll have to excuse me
for attacking you from behind!
Hey, wait! I'm not even
ready to fight back! Hey...
The hero who came in to punish him is
the Fish-Man warrior - Hack!
4000 Brick...
Do it! Kick his ass, Hack!
...Fist!
He did it!
Just kidding!
What did he do?!
Hack is the one who collapsed!
What's going on?!
What was that?
Wh-What kind of monster are you?!
Bartolomeo!