Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every single thing those guys do is interesting.
Those who have common sense
wouldn't meddle with this island.
Just wait and see, Chimney.
Whether they end up surviving this or dying,
the entire world will be shocked
to learn of this incident...
Something that no one has been able
to do in the past several hundred years.
After this battle,
the name of that straw hat kid will
be known throughout the whole world!
Robin!
He's here!
Luffy...
I've come to get you!
Chief! A guy in a straw hat is shouting
something on the courthouse rooftop!
I think it's Straw Hat Luffy,
the captain of the Straw Hat Pirates!
Don't be ridiculous! When I checked
earlier, Blueno was on the rooftop!
Wasn't he standing watch?! That idiot!
What's he doing at a critical time like this?!
I did quite a bit of fighting, so...
I'm starving!
For a time like this, I packed...
...a meal!
I'm so glad that I had these in my pockets!
This is yummy!
So he is the one? Straw Hat Luffy...
What the hell is going on?
What's Blueno do...
Don't tell me... He couldn't have...
He's a member of CP9.
He's a Six Powers master
with Devil Fruit powers.
Blueno, a superhuman with
a Power Level of over 800...
Okay! My power's back!
...was taken out by a brat like that?!
Ch-Chief! What should we do?!
Lucci... Where's Lucci?
Call in Lucci and the others!
Gather everyone here!
I'll order CP9 to annihilate
Straw Hat Luffy and his crew members!
Y-Yes, sir! Right away!
Tell the Baskervilles, too!
Tell them that if the pirates bring
down the drawbridge by some chance,
I'll cut off all of their heads!
Yes, sir!
Raise your head, Nico Robin.
They finally made it this far.
Hey, this is really crazy.
I now know that you accepted
the Government's terms
to save your friends and got brought in here.
But that agreement was casually
broken by that moron chief earlier.
It's not like someone will be saved just
because you meekly stay captured here.
So the only thing you can do is
accept their help and escape from here.
And yet, you're looking quite gloomy...
...as if you're still running
away from something.
Are you afraid of your friends
dying here or something?
If you turn your eyes away
from them, they can't rescue you.
Hey! Isn't anyone there?!
I'll have you meet Straw Hat.
What?!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Give Us Your Answer, Robin!
The Straw Hats' Outcry!!"
Listen good!
We'll shut Nico Robin away
from Straw Hat immediately!
We're gonna head to the
Gates of Justice right away!
Bring those two!
Ch-Chief!
Just do it! Now!
But...
Franky's butt is inflating!
Ahhh! What the hell is that?!
Oh, hey, Spanda!
I realized that this is it for me,
so I've chosen to explode myself.
What?!
At least I'll get to take some
detestable guys like you with me.
Idiot! Wait, you idiot!
I'll end my life with a big explosion
3 km in diameter. So don't stop me.
Don't do it! Help! Don't take me with you!
Three... Two...
Dammit! I can't die here!
One...
Stop it!
Let's go, Nico Robin!
Coup de Boo!
All right! It broke the chains, too.
Ahh! I'm falling!
Super!
That was close.
Good thing there was a fence.
Hey, you aren't hurt, are you?
If I had another bottle of cola,
I could've also taken us to the
other side using Coup de Vent...
Oh, well. Hey, Straw Hat's there.
Now, respond to him.
Ahh! We were tricked!
Chief! Franky and Nico Robin broke
the chains and went out to the balcony!
You fools! What're you doing?!
Capture them already!
If you let them get away,
I'll have you all hanged!
What?!
Oh, hey, Robin! Good! You're still there!
Luffy...
Capture them again! Don't let
them get away, no matter what!
You small fries! Stay out of my way!
Weapons Left!
Looks like Franky's there, too.
All right! Just wait right there.
It's far, but I'll try shooting myself there.
Gum-Gum...
Wait!
I've told you so many times already!
I won't return to you guys!
Go back! I don't wanna see your faces again!
Why did you come to rescue me?
Why did you come to rescue me?!
This isn't what I want.
When did I ask you guys to rescue me?!
I just want to... die!
This is interesting!
What the heck are they doing?
What're you doing?!
They risked their lives to come
all the way here! And you...
They did it on their own.
What?! Don't be ridic--
You're in my way.
Kaku! Did you do that to vent your rage?!
To vent your rage over eating a weird fruit?
Shut up! I do like its powers!
Oh? Is it just Straw Hat that's our enemy?
Yoyoi! Even if he's alone,
it's admirable that he made it this far.
Oh, yeah. Blueno is down.
What a fool!
I guess being a bar owner for five
years would make one weaker, huh?
Even if he became weaker,
could he be defeated, though?
He's been defeated. Chapapa.
All right! I'm glad that you're here, CP9!
But wait a little longer. The Straw Hats
have just started imploding!
Let's watch it.
This is really interesting!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...!
Ribbit?!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit...
Good job, Yokozuna! Keep it up!
Ribbit.
Ribbit!
--Guilty!
Whoa! "Guilty" juries!
Step aside. We'll pass down
the verdict for that frog's crime.
Ribbit!
Guilty.
Guilty!
Seriously! What the heck are these guys?!
Guilty! Guilty!
Let's go, Chopper!
No, I mean, go, Chopper!
What?! Just me?!
I never thought that someone
like the Chief Justice
would exist on this island in the first place,
since I heard that those taken to Enies
Lobby were already considered guilty,
so they'd just pass through an
empty court without stopping.
That's wrong, pirates.
This is the most authoritative,
fair court in the world.
One is judged fairly in trial.
However...!
That is, except for the fact that the juries
who judge guilty or innocent
are former pirates who're on death row,
and they wish to take you down with them.
Us, go down with death-row convicts?!
Hence, in this town, no one...
...in history...
...has been found not guilty!
Kiwi!
Guys!
--Guilty!
Dammit! They're...
Don't flinch!
If we don't get through here,
we can't bring down the drawbridge!
We left Bro's rescue to Straw Hat!
If we get stuck here,
the Straw Hats can't move forward!
Yokozuna!
To think that you got hit directly
several times with those big iron balls!
You bastards!
Don't bother! We've still got
more than 6,000 soldiers.
Now, surge into the courthouse!
Crush the pirates!
Ribbit...!
Wh-What's going on? Why are the giants...
Frog!
Hey! Tell me what's going on!
Ah... You're with the Straw Hats.
What the heck is going on?!
To think that he's been holding
back this many guards...
Yeah! That frog is something else!
Where the hell are they? They got
lost again. We don't have time for this.
Hm? Oh, yeah...
Basically, so long as I get to the upper floors,
it doesn't matter how, right?
Dragon Twister!
What?! What's going on?!
This area is dangerous, too!
As I thought, you guys are no ordinary people!
To think that you subdued the giants.
What a fearful man you are!
Hm? Er... Well...
Oh, yeah. All of your friends
headed to the rooftop.
--Rooftop?
--You should hurry there, too!
King of snipers. Leave it to me.
Huh?
You wanna die?!
That's right!
Hey, Chief. If we go over there
quickly and eliminate that guy,
wouldn't that end this whole thing?
Well, wait. A captain who came all
this way to rescue his crew member
and yet finds them turning down
his rescue at the very end...
Have you guys seen something
that interesting before?
Robin!
You wanna die?!
Listen to his pathetic shout!
I can only imagine the look on his...
What the heck are you talking about?
Wh-Wh-What?!
H-He's picking his nose!
Listen, Robin.
We've already come this far.
So, we're gonna rescue you anyway.
--Landed.
--Oof!
If you still wanna die after that,
you can die then.
Ow, ow, ow...
Are you okay, Chopper?
Yeah, I'm all right.
But what just happened?
Hmm, I have some idea.
I should've come up here
like this from the start.
Zoro! So it really was you!
We were okay because we
were on the outskirts of it,
but if we had been right in the middle
of your attack, we would've died!
Huh? What happened to you guys?
Hiyaa!
Dash! Boar Stew Shoot!
I'm the first to arrive, without a doubt.
Now, I've kept Robin-chan waiting.
I'm coming to rescue...
Moss!
Moss-head! How come
you got here before me?!
Oh? What took you so long? Did you get lost?
H-H-Hey, where'd you learn that phrase?
Ahh...! Sogeking!
What?! He's flying!
Amazing!
Where's he been all this time?
Is he... gonna land okay?
Whoa... They're gathering one after another.
Yoyoi! In any case...
Sogeking!
...to think that they've
marched into headquarters...
Although they're our enemy, that's admirable!
A-A-A bunch of pirates have made it this far!
I'm begging you, Robin!
You can go ahead and say
you wanna die or whatever,
but say those things... by our side!
He's right, Robin-chan!
Robin! Come back!
Hey, Sogeking. Can you stand up?
Hm...?
Yeah, of course. This kind of wound is nothing.
Don't worry. I'm all right.
Just leave the rest to us!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
You stupid pirates!
You won't be able to put on
a brave front for long!
I have power!
--Don't tell me...
--That's right!
The power that wiped out your hometown
Ohara exactly twenty years ago...
Buster Call!
Don't! Not that!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Robin's Past! The Girl
Who Was Called a Devil!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!