Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Everyone, come here! This is bad!
Huh? What is it, Vivi?
It's Nami-san! She has a terrible fever!
I have a favor to ask of everyone.
I know it's not my place to ask
this as a passenger on your ship,
but my homeland is in a terrible
state now, so I'd like to hurry ahead!
We can't waste even a single minute!
So I want this ship to head for
Alabasta at its fastest speed!
Of course! That's what we promised!
So let's find an island with
a doctor on it right away!
Let's cure Nami-san as quickly as
possible and then go to Alabasta!
That's this ship's fastest speed, right?!
Yeah! We can't go any faster than that!
"A Raid! The Tin Tyrant
and Tin Plate Wapol"
She needs to see a doctor
as quickly as possible...
At this rate, Nami-san will...
Hey!
Do you see a doctor?!
Do you expect him to, you idiot?
Hey, guys. Do you think...
people can stand on the ocean?
Can people stand on the ocean?
C'mon, Zoro! What kind
of question is that?
Then... what's that?!
Huh?
What's what?
Hi. It sure is chilly today.
Yeah! It is chilly today!
Y-yeah! Chilly, chilly!
Today's very chilly!
Really?
Increase buoyancy!
Yes, sir!
What is that?! A watermelon?!
Why are we shaking?!
Hold the rudder! If anything
happens to Nami, I'll gut you all!
Don't tell me this... is a ship?!
Crap! A p-pirate ship!
W-wow!
Just when we're in a hurry...
Did our jumbo underwater raid ship,
the Tin Tyrant, surprise you?!
Vivi-chan! You're in charge here!
Okay!
Hey! What's going on?!
So? What's going on?
The ship's being attacked.
Well, I had figured as much,
from the looks of things.
Are you really pirates? You're strange.
Is it just you four?
I find it hard to believe...
that a pirate group
would only have four people.
What is that guy?!
He even ate the knife!
Just watching hurts!
Well, no matter.
I'll start by asking this...
We want to go to the Drum Kingdom.
Do you happen to have an
Eternal Pose or a Log Pose?
Nope. Never even heard of the place.
Okay, you're done, right?! So leave!
We're in a hurry! We don't
have time to mess with you!
Don't rush life like that.
But if you have neither, then oh well.
For now, I'll take your
treasure and this ship.
What?!
But first, I'm feeling a bit hungry!
What is this guy?!
Don't eat our ship!
Hold it right there!
Wapol-sama is currently eating!
Shut up!
Damn that bastard! Fire!
Should've done that
from the very start...
Oh? We can have at 'em?
No, wait! We can discuss this!
They started it themselves...
The fools! They're in a hurry to die!
Gunfire?!
Karoo! Watch Nami-san!
I'll be right back!
Don't do anything you can't handle!
Reception!
All bark and no bite...
W- Wapol-sama! These guys're--!
Are you still eating it?!
Say, this ship doesn't taste half bad...
Hey, you!
Fool! You're no match for Wapol-sama!
Time to get eaten by the power
of the Munch-Munch Fruit!
Luffy!
W-what is this?!
Oh, hey, Vivi-chan.
Has something happened to Nami-san?
Eh?
What a hard-to-chew person!
Why, you--!
Go flying!
Wapol-sama?
Hey, this is bad!
Wapol-sama was sent flying!
This is terrible!
Wapol-sama is unable to swim!
He will surely perish if we
don't rescue him before he sinks!
This isn't over, you!
We will make you pay for this!
Remember us!
We'll get you for this!
Please, remember us! Please!
W-what was that just now?
They seemed to call him Wapol, but...
Doesn't matter. Don't worry about it.
He's just a moron.
That's the only possible explanation.
Have I seen him somewhere before?
"Several days earlier..."
Captain Smoker! Captain Smoker!
I've just intercepted
an intriguing signal!
What?
What an incredible full temper!
The Ryo-Wazamono sword, Kashu!
Tashigi! Hey! Tashigi!
Only in the Grand Line could
I find a legendary sword so quickly!
Tashigi! Hey!
Are you deaf, you sword freak?!
Y-yes, sir! What is it,
Captain Smoker?! Is coffee--
Just get over here and listen with us!
That's a Black Transponder Snail,
a listening device!
Listen close. We just picked up
this conversation between two men.
Ready, Sergeant Major? Here we go.
Y-yes. Please play it back.
...me, Mr. 0...
...Princess Vivi and the Straw Hat...
Straw Hat? The Straw Hat Pirates!
Yeah, mission complete!
...further orders...
via letter, as usual...
That is all. Good luck...
The rest is undecipherable.
It's a faint signal, but there are
four keywords in their conversation.
Princess Vivi. Straw Hat.
Orders via letter. And Mr. 0.
Mr. 0? Could that be a codename?!
If so, could he be connected to
that suspicious swordsman we caught
in Runess the other day?
With him... Mr. 11?
Yeah.
A criminal organization that
uses numbers for codenames
and sends orders via letter to
get tasks done. Sound about right?
Mr. 0? Criminal organization?
Dunno what you're talking about.
Don't give me your guesswork.
Then what was that letter with
orders that we found in your pocket?
I thought I burned that letter!
T-that was, uhh...
Oh? But there wasn't
anything in your pocket.
Princess Vivi...
That's the name of the princess
of Alabasta, as I recall.
She's currently missing.
Isn't the Alabasta Kingdom
in the middle of coup, too?
Could this mysterious criminal
organization and the Straw Hat Pirates
be involved in the uproar somehow?
Don't know. But this is the only
clue to Straw Hat's whereabouts
that we have right now.
Does that mean we're going to--?
Yeah. Contact HQ and
get an Eternal Pose!
Yes, sir!
Let's pay a visit to Alabasta,
the sand kingdom!
Are you sure she's not just hungry?
If so, she should eat
enough meat for 100 people!
Eating meat makes sickness go away!
Look, you...
Come on! Cheer up! Look! Look!
She isn't laughing... Not one bit...
Won't her fever go down
if we dump water on her?
You idiot!
This isn't good. The sun's about
to set for today, Vivi-chan.
Yes, you're right.
Let's drop anchor somewhere.
We can't navigate at night
without Nami-san's instructions.
Yeah.
Oh! You want my autograph that badly?!
Whew, it's cold...
Almost a full moon...
Brr! Oh, crap, I fell asleep!
You're up early, Usopp!
I can't just sit around doing nothing!
We gotta get out of this
jam as quick as possible!
Yeah. Good point.
Blehhh!
C'mon, Nami! Look!
This is weird. She won't smile!
C'mon, smile, Nami!
What's goin' on, Luffy?
"Meat"
Quit that! You're creepin' me out!
Really? Thanks!
Say, doesn't this area
seem kind of calm and cold?
Yeah, sudden, strange calms...
I guess that's another thing that
happens in the erratic Grand Line.
That's not necessarily so.
It's probably proof
that an island is nearby.
Sanji-san! Could you look
carefully out at the horizon?
Vivi-chan?
A winter island is nearby.
I'm certain of it.
Winter island?
Oww!
Climatically, there are four basic
types of islands in the Grand Line.
Summer islands, spring islands,
autumn islands, winter islands...
And each one generally has
four seasons of its own.
"Summery Summer ----------- Wintery Winter"
"Summer Is. Spring Is. Autumn Is. Winter Is."
In short, when on the Grand Line,
there are at least 16 seasonal levels
you must conquer, from summer island
summer to winter island winter.
Of course, there are many
exceptions and unknown climates.
I get it.
The Grand Line has all these
different islands one after the other,
and that's why the seas between
them have such unstable weather.
That's right. Which is why stable
weather means an island is nearby.
Yeah... I see it!
We found an island!
An island?!
Oh! An island! We found an island!
Hey, Nami! Good for you!
There's an island! You can get better!
There's an island! An island! Island!
Island! Island! Island! Island!
Just go look. I got her covered.
An island!
White! It's so white! It must
be snow! A snow island, huh?!
Hey, Luffy! Just so you know,
we're not here to have an adventure!
We're dropping by to find a doctor!
We're leaving once
we get Nami-san looked at!
Hey! Hey, Luffy!
Snow is so nice and white!
It's no use. He doesn't hear me...
H-h-hold on! Is this a good idea?!
If there's snow, couldn't
there be snow monsters too?!
Besides, we're not even sure
if people live there or not!
Oh, no! My chronic
Can't-Go-to-the-Island disease!
Snow! I love snow! It's white!
Guess I'll get us ready to land.
All this snow! I'm so happy!
This is really somethin'.
What's with those mountains?
Say, Luffy. Aren't you cold,
dressed like that?
It's -10° C right now!
That's when bears get ready to hibernate!
Huh? Oh.
So cold!
Took you long enough!
It's a waterfall of melted snow.
We may be able to stop around here.
So, who's going doctor-hunting?
No, I guess people-hunting comes first...
I'm going!
Me too!
Okay! Have fun!
That's far enough, pirates!
Hey. I found people.
But... they don't seem too friendly...
Attention, pirates! Leave this
place at once! This instant!
We came to find a doctor!
We have a sick person onboard!
We won't fall for that trick,
you filthy pirates!
This is our island!
We won't let any pirates land here!
Raise anchor and leave now!
Or else we'll blow your whole ship up!
They really hate our guts.
And we've just met, too...
Don't talk back!
They're shooting!
You didn't just do that!
Stop, Sanji-san!
Bastard!
Vivi!
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
So even,
if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool,
but I gotta go
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I know I'm a fool,
but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Do everything you can,
and you'll get a little nearer to any horizon
Okay! We're going up that mountain!
To see the witch!
Don't be crazy! That'd be fine
for you, but not for Nami!
We should treat her soon, right?
But look at how steep and high up it is!
We can make it!
I'm counting on you, Captain...
Okay! Let's go! Before Nami dies!
Don't say things that could jinx us!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Island Without Doctors?
Adventure in a Nameless Land!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!