Edited at https://subtitletools.com
So, in short, you're no longer
part of the Straw Hats,
but you still haven't quit being a pirate, huh?
If you're a pirate, then we'll take you.
Merry!!
Let me tell you what I know.
You don't even know how much the
World Government messed up my life!
If you hate the Government that much,
then why are you helping them?!
Because I have a wish I want to come true
even if I have to give up everything.
The life I once gave up on...
The heart that I lost...
The dream I could no longer have...
They picked them all up for me.
I was able to make friends who
would believe in someone like me.
Then, your wish is...
That the six Straw Hats, excluding me,
can leave this island safely!
Are you saying, for that, you don't
care if the weapon is brought back?!
You don't care what happens to the world?!
That's right. I don't!
Of all people,
over the lives of everyone in this world,
she chose the lives of the six of you.
It was for us...
Chopper! Wake up! We have to find everyone!
Chopper! Hey, wake up!
Hey, hey, he's really
seriously injured, you know...
Well, CP9 is coming soon.
Nico Robin, go on ahead
and get on board. Now!
Hey, you two! Hurry up and take her away!
Yes, sir!
A government official, marines...
and Robin-chan...
Now... how should I play it?
I carry a darkness within me
that you guys don't know about.
No matter how you look at it, it looks
as if she's being taking in by the authority.
If she wants to run,
she should be able to bring
down all those guys by herself.
Does she have her own purpose?
Oh, is there a reason that she can't run?
Sorry to keep you waiting, Robin-chan!
Oh, I've been waiting for you, my prince!
Is she doing it on purpose because
she wants me to rescue her after all?
Corgy-san!
CP9 is here!
Hm?
--You bastard! Let me go!
--I said let me go!!
--How many times do I have to tell you?!
--I'm saying you guys're scary!
--Whoa... That's Rob Lucci-san.
How intimidating...
So, they're CP9...
How many times do I have to tell you?!
--You guys're scary!
--Let me go, you bastard!
Let me go!
Hey! Where are you taking me?!
You guys're not gonna get away with this!
Just wait and see! I've got eight
thousand men under me and...
Usopp...!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"The Steam Whistle Forces Friends Apart!
The Sea Train Starts to Run"
Hey! Where are you taking me?!
You guys're not gonna get away with this!
Just wait and see! I've got eight
thousand men under me and...
Usopp...!
Good work on your
long-term mission, sirs and madam!
Lucci-san, here is your coat.
This looks pompous.
Stop it.
Yes, sir. R-Right away!
This isn't a game. Stay focused!
Everyone, get on the train!
Everyone, get on the sea train!
Get ready to leave for Enies Lobby!
I said let me go!
Who the hell are they?
In any case...
"Sorry to cause you trouble until the end"?
Is he trying to cause us trouble
even after he left the group?
A little further to the right! Spray water there!
Run more water!
A little bit longer...
We're okay here! Go help treat the injured!
Okay, got it!
Is there anyone left inside?!
Watch your step over there!
Then, it's not that Robin doesn't like us?!
That's right!
I'm so glad!
What?! He turned into a raccoon dog!
He turned into a raccoon dog!
Hey, he turned into a raccoon dog!
So, Chopper, we have to find
Luffy and the others right away
and go rescue Robin!
Okay! Let's go find them!
Where are they?
I don't know. That's why
we're going to look for them.
All right...! I'll do my best!
Whoa! He turned into a gorilla!
You guys, wait.
I don't care if you go after Nico Robin.
But the sea train for government
personnel will depart at 11 tonight.
Well... this is just my guess,
but it's highly possible
that they'll take that train.
In other words, Nico Robin will, too.
What?
After that train, the sea train will
be suspended for the time being,
since Aqua Laguna is coming soon.
Then... that means...
Yeah...
If you miss that train,
you can't sail out, of course,
which means there's no
means to leave this island.
Oh, no! This is bad! What time is it now?!
--10:30.
--What?! We've only got 30 minutes left!
Hey, can't you do something?
Stop the sea train for a while.
Well... Its destination, Enies Lobby,
is an island off-limits to those
other than Government personnel.
The engine driver is also from the
Government. He won't listen to me.
Oh, no...!
Then... the only way left is
for me to go to the station
and somehow persuade Robin directly...
--Chopper!
--Hm?
I'll tell you the directions in which Luffy
and Zoro flew, so search those areas!
If you find them, tell them to
come to the station immediately.
Okay. Got it.
Hey... guys...!
Ah! Paulie-san! You're okay!
Give this girl and her friend a hand.
What?!
G-Give them a hand, you said, Paulie?!
They're the culprits who
tried to kill Iceberg-san!
We should restrain these two!
Lucci-san and Kaku-san are still missing and...
The assassination culprits
are not the Straw Hats!
They're innocent!
We were tricked by the real culprits,
and so we falsely accused them!
--What...?
--I don't know the true
identity of those masked men,
but the Straw Hats fought against them for us!
As a matter of fact, Iceberg-san and I
are still alive because of them, right?
You don't have to look for Lucci and Kaku.
We may not see them again.
What?! You know what happened to them?!
They're visiting their hometowns.
That can't be!
Why, during an emergency like this?!
Just go find the Straw Hat!
Hey, you, shameless girl!
That again... Hey, stop calling me that!
You're going to the station, right?
I'll show you the way.
Yeah... Thanks...
Paulie-san! Hey!
Is what you just told us true?!
Quit your jabbering and help them already!
Are you trying to hurt Galley-La's name?!
N-No, foreman!
We apologize!
We're sorry!
Tell us what to do! We'll help you guys!
Bring Yagaras out! Open the cage!
Yeah!
Visiting their hometowns, huh?
It's probably not good to
give them all the details.
We don't have to make them
feel the pain we felt, right?
Chopper! I'm counting on you!
Yep! I'll be sure to bring them!
Hello! Guys!
Hello!
Hello! Luffy!
Zoro! Sanji!
Usopp, come back to us.
Everyone, please shout with me!
Okay, got it! Guys! Got that?!
Yeah!
Hello! Luffy!
Zoro!
Sanji!
Usopp, come back to us.
Turn into that canal!
That's a shortcut to the station!
We still have twenty minutes
before the train departs.
Don't go, Robin.
To think that you're sacrificing yourself...
We're never gonna let that happen!
Yagara-chan! Please! Go faster!
The last departure at 11 PM...
...from Blue Station,
Water Seven, to Enies Lobby...
--Ouch!
--Ow!
Stay here quietly.
You bastards! Treat us more nicely, you idiots!
He's right, you idiots!
You damn Government dumbasses!
Hm? Well, that's...
Due to the approaching storm surge,
the departure time has been moved
up and the train will leave soon.
Dammit! It's already leaving?
Our mission is mostly completed, huh?
Restrain yourself from making such a
frivolous comment until we get there.
Idiot.
Pardon me.
If you miss that train,
there's no means to leave this island.
Please! Let me make it in time!
Franky... Are you safe?
Straw Hat!
Roronoa!
Luffy!
Where are you?!
Hello! Where are you?!
Please come out!
Zoro! Sanji!
Usopp, come back to us.
Luffy! They're gonna take Robin away!
Answer me! Where are you?!
I wonder what actions
Luffy and the others took...
Looks like no one will make it here in time.
I repeat. The last train will depart soon.
Dammit! Th-Those bastards!
They're never gonna get away with this!
I got stuck...
It was a tragedy that I slipped.
Dammit!
I got stuck...
Luffy! Zoro!
Sanji! Come out!
Let's go rescue Robin!
Straw Hat!
Roronoa!
Where are you guys?
What about this way?!
Hello!
Straw Hat!
Zoro!
We still can't find them here.
Couldn't they be in one of the backstreets?
If that's the case, the area
might already be flooded.
It'd be dangerous to go
there to look for them, too.
Dammit! Straw Hat! Roronoa!
Lucci-san! Since the waves
are getting quite high,
we're departing a bit early.
--Could it cause you any trou--
--No. Depart.
Coo coo!
Yes, sir. Well, then...
Although I lived on this island for five years...
...I don't even feel like it's hard
to say goodbye to this place.
Hey! Did you just hear a steam whistle?!
Yeah. But it's strange.
It's not the departure time yet.
But there are no public passengers.
It's possible that they'd leave
earlier due to the weather!
Hurry up! We can now see
the station in front of us!
Please stop! Sea train!
Today's last departure
from Blue Station,
Water Seven, to Enies Lobby...
The train's leaving. Be seated.
...is now departing.
I no longer have a reason to live!
Leave me here!
Why do I have to listen to you?
You made me live then when I wanted to die.
That's your crime.
There's no place for me to go or go back to.
So let me stay on this ship.
Oh, I see... Then I guess
we have no choice... Okay.
Luffy!
Don't worry. She isn't a bad person.
It couldn't be...!
Could the Rio Poneglyph be...?!
Which means I, too,
have to guide the text on those
Poneglyphs that I read in the past...
...to the end of the Grand Line... to Raftel...
Robin!
Robin! How are you feeling?
I-It started moving.
Dammit! Those damn officials!
We're here! Thanks, Yagara-chan!
Go down the stairs
through the middle entrance!
Got it!
Robin! Don't go!
Hey, you! Who are you?!
It's dangerous! Stay back!
Robin! Get off the train! We'll fight
for you no matter who we're up against!
Luffy!
Zoro!
Where are you guys?!
I can't get out...!
Wait!
The train...!
Robin!
Robin!!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
What's this letter? No way!
Sanji-kun is on the sea train?!
Then Sanji is with Robin right now?
Yeah. We have to hurry up
and go to Enies Lobby, too.
Where did Luffy and Zoro go?
We can't do anything without those two.
We must find them! We must!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sanji Barges In! Sea Train Battle in the Storm!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!