Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
saa yukou
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
He got over the encircling walls in order to
make it to the scaffold with Jimbei's help
and faced the 3 admirals!
The Whitebeards then made
it to the plaza, too!
An all-out battle between the Navy and
the beards has begun at the Oris Plaza!
Ice Block: Partisan!
Pops, move on!
I'm counting on you!
All you have is courage.
But if you're not strong enough,
you can't save him no
matter how hard you try.
Why don't you just get lost?
He is nothing but a bundle of energy
who just bluffs. Young and clumsy.
But I like fools like him.
If I let you wreak havoc,
this island won't survive!
Then why don't you protect it?
I'm on my way, Ace!
If you wanna go further,
you have to kill me first!
"The Power That Will Shorten One's
Life! Energy Hormone, Redux!"
Garp the hero...
...took part in their protection!
He fought against Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates 20 years ago
and made his name in the world
- he's a legendary Navy soldier!
I heard that it was Garp who fought Roger's
competitor--Shiki the Golden Lion...
...here in Marineford with Sengoku
and imprisoned him in Impel Down!
Don't get tripped up by his name, you fools!
He's just an old soldier!
If you'd lived through that
era, you should know that...
...you should focus on the
enemy in front of you!
Hound Blaze!
You gotta stop destroying the city!
I told you to protect it!
Hurry and execute Ace!
--Get a substitute right away!
--Yes, sir!
Make a path!
A path to rescue Ace!
We still got those pains in the ass here!
I won't let you do it, monster!
I'll show you...
...the power of the New World!
--Now is the chance!
--Get to the scaffold!
How is he?
Not good at all! First aid won't help him!
He needs proper treatment!
Straw boy can't fight anymore!
But...
What's the matter, "Fire Fist?"
Ace...
Gol D. Roger?
You mean Gold Roger? Did
you ask me if I know him?
Don't you realize why there is so much
destruction in the world caused by pirates?
It's all Roger's fault!
His fault?
I heard that right before his execution,
he bullshitted about this
great treasure thing...
...causing the idiot pirates
who believed him to run wild.
He should've never been
born in the first place!
He was just a worthless bastard!
Even after his death, he causes
the pirates to roam the seas!
He's such a nuisance--living or dead!
He was the biggest piece of shit
the world's ever! Remember that!
Huh? What's wrong? What
are you getting mad for?
I mean, who are you, brat?!
What have you done in the city, Ace?
They're making a fuss over some punks
who almost got killed by a kid.
Oh, I thought they were dead.
What did you say?! If you cause trouble,
I'm the one who'll get chewed out!
Are you listening, Ace?!
Honestly! How could he just
leave a kid like this with me?!
You wanna know about Roger?
He was just a great liar and a murderer!
It makes me laugh that they
call him "King of the Pirates!"
--He was more like the King of the Bullshitters!
--That's right!
Roger?
Don't mention the name
that makes me sick, brat!
It's ruining my drink! Go away!
What are you looking at?!
What do you think you're
doing, you little shit!
Look at you! You got beaten pretty badly!
Hey, Ace? I heard that you're
out of control these days.
Old man, you have a grandson, right?
Does he look happy?
Oh, you're talking about Luffy!
He's growing up in fine feather!
--Old man.
--Huh?
Do you think...
...that I deserved to be born?
That's something...
...you'll see as you live.
Carry Straw boy to the ship in a hurry!
I have no choice! We gotta
save Ace boy without him...
Ivan-chan...
You came around!
Could you do me a favor one last time?
We're almost there! We'll be there soon, Ace!
Clear the way!
I'm...
Dammit!
Ace-san, wait for me! I'll
save you with my life!
We're almost there!
We're on our way, Ace!
--Ace, we'll save you at any cost!
--Wait for us, Ace!
Don't give up!
Dammit! My mind is so warped!
It's not the right time for this!
Pops and brother and friends are...
...going down one by one bleeding, but...!
Don't say "one last time!"
It'll bring bad luck!
Please! Can you...
I'm so happy and I can't stop crying!
At this last moment, I'm starting
to think that I wanna live!
I beg you! Ivan-chan!
Are you serious about this?!
--Captain Buggy!
--He's awake!
--He's alive!
--I'm so relieved!
What happened to me?
You got frozen by Aokiji and...
Captain Buggy!
Oh no! It's too late!
Damn! You said that you were
gonna conquer the world!
We really believed in you!
Oh no!
Ouch!
I got it!
Captain Buggy wanted to show us
how to save our frozen mates!
With his frozen body? How great he is!
Let's carry all the other
frozen guys to the water!
Yeah!
Hey, before that...
Ow! Save me first, you fools! I mean...
Please help me, I'm drowning...
Captain Buggy!
You saved our lives how many times now?!
Damn, you're great! We'll follow
you to the end of the world!
You guys! Thank me as much as you want!
Looks like I still have my luck!
By the way, where's Mr. 3?
The last time we saw Brother 3 was
before the encircling walls came up.
That bastard! He made it out of here!
Huh? Is this the wall that
you're talking about?
The Navy tried to round up
the Whitebeards with this!
We're caged birds because of this!
How ridiculous!
Do they really think that they
can stop me with this cheap wall?
Damn you, Navy! Be ready for it!
Don't even think that you
can get away with this!
Amazing! To have such conviction
after just being defrosted!
That's how I am!
But what should I do?!
Get out of my way, magma brat!
Damn!
Pops!
Even you can't win out against
the onslaught of time,
Whitebeard!
That's what I was afraid of the most!
Are you telling me to draw their
sympathy by putting these on?
Pops!
If you have an unguarded moment,
you will lose the fight!
Marco!
You can't look away like that!
Jozu!
Should I be the last voice
you hear before you die?
Pops!
--Hey, Pops is...!
--What?!
Hey! It's too late for you to go out now!
Look, Coby, there's no question!
It's obviously the Navy's victory!
Akainu-san got Whitebeard
and Kizaru-san and Aokiji-san got Marco
and Jozu, 1st and 3rd division commanders!
And Straw Hat can't fight anymore
after getting beaten so bad!
That was the best they can do
against all the forces of the Navy!
I will be much much stronger and...
I'll become a Navy...
...ad...
...admiral someday!
Whoa! Oh, I mean...
I-I-I'm sorry! I got carried away!
It's embarrassing! I wanna crawl in a hole!
After I met you, I became
emboldened a little bit...
Coby!
You wanna fight me, right?
Then, of course you have to
become such a heavy hitter!
After all, it was just a pipe
dream for me to become an admiral!
Even Luffy-san's strength gave out
before he accomplished his goal!
It's impossible for me because all I
do is run despite being a Navy soldier!
It's just impossible!
It's over already! So let's just
sit back and enjoy it from here!
Alright, Coby?
Are you asking me to inject
another shot of Energy Hormone?!
That's insane!
You gotta stop it now! You've
been fighting since Impel Down!
You got poisoned and you were almost killed!
You're pushing it too far already!
Like I said before, Energy Hormone is
nothing more than a temporary treatment!
If you just keep using it, you
will die for sure afterwards!
If I'd be able to do all I could...
I'd be happy to die!
Let me fight, Ivan-chan!
--Pops got beaten!
--Marco! Jozu!
If I can't fight now
and if I can't rescue Ace, I...
I'd rather take my own life afterwards!!
Let me have the strength to fight for now!
I said I can't! If I let you die now,
I'd be too ashamed to face Dragon!
You hardheaded fool!
Where's the other guy?!
What's taking him so long?!
Since it was such short notice, he's
having trouble getting ready...
Hey, hurry up!
Alright, let's go!
A-Ace...
All right!
Do whatever you want!
Hey, what are you doing to Straw Hat?!
S-Straw Hat is...!
N-No way! I thought he received
a mortal wound by getting kicked
in the teeth by Kizaru-san!
H-Hey! Where are you going?!
It's too dangerous!
Coby...
Luffy-san!
Luffy!
Ace!!
Using Ivankov's Energy Hormone,
Luffy works up the last of
his strength and runs forth.
But the Navy forces form a
massive wall in his path.
Among them stands one young
man trying to motivate himself
to achieve the heights
he once swore to reach.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Live Up to a Promise!
Luffy and Coby Collide!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!