Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
I've finally found some...
Some people with such nice memories...
Oh, good morning.
Is something the matter?
Who are you?
What?
"Was It Lost? Stolen? Who Are You?"
I can still eat lots more...
Gimme seconds!
Wh-Where am I?
And who are these people?!
--Hey.
--Yes?!
You know anything about this?
--Huh?
--I'm Sanji.
I'm a cook at the Sea Restaurant Baratie.
I remember going to sleep in
my room yesterday like always,
but then I woke up in this strange
place with you complete strangers.
Do you know why?!
N-N-No...
Huh? What?
You mean you guys didn't save me?
Save?
I'm Luffy.
I left Fusha Village and went sailing,
but then I ran into this gigantic whirlpool...
I remember getting into a
barrel and getting all dizzy...
...and then I suddenly wound up here.
I figured you guys had saved me.
Wh-What's going on here?
I remember having a silly conversation
with Kaya-chan yesterday,
then playing with Pepper and
the gang before hitting the hay...
But I don't remember a thing after that!
And these guys are the same?!
So, do you know anything?
Huh?
Do you have any idea why we're here?
I don't know what's going on,
much less who these guys are...
I'll just have to bluff for now...!
All right. I'll tell you.
It's no surprise you've forgotten
everything up until yesterday.
After all, you were attacked
by a legendary giant whale.
A legendary giant whale?
That's right. I defeated it and saved
you guys after it swallowed you.
Wow! Really?! Thanks!
Just who are you?
I'm glad you asked!
I'm Usopp, leader of a great pirate crew
that rules the seas of the East Blue!
I have the people's undying praise!
"Captain Usopp" is what they call me!
Wow! Captain Usopp!
--You know him?
--No, not at all!
Better watch what you say.
The Usopp Pirates have 8,000 members--
What?! 8,000?!
Incidentally, you're both my
subordinates as of yesterday!
For real?!
You're lying.
--Eep! You could tell?!
--See, you even admit it.
I admitted it! You dirty schemer!
You're a funny guy!
Hey, you! Don't make fun of me!
I'm a proud man!
I have so much pride that people
call me "Usopp the Proud"!
Huh? What's wrong?
Oh, it's just... I feel like I've done this before...
Me too...
What a pain.
Let's just leave it at that for now.
What we need is food. People
can't think on empty stomachs.
Food?!
Yeah, didn't you say you're a cook?
A first-class cook.
If this is a ship, there's gotta be something.
A cook...
Hey, hold on a sec!
Just who are you, anyway?!
Me? I'm the man who's
gonna be King of the Pirates!
Huh?
Whoa. This ship's been through a lot.
Oh! An island!
I wonder where we are!
I have bad news, guys. Our navigator is...
Oh? Who the heck are they?
Are they also your subordinates, Captain Usopp?
Hm?! Y-Yeah, of course!
You guys lost your memories, too?
Oh, I finally understand how a foolish
moth feels as it flies into a lamp...
People can't help but leap into
the brilliant radiance of others!
Hi, pretty ladies! Your names, please?
If you're free, what do you
say to dinner tonight?!
Man, this guy's funny!
He suddenly has a different personality...
Uhh, who are these guys?! And where am I?!
Not to mention...
Isn't that... backwards?
--What the heck is that?
--It's a deer.
Shut up, human! I'm a reindeer!
It talked!
Hey! Let's catch it!
Hey, stop! It's creepy!
Hey, girl! Help me out!
No way! S-Stay away from me!
Oh, boy... Where do I even begin to explain?
All right. Listen, everyone.
We're currently located in...
What did you just say...?
I said we're in the Grand Line.
Have you forgotten that too?
Seriously?!
Hey! What are you so happy for?!
They say the Grand Line is
teeming with monsters and stuff!
You should be freaked out!
Still, it doesn't seem so
different from the regular sea.
Is this really the Grand Line?
Navigator?
Who, me?!
Do you recognize what's on your arm?
What is this?!
It's a Log Pose.
Compasses don't work here,
so islands' magnetic fields
are used for navigation instead.
That's what that tool is for.
It's essential for crossing the Grand Line.
Tell me, Miss. I need to return
to my restaurant in the East Blue.
How can I go about that?
I wouldn't recommend it.
We've been traveling a long time;
heading back alone would be suicide.
We've continually followed
the Log Pose's directions.
And that's led us to this coral-surrounded isle.
This is all too much at once for me to believe!
Why would I be cheerfully
traveling with people like this?!
That's why.
Oh, man! That's a pirate flag!
What?! It's a pirate ship?!
Th-That's right! It's the great
Captain Usopp's pirate ship!
For real?!
Actually, Captain Usopp...
Is it me, or is that skull wearing a straw hat?
Oh!
That just means... this hat is mine!
What are you doing?! Give it back!
Don't touch my straw hat! I'll kick
your butt if you do that again!
What? I thought you lost your memory?!
I remember this! It's my treasure!
Treasure...?
It's a precious treasure a friend
gave me when I was little!
I swore on this hat I'd become
a pirate and gather a crew!
Pirates this, pirates that! What a stupid era!
But at least now I know that
everything you've said is nonsense!
I hate pirates! What I like
are money and tangerines!
There's no way that I'd
be traveling with pirates!
Hey, now. Might wanna watch your tone, girl...
Tangerines? Like those?
Huh?
Those tangerine trees...!
What was that?!
Whoa...! It just grew an arm!
Mystery tangerines?!
Just who are you?!
More important is that tangerine...
This is one of Bellemere-san's tangerines!
I know that much for sure!
What are her tangerines doing on this ship?!
Unfortunately, I don't know
much about that myself.
Why don't you check the
ship's logbook in your room?
Huh?
As I recall, there's a picture
of your Bellemere-san in it.
It's my handwriting...
Bellemere-san...
Bellemere-san!
Look at how many I got!
Some of them are still green!
You know better, Nami!
You have to pay attention!
What? But they were nice and sweet!
You ate some?! They're
merchandise, you know!
It's all right. We can eat these ones ourselves.
Okay! You're a big meanie, Nojiko!
What?!
All right, get to work, you two!
I have to go back...
Something might've happened
to Cocoyashi Village...
So... what exactly is it?
Neato reindeer!
Reindeer!
You idiot! Stay away!
Reindeer...
It's great when thinly sliced,
slowly simmered with vegetables,
and made into a stew...
What?! We can eat it?!
Reindeer steak with berry sauce is also superb.
Steak, it is!
Why, you...!
I ain't no food!
Don't eat him. He's the ship's doctor.
Doctor?
Yes. He's a brilliant doctor
beyond even human compare.
Isn't that right?
Sh-Shut up!
Being praised by humans doesn't
make me happy at all, you jerk!
Oh, you sure seem happy to me!
He's a reindeer who ate the Human Human
Fruit and gained human abilities.
Incidentally, I ate the Flower Flower Fruit
and gained Devil Fruit powers.
And Luffy has eaten a Devil Fruit as well, right?
Yeah! I ate the Gum Gum Fruit!
I'm made of rubber!
Th-Three people with Devil Fruit powers...?!
This ain't normal...
Are you guys pirates?! Real pirates?!
That's right. You are too, you know.
All right! As of today, you're a
member of the Usopp Pirates too!
What?! How come?!
You're taking him seriously?
In any case, along with one other person,
we've been crossing these seas
as a seven-member pirate crew.
One other person?
Why don't you come down, Swordsman?
You guys're making quite a
racket so early in the morning.
You're interrupting my morning nap.
Wh-Who are you?! State your name!
You're supposed to give your name
first when asking someone's name.
--Oh...
--I'm Luffy! Nice to meet you!
I'm Roronoa Zoro.
As in "Pirate Hunter"?
I've never once gone by that name.
I just wound up with it.
You're still a bounty hunter, though.
I only did it when I needed money to survive.
It ain't my goal.
But I take it you're only here 'cause
you were targeting a pirate ship?
Beats me. I got no idea why I'm here.
Are you guys notorious pirates?
You're out to get us after all!
F-Fine, bring it on! I have 8,000
people under my command!
Oh? Then I bet you're worth a lot.
I needed some food money anyway.
I'll be more than happy to take you on!
N-No! That's not what I meant! C-C-Calm down!
Say something, will you?!
He doesn't have a bounty.
Not even a single Berry.
Nothing at all?!
I have to get out of here somehow.
Gold!
This is enough to buy Cocoyashi Village
back and have money left over!
Now how do I haul it out...?
What is that?
What's that?!
Amazing! It can run on the water too!
Huh? She left!
That thing's so neat!
Miss...
I've got no idea what's going on,
but it seems like there's
no point in me staying here.
Huh? He left too. What's the deal?
What the heck's going on around here...?
I haven't the slightest, either.
This is a real conundrum...
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
This is crazy! I'd never team up with pirates!
But this is my handwriting in the logbook...
Oh, and the treasure's mine too!
Wait! Whoa! What kind of scene is this?!
Ahh! Hey! Was it you?!
Give our memories back!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Mysterious Boy with a Horn
and Robin's Deduction!"
You're never gonna be King of the Pirates!!