Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
And what do you want, Zoro?
Zoro and Kin'emon finally
got to see Luffy again
and called the others through the Transponder Snails
and checked how everybody was doing.
We are currently with the King Riku Army,
an anti-Doflamingo coalition in this country.
An army?
--Of Little People.
--Little People?
And all the people here are looking to
take down Doflamingo this very day!
Huh? A soldier?
He is willing to sacrifice his life
to destroy this kingdom!
--Franky, stop the army!
--No way!
This brave, little army...
I can't...
...let them down!
Soldier-san's gonna die.
Franky!
You're free to go all out!
We'll be there as soon as possible!
Thanks!
All right.
Let's go back!
What?!
I thought you were gonna say that!
--What's going on?! The town is...
--It's coming this way!
Doflamingo!
Tra-guy!
Stupid brat!
Hey, Tra-guy! Why are you with Doflamingo...
You've pushed it too far!
Cora-san...
Tra-guy!!
"Two Great Rivals Meet Each Other!
Straw Hat and Heavenly Demon!"
Hey! I heard some explosions and gunshots!
What happened to Tra-guy?!
Can you hear me, Luffy?!
What's happening there?!
Say something, Luffy!
I'm sorry to bother you all.
He is a Warlord and a pirate - Trafalgar Law.
He was behind the false report of
my abdication from the throne this morning.
He was?!
"Withdraws from the Seven Warlords"?
What's going on?
Dressrosa is finished!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty! Why did you resign?!
Please give us a reason, Your Majesty!
He was trying to drag me down.
But don't worry!
I've just gotten rid of him!
Is it what it was all about?!
So he almost messed Dressrosa up!
Now we're safe!
Hey, Mingo!!
How dare you shoot Tra-guy!
Straw Hat.
It's none of your damn business.
Law was originally my subordinate.
Responsibility for dealing with him
falls to me!
Kin, retrieve Tra-guy!
I got it!
Vice Admiral-dono,
Pirate Hunter is in action!
Should we catch him?
Uh-huh, all right.
Hold on a minute!
Hey! Talk to us! What's going on?!
Law-dono's got shot in front of us!
By Doflamingo!
What?!
Did you just hear that?
Pirate Hunter and Foxfire Kin'emon, huh?
I saw a child who looked like
Momonosuke on the ship earlier!
Don't listen to him!
We won't let him take Momo away!
Of course!
He is...
Excuse me.
Old man, you're so strong!
Who are you?
I should not tell you that
for the sake of both of us.
What's this heaviness?!
How can he create this much force?!
Zoro!!
Zoro-dono?!
What happened to Zoro, Kin'emon?!
Zoro-dono has just vanished...
Kin'emon!
I'm coming!
Oh yeah... It's Sea Prism Stone...
Kin'emon-san?! Are you okay?!
Oh no, don't tell me you're dead!
Vice Admiral-dono!
He can launch a sword attack from
a distance? That's dangerous.
Tell the civilians to evacuate
as far as possible from here!
Yes, sir!
I can't believe the blind old
gambler was a Navy admiral!
An admiral?!
He is an admiral?!
I hear you, Kin'emon-san!
Oh, good! You're alive!
Thank you for your help earlier.
You people were nice to me
so it feels like I'm repaying you
for kindness with ingratitude.
Life is full of ironies.
Don't be surprised!
A man who stands by Doflamingo is a...
...N...
...Navy admiral!
What?!
A Navy admiral is there in Dressrosa?!
Maybe, Doflamingo has
the Navy on his side!
That means there are hundreds of enemies!
It's not a matter of the number!
Just one admiral is already a big problem to us!
Oh no!
Law-dono! Law-dono!
Where are they going?!
Are you okay?! Say something!
Let's talk at the palace, Fujitora!
If you cooperate with me,
I'll let you catch those brats.
I will listen to what you have to say,
Heavenly Demon.
Then, I will decide what to do.
I'm not gonna let them get away!
All civilians are evacuated!
Catch Roronoa Zoro!
They know who we are!
It seems like they do!
Let's run for now!
Tra-guy!
This is Kin'emon!
Law-dono has been abducted!
What?!
Hey, Luffy! Look for the exit now!
We're gonna wait for you
by running around here!
Okay! We gotta hurry!
Tra-guy said something after being shot!
I'm sure he's alive!
It's Brook and the others!
What happened now?!
W-W-We...
Sunny! What's wrong?!
There they are!
Damn! They've found us!
We have a problem!
Big Mom's...
...Pirate ship is here!!
Ship! Ship!
What is the ship of one of the Four Emperors
doing here?!
What?!
Its figurehead is singing, isn't it?
Ship! Ship!
Catch them!
You sure?! Big Mom's ship?!
We're gonna die!
What's going on?!
Is Big Mom on board?!
--Luffy! Run with us while talking!
--Okay!
I don't know!
But I see those two that we
met on the Fish-Man Island!
Mama! I see Caesar! Grr!
They have him with them
as we thought-bon!
Let's sink their ship
and recover just Caesar-soir!
Big Mom?! That's what I'm concerned about!
Luffy! You shouldn't have
picked a fight with her!
Seems like they're here for Caesar!
Caesar?!
What do they want from him?!
Everybody wants you, you mad scientist!
Did they come to rescue you, too?!
No!
Please help me!
I don't wanna get caught by Big Mom!
Because I...
...swindled research funds from them!
What?!
W-Well...
Skip the details! They're gonna kill me
once they catch me and confirm
that I've been fooling them!
I don't care if you live or die!
Don't say that! Please!
We can't let anyone take
you anyway so shut up!
Look! Look! Look!
They're gonna shoot at us!
Somebody, take the helm!
Y-Y-Yes, I will!
Damn! Why now?!
We're rolling away from Dressrosa!
Can you shake them off?!
How do I know?!
Just pray!
--Brook! Keep trying!
--Yes, I'll keep trying!
You okay, Sanji?!
But hey, don't bring the Emperor here!
It'll throw the whole country out of control
and mess up the plan of Toy
Soldier and the others!
Come to think of it,
why is Caesar on the Sunny?!
The deal fell apart!
If not, why would Tra-guy
have to go through it?!
Stop!
Law told us to take Caesar
to the next island!
Sanji-kun, I think we shouldn't
go back to Dressrosa!
I know you want to join them
and rescue Tra-guy
and help the Little People's army
win the fight.
I'm not saying this because I'm scared!
Luffy, listen!
There are three things that we and
Doflamingo are scrambling for!
Caesar.
The SMILE factory.
And Momonosuke for whatever reason.
We haven't destroyed the factory yet
so it's still in his control.
But we have the other two with us here!
Tra-guy was sacrificing himself and fighting
to let these two get away from Doflamingo.
Maybe, he also wanted to buy time
for destroying the factory.
He went that far to save these two.
So if we go back and make it easier
for Doflamingo to catch them,
all his efforts will be ruined!
You're right. Okay!
We will take Tra-guy back at any cost!
What was the name of the next island?!
It's Zou.
Sanji!
Nami!
Chopper!
Brook!
Momo!
You go ahead and sail for Zou!
If you say so... Roger that, Captain!
But how about giving us permission!
Permission?
Yes. Permission to...
...launch a counterattack
against Big Mom's ship!
Yeah, you got it.
What?!
No!
I already picked a fight with her!
You're right!
--It's too dangerous!
--Please don't!
All right, guys!
We'll be waiting for you at Zou!
Okay!
Count on us to destroy the factory!
All of you, be safe!
Roger that!
Tra-guy's life...
Rebecca's wish...
He holds the key to all of that!
We're gonna head for the palace!
And...
...beat the hell out of Doflamingo!