Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Realizing the importance of friendship,
Luffy went back to Marineford at
Dark King Rayleigh's suggestion.
And the rest of the Straw Hats got a message
through the news
about Luffy's mysterious behavior.
Luffy doesn't do these kinds of things.
I know there is a catch.
Oh yeah! I got it, Luffy!
I got it now! Okay! Okay!
I see. That's what it is.
I see, Luffy!
I got it, Luffy!
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Honestly! He's not thinking
about how we feel - how selfish!
I see!
Oh, is that what it's all about?
I understand!
See you at Sabaody Archipelago in 2 years!
"Luffy's Training Begins! To the
Place We Promised in 2 Years!"
A FEW DAYS AGO - IN THE CALM BELT
Here he comes.
Jimbei! Thank you for everything!
No, I should be thankful to you!
Although I begged you to set
me free from Impel Down,
I'm ashamed of myself for being still alive.
I'm sorry!
I told you to not say such a thing.
If it weren't for you, Jimbei,
I probably couldn't have
made it to the Navy HQ.
So show your face.
You're right.
There may still be something I
can do for you again in the future.
In any case, see you at the
Fish-Man Island in 2 years!
I'm looking forward to the day when
you and your friends visit us!
Yeah!
Take care!
Luffy, I'm glad that you
got back on your feet.
Your hands, your smile, and all
of your casual gestures make...
...my heart flutter and twinge!
If nothing is done, I could
die from this fluttering!
I feel dizzy...
Are you okay, Hancock?
Don't worry!
We'd like to go to the training spot.
Can you take us there now?
I-I see!
Hey, set sail for Ruskaina!
Yes, Snake Princess-sama!
A DESERT ISLAND NORTH WEST OF
THE MAIDEN ISLAND - RUSKAINA
This island is perfect.
It has 48 seasons a year, so it
changes weekly. It's a harsh island.
Oh, I see.
Luffy!
I'll bring food for you everyday
from the Maiden Island!
What?! Really, Hancock?!
Could you bring that
specialty-gorgon-something?
That was so good!
O-Of course!
Wow, Snake Princess-sama!
I can bring anything you want in any amount!
And that was the 10th time
that you said my name!
I-It means we're engaged now!
No, it doesn't! And why are you backpedaling?
You said that you were married a while ago!
Hancock! I don't want you
to spoil him like that!
While Luffy-kun is training,
women are not allowed to be here!
What?!
What gives you the right to decide
those kinds of things, Rayleigh?!
I'll turn you to stone
depending on your answer!
We can find things to eat in
mountains, forests, rivers and sea!
Not his nose! Stop, Snake Princess!
If you can't live like that,
you should not be a pirate!
It's all for Luffy-kun's benefit!
Did you just say "it's
all for Luffy's benefit"?
Yes.
It's all for Luffy...
Then I'll be patient!
But, Rayleigh, this island
is truly dangerous!
If anything goes wrong...
That's why it's good for his training!
Just pray for him if you feel concern.
Shall we go, Luffy-kun?
Yeah!
--Luffy!
--Good luck!
Yeah!
Luffy, please be safe!
You ought to remember this tree.
Even savage beasts stay away from it.
It's the only safe area on this island.
Hmm, it's kind of funny looking!
Now, we are the only humans on this island.
Look at this vast wilderness!
I heard there was a country
here a long time ago.
But humans have lost the
struggle for survival.
Nature here is relentless
and the land is rough!
I smell a great adventure!
There are a lot of savage
beasts! They're uncountable!
There are about 500 living things here
beyond your capabilities now.
You have to get stronger, or
you can't even sleep at night.
How are you able to know
about them and their number?
This is something that concerns you.
You must obtain this power.
The power called Haki!
Haki?
Oh no! Something is here, old man Rayleigh!
Hey, it's right behind you!
Listen, Luffy-kun.
Haki is a
latent power that everybody has!
It's an elephant! 5 times bigger
than usual! What an elephant!
Presence, fighting spirit, intimidation...
It's no different from the
senses that normal humans have.
However, most of them
don't realize their power
or don't know how to bring
them out, until the very end.
Having no doubt!
That makes you strong!
Watch out!
Second Gear!
Jet Pistol!
Damn... What an elephant!
He's not just strong, but fast!
Watch very carefully!
There are two prominent types of Haki!
Watch out!
Don't worry.
He's trying to hit me with
his nose from the right.
It's the power to feel other's
presence more strongly,
called Observation Haki!
Awesome...
If you enhance this power, you can
tell where your invisible enemy is,
and how many there are, and
what their next move will be.
A left leg kick!
Mantra.
They call it Mantra on
the Sky Island--Skypiea!
Oh, damn!
Next, the Armament Haki.
This power is the same as
wearing invisible armor.
Old man!
I-I've seen it before.
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
If the armor is hard enough, it can
be used as the offensive power.
Ouch! I'm a rubber man
so I shouldn't feel pain!
This is an efficient part of this power.
Other than exploiting their weak
point, this Armament Haki is...
...the only effective countermove
against Devil Fruit eaters.
Logia-type Devil Fruit eaters
seem almost invincible
because of their fluid body
but you can hit them solidly.
Oh, that's why you could touch Kizaru!
And that means I could land a blow
against Smokey of the Navy or Aokiji!
You can transfer this power to your weapon.
Have you ever seen the Kuja's arrow?
Yeah...
It was almost like a steel arrow!
Observation Haki, Armament Haki...
Those are two types of Haki.
However, there are a few rare people
who can use another kind of Haki.
Watch.
That was the power to intimidate your enemy!
Conqueror's Haki!
The people who are the biggest names...
...often have this power.
However, unlike the other two,
you can control the Conqueror's Haki
but you can't train yourself to use it.
That's because it's the
owner's spirit itself.
You can enhance it only
by developing yourself!
Oh, that's what you did at the auction house!
You know what it is.
You have awakened the ability
of Conqueror's Haki already.
Don't do it!!
But don't use it until you become
capable of controlling it fully.
Because you would intimidate
innocent people around, too.
Hm? What's wrong?
Amazing!
A crewmember of the King of the Pirates
can beat these beasts
without even touching them!
Do you respect me a bit now?
Uh-huh!
But I've seen those Haki
powers at various places!
Shanks, grandpa, Eneru, Aisa,
Hancock and the Kuja warriors!
Yes, I bet you have.
But learning
how to use Haki is not easy.
Uh-huh!
Usually, we'd need more time
but you're well qualified.
I'm gonna teach you the basis of
Observation Haki, Armament Haki,
and even Conqueror's Haki in 2 years.
Uh-huh.
Most people would lean towards one
type as their preference dictates.
They find which one they prefer
and strengthen that one.
But if you can enhance each of them,
you can expand what you're capable of.
Uh-huh, I got it.
Now,
as a trainer, I'm not easy, Luffy!
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it!
--Now then, let's...
--Oh, give me a minute!
If I'm correct, he said that
this is the only safe place.
The pirate Straw Hat Luffy
will be on hiatus for a while.
Ace! Luffy!
We gotta set out to sea someday!
Let's get out of this
country and live freely!
Let's become stronger and
become pirates someday!
I'm gonna become a pirate and
defeat others and become infamous!
It'll be the only proof of my life!
I got it! Alright then...!
I'm gonna become...!
Oh yeah!
This one, too!
Everybody...
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Hey, hurry up! Let's begin!
Alright!
Let's do it, old man!
No, you must say "Thank you, Rayleigh-san."
No, Professor Rayleigh... Or Master...?
Thank you, Rayleigh!
Okay, whatever!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else's biorhythm
and pretend they aren't there!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket, and
do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Zoro! Usopp! Sanji! Nami!
Chopper! Robin! Franky! Brook!
And Ace! Sabo!
To take a pledge again...
I'll get stronger!
We are!
Two years after the War of the Best,
the time comes for the Straw Hats to reunite
with the new powers they've
gained through their training!
Their sights set on the last sea
in the Grand Line, the New World,
Luffy and friends set out once more!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Beginning of The New Chapter!
The Straw Hats Reunited!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!