Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
After forming an alliance with Trafalgar Law,
Luffy finally encountered Caesar Clown
aka the Master who rules the island
but was beaten by his mysterious power.
Meanwhile, Law, too, got taken down by
the Navy G-5 base commander - Vergo.
Why did you take them away?
The children are suffering!
What?!
Special Attack!
Fire Bird Star!
You bastard!
Gastanet!
--Brownbeard!
--What happened?!
Gastanet!
"Shaking Up the New World!
Caesar's Horrendous Experiment!"
IN FRONT OF CAESAR'S LABORATORY
Open up!
Dammit! It's as solid as rock!
Hey! Open the shutter!
Give us back Smo-yan and Tashigi-chan!
Those creepy creatures...
They went that way but...
Forget about them! Focus on saving
Smo-yan and Tashigi-chan now!
Open it, Caesar!
What's that?
An airship?!
Now, get off, children!
This is your home!
Don't ever go out on your own!
Master, thank you!
Sheep-san, give me the candy.
Master! I want the candy now!
My head hurts! Master, give me the candy now!
Of course, you can have it soon.
Everyone, go straight
back to the Biscuit Room.
I've left plenty of candy in there for you.
I have to go back to my research room now.
Relax and enjoy the candies in the room!
They are very, very delicious!
Yeah!
Let's go to the room! Show
me the way, Mr. Sheep!
It's this way, kids.
--The Biscuit Room!
--I want the candy now!
You know what to do, don't you?
Once they're all inside,
lock them up securely and
don't ever let them get out.
Yes, sir.
It's scary here!
Hey!
What's the matter, brat...
I mean, princess?
What's wrong?
Why don't you go back to
the room like everyone else
and have that sweet candy?
Huh? What?!
Don't go! Do you wanna go back to the lab?!
Get out of my way!
Usopp!
Master, give me the candy!
That's it. Come back to me, children.
Wait, you all!
You shouldn't go back to him!
Don't you wanna go home?!
1, 2, 3!
No! I wanna get out!
What are you talking about?
It's cold outside and don't you
realize what floor you're on?
Now, go back to the room.
No! Help me, Sis!
Mocha?
Let's go get the candy already!
Good girl! Go back to the room!
The candy is in that room!
Why are you people so scary?
I'm scared! I'm scared!
Sis and the others were very nice to me!
Is it because I'm not a good child?!
Oh yeah!
I'm sorry I didn't listen to you! Bro! Sis!
Help me!
Hey, get away from the door!
Damn! What a pain in the butt!
Help me! Sis!
Sis!!
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST
AND SECOND LABORATORY
Ow, ow, ow...
I'm alive!
There are a whole bunch of cuts
and bruises on Sanji-kun's body
but it's so strong!
I'm alive thanks to his body!
Where are the children?!
Usopp!
Stay with me, Usopp!
You came to save me, Sanji?
I'm Nami!
Hey, don't be so disappointed!
Now, get up!
We have to save the children!
Hey, Usopp!
Do you want milk?
No, just sugar is fine.
You don't have to take care of me.
Anyway,
what's taking Caesar so long?
Just in time.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Vergo!
No problem. I was having coffee and cookies.
That's odd. The cookies are gone.
I didn't serve you any cookies.
Oh yeah, I wasn't having cookies.
When does the experiment start, Caesar?
Soon. Monet, turn the video on.
Right away.
By the way, I wish you had your man
under better control, Vergo!
When I saw Smoker here,
I broke into a cold sweat.
Yeah, well - he was like a wild
dog. He was beyond my control.
But that'll all change after today.
Look at yourself!
Law!
I bet you were quite helpless
against Vergo! Hmm?
The deal I had with you worked in my favor!
In exchange for letting you stay here,
you're going to give my people legs?
That would be nice, of course.
But since you're stronger than me
and I'm the boss of this island,
if you want to stay here, I
need a little bit of insurance.
I wasn't planning on hurting you.
What do you want me to do?
How about this, Trafalgar Law?
I want to entrust my dear
secretary Monet's heart to you!
Is that okay, Monet?
Yes. No problem.
In return,
let me keep your heart!
And that's a deal!
As long as we have each other by the balls,
you can't do anything bad.
And I feel safe.
I knew I shouldn't trust anybody.
It's your own fault!
I bet you learned it the
hard way already but...
...Vergo has your heart.
Hey!
I know it was impossible even for
a man such as yourself to notice
but Monet tactfully transformed
herself and followed you.
Hey, are you alright?! Tra-guy!
I know what you guys are up to.
What a shame, Law.
I thought we became good friends.
You've been saved by your
diligent secretary, huh?
I should've been more careful about Monet.
Seeing as how the "Master" was
so dumb, I didn't care much.
Watch your mouth, young man!
I can't believe it! He took your
heart and you're still alive?!
How stupid can you be, letting him
take advantage of your own ability?!
Where is mine?
It's here!
Smo...
Master.
The video is ready.
Oh yeah?
You're a lucky man!
Alright, put it on.
It's a huge ball!
What is he up to?
Finally!
Something is on the screen!
What is that? Where is it? That looks like...
...a candy! It's a huge candy!
When did they place that
Video Transponder Snail?
VARIOUS PLACES IN THE NEW
WORLD UNDERWORLD BROKERS
Thank you for waiting, brokers.
It's going to start soon. The Smilies...
...that made their way
from the Burning Lands separately...
...will all arrive at this
central part of the Ice Lands very soon.
When they merge into one another
and become one big "Smiley" again,
the experiment will begin.
You see - Smiley is...
...the H2S poison gas bomb itself...
...the same one that killed
everything on the island...
...four years ago!
H2S gas?
Last time,
despite the fact they were
growing weaker by the minute,
those afflicted with the gas
were able to take cover.
That was a problem.
So what I'm going to do is give Smiley,
the weapon from four
years ago, a big "boost."
It will add a new effect to the poison gas
and the weapon of mass destruction
will reach completion.
The new weapon that will make
its debut today is called...
...Shinokuni!
THE ICE LANDS - THE CENTRAL PART
They're coming!
Can we even outrun such monsters?!
Oh, it's coming!
It finally coalesced into
one blob on this side!
First of all, what is that?!
What difference does it make now?! Just run!
Hey, guys! I see a ball!
What's that?!
It looks like... a candy?!
Somebody's there underneath it!
VEGAPUNK'S DRAGON - SMALL SIZE
Master, I see a big, gel-like creature.
I think that's Smiley.
Now we are going to project Master's
video on the fog as planned.
Yes.
Then you all have to get out
of there. It's too dangerous.
Hurry up with the dragon sled...
What?
This is...
We have a problem! The sled is melting!
It's useless now!
How did it happen? Is it some
kind of chemical reaction?
We can't use it!
The dragon escaped!
What's going on?! One thing after another!
Wh-What?!
This is terrible!
That's a bit overdramatic.
You all, just run!
The protective suit won't help!
Take it off and run to the lab now!
What? O-Okay!
Take the suit off?!
The Master is always right!
I'm sure he has a plan! Do as he says!
Let's go!
Hope this works right!
Oh?!
Somebody's image is being
projected in the air this time!
Forget about all that crap! Just run!
Smiley! I missed you!
It's been three years!
Oh yes, Smiley?
This brings back memories!
I have something good for you!
Wait! Wait, Smiley!
You have to wait!
You must obey me! Just as I taught you.
Wait! I said "Wait"!
We have a great deal to talk about!
Do you remember?
That was just...
...four years ago!
A-All right.
Yeah, all right! You can eat now! Oh yes!
He's not listening to you.
Enough!
It's acting funny.
What is that?
That's a big candy!
Good boy, Smiley.
Nobody can stop him now!
Used in the past to convert Punk
Hazard into a land of death,
Caesar's ultimate poison is unleashed.
It swallows person after person as it spreads...
...and closes in on the Straw Hats as the island is transformed into a hellish landscape.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Deadliest Weapon of Mass
Destruction in History! Shinokuni!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!