Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Into the sea!
Usopp?!
We're gonna be saved! She came to rescue us!
We've got one more friend, right?!
Chopper! Did you look below?!
I did!
Cien Fleurs!
Delphinium!
I'm moving! Is Robin doing this?!
Into the sea!
Into the sea...!
Follow Luffy!
Here we go!
Here we go...!
Into the sea!
The pirates are jumping into the sea!
How stupid! There's no way that they
can survive after jumping into this sea.
Let's go back, everyone!
Fire!
Back to the seas of adventure!
Get on the Merry!
Merry!
"Everyone Makes a Great Escape!
The Road to Victory Is for the Pirates"
What're they trying to do?!
There's no way that they'd be
saved after jumping into the sea!
There should be power
holders among them, too!
That's suicidal!
Hey, hold on a sec...
What the heck is that?
It's a ship! From its pirate flag,
it's the Straw Hat Pirates' ship!
How did it sneak in undetected
by all our battleships?
I don't know who you are, but thanks for...
What the heck?
--Oof!
Is something wrong, Sanji-kun?
Hmm... Well, Nami-san...
The rope ladder was definitely dropped,
but there seems to be no one here.
What?!
Yaay!
Merry!
Seriously, learn how to swim, brother!
Now, get on board, power holders!
Robin-chan!
Throw yourself into my arms!
This is the Merry! It's the Merry!
I really love the Merry!
Merry... Merry...
My Merry is alive!
Why... Why are you so...
If... If I was... If I was more...
I can't believe it! This ship
was dropped into the sea!
Who on earth sailed the ship here?
We'll talk about it later!
Give us your instructions!
--That's right.
--Let's get out of here!
Hey! What're you doing, Sanji-kun?!
N-Nami-san!
That was close! I thought I was
gonna be killed by the battleships!
Hey, Robin! You saved me! Thank y...
Just leave the rest to us!
Luffy... and everyone...
Thank you!
Don't worry about it.
Say stupid stuff like that
after we escape from here.
What do you mean "stupid stuff,"
you damn moss head?!
What do you mean, you damn moss head?!
Shut up! If we die here,
it'll all come to nothing!
Apologize to Robin-chan, you bastard!
He's right! Apologize to Robin!
That's enough!
Hm? Hey, Chopper...
You can move now?
What?
Y-You're right! I'm moving!
I can move now! Zoro!
Apologize to Robin already!
Give up yet?
No! No!
Now, guys! We're gonna
hurry up and get outta here!
Yeah!
Hey, hey... Give me a break!
Are you guys letting them get away?!
If they're getting away anyway,
might as well just blow up Nico Robin!
But we have to capture her alive!
Admiral Aokiji asked me to tell you that.
All ships! Prepare to fire cannons!
A-Admiral Aokiji did?!
Okay! Aim at them!
All ships! Prepare to fire cannons!
That was a big lie. I'm not gonna let
them get away. I'm gonna kill them.
Now that it's come to this,
I'm gonna kill them all!
Hey! Hurry up and load the cannonballs!
So Spandam is alive.
They're gonna fire at us!
Catch the wind from starboard and head east!
We can't! We're completely surrounded!
The number of cannons
aiming at us is overwhelming!
It's impossible that they
would all miss this ship.
Fire!
Ahh! They're coming!
Hey, are they firing at each other?
None of the other attacks are hitting us, either!
Where are you all aiming?!
There's something wrong! It's like
the cannons are aiming themselves!
Don't give me a weird excuse!
Keep clear!
We can't! We're gonna collide!
It's coming this way! What the hell is going on?!
What's the matter?! What's going on?!
L-Look over there!
What the hell?!
The Gates of Justice started
closing at some point!
The currents blocked by the
gates are producing whirlpools
and we can't control the rudder!
So that's why our aiming was off the mark!
Don't get swallowed by the currents!
Wh-What the hell is going on?
Put out the fire! Hurry up!
This is it! Everyone, get out of here!
Idiots! Why did you close the gates?
What're you morons doing?!
The lever to open and close the gates is inside
the third column of the Bridge of Hesitation,
so we couldn't have done anything!
Whoa! This is more than I expected!
Sanji! Don't tell me you did something earlier!
Yep.
These guys aren't the kind of enemy we
could escape from with just guts, right?
Bingo!
Th-That's amazing, Sanji!
Are you a genius or what?!
We can't go on rejoicing forever.
The whirlpools are a problem for us, too.
Ahh! That's right!
--We're gonna die!
--Shut up, you guys!
There was no sea that the Merry
couldn't cross with us on board!
Ohhh...
--That's right! We're counting on you, navigator!
--Nami-san! You're so cool!
Just hang on until I can figure out
the trajectory of the whirlpools!
Leave it to us!
One-Sword Style... Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
Dammit! I can't do the Hundred-and-eight
version with just two swords!
You can just take a break, then.
What'd you say, you jerk?!
H-Hey! They're coming again!
Collier Shoot!
Cien Fleurs! Defense!
Here! I'm returning these to you!
Triple... Flame... Stars!
I wonder if Zoro and the others are okay.
I wonder...
--Chopper!
--Hm?
They're fine, so just focus on steering.
O-Okay.
Dammit! Why?! Why can't you bring down
that puny little ship with seven battleships?!
You useless morons!
Hey, they're coming your way, Usopp!
Okay! Leave them to me!
I missed one! Sanji, take care of it!
Basses Côte!
Ahhh! I'm gonna fight, too!
You idiot! You can't move, can you?!
He's right, Luffy. Leave this one to us...
...and take it easy!
Ahhh! I don't care what you guys say--
I'm gonna fight!
I'll give a medal to the one who actually
hits them! So hurry up and hit them!
All ships! Concentrate all
attacks on their back deck!
That's enough, Luffy!
Fire!
Shut up! I'm your captain!
Whoa!
One...
Two...
Three!
Oh, crap! They're bouncing back!
That saved us, captain!
Just as we'd expect from our captain!
Hey! Are you guys demons?!
Victory!
I see it... the road to victory!
Chopper, hard aport at 9 o'clock!
O-Okay!
The pirate ship escaped towards the falls!
Fire! Fire! What're you doing?!
Are you all idiots?! Sink that ship already!
It seems that they caught
the flow of the whirlpools!
They're moving at an incredible speed!
I'm gonna be useful, too!
Go for it, reindeer!
Go! Speed forth with all your might!
Dammit! Dammit! Those bastards!
With the entire military force
of Enies Lobby at our disposal...
With the power of Buster Call,
as strong as an entire country's military...
Why... Why in the hell can't we...
Why...? Why can't we take a single woman...
...from a puny little band of pirates?!
Chief!
If I hadn't recognized
the value of your existence,
it would've been practically worthless!
There's no hope left for you!
So you were so unhappy it'd make you cry?
Help!
Help...
Clutch!
C-Chief!
--Fight! Fight! Fight!
--All right... it's about time.
Franky!
Could you do that thing?!
Got it!
Everyone, be prepared for a shock.
Block their route! The enemy ship
can't get out of the whirlpools!
It'll be rough on the ship... Sorry about that.
Coup de Vent!
Th-The pirate ship is flying!
Is this really happening?!
They've gone outside of the fleet's range!
Don't underestimate what she's been through!
The Merry flew 10,000 meters high in the sky!
Special Attack! Super Smoke Star!
It's a smokescreen!
Those bastards...!
After them! We bow to nobody in speed!
We can't! We're caught in the whirlpools!
It's taking everything
we've got just to stay afloat!
Fire! Fire!
It seems that Straw Hat and
the others were able to escape!
All right! We'll go back, too!
Did everyone get on board okay?!
Yeah! I put the seriously
injured in the passenger cars!
Okay! Those who're outside, hang on
tight so that you won't be thrown off!
The whole thing is over, huh?
Yeah.
I'd heard rumors,
but I never realized that a Buster Call
was such an inhumane thing.
Well, Enies Lobby was eliminated in the end.
Maybe Iceberg-san will take
some measure of relief from that.
Yeah.
Whoa! You guys, don't come in here!
We never would have
made it without your ropes!
We owe you our lives!
Shut up! Get off of me, you pervs!
You're as innocent as ever.
You really are innocent.
You two... Enough is...
Oh, boy! You've got it tough, huh, Paulie?
Oh, my! We'll take good care of you!
P-Please, I beg you... Get out of here.
Go! Puffing Tom!
I-I didn't realize that you were here.
We'll still pursue them, so...
We can't possibly let it end like this.
To maintain our dignity as the Navy--
no, the World Government--
we'll bring down the Straw Hat Pirates
and we'll bring in Nico Robin, a criminal
of utmost importance, without fail!
Therefore, fleet reinforcements
and additional marines are...
Don't bother.
But...!
We used a Buster Call, an attack as
strong as an entire country's military.
When we see the blunder this fleet
made and the current situation
of Enies Lobby, the symbol
of law, it's quite obvious.
On this matter, we've been
completely defeated.
Is the top of this sheep head here okay?
Yep. That's my seat.
There you go. Be careful not to fall.
Yeah. Thanks, monster granny.
Thanks, Merry.
Thanks to you, we were able to escape.
I never thought that you'd come, Merry...
But when I think about it,
you've always protected us.
I'm so glad that you're our friend.
Thanks, Merry!
At any rate...
...you guys sure did pull one
outrageous stunt back there.
To start with, to think that you shot
through the World Government's flag...
Well... it's not a big deal.
All we did was take back a friend
who was taken away from us.
Thanks for helping us save Robin.
Well, to me, it was no big deal.
Anyway...
...this fight...
...is over...
...and we won!
Yeah!
Merry...
Merry!
Merry...!
Your name is the Going Merry!
And you're one of us!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Thank You, Merry!
Snow Falls over the Parting Sea"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!