Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
The Straw Hats have left the Fish-Man Island
and finally reached the New World.
They met a Giant girl named Lily
who ate the Mini-Mini Fruit
and decided to help her save her father
- Panz Fry from the Navy's ship. However,
a mysterious group called the Neo
Navy threw the situation into chaos.
After finally rescuing Panz Fry, Shuzo and
his clan are hot on the Straw Hats' tails!
Rescue mission accomplished!
Yeah!
Now, bring that food here!
I'll make them my heavenly food!
Really?! Thanks, frying pan pops!
Shuzo-san, I found them!
They're hiding behind a reef!
How annoying! All ships, prepare for battle!
Let's blow them up along with the reef!
I-I'm afraid we used up all our
torpedoes in the battle earlier
and we're almost out of bombshells too.
No, we still have a torpedo.
We can use this submersible as a torpedo!
We are the proud soldiers of
the Neo Navy's flying squad!
We trusted in Master Z and
Shuzo-san and got this far!
Shuzo-san! Let us fight with you! Please!!
I'm proud of you guys! I'll
care for you to your deathbed!
Fight to your heart's content
as a Neo Navy soldier!
All torpedoes, go!
"Z's Ambition! Luffy vs. Shuzo!"
--Pops!
--Dad!
What?! What?!
--It's them!
--I can't believe this!
Ch-Charge!
You bastard!
--That's not a torpedo!
--It's a manned ship, isn't it?
Long live the Neo Navy!
What's wrong with them?!
They're launching themselves like torpedoes!
They must be nuts!
Nice to see you again, accursed pirates.
You can't get away!
It's that guy! How did he find us?!
I used this!
A Vivre Card?!
When you were taking off,
I threw it onto the raft!
Ochenta Fleurs!
I won't allow them to die in vain!
He's super crazy!
You damn pirates are the reason
that the New World is corrupted.
So all we want is...
...to exterminate you all!
No! If you move too much, your wound will...
Iron Body!
Dad!
Lily!
No, stop!
You escaped death earlier!
But it's come for you again!
Dad!
I'll fight you!
--Luffy-sa!
--Go, Luffy!
I won't let you hurt that old man!
A rubber man? Oh right.
You're a pirate too and I'll
kill you sooner or later anyway.
Then why don't I kill you first? As you wish!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Finger Pistol!
...Jet Whip!
--Gum-Gum...
--Shave!
...Jet Bazooka!
Moon Walk!
Armament!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
--Yeah!
--He did it!
Iron Body!
Your Haki is not strong enough to beat me!
What?!
--He uses Haki as well, huh?
--This is going to be difficult.
His hands are annoying!
I guess that's all you got!
Third Gear!
Luffy!
You haven't collapsed yet?
How did you like the Haki-wrapped bombshell?
My lovely partner - Beast Cannon Alpacacino!
He's a bazooka that ate a Devil Fruit!
Finger Pistol Five!
Luffy!
I defeated your captain!
Luffy-san!
That bastard!
D-Don't do it!
Dad!
Usopp-sa, could you do me a favor?
Fling me into that guy's body!
What?!
I'll expand myself in his body
and break him into pieces!
Okay, I'll do it!
Ready?
Yeah!
Alright, go!
Luffy-sa! No!
Luffy-sa!
I knew your plan all along! So stupid!
All of you, go to hell!
H-Hey!
Not yet.
What?
It's not over yet!
No way!
You fool!
I... I'm gonna kick your ass and...
...eat that old man's heavenly food!
Luffy-sa, here we go!
Whoa-whoa!
Oh wow!
It's super!
What's this? I got horns on my head!
What happened to you guys? You got smaller!
No, you got bigger, Luffy!
Lily slipped into your
body and expanded herself!
She did?!
That's right, Luffy-sa!
Oh, there you are!
I was wondering where your
voice was coming from!
Giant Luffy! How cool is that?
Yeah! I became a Giant!
How absurd! Even if you get bigger,
you're the same despicable pirate!
Oh, I forgot about you guys!
How could you?!
You bastard!
Don't get carried away!
Giants are too slow - I don't think
you can keep up with my speed!
Second Gear!
--Hey! What's going on?!
--It's a fast, hot wind!
You pirates are worthless!
And your worthlessness is no match for me!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Jet...
Finger Pistol Ten!
...Spear!
Th-That was too much!
I almost died!
Luffy! Lily!
Thanks, Lily!
Don't mention it.
I'm so happy that I could help you!
Thank you, Luffy-sa!
All right! Now I can have
pops' heavenly food!
Uh-huh!
Th-The food is ruined!
You can't complain because you did it.
--Let's go.
--No! Food!
We'll get some food on our way and head
for a volcano somewhere. What do you say?
Sounds good.
All right! Let's go!
What should we do about his raft?
We can't load it on the ship.
--Seems like it's not a problem.
--Oh.
Super!
I think he made something.
The great shipwright - Franky! Thank you!
Don't mention it! Super!
You bastard! You survived?!
How did you find me?!
Like you did to the Straw Hats,
we secretly put this on Panz Fry's body.
It's a method of tracking pirates that
I learned from a teacher long ago.
It's inexcusable for you
to drag us Navy soldiers
in for the purpose of killing all pirates!
We'll take you all to Impel Down.
Impel Down?! No way!
We're not gonna tell you anything no matter
how much you torture us!
If you wanna kill us, just
do it here in the New World!
No, it's up to the law to decide.
That's how the Navy's justice works!
Luffy-sa! Everybody! Thank you!
I'll never forget what you did for us!
Don't make a big deal out of it.
See you! Thank you for the food!
Don't push yourself too
much, you heroic chef!
Yes, thank you! The great doctor - Chopper!
The great doctor? Me?
Compliments like that don't impress me!
Lily! Let's fight together again as Giants!
Uh-huh! You were the strongest
Giant I've ever known!
See you again!
All right, let's go!
Yeah!
What I feared most has happened.
SHUZO WILL BE PLACED IN IMPEL DOWN
I should have made myself clearer to him.
I'm sorry!
Do you think the Navy found
out what we are up to?
Don't worry.
But...
They won't say anything no matter
how horrible the torture.
After all, isn't he a member
of our indomitable Neo Navy?
You're right.
Master Z. We will arrive
at the First Island soon.
Now, it's finally time to
fight! Let's terrify them all!
The last day of the New World is nigh.
We will kill all pirates
with our own bare hands!
As the Straw Hats sail the Maubeugemour Sea,
the first island of the New World appears before them.
As the crew marvels at its bizarre appearance,
they receive an emergency distress call
and then head toward the island.
But that will lead them into a battle larger than any they have ever faced!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Arriving! A Burning Island - Punk Hazard!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!