Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After forming an alliance--
with Trafalgar Law,
Luffy finally encountered Caesar Clown
aka the Master who rules
the island. However...
You shouldn't underestimate me.
You're a Warlord-sama now, aren't you?
You've done so well.
When did you come here?
Vergo!
It's inevitable. This is
Joker's important territory.
I can't just let those who learn
about his identity walk away.
Hey, Tra-guy, who's Joker?
He is a member of the Seven Warlords
authorized by the World Government.
He is Don Quixote Doflamingo.
"Save the Children! The
Master's Evil Hands Close in!"
Doflamingo...
Who is that?
Didn't you see him at the Navy Headquarters?
At the Navy Headquarters?
Oh yeah!
Hey, you, gator guy!
You turned me down and now, you
wanna team up with Whitebeard?
It makes me jealous.
That bird guy!
You better not take him lightly.
He's right.
And they say that Doflamingo
attacked Moria after the War of the Best!
He attacked Moria?
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST AND SECOND
LABORATORY NAMI AND USOPP'S GROUP
Master!
So...
...you're the one who
kidnapped these children?!
Why is he here?
Luffy and the others couldn't meet him?
How could you do such a horrible thing?
Horrible?
Why did you take them away?
The children are suffering!
What?!
Hey, no! Don't, Nami!
You're making them suffer!
Whoa-whoa,
Law said he's a Logia-type Devil Fruit
eater with a 300 million berry bounty!
What did you give to such small children?!
They said they want to go home!
I'm sure their parents are looking for them!
We will get them out of here at any cost!
Where are the children who wanna go home?
Master!
Hey!
--Master!
--Hey, wait!
Don't go! Do you wanna go back to the lab?!
Get out of my way!
Usopp!
Candy...
What?
Master, give me the candy!
That's it. Come back to me, children.
Wait, you all!
You shouldn't go back to him!
Don't you wanna go home?!
Don't touch me!
Cockroach!
Go away, cockroach!
Nami!
--You alright?!
--Y-Yeah.
You brat, don't push your luck!
No, Usopp!
Let go of me!
We have no choice but to stop them by force!
He must be hallucinating!
He called you a "cockroach"!
But...
They're victims!
It's not their fault!
Unchain me!
It's painful!
But we have to do something
before they beat us!
Focus that anger at...
...that jerk!
Take these off!
Unchain me!
--No way!
--They broke the chains?!
Amazing!
You became so powerful!
That bastard!
Candy...
Master...
--Master...
--Give me...
That gas bastard! I'll show him!
This should work against gas!
Special Attack!
Fire Bird Star!
Kids, move aside!
What?!
Did you think I would catch fire and explode?
You knew my powers are gas-based, didn't you?
But it's too bad. I put the fire
out before it even touched me.
Poison gas is not the only
kind of gas, you see.
The air all around us is gas, too!
Which means I can manipulate
the air within a certain area.
--He can manipulate...
--...The air?
If I remove the oxygen, fire can't burn.
And you people can't even breathe!
Master?
Like this!
Usopp!
Black Ball!
Storm Cloud...
Master...
C-Candy...
Candy...
Hurry...
Were you wondering if
Straw Hat didn't meet me?
Well, he did.
Straw Hat and two others.
I made them suffocate!
Hey!
Candy!
--Master! Candy!
--Candy... Candy... Candy...
--Candy! Candy!
--Hurry!
--Master!
--Candy!
Give me it! Give me it!
Children.
I'm only giving it to the good
children who go back to the lab!
Good children only?
That's right!
Yes, yes! I'll be good!
Then just wait a little bit longer, can you?
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
Let's go back! Master!
Okay, okay! Well, before we do...
Kill these devils who took you away
and tried to worsen your pain!
Kill them...
Crush their skulls with that giant pipe!
Uh-huh...
Don't...
I can't think clearly...
Caesar!
--Browncolor?!
--No, Brownbeard!
Straw Hats!
I came to my senses!
I don't remember this one.
Oh yes! You're my dutiful
lackey - Brownbeard!
You bastard! Did you even forget who I was?!
Of course not!
What happened to you?
Your whole body is charred
and you look terrible.
That's because you ordered them to kill me!
I remember now!
You're Brownbeard, aren't you?
Your name is also on our kill list.
He was easy to manipulate because
he was so dumb but he's a pain now.
I don't need him.--
Kill him.
The Cool Brothers, huh?
That's how you got charred.
I trusted you.
Don't be so angry.
You're still alive after getting
attacked by the Cool Brothers.
You're very lucky!
Shut up!
Caesar!
Hey, children, it's dangerous here!
Get on board the Flying Gas Balloon outside.
Let's get away from here!
Wait, everybody! Don't go!
Caesar!
I don't care that you fooled me.
I don't care about myself anymore.
But I want my crew back!
I'm not gonna let them go
through hell like I did!
Idiot! You don't have a crew anymore!
You and all of your crew
became my subordinates!
Stop acting like a captain!
You're just a shitty pirate who
got beaten in the New World!
Hey, Nami! Let's go after the kids!
Okay!
They will keep following me
thinking I'm their savior!
They're too dumb to notice.
They don't know that I kept them
alive because they're my guinea pigs!
You bastard!
Gastanet!
--Brownbeard!
--What happened?!
Gastanet!
PUNK HAZARD - THE MIDDLE LAKE
They're so persistent!
How far is the lab?
The one that was on the other side
made it completely to this side now!
Which means this one is the
last piece of him, doesn't it?
It merged with a smaller one?
It's getting bigger and bigger!
Just keep running to the lab!
Wait for me!
Momonosuke!
--Open it!
--Give us back Captain-chan!
Give us back Smo-yan!
CAESAR CLOWN'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT
It's starting to move!
They're all heading in the same direction.
Where are they going?
CAESAR'S RESEARCH ROOM
I found out the formula of the
drug and I found sedatives.
Now I have to find a way to
rescue-- Luffy and the others.
Easy...--
Wh-Who was that?
Can I have the candy?
Where did the Master go?
Master...
Hey, Master!
Where are you?
This is Caesar. Are you there, Monet?
Yes.
I retrieved the children safely.
Is Smiley's food ready?
Everything you ordered me
to do is prepared, Master.
The Navy soldiers are in
front of the closed shutters.
And we can transfer the Straw Hats anytime.
The Video Transponder Snails
are on standby outside.
So, when Smiley gets there,
we can start broadcasting the fun experiment?
Yes.
Great. Connect me to all the receivers.
Okay.
To all unlawful "brokers" wherever you are.
I'm sorry to contact you on such short notice
but you all are very lucky to see this!
What you're about to witness is the
deployment of a poison gas weapon.
I added a new feature to the
one from four years ago.
It's something those scum from the
Government-- can only dream of creating.
Today, we have uninvited
guests here on our island.
That's why I decided to
perform the experiment.
Invasion, war, domination.--
It has various uses.
If it appeals to you,
let's talk business.
Give us back Captain-chan!
Are you interested in a
weapon of mass destruction?
No.
But...
...I'd lose nothing by
learning about it, right?
An agreement has been made between Law and Caesar.
As that secret comes to light...
...Zoro and gang, fleeing from Smiley, come upon a large object.
It is nothing less than an indication of the beginning of Caesar's fearsome plan!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Shaking Up the New World!
Caesar's Horrendous Experiment!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!