Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Usopp knocked Sugar out
and freed the toys who had
been forced to labor as slaves
but Doflamingo trapped everybody in the country
in the Birdcage.
Think!
You either come to kill me or
side with us Don Quixote Family
and punish the 12 fools who rebel against me.
If you make the wrong decision,
the game will not end.
I'll pay 100 million berries
for each star rating!
100 million berries?!
These are the criminals in Dressrosa!
First, the One-stars...
REBECCA
A CONVICT GLADIATOR OF THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
(KING RIKU'S GRANDDAUGHTER)
NICO ROBIN - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
"DEMON CHILD"
FOXFIRE KIN'EMON - A SAMURAI
FROM THE WANO KINGDOM
VIOLA - THE FORMER PRINCESS OF DRESSROSA
CYBORG FRANKY - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
Next, the Two-stars...
KYROS - THE FORMER ARMY
COMMANDER OF DRESSROSA
PIRATE HUNTER ZORO - A
PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
And as for key figures of each group,
I give them three stars!
SABO - THE CHIEF OF STAFF
OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
STRAW HAT LUFFY - A PIRATE
THE CAPTAIN OF THE STRAW HATS
TRAFALGAR LAW - THE CAPTAIN OF "THE HEART PIRATES"
THE WARLORD(TENTATIVE), "SURGEON OF DEATH"
RIKU DOLDO III - THE FORMER KING OF DRESSROSA
Plus, there is the man who
pissed me off the most today!
It's all his fault that you people have to
play such a bloody game!
The one who kills him will get...
...500 million berries!
"GOD" USOPP - A PIRATE OF THE STRAW HATS
F... Five...
Soldier-san?! He turned back
to a human, too, didn't he?!
Tell me, Lucy, what kind of a man is he?!
What kind of a man?!
What are you talking about?!
That one-legged soldier was...
...your father!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
I will always be by your side!
I thought so...
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
So stay with my friends!
I'm gonna bring an end to
this stupid game in no time!
So survive! Okay?!
Uh-huh!
"Breaking through Enemy Lines!
Luffy and Zoro Launch the Counter-Attack!"
Luffy, who are you with now?
I'm with Zoro and Tra-guy. And...
Riku Doldo III, and I'm Viola.
--What?!
--King Riku-sama!
Viola-sama's there, too?!
Okay, so there are five of you.
On my side, we have...
What?!
What's wrong, Robin?
Anyway, I'm going to move there
with Usopp and Rebecca.
Do you know what you're doing,
Straw Hat-ya?
Our plan was to destroy the SMILE factory
and provoke a conflict between
Doflamingo and Kaido.
But if we kill Doflamingo now,
Kaido will direct all his anger over losing SMILEs,
...at us!
Then we'll have to fight face-to-face
with the angry Emperor!
That's not an issue now.
Take a good look at this country!
If I stop now, what's gonna happen to it?!
Look for the criminals!
Catching them is the only
way for us to survive!
--Did you find one?!
--No, I didn't see any of them!
When you find the criminals,
tell everyone immediately!
Somebody, stop me!
That was close! Don't let your guard down!
I can't control my body!
Poor people...
Keep walking!
Issho-san, don't we need
to capture Doflamingo?
Restrain as many out-of-control
people as possible
and focus on Straw Hat and
Law's pirate alliance!
What?!
Send that message to all units!
Alright, let's go!
Wait! I'm still cuffed!
They'll come off.
No, they won't!
--I'm gonna get the key!
--Do you know where it is?!
When we fell, I saw...
It must be somewhere on this plateau!
I'll find it and... What?!
How should we get there?
Go straight!
--Is he gonna jump off?!
--No way!
Wait for me, Doflamingo!
So many people are coming out of
the basement of the Colosseum!
Wh-What the hell is going on?!
Because of the geographical shift,
the basement has surfaced to the ground above!
I bet they are the ones who were forced
to work at the underground port!
Soldiers!
Officials!
Pirates!
I-I can't believe that many people
were enslaved, unnoticed by anyone!
Where's Straw Hat?
Maynard!
Who told you to fight in
the competition-dara?!
That was out of line!
You could have been killed!
But Bastille-san, I got to see everything
that's been going on here because of it!
MAYNARD THE PURSUER
A VICE ADMIRAL OF THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
(A CONTENDER OF THE GLADIATORIAL COMPETITION)
If we can take Doflamingo into custody,
the world may turn for the
better, even if only a little!
Where's Issho-san?!
IN THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
I'm glad to be back.
I can conduct investigations
without any interruption.
These are...
This trading ship from the
Kingdom of Biggschots has been
disguised as a pirate ship.
This port seems like a place where
secrets from various countries come together.
What are we gonna do after all of that?!
There are a bunch of Navy soldiers out there!
We're in big trouble once they find out about
our trade with Doflamingo!
I know! That's why we came back!
But we can't get out of here with the ship
because of...
We just need to destroy all the evidence.
Along with this ship!
--Alright? Now get down to it!
--Yes, sir!
I won't let you do that!
Who are you?!
Boy...
You can't burn all this crucial evidence!
Don't do it!
--I-I'm sorry!
--Honey!
Guys! Get away from me!
Why, Issho-san?!
Doflamingo can't keep his position
as a Warlord after this!
We have to capture him now!
The Navy has been doing
the same thing over and
over again just like that!
You have been in the Navy for a long time
haven't you, Vice Admiral-san?
Weren't you even listening all this time?
To these screams filled with anger?
They are not crying! They are angry!
Does the World Government...
pretend to be God or something?!
I need you to honor my decisions.
Law and the others' target
is the SMILEs, isn't it?
Hey Doffy! Don't we have
to protect the factory?
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE
(THE SUNFLOWER FIELD)
They can't open the doors.
They're all made of Sea Prism Stone.
And I have the keys to the factory here.
What?!
--Young Master-sama?!
--You know what you're doing?!
The enemies don't need hope.
How powerless.
I can't believe you couldn't even
protect this little girl, Trebol.
Shut up, "g"eezer!
She's not really a little girl!
Hey hey, Doffy!
I'm really sorry about Sugar!
I didn't expect a guy with his hands
and feet bound would knock out Sugar!
--How could I see it coming?
--The same can be said for the Flare-Flare Fruit!
I didn't expect the No.2 of the Revolutionary Army
was fighting in the competition.
How could I know?!
Right, right!
Don't make excuses!
How ungraceful! Idiots!
Un"g"raceful... There's the "G"!
Let bygones be bygones.
Even if I blame you two,
we can't change the past.
Right! That's our boss!
Nice try, Lao G!
I'll let you forgive me if you insist!
But Doffy, when it comes down
to it, the Navy is an obstacle.
What should we do with Fujitora?
I already talked to him.
The Navy won't come after us.
But once we've done using Fujitora,
he needs to be taken out.
I will take care of you after that!
What do you say?
I'm just a newcomer
picked through the World Military Draft
but since being appointed as a Navy admiral,
there is something I want to do.
The complete abolition of
the Seven Warlord system!
There's no advantage of keeping him alive.
I don't think it's gonna be easy though.
Listen!
Restrain all those people who are out of control!
Find the Straw Hats and Trafalgar Law!
Yes, sir!
The Navy is not antagonizing us-in, it seems!
Do they really wanna treat the
Young Master as a Warlord?
That's a little too lenient, isn't it?
Ah! Maybe they feel threatened by
the Birdcage, don't you think?!
That aside, that pervert,
I can't believe he still had
the energy to run away.
Where the hell did he go?
"Where did he go"? He's wounded so bad!
He must've been taken out by
the people who are controlled
by the Young Master by now-in, I bet!
He's not that weak.
Didn't you guys feel that guy's iron will?
I intend to keep wrecking
the place for no reason!
Prepare for it!
Half-hearted attacks won't bring him down.
We have to finish him off for sure this time!
Oh! So hard-boiled!
That must be the SMILE factory!
It's so defenseless!
It's practically begging to be shot at!
A balloon is falling from the sky-in!
A balloon?
If you don't wanna get hurt, stand back,
you little tramps!
Law!
How could you show your face here
after everything, you shitty brat?
Brother Law?
Well, I barely remember him.
--H-Hey!
--That's...
Straw Hat Luffy!
Trafalgar Law!
Pirate Hunter!
This is the worst spot to land!
Hey, Straw Hat!
When I get uncuffed, I'm gonna kill you first!
I tell you, there is no
good spot to land here
since everybody in this country is our enemy!
Anyway, we've gotta run!
Okay!
Chase them, chase them!
Zoro, that's not the way!
Straw Hat, it's not this way either!
--We found the criminals!
--Two Three-stars and one Two-star!
Don't let them get away!
Stop!
Ah! Brother Law! It's so nice to see you!
Who is he? Do you know him?
That's Dellinger! Don't
underestimate him! He's...
Not bad!
I got caught!
The strange guy came swimming in the ground!
Do it, Vise!
Run! He's a super weight human!
What?! Damn! Let go of my feet!
Ton Ton! Ten-Ton Vise!
I can't pull them out! My feet are stuck!
I'm not gonna miss it this time!
Pistol High-Heel!
Too heavy!
Ouch!
Great! My feet were released!
Watch out this time! Let's go!
We'll take the money!
Your heads are worth 800 million in total!
Prepare to die!
Shoot!
There are the Two-star and Three-stars!
Damn! They're pains in the ass!
But is it okay to chop them up?
There are some civilians, too!
Okay, I'll use my Haki to...
Stop it.
He who shoots oft at last
shall not hit the mark.
The Navy admiral!
The gambling old man!
Luffy and Zoro clash with Fujitora!
And in the midst of the fierce fight,
the silent top executive Pica
emerges from the ground...
...with a rumbling that
shakes up heaven and earth,
showing, at last, the
extent of his strength!
His tremendous power that
can destroy the whole town
bears down on Luffy and the others!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"With a Rumbling of the Ground!
The God of Destruction - Giant Pica Descends!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!