Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After landing on the Sabaody Archipelago,
the Straw Hat crew succeeded in
rescuing the kidnapped Camie.
However, a battle began
with marines lying in wait.
We're all set to escape!
The group then attempted to break
through the navy's siege and escape.
"Roger and Rayleigh
-- The King of the Pirates and His Right Hand Man"
Are you alive, Peterman-san?!
How dare they do this to our boss!
Dammit!
Damn them!
Still...
I never expected Duval to have such
a handsome face under that mask!
Well, see ya! Feel free
to call us again anytime!
We'll be at your beck and call until you
can safely set sail for Fish-Man Island!
Okay! Thanks, you guys!
No problem at all!
Just quit winking.
Oh, and one other thing...
Don't forget this, Miss Mermaid!
Oh! My backpack!
That idiot Peterman had it!
Thank you!
Alright! Let's go, Life is Rosy Riders!
Yes, Hand-Rose!
Their shouts sure change a lot.
They're probably trying
to find one that clicks.
Now, then. Let us hurry inside.
We need to get Hachi into a bed!
"Shakky's Rip-Off Bar"
Hey, Shakky! I'm back!
Oh, welcome back, Ray-san. That
was sooner than I expected.
I'm impressed you guys managed to find him.
Ol' Hachi's been seriously hurt.
We need to get him into a bed.
What happened?!
This is bad! I'll get a bed ready right away!
Oh, you said you had something
to tell me afterward, old guy...
Eh?!
On the Pirate King's ship?!
Yes. I'm Silvers Rayleigh,
the ship's vice-captain.
Nice to meet you.
Vice-captain?!
You didn't tell them, Hatchan?
We only needed his help
with the coating, so...
Oh? You didn't realize it?
I know his name so well!
It's in so many books!
It's definitely a name everyone
hears at least once...
Gold Roger...
I seem to vaguely recall a rookie named
that long ago, but I'm not sure...
How do such a big-shot and
an octopus know each other?
Hachi rescued me over 20 years ago,
when I was stranded in the sea.
He saved his life. He was still
a child at the time, though.
Hachi and I remained close after that,
until he joined the Sun Pirates.
You mean Arlong, right?
Still...
Even though Gold Roger was
executed 22 years ago,
you didn't get your head chopped
off for being vice-captain?
The navy caught the entire crew, didn't it?
We weren't caught.
Roger turned himself in.
The government might've made it
sound like they had caught him
as a way to show its power, though.
The King of the Pirates
turned himself in?! Why?!
Because we saw an end to our journey.
About four years before the
day of his public execution,
Roger caught a fatal illness.
Not even Roger could avoid the suffering
that this terminal,
incurable disease brought.
But, there was one man with the
skill to ease his suffering:
a man at the Twin Capes named Crocus,
who was the most respected lighthouse
keeper and doctor in the sea.
We asked for his help and brought him
on as ship doctor for our final voyage.
Finally, three years later,
while managing to escape death,
Roger achieved what was
said to be impossible:
he conquered the Grand Line.
C-C-Crocus-san?!
At the Twin Capes?!
Oh, that brings back memories!
Huh?! That old guy wasn't
there for 50 years straight?!
He was a member of the Pirate King's crew?!
Come to think of it, he did mention
being a ship's doctor for a few years!
So he was a pirate for
those three years, then?!
The fact that you've met him
must mean he's still doing well!
Crocus agreed to come aboard
because there was a certain group
of pirates he wanted to look for.
Brook! It was you guys he set
out to find, no doubt about it!
Crocus-san...! You even
went to such lengths...!
He was only a crewmember for three years,
but he was unquestionably one of us!
At this age now, it'd be
great to see him again...
So, what happened after he conquered the sea?
That's when it all began.
The world started calling
Roger "King of the Pirates."
He hadn't been King of the Pirates
the entire time before or anything.
Titles hold no meaning
for a man about to die.
But Roger was overjoyed.
He loved doing everything in a flashy way...
Whether it was celebrating or fighting...
He even seemed to enjoy thinking
out a plan for the future,
even though he wouldn't be a part of it.
Eventually, as per captain's orders, the
Roger Pirates were secretly disbanded.
One by one, everyone discretely left.
As comrades, we all risked
our lives together,
but I know almost nothing about where
they are or what they're doing now.
Then, about a year after we disbanded,
Roger turned himself in and was arrested.
It was then announced that
he would be publicly executed
in Loguetown, the East
Blue town he was born in.
I hear that many of the young
faces in the town square that day
went on to make names for themselves
on the high seas today.
The world focused its attention
on the Pirate King's execution.
I didn't attend it.
The final words he said went like this...
I'm not going to die, partner...
The World Government and the
navy must've been shocked.
With only one last remark from Roger,
the public execution meant to serve
as an example to other pirates
instead became the opening
ceremony of the Great Pirate Age!
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
In his last few seconds, he
changed the dim flame of his life
into a hellfire that spread across the world!
I've never laughed as much
as I did on that night.
Nor have I ever cried as much...
...or drank as much as I did on that night.
Our captain lived one hell of a life!
It's like we just heard something incredible!
It's almost like a different story,
hearing it from someone who was there!
Then it's almost as if Roger created
this Great Pirate Era on purpose!
That... we still can't say.
Roger is dead.
Only the people living
now can create this era.
I'm certain there are people who
inherited something from Roger
on that day in the town square.
Your good friend, Shanks,
is probably one of them.
Eh? You know Shanks, old guy?
Have you also heard of the East
Blue pirate known as Buggy?
Buggy...
The two of them were apprentices on our ship.
Eh?! Shanks was on the Pirate King's ship?!
What? He didn't tell you about that?
I ran into him again on these
islands about 10 years ago,
and he'd lost his trademark straw
hat, along with his left arm.
When I asked what had happened,
he cheerfully spoke about you.
It was a real shock, Rayleigh-san!
There was a kid in East Blue who said
the same thing Captain Roger did.
Those same words of our captain!
And I've wanted to meet you--
Monkey D. Luffy-- ever since.
Shanks!
I'm afraid I can't, in good mind, babble
on about things Shanks hasn't told you.
In any case, you've done
well to come this far!
I'm sure he's eagerly waiting
for you in the New World.
Really?! Do you think so?! I
can't wait to see him, too!
Now, then. Let's get down to business.
You wanted your ship coated, is that right?
I should get back to my real work, anyway.
That reminds me, coating
costs a lot of money...
No, that's all right, Hachi. I can't
take money from friends of yours.
That's a relief. Thank you, Rayleigh.
I dunno why, but he's doing it for free!
We appreciate it! You're one generous guy!
It sounds like we just saved a ton of money!
Rayleigh-san.
I have a question!
What exactly is the "Will of D"?
Roger's name was engraved in ancient writing
on Poneglyph I saw on a sky island.
How was he able to use that writing?!
"I made it here. I will guide this
text to the ends of the earth."
"Pirate Gol D. Roger"
Do you people know what happened to the world
during the Blank Century
that began 900 years ago?!
Yes. We know.
We learned the entirety of history.
But, Miss. You mustn't be hasty.
Continue to move forward one
step at a time on your own ship.
We-- and Ohara-- might have
hurried a bit too much.
Even if I told you everything
about history right here,
you still wouldn't be able to
do anything as you are now.
Once you've taken the time to see the world,
it's possible you'll be led to
a different answer than we were.
But, if you still insist on hearing it,
I can tell you everything
about this world right now.
No, I'll pass. I'll continue my journey.
It will all come into sight someday.
I'm sorry for what happened
to your homeland of Ohara.
However, Roger didn't decipher that writing!
We're pirates.
We can't possibly match
the intellect of geniuses
like Clover and the scholars of Ohara.
He heard the voice of the
universe, that's all.
Whoa, are you sure, Robin?!
Are you sure you didn't just
pass up an incredible chance?!
Umm, old guy! There's one
more thing I wanna ask!
The legendary great treasure, the One Piece!
Is it really--?!
Usopp!
I don't wanna know where the treasure is!
I don't wanna know if the
treasure exists or not!
We've put all our lives on
the line and set out to sea,
even though we don't know anything!
I'd rather give up being a pirate than
have the old guy tell us stuff now!
I won't go on a boring adventure!
S-S-Sorry! I knew that, but it
just slipped out of my mouth...!
I-I don't wanna know, either!
Oh, I forgot! I have the "I'll Die If
I Learn About the One Piece" disease!
Hold on, old guy! Don't say anything!
Do you think you can do it?
The Grand Line still far surpasses
anything you can imagine!
Your foes will be powerful, too.
Can you rule this mighty sea?!
I'm not gonna rule anything!
It's the freest person in this sea
who's the King of the Pirates!
I see...
I really am a fan of yours, Monkey-chan.
Your ship is in Grove #41, was it?
I think I'll head over there.
What will you do?
There could be an admiral on
these islands as we speak.
We'll only be a nuisance if we stay here,
so maybe we should go shopping somewhere?!
What is this, "Laid-Back Life"?!
We're being chased! We gotta hide, you idiot!
Yeah. The people chasing us might
show up if we all stay together.
It'll help him finish the work more
smoothly if we lay low in town.
Then let's just split up and then
meet back there when he's all done.
Who're you to talk strategically about
meeting up and stuff like that?!
Shakky. Do we have any?
Yes, there's one left.
This is a Vivre Card!
Oh, if you know what it is,
that simplifies things.
Since I happen to be a bit notorious myself,
I think I'll move it from Grove #41 to
somewhere else before I start on it.
I'll need three days to complete the coating.
It takes three whole days?!
Your life depends on this work.
It's the fastest I can go.
I guess it's three days of
wilderness survival then!
How frightening!
Sundown in three days, let's say.
I don't know what grove I'll be on then,
so wherever the Vivre Cards lead you,
I'll be there finishing the
coating and waiting for you.
You should probably also
buy whatever you'll need
for your underwater voyage
to Fish-Man Island.
Luffy-chin! Everyone! Thank you so much!
Yeah! Thanks so much!
I'm sorry I caused you so much trouble!
I can't thank you guys enough!
We'll show you the way to Fish-Man
Island, so don't worry about a thing!
Watch out for the navy
for the next three days!
Hachi! Get plenty of bed rest!
Let's meet again in three
days. We'll see you off.
See you later, lady!
We're up against an admiral! We gotta
make sure none of us gets killed!
Don't say unlucky things like that!
Three days, huh...
Alright! Let's go!
To the amusement park!
Hey, now!
A navy warship's been
spotted from the harbor!
The admiral's here!
This is Kizaru.
I've arrived.
Please respond.
Is the admiral really coming?
I don't want to meet him!
The one we met before, Aokiji, was crazy
strong with that freezing Devil Fruit power!
Oh, dear! I bet the other
admirals have powers, too!
I'm scared!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"No Escape!? Admiral Kizaru's
Light Speed Kick!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!