Edited at https://subtitletools.com
The exit is real close now. We'll keep
on going and go down in one shot!
What? No way... What?!
All right! The sea train has come out!
Guys! Now we're gonna charge forth, too!
Yeah!
Jump! Sodom! Gomorrah!
Straw Hat!
Thank you for helping us,
the entire Franky Family!
Whoa! Cool!
Those must be the highest-grade bulls.
I decided to go with you guys.
The enemy who took your friend away
is also the culprit who tried to kill Iceberg-san.
In addition, there are lots of
things that I wanna say to them!
Well, then...
Although we got in fights back in
town with both the Franky Family
and the Galley-La shipwrights,
we're all going after the same enemy now.
This is bad!
I told you, didn't I?
My job ended when the train got on the railway.
No one can stop it anymore.
Hey, Luffy!
When we have the same goal...
...it's senseless to fight separately.
Listen. We're comrades.
Guys! Don't let that big wave beat us!
We'll all achieve our goal!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Now, guys! Show me what
you can do about this wave!
All right! Fire all the cannonballs
we have at the wave!
When it comes to cannons, leave it to me!
Franky Family! Don't be
intimidated by the wave!
Prepare the cannons!
Roger!
Get a move on!
Yeah!
Ah! The portable transponder snail is ringing!
It's from Sanji-kun!
Wh-What the hell...
The same thing here!
They were all taken out!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Smash the Wave! Luffy and Zoro
Use the Strongest Combo!"
Hey, you!
Yes, Captain T-Bone!
That wound... What happened to your arm?
Hm...? Oh...
I got bitten by a bug earlier.
When I scratched the area, it bled.
That's not good! We should
stop the bleeding immediately!
--Ahh!
--Let's make do with this.
Y-You tore your precious cape!
"Justice"
Now, this should do.
When my subordinates bleed,
it's my heart that gets wounded.
Captain T-Bone...
May the world be in peace
and kindness again today.
His face is super scary.
--Captain!
--What'd you say?!
I... I haven't said anything.
If it's something I can do, I'll do it,
even if my body gets destroyed.
Er... Well...
The officials in car #6 and #7
have been wiped out.
In addition, the two criminals
detained in car #6 are missing as well.
What?!
We can't tell whether there's an intruder
or they escaped by themselves.
For Heaven's sake! Save the lives
of the injured immediately,
and let everyone on this train
know about this situation!
Yes, sir!
Nami-san! Nami-san, can you hear me?
Yep, is that you, Sanji-kun?!
Things are taking a turn for the worse here.
Turn for the worse?
Sanji-kun! What was that voice?!
Hey! What's going on?! Sanji-kun!
Hey, hey...
Yeah, because of that idiot...
I-Idiot?
Ah! Again! What?!
--Are you okay?!
--What's going on?!
--Just kidding.
--Are you okay, Sanji-kun?
--But you look panicky.
--Who's the idiot you're talking about?!
Actually, there are two idiots.
Demi-Cannon!
Take these!
We're not even making a dent.
Should have expected as much.
No! Those puny cannons won't work!
Guys! Stay back!
Leave it to the Franky Family's special cannon!
Target! Aqua Laguna!
Fire! Super Scrap Cannon!
Dammit! Don't flinch! Keep firing!
Replenish the cannonballs!
Got it!
Aim at the front! Focus on one spot!
Go! Focus pocus!
Do your best. The railway surfaces a little,
but we can't go over Aqua Laguna.
If we directly hit it, even Rocketman
will easily get destroyed.
Ahhh! Are we gonna die?!
I told you to prepare yourselves, right?
What?! That includes us?!
I see... Then Robin is still...
At any rate, it sounds lively over there.
Say, Sanji-kun...
I'll tell you the reason for Robin's actions
and our current situation, so...
Be quiet!
Listen, Sanji-kun. I'll tell you everything
about the reason for Robin's actions
and our current situation.
So please listen carefully.
Ahhh! We're gonna crash!
Oh, no! We're gonna die!
We're gonna die!
If you have time to whine, keep firing!
Find a way out!
Hey, Luffy.
Yeah... Let's go, Zoro.
Hey! Keep firing at the front!
What're you guys gonna do?!
We'll fire...
...a cannon.
What's a hundred and eight times two?
Two hundred and sixteen.
Two hundred and sixteen...
That's long and hard to say.
Then, pick whatever.
Wh-What are they doing?!
One is weaponless and the other is
using swords. What're they trying to do?
They told us to keep firing.
Enough talking! Just back them up!
Yeah!
Okay, then... three hundred!
Okay!
Gum-Gum...
Three-Hundred Pound...
We're gonna crash!
...Cannon!
Yeah!
Okay, then... three hundred!
Okay!
Gum-Gum...
Three-Hundred Pound...
We're gonna crash!
...Cannon!
Sanji-kun!
We're gonna die!
It's finally time.
W-We got through!
We got through Aqua Laguna!
I thought we were gonna die!
Yay!
Ow...
Hey! Are you okay, Nami-san?
Yeah, somehow...
That was really something. They don't
call themselves pirates for nothing.
If they were our enemy, they'd be fearsome,
but if they're on our side, no one
is more dependable than they are!
Straw Hat!
Naturally, I was prepared to die.
What incredible guys...
Don't let your guard down.
We are not through the storm yet.
Yeah!
There's nothing that we're afraid of now!
That was fun!
Straw Hat! You're amazing!
That was beyond human power!
Oh, sorry.
Luffy, come over here.
--Hm?
It's Sanji-kun.
Hey, is that you, Luffy?
Oh, Sanji! How's it going
over there? Where's Robin?
Robin-chan is still in their custody.
Nami-san just told me
the reasons for her actions.
Yeah, I heard... everything.
I see.
Yeah... Well... that's what's going on.
Go ahead and give them hell.
What?!
Whaaat?!
Hey!
Don't be reckless, Luffy!
Tell him to wait until we catch up!
Hey, Cook! Can you hear me?!
There are crazy guys on that train, so...
That's okay.
Zoro...
What would you do if it were you?
Hm?
After hearing that Robin lied and was
taken into custody in order to save us,
could you just stay put?
It's no use trying to stop him.
You know me well.
Hey, Moss Head! Are you worried about me?
Why would I be, you idiot?!
But sorry...
After hearing what Robin-chan was thinking...
...even if the Captain orders it,
I'm not gonna stop!
Ahhh!
Why'd you break it?! I wanted
to ask Straw Hat something, too!
Huh...? Who cares?
You should've told me beforehand.
Even if I didn't tell you, it was obvious,
wasn't it?! Don't be so cocky!
I'm not being cocky.
I wonder if he'll be okay.
Granny! Have the train go faster!
Faster?
Yeah! Like, more wooosh!
Don't worry. It's already going
faster than the limits of its speed...
So fast that it can't stop by itself.
So, things like that were happening...
...while I was gone?
Robin-chan doesn't know anything
about the Merry... or about the
huge fight between you and Luffy.
In order for all six of us,
including you, to stay safe,
she sacrificed herself and obeyed their orders.
She did it for us.
What a moving story!
Why are you crying?
You dummy! I'm not crying!
Dammit! I can't believe it!
Nico Robin is said to be a
cruel, inhuman, evil woman!
But the truth is... she's got touching
affection towards her friends!
Robin-chan is within a stone's throw.
Anyhow, I'll go rescue her!
All right, then! I'm Franky,
the leader of the Franky Family!
I'll give you a hand, mister eyebrow!
To tell you the truth, I've got
a reason for not wanting Robin
to be in the Government's custody, too.
Most of all, when I hear such a poignant tale...!
Hey! Let's go, Long-nose!
I'm...
...not coming.
It no longer has anything to do with me, right?
If the World Government itself
becomes your enemy at last,
I don't wanna be part of it.
You'll join with Luffy and
the others as well, right?
After all my blustering,
and after humiliating myself,
how could I be with you guys?!
I'm sorry, but I'm no longer
honor-bound to go rescue Robin!
I left the Straw Hats!
See ya.
H-Hey! "See ya," you're saying?!
There's no place to escape to!
--That's okay.
--Hm?
Leave him alone.
That idiot's being stubborn.
Search every nook and cranny!
There's gotta be some evidence somewhere!
Th-This isn't good!
Let's make do with this!
Wanze-san! The train's in a whole lot of trouble!
Shut up! I'm the one who's
in a whole lot of trouble!
Nero-san! The criminals made an escape!
Hm?
How was it over there?
Was there something unusual?
Nothing for now.
I see.
Hm?
Oof.
Ah!
Ahhh! I found them!
Oh, shoot!
Metallic Star!
Who's there?!
He told me everything.
I heard that you guys want
to rescue a mademoiselle.
That alone is reason enough
for me to lend a hand.
I will fight alongside you!
My name is...
...Sogeking!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
We'll now start the meeting for
Operation Rescue Robin-chan.
Sanji-kun, we've never met before.
Don't you have any questions?
First, we'll efficiently reduce
the number of enemies in the train.
You know, like my origins
or my killer techniques?
And then, we'll crush the main forces in turns.
Sogeking! "I'll-Do-My-Best" Star!
Hey! Give it a rest already! Just listen to me!
Oh, okay. Sorry.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Mysterious Man Appears?!
His Name Is Sogeking!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!