Edited at https://subtitletools.com
2 years have passed since the war between...
...the Navy Headquarters, The Seven Warlords, and the Whitebeard Pirates.
On the desert island north west of the Maiden Island - Ruskaina...
Luffy!
Yeah! I'm coming!
I can't believe it. It's been 2 years already.
Hey!
Look carefully. She's my friend.
Luffy, the ship is ready to sail out at any moment!
Okay, thanks!
That's amazing.
He's the boss of the island now.
But because I became friends with them, I couldn't eat them.
They look yummy.
It's okay, Luffy.
We put everything that you like on the ship.
And I think I'll be a good wife since I'm thoughtful like that.
I'm not gonna get married. Thank you for the food!
I can't help loving you even if you're so bitter!
Rayleigh left 6 months ago.
He must be waiting to see you at Sabaody.
He was done teaching me the basics in first 18 months.
I have to say goodbye to you guys and the island.
Alright...
Let's go!
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates, once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
SHAKKY'S RIP-OFF BAR
It's been 2 years.
It went by fast when I look back now.
Yeah.
I can't wait to see how much they've grown.
Don't be hasty.
We don't even know if they can all get together safely.
Because they're infamous throughout the world now.
Oh!
Ah, you're the first to arrive.
What? Nobody has arrived yet?
They never change.
"The Beginning of The New Chapter! The Straw Hats Reunited!"
OVER 10 DAYS LATER AT A BAR
Did you know that the Navy HQ has been relocated?
What? Was it?
Yeah, they switched its place with the G1 branch
symmetrically over the Red Line.
That's how determined the new Fleet Admiral after Sengoku is.
After all, he set up the HQ in the sea where The Four Emperors operate.
But thanks to the switch, the HQ has less sway here
so there are more lawless areas on this island.
Hmm, no wonder this town seems rougher than 2 years ago.
Hey, did you see this?!
Yeah, I was shocked, too.
I can't believe the Straw Hats have surfaced again!
Yeah, no one has heard from them for
2 years so we thought they were dead.
URGENT CREW NEEDED
I can't believe they're recruiting!
Pirates who survived through the first half of the
Grand Line keep coming to this island.
So he wants to expand his group here to run wild in the New World!
It's so exciting! Maybe I wanna join!
No way!
There are people with bounties over 100 million on the island now.
They're not gonna take you for sure!
What?!
Hey, old man! Give me a drink!
And something to eat, too! As much as you have!
Y-Yes, right away!
Hey, could they be...
I have no doubt! They're...
The Straw Hats...
GROVE #33 SABAODY PARK
A CONCERT HALL SABAO DOME
Hey, don't say that!
Can't you do anything...?
Tickets are sold out! Of course they are!
It's the world tour of the superstar Soul King Brook!
And today is the last show!
The place is already packed!
Manager!
I'll put on a great show today!
Yes, that'd be nice!
Your TD is doing very well and they were sold over million copies now!
You certainly are the king of soul music!
Listen to the crowd!
Soul King! Soul King! Soul King! Soul King!
Manager...
Before the concert,
I have something important to tell you.
What is it?
Come on, baby!
Yeah!
Because I'm a skeleton, it's...
Bone!
--Bone to be wild!
--Bone!
Bone! Bone! Bone!
Bone!
It's nonsense to become macho just to attract women
Soul King is mysterious
He's nothing but bones!
I can't believe it... How selfish can he be!
Hey, give me a Transponder Snail!
I'm not gonna let you do whatever you want, Brook!
Let's make today a great anniversary!
I've missed Sabaody.
I'm finally back.
Women! Real ones!
Ah, there's no doubt!
There are actual ladies in front of me!
These are the real ladies that I've longed for
every single day, on this island!
Viva Sabaody!
I need lady!
Sanji-kun!
We'll leave you here.
I don't want to part but see you again somewhere!
I don't wanna see you again!
Thank you for the ride! Say "hi" to Ivan! Bye!
I'm a real man - Sanji!
Just come back from hell!
You know what they say?
Boys can't help swearing at a girl they love.
I know. It happened to me.
I don't wanna let him go!
Wait for me, Nami-san, Robin-chan!
Ah? Did I hear it wrong?
A 55 million berries bounty?
A PIRATE "STRAW HATS" CAPTAIN - MONKEY D. LUFFY
Check the poster once again!
It says "At least 70 million berries bounty."
We're not gonna deal with captains with less bounty.
How did you guys even get here safely?
Dammit!
Go away, pest.
Don't you know that I'm Dragon - the Revolutionary's - son?!
NAVIGATOR - NAMI
SHIPWRIGHT - FRANKY
We don't need some half-ass!
Because we're the chosen pirates!
SNIPER - SOGEKING
We're in another league.
Don't think that just anyone can join us.
Go home.
He's so merciless. Straw Hat Luffy!
Can't be helped - he has achieved a lot.
Hey, Franky. How many people we got so far?
About 100 people.
3 whole pirate groups joined us.
10 of them are with a bounty.
That's good. 2 of the 10 are high-profile rookies.
"Wet-Haired" Caribou and "Blood Splatter" Coribou
who are known for killing Navy soldiers.
They're captain brothers with 210 million and 190 million bounties.
It's great to have them!
Let's get more followers! Old man, we need more drinks!
Y-Yes!
Hurry up!
Oh? And you woman, who's been there for quite a while.
Stop drinking alone quietly and come join us!
She's cute.
Hey sister, can't you hear me?!
Hey, he's talking to you.
That's okay. I'm waiting for someone.
What?
She turned him down.
Hey, hey, you better say yes!
He's Straw Hat Luffy!
Remember?
He's the crazy pirate who burst into the War of the Best 2 years ago!
You know him, right?!
Waiting for someone?
He must be a wimp who'll apologize in tears
once he hears Captain Luffy's name anyway!
So come here now!
I'll only say it once!
You're no match for me so I'm not gonna drink with you!
What?
Do you understand, Straw Hat... who?
Did you say "who"?!
I'm Straw Hat Luffy!
Hey, you better apologize! You're in danger!
Huh?
You've got a lot of nerve!
Let me handle it.
Hey you! You're a funny woman.
Then I'll make it easier for you.
Are you gonna drink with Captain Luffy?
Or do you wanna die?
For your information, I have a bounty, too.
I'm a cat burglar - Nami!
Don't mess with me!
Sure Kill: Green Star...
..."Devil"!
Huh?
Wh-What is this?!
What is this?!
Help me, Captain!
You fool! Stay away from me!
What is that plant?
So, young lady, do you wanna drink with me?
Usopp, long time no see!
I can't believe it! You became stronger!
You have blossomed yourself!
What?! She had been waiting for that geek?!
Did you do that?
Yes, I did! That's my new weapon - Pop green!
It's not like I was watching the sea and doing nothing for 2 years.
I'm sorry
but I no longer belong to the weak trio with you and Chopper.
I became a warrior who isn't fazed by anything!
Hey, dude! Is this what you've done?
What?! Sogeking?! Why?!
Usopp, forget about them!
Let's go somewhere else.
I need a favor to ask of you, too.
Wait, you guys!
Huh, Luffy?!
Let's go!
Hey, ma'am, you haven't paid yet!
Keep the change!
Damn, this is setting a bad example for others!
Bring them back!
Dammit!
Huh?! What are these black bubbles?!
What the hell is this? A cloud?!
Wh-What happened?!
...So I studied about the new technology...
Really? You were in the sky?
Find those two and kill them!
I have a report! At the Sabaody Archipelago...
What? The Straw Hats?!
Yes, sir! Word is that they're recruiting new crewmembers there.
Let the headquarters know about it.
If he's really alive, that's not good.
Call soldiers up right away!
And intensify the search on the Sabaody Archipelago!
Did I shake them off?
Brook's concert?
The Straw Hats' recruitment?
What is going on?
What is Soul King?
There's no mistake...
There isn't even a scratch on it.
Sorry to keep you waiting, Sunny!
We'll be sailing out soon!
Grand-Bun is good, indeed!
I wonder how everybody's doing.
I hope I can see them soon!
--Mister, make it bigger!
--Thank you!
Hey, you alright?! Hey!
He's horrible!
He shot her out of the blue!
Terrible!
Hey, stay with me!
Why did you do that?!
Did we do something to you?!
I said "sorry"!
I mistook her for someone else!
I'm sorry. I was looking for a couple like you guys.
A long-haired woman and a long-nosed man.
You mistook her and shot her on the spot?!
How horrible he is! Straw Hat Luffy!
Huh? Don't tell me that you have something against me!
Looks like you do.
Don't hate me, hate those two!
Hey, stay with me! You alright?!
Find them, guys! Those two!
We can't just let them get away!
Kill them as a warning to others!
Oh, did it hit you? Sorry!
Bye!
What's wrong with him?
He doesn't know Straw Hat Luffy?
H-He's gonna get killed!
Wait a minute!
Huh?
The fake Luffy who appeared in front of Luffy
attempted to boost his crew's power
by calling them Straw Hats.
Facing the pistol-wielding fake,
Luffy's newly acquired powers activate.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Explosive Situation!
Luffy vs. Fake Luffy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!