Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that
the prize for a fighting
event was the Flare-Flare
Fruit, he decided to enter.
The first round is a battle royal
where only one can win.
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates won
the match of Block A.
Now, the battle of Block B has begun.
Competitors led by Dagama, the tactician,
are protecting Elizabello II,
the king of Prodence Kingdom!
When is he going to throw
the devastating King Punch?!
Bellamy!
"Atrocious"! "Evil"!
Those are the words only fitting to this man!
Is he the top contender
to beat Elizabello II after all?!
In the meantime,
the Jiaokungdo martial artist - Blue Gilly
and the mysterious gladiator - Ricky,
the two strong men are fighting each other!
4000 Brick...
...Fist!
Just kidding!
What did he do?!
Hack is the one who collapsed!
What was that?
Wh-What kind of monster are you?!
Bartolomeo!
"A Deadly Blow!
The Astonishing King Punch!"
Hack got defeated!
He couldn't even reach Bartolomeo!
What did Bartolomeo do to him?!
Damn! I was rooting for Hack!
That chicken head!
Gyats-san, you have to be fair!
Relax!
We can't see a clear winner yet!
B Block - 24 competitors remain.
It's gonna be over soon, huh?
He looks like something.
Everybody's got a wound or two now!
It's about time!
Powerful competitors are getting eliminated
one after another!
Following Hack's defeat,
the unknown gladiator,
Ricky, also got taken down!
Blue Gilly is strong!
--Blue Gilly-sama!
--So cool!
What do you think you can cut
with such a blunt sword, old man?
I guess I can't fight aging.
I can't stand all this cheering.
I can't stand you, Doflamingo!
There aren't that many men left
thanks to Dagama's tactics!
Yeah.
Most of the competitors are gone
except for us.
Can't believe I'm still here.
I'm glad that I allied with them!
Me, too!
When Dagama gives us the cue,
we'll disband.
Then we'll fight amongst ourselves
until one of us wins.
Let's take down as many
enemies as possible for now!
I know!
Blue Gilly!
Here he comes!
Guys! Take care of Blue Gilly
while we're fighting together!
Okay!
Dagama?!
You did a fine job, you stupid dogs!
Why?
Hey, you haven't given us the cue!
Don't tell me he... Hey, Dagama!
You two!
Sorry! I've been told to hunt you dogs!
Were you plotting together?
To get rid of us from the beginning?
I will pay you later!
Your job is done now!
Dagama!
Warriors who can't use their brains
just end up as someone's
puppets on a battlefield!
I'll be counting on you, Longfeet man!
Now you turned your back to me,
you're dead, too.
Blue Gilly.
We of the Prodence Kingdom
will win the Flare-Flare Fruit
at any cost!
What?!
You betrayed me, Blue Gilly!
Dagama the tactician got eliminated!
--Way to go, Longfeet guy!
--Blue Gilly-sama!
I can't believe people would trust a
dubious guy like him
in the first place.
Oh? On the other hand...
--Go, Bellamy!
--Kick his ass!
Our man - Bellamy is beginning to attack!
His target is the "most annoying pirate
who should just go away"!
Bartolomeo!
Huh? Me?
Just go away already!
What?!
Bellamy who went in for the attack
is down on the floor?!
What did Bartolomeo do?!
Bellamy delivered an attack
and got hurt like Hack!
What did he do to him?
What did he just do?
Damn it all!
I shouldn't be...
...struggling like this right here!
Go, Bellamy!
Spring...
...Death Knock!
I-I can't believe it!
Our man - Bellamy is worn out!
What kind of Devil Fruit did he eat?!
Bellamy! You can do it!
Bellamy...
I've no interest in the Flare-Flare Fruit
but I have my own reason to win this thing!
I'm gonna get on board Doflamingo's
ship to ride through the
"wild wave" that will come sooner or later.
I'm done picking on you.
Hey, Bellamy! Don't give up!
Now what are you gonna do, Elizabello?
Nothing is more helpless than a king
without his court.
Everybody was dying to kill you.
All the people who had been guarding you
have turned against you.
What's the matter?
You can't do anything
without Dagama, can you?
Dagama did a great job.
I'm all set now.
All I need to do is throw it!
You guys are the ones who were protected
while we were in that battle formation.
Because nothing is more dangerous
than an exposed blade.
Don't you think so, you punk?
Hey, I just thought of something.
What?
There was a report about
the king of Prodence.
They said he destroyed an
enemy country's fort
with a single punch.
No way! He must've used some kind of weapon.
No, they say it could take down
even the Four Emperors!
What?
If it's true, he's gonna throw a punch that
will destroy this part of the Colosseum!
What?!
No way! That can't be true!
I've heard the same thing!
No! He can't throw such a destructive punch
at a place like this!
There is a restlessness in the air!
The king who kept quiet
in the battle formation is
now on the move!
We of the Prodence Kingdom will win
the Flare-Flare Fruit!
Hey!
Hey, are you listening?
What do you wanna talk about?
Like I said, in order to
destroy the SMILE factory,
I gotta beat up someone in the Doflamingo...
Halt.
What?
I'm busy! I've got work to do!
I'm sorry but I have no time for this.
If you have nothing to talk about, I'm gonna go now!
Bye!
You...
You keep talking about this radical plan
but why do you want to do such a thing?
You seem like you know things
that ordinary people don't!
What is your true purpose?
My true purpose?
What's going on?
Damn!
This doesn't look good!
You've got to be kidding!
Whoa-whoa, we better go!
Run!
Maybe, he really did destroy the fort!
You're so persistent!
What's this?! Get it off of me!
No way! Don't underestimate
the power of my spring!
King...
I'm gonna kill Elizabello!
Outta my way!
Shooting...
...Punch!
What's going on in the Colosseum?
How...
How powerful was that?!
I don't think anyone in the
ring could survive that!
Elizabello II wiped out all of his enemies...
...with a single punch!
What a man!
That was a hell of a punch!
I've never seen something like that before!
Bellamy! Blue Gilly!
And all other potential
winners have been eliminated!
The battle royal of Block B - 138
competitors - the winner is from
the Prodence Kingdom...
Hey, look! Somebody's there!
You see? Right over there!
The audience in that direction
didn't get blown away
because of his defense!
Barrier!
People can create barriers
by crossing their fingers.
It's common knowledge!
Even kids know it!
I'm a barrier human who ate
the Barrier-Barrier Fruit!
Barrier Crash!
"The Fighting King" - Elizabello
II got knocked out!
The winner of Block B is...
Dammit!
...Bartolomeo!
All of you, go to hell!
--Go away!
--Screw you!
What? That strange guy won.
I will dedicate the Flare-Flare Fruit
to that person!
Then, you, too?!
Shh! Shh!
You're too loud!
You're plotting to destroy the factory, too?!
Indeed! My friends and I have been
carrying out preparations for it!
Tell me where it is!
I'll destroy it right away!
You can't do that!
Why?!
Because we want to save the
workers in the factory!
The workers in the factory?
Yes!
Our plan could lead to
the fall of this country!
It's a big project!
If you have the nerve and are
determined to go against Doflamingo,
I'm going to tell you everything
about this tragic kingdom - Dressrosa!