Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesometreasure
at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be Kingof
the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse ofthe
tail end to the future
The horizons everyonedreamed
of were separate at first
but now they can be seenthrough
a single telescope
A bitter compass of destinyis
leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieveyour
dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse ofthe
tail end to the future
The Straw Hat Pirates have fallen rightinto
the middle of the fortress Navarone.
Zoro was captured.
In addition, Luffy and theothers
infiltrated the base,
and an impending crisis
drewnearer to them each minute.
"The Navy's Dragnet Closes
In!The Second Member Captured!"
Navy Command Branch 8...
That's the official name of Navarone.
People also call it the Navy'sstrongest,
an impregnable fortress.
Its headquarters should bein
that island in the center.
But that's about all we know.
We don't have to know things like that.
You want to investigate a fortress now?
Aren't ancient ruins enough for you, Robin?
Of course! We're in the enemy's midst.
Even so, we don't have the
luxuryof looking around forever!
What I wanna know is whetherthe
Going Merry is okay or not.
Where the heck did you go, Merry?!
It's probably reasonable to thinkthat
it was seized by the Navy.
Geez...! How can you saysuch
a thing so calmly?!
Even if we find the ship, how
arewe going to get out of here?
Are you saying that the
Navywill show us the way out?
W-Well...
That's why we should
thoroughlyinvestigate first. Right?
I wouldn't be a pirate if
Iwere scared of the Navy!!
I can't take this anymore. I'll leavethe
thorough investigation to you.
My leg!
Robin! What the hell are you...?
Found them?!
No, sir!
Some of the Straw Hats'rehiding
around here for sure!
Leave no stone unturned!
Yes, sir!
There's no way they can escape wheneven
that Roronoa Zoro was captured.
Z-Zoro was?!
Are you all right, Long-nose?
D-Did you hear that?
This means they now know that it'sthe
Straw Hat Pirates, not a ghost ship.
Our enemy's in a frenzy. Why don't youworry
about yourself instead of the ship?
I don't care! Sorry, but that shipis
more important than my own life!
I'm going! I've decided! So
don'tget in my way anymore! Later!
He's impossible...
I've come all the way in
astorm to such a remote base,
and they send no oneto escort me?! How rude!
Hm? Hey, you over there!
Yes, sir!
I'm supposed to meet
thecommander of this base.
Inform them to send someoneto
escort me immediately!
"Justice"
Yes, sir! Before that, please tell me
whatbusiness brought you to our fortress.
I don't have to explain it to a mere private!
Excuse me, but may I
haveyour division and rank?
I'm saying I don't need to explain it to you!
Contact your headquarters immediately!
Even if I did, I don't
think it'd do any good.
What do you mean by that?!
Since Commander Jonathan is eatingright
now, I think he's in the dining hall.
Then all you have to do is go tothe
dining hall to talk to him, right?!
Um... don't you know the motto of Branch 8?
Motto, you say?
One! Wash your hands before eating!
Two! Never leave food on your plate!
Three! Never mention work while eating!
Four! After eating, make sure to brush...
That's enough! So to
thecommander at this base,
eating is more important than
aVIP sent by Navy Headquarters...
Is that what you're saying?
Yes, sir! That's correct!
All right, I get it. I'll go
toyour headquarters on my own.
Before I go, I'll give you a piece of advice.
Find another job while you can.
Huh?
The hedgehog that has now becomeuseless
in this area of sea...
The odd commander who stays inside,never
setting even a foot outside of it...
The Navy doesn't need
either of them at all now.
I'll probably report them
toHeadquarters at some point.
Hmph! That darn badger! He'll nolonger
be a commander in a few weeks.
Go ahead and enjoy the fewNavarone
meals that you have left.
Guess it was just my imagination.
Navy Headquarters Inspection Division...
What a good person to bump into.
Whoa! Yum!
The new cook is pretty good!
It's just like what those guys whoate
first thing in the morning said!
Everyone! The next 100 soldiers're waiting.
Hurry up and finish eating!
Aye aye, sir!
Here you go.
Hey, Jessica...
This is your usual dish, right?
Any problem, Commander?
Well, my men are carrying on
aboutthe incredibly delicious food
prepared by the cooks from Marie Jois.
So I came here looking forward to it.
You don't like it? When I, the
executivechief chef, cooked it for you myself?
You can't continue to eat the same
kindof food as the younger ones, right?
It's a healthy dish filled
withlots of love. Bon appetit!
But it has lots of vegetables as well...I
don't like broccoli and carrots.
Branch 8's Motto 2!
Ah, um... A-All right... Here!
See? I'm eating it.
Whoa! This is yummy! This one's yummy, too!
Guys! Keep up the good work!
What's that newbie doing?!He's
been sampling food all this time!
Don't worry about him. He only does tasting.
No matter how I look at him,he
doesn't look like a cook
who was in charge of thekitchen
at Navy Headquarters.
In contrast, look at you!
You're very skilled!
You're quite popular among the soldiers, too.
Thanks. I'll write downmy
recipes for you, then.
Prepare food for table 8! Please hurry up!
Aye aye... sir!!
For a beautiful lady, I'd go
throughhell and high water! There!
Wh-Whoa!
Oh! That looks yummy! Okay!I'll
take it to the table for you.
Hold it! If you touch that food,you
won't be eating meals. Got that?!
Aye aye, sir!
I wonder if he really gets it...
In any case, the guy at
table 8 sure is lucky.
She may not look it, but
shecherishes her husband, so...
Oh? Jessica-san has a husband?
If you have time for
chit-chatting, get to work!
Who the heck is this"luckiest
guy in Navarone"?!
It's the Commander of this place, Branch 8.
What?! The Commander, you say?!
Crap! Luffy...!
Here you go!
Thanks. You can go now.
Aye, aye, sir!
This tastes just like theysaid
it did. It's amazing!
This dish lives up to my expectations!
Yeah, you're right!
Let me have some, you cheapskate!
You certainly live up to my expectations!
Oops! Dammit! Looks like I was late!
Welcome, Straw Hat Luffy.
I'm Jonathan, the Commanderof
Navarone, Branch G8.
Straw Hat, I don't wannaget
violent in the dining hall.
But could you answer me one question?
If I answer, can I eat half of that stuff?
Hm? Not just half, you can eat it all.
Really? Then I'll take it.Sorry
that I called you a cheapskate.
Idiot! Hurry up and get out!
No matter how hard I think,I
can't figure out your purpose.
Right. It is said that Captain Smokeris
the one who defeated Crocodile.
It's not as if you gained reputationin
Alabasta, or even money.
What would someone like that want from us?
What did you come to this fortress base for?
What for? Well, when we fell fromthe
sky, we happened to land here.
Hm?
The Grand Line really
is an interesting place.
I've come to like this fortressquite
a bit as well, you know!
You have good food here.I
guess I'm just lucky.
Listen, Straw Hat. Even if you'vegot
the power of a Devil Fruit,
it's impossible to escape Navaronewithout
some sort of miracle.
I'll leave when I want to.
Even after you hear thatRoronoa
Zoro was captured?
Zoro?
That idiot...!
Fortress guy, where's Zoro?
And if I tell you?
What else? I'm gonnago rescue him right away!
You don't have to be so hasty.We'll
take you to the same place soon.
There's no point stayinghere
any longer! Let's go!
Ahh!
Jessica-san...
Little did I know you were Straw Hats!
Your skills are too good for a pirate.
Give it up! Cooks in Navarone
aretougher than your average marine!
Hmph! I come from a
placewith many such cooks!
That said, I can't attack Jessica-san...
Now what should we do?
I'm starving!
Give us food!
Give us the new cook's
famousridiculously tasty food!
Bring it already!
Wait! We're in the middle of something!
Now! Let's go!
Straw Hat!
See ya, fortress guy!
Our enemy is the Straw Hat Pirates!
Be ready to engage in battle at any time!
To uphold the honor of Navarone,we
must capture them without fail!
Yeah!
Yipes! Those marines're too fired up!
It's really dangerous to keep playinghide
and seek in our enemy's midst!
I'd better do something
aboutmy appearance, at least.
Hm? Yeah... Hm... All right!
Transformation complete!Now
I should be able to openly...
Hold it!
Ahh!
If you're a Navarone marine,you
should dress neatly.
Huh?
This is why I say new recruits are trouble.
Yes, sir! I'll be careful, sir!
Um, by the way, I'd liketo
ask you something, sir.
Do you know how to get to the
dockwhere the Straw Hats' ship is?
It'll be six blocks down from over there.
Thank you very much... sir!
Hey! But the dock is...
That was all I needed to know, sir!
M-Merry! You're okay! Thank God!
A carvel-built caravel that uses a
lateensail with a stern rudder in the center...
The model's a bit old,but
it's really a good ship.
Huh?! Who are you?!
If you don't know me,then
you must be a newbie.
Y-Yeah, sort of...
This ship must've hadquite
a few wild journeys.
Though it's covered with patches,the
repairs were done appropriately.
It's a happy ship filled with lots of love.
You can tell that much?!
It doesn't matter if it's
aNavy ship or a pirate ship.
I can tell for the most
part at the first glance.
That's quite a compliment! Thanks!
Idiot! I'm not praising you!
Well, don't get so upset! I like you!
You sure are perky for a newbie.
You haven't changed, putting pirate
shipsin the same league as navy ships...
Hm?
Lt. Commander Drake, you need to waitat
least a week to have the ship repaired.
It seems that marines these days
are under the mistaken impressionthat
damaging ships is their job.
Thanks to that, docks are kept very busy.
Quietly...
Don't worry. I didn't come here tobother
our veteran maintenance soldier.
Quietly...
I came for the other guy. Hey, you!
Y-Yes, sir!
Which unit are you with?!
Ugh! Wh-Wh-Which unit...?
You can't even tell me
which unit you're with?!
Um, let me see... I think it's Unit 18, sir.
Unit 18 is a sniper unit, isn't it?
Don't you know that this dock is
off-limitsexcept for the maintenance soldiers?
Um... I'd forgotten that, sir! I'm goingback
to the sniper unit right away, sir!
There's no need for that!
No need?!
Take him!
Yes, sir!
What did I do?!
It was reported to me that
asuspicious new recruit was seen.
By the way, Unit 18 isn't asniper
unit, it's a supply unit.
Ah, my bad! That's right! It's a supply unit!
Stop it, you idiots!Where
do you think you are?!
To us, the maintenance
soldiers,this is a sanctuary!
If you shed even one drop of
blood,you won't get away with it!
Pull back your swords.Take
him to headquarters.
Yes, sir!
Hmm, so this is the man...
Commander, he insists that he's a marine,
but the circumstantial evidence
clearlyindicates that he's one of the Straw Hats.
You!
Yes, sir!
What's your name?
It's a secret.
Which unit are you with?
Why did you take the trouble to goto
the dock where the pirate ship is?
It's a secret.
Secret, huh?
Yes...
Let's imprison him right
awayand put the screws to him!
Now, hold on, Lt. Commander.
Come to think of it, I hear that a
specialinspector from Navy Headquarters
was on board the Stan Mareythat
arrived this morning.
Yes?
A special inspector?
C-Commander...!
It's natural that an inspector would
hidehis name and division to investigate.
Th-That's ridiculous!An idiot
like him wouldn't be...
I'm surprised that you figured it out.
That's what you'd expect fromthe
Commander. You're right.
I'm a special inspector fromNavy
Headquarters, Captain Usopp!
Is there any illegal activity in Branch 8?!
Are military laws and regulationsbeing
properly followed?!
Are the marines full of enthusiasm?!
So, I disguised myself as a
mereprivate to get the inside scoop.
That's the story!
We apologize, Captain!
Don't be ridiculous!
A special inspector has higherauthority
than a branch commander!
There's no way an idiot
like you could be one!!
Idiot? Idiot?!
What're you saying, Drake whoever,when
you're a mere Lt. Commander?!
What?!
I can have you court-martialed forinsulting
a senior officer, you know...
But...!
Do you wanna experiencethe Navy prison? Huh?
I'm sorry, Captain. I was thinkingabout
sending someone to greet you,
but I got delayed. Please forgive me.
Well, so long as you understand...!
Commander! Special inspector Major Shepherd
from Navy Headquarters has arrived!
Got it.
The real one showed up?!
See, I was right!!
You son of a bitch! Acting so impertinent!
Ahh, I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
What's the matter?! What happenedto
the spunk you had earlier?! Huh?!
I'm sorry.
What was that about the Navy prison?! Huh?!
What?! Are you apologizing?! I can't hear it!
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Do you think such a ridiculousspecial
inspector exists?!
I'm really sorry. I'm sorr...
Hm?
Nice to meet you, Commander Jonathan.
You'd better be prepared! Huh?You
stopped apologizing?! Huh?!
R-Robin!
What is it?! Huh?! Where'sthe
spunk you had earlier?!
Oh, I get it! She's disguising herself, too!
What was that about the Navyprison?!
Huh?! Say that again!
All right, then...!
Hey, Major! I didn't knowyou
were in Navarone as well!
H-Hey! It's me! Captain Usopp,also
from the Inspection Division!
Did you forget me since
you'vebeen traveling so much?!
Major Shepherd, do you know the Captain?
No, I don't know him.
Ahhhhhh!!
See?!
H-Hey! It's me! It's me! Hey!
Hey!!
Imprison him!
Now I'll start investigating Navarone, okay?
Please be my guest!We welcome
you, Major Shepherd.
Thank you very much.
That darn Robin! Does she have
agrudge against me or something?!
That's a betrayal!
You agree, don't you, Zoro?!
Dammit! If Robin had onlygone
along with what I said,
I would've taken Merry back by now!
You should thank Robin.
Why should I?! Why should I?!
You've got me with you.
O-Oh... I see... She thought thatit'd
be safer for me to be with you...
Robin was concerned about me...
But...
...is this place... safe...?
It might've been better if Ididn't
check into it, because...
...that way I would've
stillhad hope for the escape.
To think that there's
only one escape route...
Zoro!!
Where are you, Zoro?! Zoro!!
Shut up! Be quiet!
Oh?!
Hey, this way!
In addition to Zoro, we've also captureda
crew member with a long nose!
Straw Hat and the other members
aredefinitely close by as well! Find them!
Yes, sir!
Hey, what should we do now, Captain?
Straw Hat and a very skilled cook...
A swordsman and a man with a long nose...
A doctor and nurse we've never seen before...
And one more...
...who calls herself Major Shepherd...
That makes seven people...Now it makes sense.
We've already capturedthe
ship and two of them.
The rest of the Straw
Hats are within my hands.
So, what will you do now, Monkey D. Luffy?
I'll just sit back and see what you can do...
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,on
the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give
in,even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared
of,we can overcome it
Luffy, we're right here!!
Luffy, don't come!! No,
Ichanged my mind! Come get us!
Hey, Zoro! What should I say?!
How should I know?! Tell them
tocome if they want or something.
Well, that's...
Hang in there! I'll rescue
you right a... waay...
What the..?! Oh, I see! This
isthe Sea Prism Stone's doing!
Dammit! This is a trap!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Daring Luffy and Sanji!Their
Great Rescue Operation!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!