Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
1,867... 1,868...
1,869...
I got one!
Look!
Amazing!
Ahh! I've got something, too!
This is big! This could be
the guardian fish for this area!
Really?!
That's amazing!
All right!
Guardian fish...?
We can't eat that at all...
Ahh! Shut up!
You haven't even caught
a single fish yet! Don't complain!
Okay then. Just watch.
I'm gonna catch a big one!
Can you catch any?
I'm sure I will somehow...
Nami-san!
I brought you a tropical juice
that's great for your beauty
and makes your skin smooth!
Thanks!
That's not fair!
I want some, too!
Smooth skin!
Hey...
what do you want smooth skin for?
To get cuter!
The wind's fine. The current is fine, too.
It looks like we won't
have any problems today.
Something's taken the bait!
What the heck is this?
It's huge!
Hey, Luffy! What'd you catch?!
"Uprising of the Navigator!
For the Unyielding Dream!"
What a huge turban shell!
Hey, it's not actually a turban shell.
What're we gonna do with it?!
I wonder if this is edible...
You wanna eat it?!
Maybe cook it in its shell?
Hey, you too?!
Ahh... Boy, I thought I'd die!
Hi, everyone.
Who... are you...?
Oh... Pardon me for not
introducing myself sooner.
With a single call, I'll cordially
deliver products to your town.
I'm Rice Rice from
Transponder Snail Mail-Order.
Very nice to meet you.
Transponder Snail Mail-Order? What's that?
Well, I was in the process of
making a delivery with the Escar,
but I got caught in a heavy storm
and got shipwrecked with the
waves throwing me to and fro.
--I see...
--You must've been shaken up.
Shaken and stirred.
Just kidding. You're quite clever, Miss!
Here, drink some water.
Thank you for saving me.
This isn't much,
but as a token of my gratitude,
I'll give you these catalogues.
With a single call, I'll deliver
the products to you.
Oh, that's convenient.
So you'll deliver even
when we're on the sea?
That, I can't.
Oh... really...
Yes...
Our motto is safe, reliable and cheap.
--And our mission is...
--It's quite roomy inside.
Our company is, believe it or not...
--Ahh! What're you guys doing?!
--Wh-What's this?!
Okay! This is what I'm going
to introduce to you today.
The Buru Buru Blade, which is
familiar to people by now.
The Buru Buru Blade is our
company's top product.
And today, I'll introduce
you to this new model!
I'm sure that many of you are already
using the old Buru Buru Blade.
But the old model didn't, well,
let you change the weight load,
which was bad!
It was fine for fathers,
but many wanted small
children to be able to use it.
I don't know what it is, but it looks fun!
So, this new model lets you
keep a certain rhythm and...
This is fun!
You know all about this one, right?!
This is the Abu Abu Slider.
Our company's No. 1 product!
A new model has been
released! Give this a try!
How is "top" different from "No. 1"?
Who knows?
And, this is our best-selling
product! The "Golden Fish"!
This is recommended for people
who don't exercise much these days.
I'll offer these great weight loss
products together as a set!
And, today only, I'll also add
20 bottles of plenty sweet Mero Mero
Juice made in the West Blue,
a 26-volume encyclopedia set
that will definitely be useful,
and a pair of binoculars that are
convenient for various things!
How much do you think all this would cost?!
A pretty penny, to be sure!
Just leave it to me!
Today only, I present this as a token
of my gratitude for saving my life!
Are you gonna give them to us?!
Just take them, you thieves!
How about 23,800 Berries?!
So you're selling them...!
I want them!
You wanna buy them?!
Oh! You carry kitchen knives, too?!
Yes! You're talking about this, right?
This is one of the high-quality items
produced individually and carefully
by a craftsman in High Mountain.
Look at this elasticity.
And its excellent sharpness will last forever.
A dozen table knives,
a pair of all-purpose kitchen
scissors that can cut anything,
a paring knife, and an electric
whetstone! I'll add all these!
If you act now, it's 2,980 Berries!
For you, Miss, here is a Smooth Skin Soap!
It can make your skin as smooth as an egg!
I see... You do have everything.
Yes.
From mineral water to cannonballs,
there's nothing we don't carry.
You have living things, too?
Well, we don't.
What? You don't?
We don't have what we don't carry, so...
Say, do you have paper?
Huh? Paper?
That's right. Strong paper
that's big and hard to tear,
so that it'll take more than a
small sea breeze to get damaged.
Then, please leave it to me.
Transponder Snail Mail-Order
presents with confidence
the best paper, A-Thousand-Year Paper!
A-Thousand-Year Paper?!
A-Thousand-Year Paper is manufactured
by using the A-Thousand-Year Tree
that naturally grows on Eight-Nine Island.
This paper keeps away bugs,
and it's said that it won't fade
for at least a thousand years,
even if it's kept exposed to the sun.
It's the best for writing family
trees or drawing treasure maps.
Paper airplanes, too?
Huh...?
That would be a waste...
So how much is it?
You're gonna buy it?!
Of course!
I caught her purchasing desire!
I take it she's the type that price is
no object once she decides to buy.
Then, I'll just stir up her urge to buy as
much as possible and jack up the price.
Even if you're interested...
it's a valuable item in short supply...
Even if you order now,
I don't know if it'll be available
in five years... or ten...
But isn't there some way
you could sell it to me?
I'll pay any price.
What?!
The Nami who would rather
count money than eat her meals...
The Nami who is a money monger...
...will pay any price?!
You guys're going too far...
Okay, then... If you insist that much...
A ream of 1,000 A-Thousand-Year Papers
normally costs 60 million Berries,
but how about a special price of 48 million?
48 million Berries...!
Does that mean that it costs
48,000 Berries a sheet?!
Can't you drop the price a little more?
Well then, I'll make it a lot cheaper...
How about 47.5 million Berries?
2 million Berries!
4.8 million Berries!
This sounds fishy...
Can't you go cheaper?
We'll buy it!
Sanji-kun...
You have the money?
Nope!
But if we hand him over to the Navy,
we'll have that and change.
What?!
Sorry, Luffy. This is for Nami-san.
Wait a sec!
Luffy...?
Ahh!
Luffy... You mean... that Monkey D. Luffy?
Yeah, that's me.
Sanji! Whatever, just untie me.
No, I can't.
Th-Th-That odious pirate with
a 100 million-Berry bounty...
That Monkey D. Luffy...?
Come to think of it... that's a pirate flag!
I can't believe I missed
such important details!
I said untie me!
No!
Uhm...!
I just remembered that I have
an important appointment.
Goodbye!
Thanks for everything!
Hey, you forgot something...!
What's with him?
Maybe he was scared of you...
Wanted man, Monkey D. Luffy.
Really...?
Listen. I'm going to work now,
so don't interrupt me, okay?
What do you mean "work"?
It's a secret.
That's not cute, you know...
Leave it to me!
I won't let anyone near you
until you're done with the work.
But... what if the wind direction
suddenly changes or something?
Don't worry. Those clouds...
If they don't move,
we'll have a fine day today
and there'll be no problem.
Come get me only when something
changes with those clouds.
Let's see...
Things have been hectic
and I haven't had free time since
we entered the Grand Line, but...
Little Garden...
Drum Island...
Alabasta...
I've written down all
the routes that we took.
I've stolen... no, obtained maps of the
surrounding areas from towns as well.
I'll draw... my own world map...
my dream since childhood...!
Guys!
We'll make the deck spick-and-span
while Nami-san's working.
Okay!
Do your best!
You're gonna do it, too!
--You traitor!
--No fair!
--That's right!
--Then what about that woman?
Don't be ridiculous! She's a lady!
How stupid! It doesn't matter
if it's a man or woman...
Just help us, Moss-Head monster!
Ha ha, very funny,
Love-Love Machine goblin.
Just help us, or I'll beat
you up, you bastard.
Go ahead. You think you
can beat the monster?
You say that because you
don't know my goblin power.
Oh, really...
I'll cut you down!
Want me to gut you?!
I'll cut you into pieces!
Go! Go! Fight! Fight!
S-Stop it, both of you...
Usopp! Don't just stand there and
watch. Let's stop them already..
Don't be ridiculous!
Don't underestimate me!
You know there's no way I can stop them.
Oh, yeah...
Didn't I tell you to be quiet?!
Mellorine...
J-Just one hit...
For Pete's sake...
Hey, Bellemere-san...
Bellemere-san!
Bellemere-san...
Hm?
Say, where does the wind come from?
From the sea.
Sea?
That's right. The wind born on the sea
brings blessings by blowing
on Cocoyashi Village.
Not just wind. The rain, clouds, rainbows...
Everything comes from the sea.
I see... Say...
then where does the sea come from?
--What?!
--Nami.
Don't give Bellemere-san such a hard time.
But... Nojiko...
Nami, you really are a curious girl.
Nami...!
Nami!
I heard you did it again!
The lady at the bookshop
stormed into the house in a rage.
Now, let's go home. The dinner is ready.
Say, Bellemere-san...
What's beyond that sea?
Who knows?
I don't know what
lies beyond the Grand Line.
Even though you were a marine?
I was, but the sea is too big.
I wanna see... what's beyond the sea...
Nami...
I wonder if I can go beyond that sea...
You're a strong child.
If you really want, you can
go anywhere you want.
Then I've decided!
I'm gonna use my navigation skills
to travel to all the world's oceans
and make a world map of everything I see.
I sure will...!
That's right. I definitely will... some day...
I will complete my own world map.
Hey, Luffy!
Watch!
Whoopie!
Amazing!
--Amazing! Amazing!
--Right?
Geez...!
Ah...
You've been working hard.
Are you done?
No... But what is this?
Hey, what're you guys doing?
Cleaning.
This is pretty fun. Wanna do it, too, Nami?
What's going on? It's noisy.
What?! The Smooth Skin Soap?
Hey, it's dangerous.
It's okay! No problem!
Luffy!
That idiot!
Gum-Gum...!
Bungee... Jump!
Move away!
Watch out, Nami-san!
Are you okay, Nami-san?
Ah!
Ow, ow, ow...
Ahh! My map...
Oh, you were drawing a map?
What? Map?
So that's what your "work" was...
That's right.
It's the only map in the world
that recorded our journey
after entering the Grand Line...
And yet...!
My dream is to complete
my own world map!
Leave!
But...
Just leave...
Nami...!
What?!
I'm sorry...
If "sorry" were enough,
there'd be no need for the Navy!
Now, leave already.
If you don't, you'll be fined 100,000 Berries!
It's your fault.
Why's that?!
--Well, I think so, too.
--I think so, too.
--Seriously, those guys
--What?! You, too?!
--Now, Luffy, cheer up.
--always get in my way...
Hmm...
Hm? Smells like rain...
There's a problem! Luffy! Luffy!
There's a problem! The clouds...!
Spiders have ten legs.
No, they have eight.
Hey, that doesn't matter! Wake up!
--Centipedes have 100 legs...
--Usopp! Sanji!
Wake up! Zoro!
Someone!
There's a problem!
Nami...!
You'll be fined 100,000 Berries!
Wh... What should I do...?
Done!
If I do say so myself, this is perfect!
Am I a genius or what?
What?
Hey, what happened?!
Nami!
Hey! What were you doing?!
Why didn't you tell me
before it got this bad?!
Because... you said we'd
be fined 100,000 Berries...
You dummy...
Hey, you guys! How long are
you gonna keep sleeping?!
Ahh! What the heck is this?!
--It's a tornado! It's a tornado!
--It's obvious!
Luffy! Zoro! Fold the sails!
Okay!
Usopp! Chopper! Secure the
stuff on the deck using ropes!
Got it!
Sanji-kun! Turn to starboard!
Umph!
Point the bow of the ship
away from the tornado,
or we're gonna get swallowed!
Okay!
Hey, hey...
Listen!
If my precious map gets washed
away by waves or something,
you'll all pay...
dearly.
She really is scary...
The atmospheric pressure has risen
and the rain has stopped, too.
Thanks for your work. You can rest now!
Okay!
Well then, I'll go back to work,
so watch the clouds again.
You're not done yet?!
Of course not!
My goal is to draw up the world map.
I've just finished the first one.
The real work starts from here.
She's really going at it...
I like Nami-san that way, too!
I wonder if there'll be a
100,000-Berry fine again...
Probably...
You've been reading all this time?
Now, unfurl the sails!
Full speed ahead!
Yeah!
So, I'll leave the rest to you.
Hey...
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
Hey, do you know about the Navy's curry?
Nope.
It's famous.
I hear that the chef on each ship
competes with all the others.
Oh, yeah? That sounds yummy.
The kid who fell from a Navy ship
earlier says he is a probationary cook.
It reminds me of my time
at the sea restaurant...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Recipe Handed Down!
Sanji, the Iron Man of Curry"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!