Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
Here we go, always, be the best
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed
a pirate alliance with
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped along with the entire island.
I'll pay 100 million berries
for each star rating!
100 million berries?!
On top of that, he put prices on
the heads of Luffy and 11 others,
and now they're being hunted
by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
Is that...
Sugar is awake now!
Oh no!
It sent chills down my spine
when I realized Robin had been
turned into a toy, too, earlier!
I didn't even realize
I had forgotten about her!
If Sugar touches Luffy,
I'll forget about him like that!
Your friend disappears
and you won't even know it!
I can't take it!
I have no option left now!
I'll shoot her from here!
Do you know the position you're in?
Our bond can't be broken
even if anyone tries.
Just remember.
If Luffy ever calls for my help,
no matter where I am in the world,
I'll be there - forget my position!
Dodge, Farul!
Farul!
Stay with me!
What a powerful jaw!
It crushed his head!
Don't die on me, Farul!
Are they invincible?!
Pop Baller!
Oh no! My Yellow Cubs...
Robin-san!
Rebecca, take the key to the Sunflower Field!
I'll be fine!
Cien Fleurs!
Wing!
Robin!
Luffy! Tra-guy-kun!
You guys are here!
She got away...
Well, she's just one little tramp.
I know she can't do anything
even if she can get to the Palace.
Luffy! Tra-guy-kun!
And Soldier-san, too!
Just go now!
To the Sunflower Field on the fourth level!
That's right!
Rebecca's waiting for you!
Just go!
Okay.
"Risking Their Lives!
Luffy is the Trump Card for Victory!"
It's the fourth level! We're here!
Uh-huh! Thank you all!
Thank you, Yellow Cubs!
Thank you!
Robin-san and Bartolomeo-san...
Are they okay?
I know they are!
Usoland's friends are strong!
Yeah! You're right!
Uh-huh!
Rebecca-sama!
We have to go save Princess Mansherry now!
Uh-huh!
Is it okay to leave you here alone?
I'll be fine! Lucy and the
others will come soon!
Go save her!
Okay!
Rebecca-sama, you take care, too!
Uh-huh!
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
Father-sama must be
somewhere on this battlefield, too...
Somebody made it here, huh?
It's you...
Gum-Gum...
--Luffy-senpai, let me take this!
--Crest Head!
Barrier!
Those are balls of explosives!
They'll explode before you deflect them!
Wow! Cool!
Oh no! I don't deserve such praise!
Bartolomeo...
Go!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Whip!
Cool!! I just saw his Second Gear
and Jet Whip up close!
So impressive!
Hey, Straw Hat-ya, just get rid of them
and let's move along already!
You're taking too much time!
Hey, you!
Don't talk to Luffy-senpai like that!
I've got an idea!
Barrier-bility: Stairs!
Awesome!
You saved us a lot of trouble!
Please use it, Luffy-senpai!
Why're you looking the other way?
Thank you, Crest Head!
Th...
...a...
...n...
...k...
...you?!
Thank you! Thank you! Thank you! Thank...
Not at all!
I'm the one who has to thank you
for being born!
All right!
We can go straight to the fourth level this way!
Let's go, Tra-guy!
Go!
Issho-san! Ow! Ow!
No good! We can't get closer
because of the fire!
We can't go around either because
the collapsed buildings are blocking our way!
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
The troublesome guy gained
a troublesome power!
Fire Fist!
Hey you...
What are you trying to do?
I know Navy admirals are much more powerful!
Stop messing around!
You're an odd person.
I thought you wanted to keep us Navy at bay.
How long will you keep up with the act?
Oh boy...
As you can see,
I need people to go easy on me...
I don't discriminate.
You scare me.
You're not known as No.2 of the Revolutionary Army
for nothing, I guess.
But I'm in the position that
requires me to do this.
Please understand.
Gravity Blade!
Raging Tiger!
Horizontal gravity?!
Yeah! This is just what I expected from him!
This jerk! What is he up to?!
It's an all-or-nothing gamble.
I'm determined to bet my life on it.
However...
If you lose your dice,
the game is over before you can even roll.
The Top Executives of our Family are
guarding this plateau...
I didn't think anyone could reach it
but there was a slight chance, so...
...I've been waiting but...
Rebecca!
I can't believe you made it here.
Soldier!
I'm gonna go first!
Oh, wait, Soldier!
Cabbage!
I'll keep them here! Just go, Straw Hat!
My beloved horse was harmed
on this level!
I can't go farther without
vengeance against those jerks!
Go!
Luffy, dodge! It's the bombs!
Let me take care of it!
Why not use your barriers?!
Hey, Bartolomeo!
What were you doing?!
There is a limit on the size of the barrier...
that I can produce at once...
And I used it up on that staircase!
But that's all right!
If it helps Luffy-senpai...
I'm happy to die!
I am!!
You son of a...
I'll fight with you until you're
able to use barriers so hang tough!
These dolls have no delicacy!
Cinco Mano! Spank!
Nico Robin!
I know how you feel...
Rooster-kun.
Our captain is...
...worth risking...
...even our lives!
Luffy is always
the trump card that leads us to victory!
Mil Fleurs! Gigantesco Mano!
--I won't let you lay a finger on Luffy!
--That's right!
I'm coming now!
Wait for me, Mingo!
The Top Executive, Diamante,
launches powerful attacks while
Rebecca struggles desperately to hold on!
But she is finally driven into a corner,
moments from losing her innocent life,
when the legendary, undefeated warrior,
Kyros, shows up at the Sunflower Field!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Tearful Reunion! Rebecca and Kyros!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!