Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I'm a captain at Navy Headquarters!
I will not live on in disgrace!
I'll stop you guys
by slashing you in two!
I can't allow that…
...as our destination lies
beyond where you stand!
Bring it on!
I hate crooked sword attacks!
Right-Angle Flying Bird…
Three-Sword Style…
Bull Demon!
…Bone…
Phoenix!
He discerned it?!
Bold Hooves!
R-Roronoa!
He defeated Ship-Slasher!
To think that he
followed the sea train
from the detached cars
in this storm…
How admirable!
But we can't stop here.
I'm sure your justice is deep, too,
but we also shoulder
all sorts of things.
Hiss! You're the very definition
of "all bark but no bite."
Now, now, now, now!
Aren't you guys being
deceived by that woman, too?!
She's the lowest of the low,
who lived one betrayal after another,
and survived until today
in the underground!
I'll take your life!
Take this!
Decoupage!
If you like,
why don't you add your last
words to them while you're at it, buddy?
Ultimate Hammer!
Hey, where on earth
did you come from?
Yow!
Did you finish taking
care of the ramen guy?
Yeah, I did, just now.
It's suddenly become noisy.
So the soldiers for this escort mission
were annihilated after all, huh?
We didn't expect much, though.
They're the ones who
kidnapped Robin-chan, aren't they?
Be careful.
They use strange martial arts.
Who's this?
He's probably that CP9 newbie
that Corgy was talking about.
If I remember right,
he's a Four Power
Master named Nero or something.
Dammit!
You're gonna get it now!
People call me a fighting genius!
I don't care anymore…
I'm gonna kill you!
Hey, newbie.
Y… You must be Rob Lucci, right?
Sorry that I didn't
introduce myself sooner.
Please wait a moment.
I'll kill him first and…
We're capturing Franky alive.
To think you let your feelings take
control and lost sight of our mission...
Well, forget it.
I'll give you three seconds.
So hurry up and run.
Three…
Run…? From whom?
Two…
What…? Hey!
You're kidding, right?!
One.
Stop it! Don't be foolish!
It's all right! Now
let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through
our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together,
let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail--
let's raise anchor
Cut through
the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey
fraught with injury
but what you cherish most
will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right!
Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up
the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map
leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag--
together, we're one
One Piece
"Scramble over Robin!
A Cunning Plan by Sogeking!!"
I'll give you three seconds.
So hurry up and run.
Three…
Run…? From whom?
Two…
What…? Hey!
You're kidding, right?!
One.
Stop it! Don't be foolish!
Shave!
A person like you who does
everything halfway
is unfit for CP9!
Unless you've mastered all Six Powers,
you aren't superhuman, boy.
Kalifa.
Yes.
Inform our chief later…
...that the newbie was so
weak that he was useless.
Okay.
These guys are supposed
to be working for justice?
Can't tell which side is evil, huh?
Officials from the World
Government sure are ill-mannered.
This is my duty, so…
See?!
My sense of smell
is absolute, Nico Robin!
I want you to take off that cape.
Now! Now! Now!
Dammit! This is it!
W… Wait!
My name is Sogeking.
I'm the man
who hails from the island of snipers.
Soge?
Wait!
You think you can
get away with this?!
That's right!
Don't underestimate the resolution
of a man who is willing to go this far.
L… L… Lucci-san!
I guess I don't have to ask
why you are here, intruder.
Given the way you opened the door,
it doesn't seem like
you have a lot of patience.
Yeah, I'm ill-bred, so…
If this is about Nico Robin…
…give it up.
This is too big of an issue for you
guys to get yourselves involved in.
There are people in the world who
were born under an unlucky star...
People who are better off
dead for everyone's sake.
What are you talking about?
For example…
Suppose there exists a devil that
would burn the world to the ground.
If the person who
can raise this devil
is an innocent girl
who's only eight years old...
…don't you think…
…that someone
should kill
this girl for everyone's sake?
Huh? What's your point?
I'm telling you
that is Nico Robin's life.
She is a real criminal now,
but it started simple like that.
Ever since she can remember,
her existence itself was a sin.
She can make others happy
only by disappearing.
That's the misfortune she carries.
Essentially,
she should've died 20 years ago.
I'm really glad that this
woman will be put to death.
Hey…
Enough of your crap!
You son of a bitch!
Don't say anymore!
However, the Government
will probably spend years...
…squeezing out all
of Nico Robin's knowledge,
experience and intelligence.
How much agony she'll experience
before she dies...
you just watch and--
We're not gonna let that happen!
Hey, hey, wait, Robin!
You shouldn't go that way!
Hey! Seriously! Seriously! Wait!
Hey, I said, wait!
Whoa!
Robin-chan!
Th-This isn't good…
Good! Are you okay?!
Are you hurt?!
Oh, shoot!
When I went to all the trouble
of getting in from outside,
and even brought
that official down!
So that's Nico Robin?
She indeed bears a resemblance to
the picture in the wanted poster.
Let's go back together this time!
I'll bring these guys down
right away, so…
Okay, Robin-chan?!
Usopp!
What're you doing, Robin-chan?!
Ow…
Even if I explain, you guys
just won't get it, will you?
What're you doing, Robin-chan?!
Ow…
Even if I explain, you guys
just won't get it, will you?
Franky-kun!
Detach car #3!
What're we gonna do?!
We're gonna run!
Run?!
Hey, what do you mean?!
You, too, hurry up!
One moment will decide the game!
Don't let Franky get away.
Right.
Sogeking…!
Smoke… Star!
What a petty thing to do!
We got Nico Robin!
Hey!
Let me go!
All right!
Run!
Turn back!
Hey, he said we're turning back.
Oh, yeah?
That's a relief.
Well then, we should get
ready to turn back, huh?
Yeah.
What?!
Whaaat?!
Why?! When we came this far?!
What about Robin!
What about Usopp?!
Hey! What're we gonna do
about them?!
Dinner time?
What's that guy thinking?!
Straw Hat!
Why are we turning back?!
That's right!
Tell us why!
You've got it wrong!
What?
I was telling
that frog that jumped
on the railway to turn back!
Ribbit! Ribbit! Ribbit!
It's Yokozuna!
Yokozuna?
What the heck is that huge frog?!
Watch out!
Step aside, frog!
Ribbit!
We're gonna collide!
All right!
We got Robin back!
At any rate,
that sure surprised me.
To think that we suddenly switched
to a "Running Away" strategy.
A smoke screen is so stupid
that people wouldn't normally
think of using it.
It's best
if we can achieve our goal
without fighting scary guys like them.
But…
...I don't know if things
are gonna be that simple.
Yeah.
Don't let your guard down
until the cars are really far apart.
What the hell…?!
Thorny whips?!
I caught it…
Blueno.
Okay.
Is he gonna use the whips
to cross over?
They pulled us back!
What power!
A smoke screen?
What a worthless thing to do…
I guess it couldn't
have worked after all.
Don't kill any Straw Hats.
That was the condition.
Sogeking!
Ah, yes.
Protect Robin-chan
at all costs, okay?!
Hm…? Yeah!
Sorry, but I'm going to…
…make you let go!
Why is his body so hard?
I told you that they use
strange martial arts, didn't I?
Concasser!
He's got quite a heavy kick.
Iron Body almost got broken down.
Blueno, don't take him lightly.
He doesn't have a bounty on him,
but he's one of their main forces.
You just noticed that,
you damn jerks?
Whoa, R-Robin!
Hey, hold on a sec!
Ow… Wh-What're you doing?
Ocho Fleurs!
Clutch!
Long-nose!
Hey! Why, Robin-chan?!
How many times
do I have to tell you?!
Leave me alone!
Can't be…
Hey, pay attention.
Eyebrows!
Geez… Why are all of you
being so stubborn
even towards your friends?!
This is…
a perfect chance to run, right?!
Franky!
That was uncalled for.
Didn't expect that, did you?
Why are you taking sides
with them in the first place?
I just can't bear to watch
those guys act like that.
Not when there's a team that couldn't
go back even if they wanted to!
I wonder who you're talking about.
Yow!
You guys, don't worry about me!
I've got a plan!
Once you've joined up with Straw Hat,
get back to town somehow!
Franky!
Wait!
I won't run away!
Wait, Robin-chan.
Why are you acting
like that at this point?
We came to rescue you
knowing all the circumstances!
If we just do something about the
Government's attack, Buster Call,
there shouldn't be a reason that
you have to obey them, right?!
That Buster Call is…
…indeed the problem.
Wha…
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross
the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring
than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end,
we can all surely smile
Stop it! Let Robin-chan go!
Robin-chan!
Why aren't you saying anything?!
Robin, you're still hiding
something, aren't you?
That's okay.
But
a pirate cannot leave their group
without their captain's permission.
So, Robin…
believe in Luffy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Judicial Island!
Full View of Enies Lobby!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!