Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in
which a winner will get the Flare-Flare Fruit
as the prize - and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law who's
been captured by Doflamingo.
--Let's make our way up!
--How we go up doesn't matter, right?!
What're you up to?!
That must be it!
Where did they go?!
Boy! We made it straight to our destination!
Meanwhile, Usopp and Robin put Operation SOP
into action along with the Tontattas. However...
Are you still going on with this?
Making Sugar eat
this clump of Tatababasco Sauce is...
...our responsibility!
Doce Fleurs!
Do it now!
Put the Tatababasco grape in her mouth!
That's it!
Stop wasting your time!
"A Liar!
Usoland on the Run!"
What the hell is going on?!
They say there are some intruders.
But we have Trebol-sama on our side!
I feel sorry for them
because no one can get away from him!
How many times do they have to challenge me?!
I dropped my guard!
I've been turned into a toy!
Everybody must've forgotten about me.
Usopp!
Where did he go?!
Please, Usopp!
All I have is you!
Change me back into a human!
THE TOY HOUSE
Now is our chance! Shoot him dead!
Hey, wait a second! What are you doing?!
He's mine to kill!
Give yourself up, Franky, without resistance!
Shut up...
Shut the hell up!
I intend to keep wrecking the place for no reason!
Prepare for it!
What?!
If I go underground with these guys chasing me,
it's not gonna help the Little People!
I'll leave Operation SOP up to you, guys!
Bring it on!
I'll take care of business here!
I'm counting on you, Usoland!
THE ROYAL PALACE 2ND FLOOR
- THE SUIT CHAMBER
Hey! How long do I have to wait like this?!
What's wrong? You look pale.
The Little People of the Tontatta
have been beaten up by Trebol,
a top executive of the Family!
What?!
My friend should be with them!
Yes, there is he.
The one with a long nose...
Usoland!
But he's...
Then, let's wait!
As long as he's there, it's gonna be fine!
I'm sure Usopp will take care of it!
They were trying so hard to
make me eat this.
It must be poison.
Smells awful.
We can't do anything anymore...
Don't worry!
If something goes wrong,
I'll make everything right for you!
Usoland...
I can't believe them!
Move!
Where're you going, buddy?!
Yes! I escaped!
Forgive me, Tontattas!
Usopp! Where are you?!
Where did you go?!
Oh yeah! I can write a picture book
to tell future generations how brave you were!
"The Honest Tontattas"!
The title sounds great!
I need to survive!
It's Franky's fault!
Why hasn't he come to help?!
I'm not gonna die for some stupid lie that I'm a hero! No way!
OK, I escaped from them
but the problem is how to get myself out of here!
I don't think I can get out through
that tunnel we came in through by myself!
Oh yeah! He said there is a lift!
Hey, all of you out there!
Hey, hey!
You didn't stop working, did you?
It's not a show, you fools!
Oh no!
Get back to work!
Keep moving those boxes!
Don't take a break!
Hurry up, you idiots!
Somebody's trying to
fight the Don Quixote Family!
This is the first time
since I became a toy eight years ago!
Whoever it is, please bring down this place!
A show?! I've had enough of it!
What should we do with them?
...so...
...la...
Hey, hey! Are they saying something?
--...so...
--...la...
...d!
...la...d.
...sola...nd.
Uso...la...
U-Usola...nd.
Dammit! Where is the lift?!
Uso...land.
Usolan...d.
Usoland.
"Usoland"?
I know someone is helping you - who is it?
You mean Usoland?
The name he said earlier.
Run! Run!
Usoland...
Usoland!
--Usoland!
--Oh, everybody!
Usoland!
--Usoland!
--Uso...
Usoland!!
Usoland?
Whoa, whoa! Don't call my name!
Usoland? Hey, who is that?
It's the name of their associate he mentioned earlier.
You asked him.
Idiot. Drop dead.
I'm not gonna die, you little shit!
Drop dead.
Drop...
Usoland is our hero!
H-H-Hero?
He will save you guys, then?
That's right!
Not just us!
He said he will make everything right!
The toys who are being forced to work here, day after day.
--What?
--Is he talking about us?
Our friends who are enslaved in the factory.
The toys who look to be
walking down the street happily
but never stop crying inside.
The poor Big Humans who don't even know...
...that they've lost their loved ones.
Usoland will save them all!
He's the legendary hero!
Is that all you have to say?
What?!
No, I don't wanna be a hero! Hell no!
You guys are so pathetic! That's all lies!
What?!
You guys got fooled again!
Y-You really think so?!
He's not coming to help you
even though you're all hurt so bad!
That says it all, doesn't it?
Where's the hero?
So, where?
But he said it himself!
I'm sure he's laughing at you fools somewhere now!
Since you guys are so honest,
I bet you're not making it up and
there was actually somebody who told you
that he'd make everything right.
But he just chickened out when the need arose.
So you'd better abandon your hope!
I'm sorry but he's kind of right!
You'd better run, too, guys! Good luck!
N-No...
Shut up...
Shut up!
Usoland doesn't lie!
Usoland said...
I am a descendent of Noland!
Cool!!
Usoland said he will save us
no matter what happens to us!
That's what he told us!
Yeah!
That's right!
--That's right!
That's what he said!
He promised us!
The hero would never lie to us!
Stop insulting Usoland or...
...we'll make you pay for it!
You two had better prepare for it!
Once Usoland gets here, you guys will...
Pigya!
"Pigya"? How funny!
The Tontattas' death-cry is...
"Pigya"!
Leo!
--Leo!
Yeah! Leo is right!
Operation SOP will be okay!
Usoland will...
Usoland will pull it off for sure!
Pigya!
That's right!
It's you two who are pathetic!
Usoland will...
Pigya!
Just give it up already!
When we're in danger, the hero will...
Pigya!
Then, call the hero now!
Your hero!
Whoa! Something horrible is happening...
Stop...
Stop!
Stop!!
Enough already, you bastards!
U-Usoland!
Usoland!
Uso...land!
Usopp! I'm glad he's here!
You guys! How can you trust me that much?!
You little fools!
What?!
They're right! It was all lies!
I'm not the legendary hero
and my name is not Usoland!
What?!
I'm the deadly sniper of the Straw Hats!
My name is Usopp!
I'm a pirate!
--O-Of the Straw Hats?!
--What is he doing here?!
Why...
Why are you saying that?!
You may be a pirate
but you're a hero, aren't you?!
I said I'm not! A pirate is a pirate!
Don't make me repeat myself!
I was fooling you guys!
But you never stop believing in me!
So you have...
...taken the trouble to come and
tell them that you were lying?
Yeah. Otherwise these fools will wait for me until they die!
Then I won't be able to sleep at night so instead,
I wanna thank them for believing in a guy like me
and I plan to sacrifice myself for them because...
...that's way cooler, isn't it?!
What?
My name is Usopp!
Remember my name, Tontattas!
If I die,
build a statue of me beside Noland's!
I'm gonna become your legendary hero now!
Usopp!
Usopp of the Straw Hats?!
Is he gonna save all of us?!
You're desperate!
I'll take my chances!
Kill him.
All right!
Special Attack: Green Star - Platanus...
...Shuriken!
How do you like that, monster?!
I'm the legendary hero
and the sniper of the Straw Hats,
Captain Usopp!
Usoland!
No, Usopp!
No, I said Usopp!!
The legendary hero...
Usoland!!
Back in old days in Dressrosa,
there was a brutal man who people feared as a beast!
His name was Kyros!
When King Riku came face-to-face with this
wild man, a miraculous story of a legendary warrior began!
On the next episode of One Piece!
A Fateful Encounter! Kyros and King Riku!
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!