Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Luffy...
"Luffy in Big Trouble!
Fishmen vs. the Luffy Pirates"
What the...?
Which one of you is Arlong?!
Arlong?
My name happens to be Arlong...
I'm Luffy.
Luffy?
So, what are you?
A pirate!
That's him! He's here!
The guy who likes taking walks!
Hold it, you.
Where do you think you're goin'?!
You need to run things
by us first, kiddo.
Yeah!
If you don't stop...
Move!
What does a pirate want with me?
Who the hell are you?
Luffy... Help me...
Don't make our navigator cry!
Why, you...
How dare you insult Arlong-san?!
Butt out, small fries!
Yeesh. You just had to
run on ahead by yourself...
It's not like I'd lose on my own.
Idiot! When did I say
I was worried about you?!
I just don't want you
hogging all the prey!
Oh!
I-I don't mind if you
hog them all, though!
You sure got some guts.
That's him! He's the
unknown swordsman!
It's Roronoa Zoro.
Yeah? Yeah, I thought so!
He tricked me!
Look, sine, and hinker...
No! Hook, line, and sinker... right?
Look! It's Long-nose!
D-Didn't Nami kill him?!
The bastard's alive. Which means...
I knew it.
The girl was a traitor,
just as I suspected!
Hey! Who are those guys?!
Hold it!
He sent Arlong flying!
Unbelievable!
No ordinary human could do that!
They're...
Do you still want to
try to break in now?
If you go, you'll wind up
putting a damper on this fight.
You'll only get in their way!
B-But... why are they fighting?
What reason do they have to fight?!
Reason to fight?
Big Sis Nami was crying!
Do they need any more reason than that
to put their lives on the line?
A pirate, huh? I see...
So that's what you guys' deal is.
You were after Nami
from the very start.
But...
What can you four inferior
creatures possibly do?!
Fool! You're not worth Arlong's time!
He'll be more than enough!
No!
It's coming!
What the... What the...
What's going on?!
The whole lot of you
will be food for him!
Come out, Momoo!
A-A monster!
It's the Grand Line monster that
destroyed the town of Gosa!
It's here!
T-That's...
...the sea cow, Momoo!
Oh, it's him?
He's a friend of the fishmen?
Wait! Momoo! Where are you going?!
Hey! Stop! Get back here! Momoo!
Momoo. What are you doing?
Though, if you wanna
run away, I won't stop you.
Understand, Momoo?
It's coming! It's coming!
Alright!
Follow after Momoo!
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I'll do it! This is a waste of time!
What's he planning now?!
I don't get a very good
feeling about this...
His arms stretched!
He has a Devil Fruit power?!
What?!
Who cares?
Go!
Whoa! Run!
What? What's he doing?!
I dunno, but it doesn't look good!
Gum-Gum...
...Pinwheel!
I didn't come here
to take on these guys!
The one I wanna beat up...
...is you!
That's perfect, then.
I was just thinking of killing you now.
That was dangerous, you!
Are you trying to kill us, too?!
Huh?
What destructive power...
I can't believe a human exists
who can throw that giant beast!
Is this battle of this world?
Huh?
Huh? Huh? Huh? Huh?
What are you doing?!
Huh?
How dare you hurt our brothers?!
It would seem we need to fight, too.
Looks like we need to teach them
the differences between our species.
The main forces finally show up, huh?
Arlong-san. Please stay there quietly.
If you go on a mad rampage,
you'll tear all of Arlong Park into pieces.
We'll take care of these guys!
Yeah. Do as you wish.
Yikes!
Hey. Hey, there. There's something I...
That octopus is up to something.
Octopus is best with
a little salt and sliced up.
Add some olive oil and paprika
and it's a perfect snack while drinking.
Hey, I'm kind of in trouble. Hear me out.
Take this! Zero vision!
Hachi Ink Jet!
You idiot! Why didn't you dodge?!
I can't see!
Now to finish you off!
Hey, Luffy! Run!
Yeah, that's the problem.
I can't seem to move!
Huh?!
M-My feet are stuck!
You're the one who
stuck them in the ground!
Why does he have to be so--
Hachi Ink Jet on the Rocks!
What a pain.
Sanji! Great! Great!
Seems I've wound up following
one hell of an idiot of a captain.
Agreed.
He's... awesome!
But he's 100 times better than
a damn gang that'd hurt a lady.
Lady?
To think you'd bust in here
just for that one lousy girl.
You really know how to make us laugh!
Lousy girl?
Just try and insult
Nami-san one more time.
I'll use a buttered frying pan to
turn you into meuniere, Fish Man!
You seem somewhat
skilled for a human.
Any sort of chivalry from a
pirate is obviously half-hearted.
Go ahead and see if my
chivalry is half-hearted or not.
I was raised by an unbeatable
pirate for half my life.
It appears you don't know the
true level of the fishman species.
Oof! Oof!
They're still really stuck.
Still?! They're still stuck?!
Yep, they're still stuck.
I get the feeling just pulling
me won't get them unstuck.
Are you even trying?! Are you
even trying to pull your legs out?!
What're they playing
around in Arlong Park for?
I'll kill them!
Hey, you! Get unstuck already!
Get back here!
Hey, octopus.
They're busy right now.
I'll take you on.
Roronoa Zoro! Yeah! I forgot!
How dare you trick me!
Yeah! And you cut down
tons of my brothers!
I'm not interested in these old stories.
It doesn't matter what reasons
you have for wanting to kill me.
The situation's changed now!
You're not trying to destroy us.
We're trying to destroy you!
A-Alright, Zoro!
That octopus is all yours! Nice!
Luffy!
I'm back...
Why, you...
My bad...
Seems you really do
want me to kill you.
Wasn't that the guy
who saved Gen-san?
You're the people
from Cocoyashi Village!
Oh?
Judging from the fact that you have
weapons, I take it this is a rebellion?
Then you're all--
Exploding Star!
Big Bro Usopp!
You're dealing with me!
If you wanna die that badly,
I'll get rid of you right now!
Just who is that lad?
He's brave one minute,
then runs away the next.
He's a baffling man...
Get back here, Nose!
Well, you got a big mouth!
Why are these people pirates?!
You're all pathetic. Move.
I'm sick of watching this.
Arlong-san! We asked you
not to go on a rampage!
I won't. I just thought up a fun game.
Game?
I'm going to beat you up!
Do you really think you can beat us?
So what if we do?
We do, stupid-head! Let go!
Sounds like he has something to say.
What the... What the...
People with Devil Fruit
powers can't swim!
Though, even people without
powers would sink in this situation!
He's gonna throw him into the sea?!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Oww!
Fool.
Darn you!
How pointless.
Luffy!
Damn you!
I'm coming to save...
Idiot! Don't get worked up!
They want us to go in the water!
The fishmen'd obviously have
the advantage in an underwater fight!
There's only one way to save Luffy!
Take these guys down in an
instant, then go into the water?
Let's do it! There's no time!
Yeah!
Just how many seconds
will Rubber Man hold out?
Oh, so that's the game?
I see.
You can have the fish.
You can cut and trim the octopus.
This is bad... I'm out of strength...
What do we do?!
He can't help himself now!
Big Bro Luffy's going to die!
To think they can't
even breathe underwater...
Humans are utterly pitiful creatures!
Bring it on! I challenge you, Octo-Man!
Game! Game!
I'll take care of you in five seconds!
No, three seconds!
Don't be in such a rush.
No matter what happens, none of
you have any hope of surviving!
Hachi Ink Jet!
Hang on, Luffy!
I-I'm gonna be killed!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
I-I can't breathe!
You damn octopus!
I don't care about you!
I gotta hurry and save Luffy!
Hey! Are the wounds
you got from Hawk-Eye...
Shut up! I can't afford to faint here!
Wait, is running all I do?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Submerged!
Zoro vs. Hatchan the Octopus"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!