Edited at https://subtitletools.com
So, you guys stay and wait
on the sea for five minutes
and charge in to the main island in
Rocketman through the main gate.
We'll go in first and break open the
main gate and the main island front gate
so that the train can pass through.
We'd like you guys to go after only CP9,
avoiding unnecessary battles.
Okay, got it.
Oof!
What?!
Why the hell is he doing things on his own?!
That man doesn't have a
clue about the plan at all!
How dare you, pirate?!
I'm in a hurry.
More people are coming later, so... See ya!
Don't let them open it! Defend it at all costs!
Move! You're in our way!
Rush in!
We broke through the first gate, the main gate!
Hey, Sogeking.
Hey!
Hey, that hurt!
About how to use this takt for chilled air...
Hm? Let me see...
Do not ask me!
I wonder... if everyone is okay.
Just sit and wait patiently, Chopper.
It's bad enough our captain has no patience.
"Kashii
'Main Island Front Gate'
Gatekeeper, Enies Lobby"
"Oimo
'Main Island Front Gate'
Gatekeeper, Enies Lobby"
I didn't get enough sleep.
I'm gonna get rid of them
quickly and go back to bed.
Me, too.
G-G-Giants!
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
How many friends did you bring?
There are 10,000 soldiers in Enies Lobby!
Yeah, I'm by myself.
Get out of my way!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Main Island Front Gate"
"Main Gate"
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
"Battle against Giants!
Open the Second Gate!"
We're not gonna let you through this gate!
If you don't give up and go back,
we're gonna stomp on you!
Don't flinch! Big Bro Franky is
on the other side of that gate!
Show them a fight worthy of
Bro's name, Franky Family!
Don't give in! Open the path for Rocketman!
Break open the doors!
We're not gonna let even
an ant pass through this gate!
--Destroyers!
--Everyone...!
Dammit! How dare you bring down
some of our strongest forces?!
Go!
What the...?!
--Zambai!
--Kiwi! Mozu!
Galley-La!
Sorry that we're late!
It took longer than I thought to switch
Sodom and Gomorrah to land mode!
Zambai! The Destroyers are...
I know.
We have no time to patch them up right now.
In order to get to where Bro is,
we have to open this gate at any cost!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Let's make him lose his balance, Mozu!
Roger, Kiwi!
Hull... Dismantler Slash!
Rope Action...
...Timber Hitch Tug!
Ow...! Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Kashii!
Tilestone!
Yeah!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
Trunnel Lock!
Work completed!
You bastards...!
I'm gonna crush you!
Ahhh! Kashii!
All right!
How dare you...?!
Guys! Let's take the other one down!
Yeah!
So what's the current status?
Sir. Kashii and Oimo should be
dealing with them right now
in front of the main island front gate.
So I don't think there'll be any issues.
I see. So did you capture Straw Hat,
the one who infiltrated the main island?
Well... Er...
...this is just an estimate,
but it's about four hundred...
Four hundred? What're you talking about?
Our casualties, sir!
Huh?! Our casualties?!
Are you saying that four hundred
guards have been taken out?!
It looks like there are a hundred more down...
Well, I'm sorry. I need to correct the number.
Obviously! Our guards
are not trash or anything.
I'll be damned if that
many have been taken out!
If there are casualties,
make sure you get the details right!
Er... well then, here is the report.
The current casualties we
have here are five... Gahh!
Five are down?! So it was
actually just five guards?!
Geez... You can't even make a report properly?
Five... hundred guards...
Looks like Straw Hat Luffy isn't fighting;
he's just running around the island.
Well, that's just natural. No one is
stupid enough to fight that many guards.
It's just a matter of time before he's captured.
Welcome back, sirs and madam.
Chief, Mr. Lucci and the others are here.
So they're back?
Show them in here.
It's been a while, Chief.
Yeah...
Cutty Flam, the criminal who is responsible
for assaulting Government officials
in Water Seven eight years ago...
Nico Robin, the criminal who
was involved in the incident
where Navy battleships were
attacked in Ohara in the West Blue...
We've completed the escort
of these two without a hitch.
They're both behind those doors.
Welcome back! Lucci, Kaku, Blueno, and Kalifa!
That's sexual harassment.
Just calling your name is?!
Long time no see, Lucci.
It appears that your audacity
has increased considerably.
It appears that your stupidity has as well, Jabra.
What'd you say?
Stop it, both of you. We just got back.
Yoyoi! He's right. Stop it, you two.
We have been reunited after five years!
Chapapa...
Chapa...
Cha... pa...
Ow...
I thought you'd get on it right away, Fukurou.
Six Powers Skill, Competition!
Suppose an armed guard's
strength is Power Level 10.
"Power Level 10"
Your power levels are...
I'm gonna reveal them.
I'm gonna reveal your strength.
First, Kalifa. She is Power Level 630.
Blueno is Power Level 820.
Kaku is Power Level 2,200.
Lucci is...
...Power Level 4,000!
4,000?! Hey, did you measure it properly?!
I've never heard of such a high Power Level!
That was accurate! They've all
gotten stronger! Chapapa!
Since I measured Jabra and
Kumadori's too, I know who's stronger!
Hey! Objection, Fukurou!
Setting Lucci aside, what's the deal
with me being weaker than even Kaku?!
Chapapa!
Kaku has gotten stronger, too!
Hey, don't be so sure of yourself, Kaku!
"Competition" is a technique that just
measures one's martial arts ability.
In real battles, my Devil Fruit
powers are added to my abilities.
Just don't forget that you can't defeat me.
Think whatever you like. I'm not
interested in things like that.
That's right. Don't listen to a stray dog.
A stray dog, Lucci?! You damn goblin cat!
Hey, stop it, both of you!
At any rate, Jabra is lashing
out at us quite a bit, isn't he?
All the guards on the island
are talking about Jabra getting rejected
by the waitress Gatherine yesterday.
Oh, that's why.
H-Hey, hold on a sec! Why does
everyone know about that?!
I told the guards on the
main island about it. Chapapa!
So you're the one?!
"Gatherine"
Geez...
This is all because you started
right in on that stupid ranking stuff.
Having mastered the Six Powers,
you all have far surpassed average people.
Power Level 500 would be enough for
you to be called superhuman, right?
Chief is Power Level 9,
less than one guard. Chapapa.
Don't say that! It's okay because
I'm your Commander in Chief!
Besides, I have a highly valued sword, right?!
I've always known that you're weak, Chief.
H-H-Hey, you shouldn't be so blunt, Kalifa.
That's sexual harassment.
What?! Because I responded to your comment?!
Chief...
Wh... What is it?
That's sexual harassment!
You mean my existence?!
Yoyoi! Kalifa! How rude of you!
Chief! I will... I will take
responsibility by committing hara-kiri!
Hara-kiri! Iron Body!
How regrettable...! I can't die.
I said just die already, you jerk!
Could it be that it was you, Mom,
up in heaven, who made me stay alive?!
Is that right?
I see... So your mother was...
Jabra, so you understand how I feel?
Yeah, especially since I got rejected recently,
I understand well how someone
who lost their loved one feels.
Mom!
Gatherine! Am I not good enough for you?!
Chief.
What? Wh-What is it?
Looks like the short play is... over.
O-Oh, okay.
Anyway, you've done a great
job over the past five years.
To think that you caught not only Nico Robin,
but you were even able to capture
that annoying Cutty Flam...
Well done!
Once the good news gets out,
the entire world will praise your efforts.
Can you guys tell how proud I am
as your Commander in Chief?
Oh, that's right... This isn't really a
reward for your efforts or anything,
but I do have something I wanna give you.
Well, I'll do that later.
So, in any case, let me meet...
...the "hope" of the entire world!
Now, guys! It's time!
Let's go, shall we?
They should've opened those two gates by now.
Charge ahead! Charge ahead!
Samurai-man! Take care of the iron fence!
Leave it to me.
Ouch!
Hurry up! We don't have much time left!
Hurry up and open the gate!
Don't flinch! Go!
Where am I?!
This street is hard to walk on!
Whoa! Ow!
Just wait, you darn Robin!
Don't think that you can leave
the Straw Hats so easily!
He came out!
Gum-Gum...
Capture him!
...Yo-Yo!
The Commander in Chief wants
to see you. Both of you, go inside.
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Are you guys all ready?!
We're gonna charge into Enies Lobby!
We're changing our plan.
They closed the main gate.
What?! What're we gonna do?!
Unless we do something,
we're gonna crash into the gate!
Hey, do something!
No need to worry. There's a way.
--That's our Zoro!
--Just leave it to... luck.
So it's up to luck?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Find A Way Out! Rocketman Takes Flight!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!