Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards have invaded to
the plaza to make it to the scaffold!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
with the Whitebeards' assistance,
Luffy ran on the path that Inazuma
created and finally made it to Ace!
I'm a remnant from the old times!
There is no ship that can
bear me in the new era!
Let's get it over with!
"The Power That Can Burn Even
Fire! Akainu's Ruthless Pursuit!"
--Marineford is in danger!
--Stop Whitebeard!
ABSOLUTE JUSTICE
He's willing to destroy the whole island!
Pops!
I don't wanna leave you!
You gotta come with us!
Pops!
Do you disobey your Captain's order?!
Why don't you just go, fools?!
Pops!
Now is our chance! Kill
Whitebeard! He's dying already!
Pops!
Hurry up! Let's do as Pops said!
You don't mind leaving Pops behind?!
Yeah, how dare you!
Stupid! No one wants to leave him alone!
Then...
Grumbling about it at a time
like this is the same as trampling
on Pops' determination!
Can't you understand?!
Pops!
Hurry and get ready to sail out!
Ace!
We're gonna leave soon! Come on now!
Commander Marco, let's go!
Pops...
--You messed with us!
--Die!
W-Wait! All I want is to get away!
I have no intention to fight...
W-What?!
My wax is as strong as steel!
There's no way that a
normal sword can cut it!
He's also a Devil Fruit eater!
No wonder!
He's strong enough to try to protect
"Fire Fist" even at Fleet Admiral Sengoku's elbow!
No no, don't overestimate me
like that! I'm not a big deal...
Oh no!
Damn Whitebeard!
I can't believe he still has that much
power after getting wounded so badly!
Since he isn't concerned about
"Fire Fist" Ace anymore...
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
It's clear his intention is to
sink Marineford into the ocean.
Along with himself!
Vice Admiral Garp! You're alive!
He wants to change the era?
Yeah, the time is right.
What happened to Whitebeard?!
His allies who have been
sold out are all dead now?!
Is the connection still out?!
How long should we wait?!
Damn! We couldn't see the whole picture
because Buggy the Clown stood in our way!
The guy over there must be...!
The great pirate--Captain Buggy the Clown?!
Yes, that's who I am indeed!
What did he want to say?!
If nothing is done, I can't report
anything to the head office!
What's going on at Marineford now?!
What?!
The Transponder Snail hasn't come out yet?!
Damn! Captain Buggy is about to beat
Whitebeard - it's no time for this!
Don't say it as if it's so easy!
He's dying but he still has boundless
power - didn't they see it?!
Why did I even say that I'm gonna beat
that man?! I really screwed this up!
I can't do it! It's impossible!
What?! We gotta broadcast Captain
Buggy's big moment all over the world!
Get it out at any cost!
--Come out now!
--Or we're gonna burn you out of it!
No, we gotta soak it into water!
--Let's do that!
--Come on!
--Stop it, fools!
--Huh?
It's not like he volunteered
to be a slave for the Navy.
But he got beaten up in the
battlefield like this.
Don't you feel sorry for him?
Just let him go, okay?
Then we gotta cancel "Captain
Buggy's beating beard
and broadcast it live to the world" plan?!
No way! Even you want to
pull out from Marineford?!
I'm disappointed in you, Captain Buggy!
Oh no!
When it comes down to it,
they're all strong guys who've
been locked up in Impel Down!
I better not make enemies of them!
The Transponder Snail came out voluntarily!
Oh, he's...
...crying!
Oh yeah! He came out because he was
touched by Captain Buggy's kindness!
Captain Buggy can even win
the hearts of the Snails!
He's amazing as we thought!
That is the man who will conquer
the world - he's our Captain Buggy!
D-Damn bastard! Why didn't
he just stay inside?!
Now there's no way that I can back out!
Alright, let's begin!
Captain Buggy, make a declaration
to conquer the world now!
--It's your moment!
--Smoke: good, lighting: good!
Stand by!
Oh no, I mean... Dammit!
This leaves me one choice!
Alright, shoot my bravery!
Capture the moment that I kill Whitebeard!
--Hey, look!
--The picture's back!
But I can't see what's going
on because of the smoke!
Is the Navy losing?! What
happened to Whitebeard and Ace?!
--Um, well...
--Transponder Snail, go lower!
Hi, everyone! I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
You again?!
Get to the sea now!
We who remain have to go back
to the New World safely!
Don't let them get away!
Kill as many as you can!
I'm the only one that you
ought to worry about!
Commander Jozu!
Looks like he's badly
injured but he'll make it!
Captain gave us an order! Come with us!
Brenheim! You gotta carry Jozu!
Straw boy! Why are you standing around?!
Ace, let's go! The old man
has made up his mind...
I know! And it won't be in vain!
Back off, you bastards!
We don't need words now.
Just tell me one thing.
Are you happy to have me as your father?
Still some fight left in you?
You are too valuable to let die now, boy.
If you still wanna run wild, run as wild
as you want on the sea under my name.
Become my son!
Of course I am!
Wh-What was that?!
--The scaffold was destroyed!
--So was the Navy HQ!
Did Ace get executed?! What's going on?!
Move the camera to Whitebeard!
I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
The great pirate--Captain Buggy the Clown!
Is it true that you're
gonna beat Whitebeard?!
And with his head in your hand,
you're willing to become
one of The Four Emperors?!
I'm Buggy and I'm a legend!
You're just repeating that!
Say something forward-looking!
Let's do it again!
Enough with Buggy! Show us
Marineford as it stands!
Oh yeah!
You're not what we're interested in!
No, I mean... I just wanna
do something flashy...
What are you doing?!
Run! Run to the ship!
--Ace-san, Luffy-kun, get in front of me!
--Jimbei!
They want to get you two!
But what the good old man wants
is as many survivors as possible!
Good old man!
We've stolen a Navy ship! Get on board quick!
Do they really think that they can
get away?! How simple they are!
Admiral Sakazuki!
You guys, move aside a little bit!
You two, just keep going
until you get to the ship!
As soon as you rescue
"Fire Fist" Ace, you run!
The Whitebeards must be a group of cowards!
What?!
He's trying to stir you up obviously!
If you stop, you're playing into his hands!
Well your captain is that guy
so you can't help it, can you?
Because after all, Whitebeard is just a...
...loser from the old times!
Ace!
A loser?
Take back what you just said!
Hey, don't, Ace! Don't stop!
Just let him say whatever he wants!
He mocked Pops!
Ace!
Did you say "take it back?"
Not in a million years! I'll tell you why.
Your father Gold Roger
conquered the Grand Line
and opened the door to the new era called
the Great Pirate Era by sacrificing himself.
As a Navy admiral, it's
not my place to say so,
but he was true to his name:
the King of the Pirates!
In contrast, what has Whitebeard done?
I wonder if he really had
the intention to fight .
I assume that he established
a large family someplace
and was satisfied being a
big fish in a little barrel.
There are some fools in the world
who'd say that his name is
keeping peace on various islands
but if you ask me, he's just keeping
lightweights in fear of him
and he thinks that he's a
hero which makes me laugh!
When Roger was alive,
Whitebeard had second billing
and even after Roger's death,
he couldn't become a King.
That means he'll never better Roger
and he'll be a loser forever!
That's who Whitebeard
is and that's the truth.
He's a poor man when you think about it.
He gathered some punks who call him Pops
and roamed around the sea
with his fake family.
Stop it.
And although he reigned the sea for years,
he couldn't become a King and gained nothing
and at the end, he was stabbed by a fool,
one of his sons who fell for my line
and he will die to protect that son.
Don't you think that his life is so empty?
Stop it!
Don't do it, Ace, come back!
Ace!
Pops gave us a place to live!
You can't understand his greatness!
People don't deserve to live
if they can't live justly!
Punks like you guys don't
deserve a place to live!
Stop it!
Whitebeard will die as a loser! It's
fitting for a big fish in a little barrel!
Whitebeard is a great pirate
who shaped this era!
Don't make fun of the man who saved me!
Don't do it, Ace!
The name of this era should be "Whitebeard!"
Both Whitebeard and you
guys who call him Pops
are the same after all--losers!
Ace has been burned!
Are you careless because you
ate a Logia type fruit which
is the most powerful of all?
You're just fire but my
magma can even burn fire!
My power is far stronger than yours.
Ace!
Hey, Luffy-kun, you should not fight anymore!
Ace's Vivre Card!
Gold Roger the King of the Pirates,
Dragon--the revolutionary.
I was amazed to hear that sons
of those two are step brothers.
You two have bad blood in your veins.
I don't care if the others get
away as long as I get you two!
Watch what I do.
Wait!
Luffy!
This is certainly a Vivre Card.
But I haven't told you that this card
also tells you how much
vital energy the owner has.
This card belongs to someone
who you care for, right?
Yeah, it's my brother's!
Hold onto it, always.
That paper will lead us to one another.
Ace is pierced by Akainu's
fist while protecting Luffy.
Jimbei and the Whitebeard
Pirates try to save him,
but Ace, realizing he is about to die,
finds the voice to convey his feelings
to his friends one last time.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Looking for the Answer! Fire Fist Ace
Dies on the Battlefield!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!