Edited at https://subtitletools.com
To think that you left the friends
you traveled together with
all the way from the East Blue, for the ship...
What are you guys crying for?
You dummy! We're not crying, you dummy!
But it's true that I was moved by your
protecting this ship all by yourself
while all those things were happening!
We're not crying! None of us are crying!
What the heck is their problem?
Anyway, now you know that those guys
and I are no longer friends, right?!
I'll...
I'll sing about your hardships!
The song title is, "Severed Friendship!
Northern Wind Chop!"
Yay! Bro!
Are you making fun of me?!
Bro!
Help...
I'll say hello to "Bro" for you.
We now know the location.
Let's go.
Mister, I made some tea.
Why don't you take a break?
Hm? Oh, thanks. I'll have some
once I finish fixing this spot.
Ouch!
So, brother...
Hm?
I'm gonna get to the main issue.
What're you gonna do after you fix that ship?
What am I gonna do?
Of course, I'll go on an
adventure with her again,
and someday we'll go back
to our home, the East Blue!
It's not like we went around the world,
but this is a ship that went to the Grand Line.
It'll be good enough to
call it a triumphant return.
I'll hold my head up and--
No, you won't be able to go back...
...to the East Blue.
To begin with, it's too far.
Bro?
When we pulled up the ship earlier,
I was observing her very carefully.
Stop it, you bastards! What're you
gonna do with the Merry?!
Take off the ropes! Let the ship down!
If you do something to the Merry,
my 8,000 men will teach you a lesson!
Hey, are you listening, you bikini jerk?!
If you underestimate me, you'll regret it!
I'm Captain Usopp, the king of
the East Blue who is feared by all!
--Shut up.
--Ow, ow, ow...
Don't pinch me.
Be quiet.
Shut up! Ouch!
Sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
That ship is at the end of her life.
The assessment by Galley-La is correct.
As someone who's in the demolition business,
I suggest you demolish her.
What? That's ridiculous!
I'll help you demolish your ship!
What?! What're you saying, you jerk?!
Wait! What're you doing?! Stop right there!
Bro!
I'm just saying I'll help you demolish that ship.
Don't be ridiculous! I won't allow that!
The Merry is my ship!
No...! She's...
...no longer a ship.
What?
What'd you say?!
I asked you earlier what you were gonna
do after you fixed this ship, didn't I?
If you were going to offer your
life to the sea with this ship,
I wouldn't have said anything.
But... you said that you wanted to
go back to the East Blue on this ship.
So I'm trying to stop you... brother.
This ship... can no longer
even reach the next shore.
Listen. Ships are born with a promise
to carry you across the sea
from one shore to another.
In other words, once a ship can
no longer carry you to shore...
Hey!
Stop it!
Once she can't carry you to shore...
...she's no longer a ship!
Bro!
Stop it!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"The Man Who Is Loved Even
by His Ship! Usopp's Tears!"
You bastard! Move away from Merry!
You son of a bitch!
If you don't get it...
...take a good look at her...
with your own eyes!
Sorry, Merry.
I'll fix you right away.
I'll fix you right away... I'll...
As many times as you need...
I'll fix you as many times as you need!
As many times as you need!
Hey! Enough already, Long-nose!
You saw the bottom of the ship, right?!
With the broken keel at the root of her,
the outer panels are slipping off
and the frames are torn, too!
When a ship is like that, she'll just fall
apart from the outside with each wave!
And yet, you think a total
amateur like you can...
Shut up!
I don't want you to tell me anything!
Keep your mouth shut, or I'll
beat you up, you hooligan!
At...
At heart...
...I know it.
Huh?! What did you say?!
At heart...
At heart... I know it all.
I... I...
I know that Merry is at the end of her life!
At heart...
I... know...
When I heard the assessment,
I was convinced that what I saw
on that day really happened.
First, I thought I was dreaming.
I thought there was no way
something like that could happen.
On one foggy night...
in a forest under the moonlight,
I heard the strikes of a wooden hammer.
The sound was coming from the ship,
although no one was supposed
to be on her at the time.
It came from our ship, which was
scarred and washed ashore.
It was very foggy, but I
definitely saw someone there...
...striking a wooden hammer.
I couldn't figure out who it was.
But then, when the morning came the next day,
the ship was lousily fixed.
The completely broken mast
was also fixed as it used to be.
But the really mysterious thing was that...
...whoever fixed the Merry
knew how she originally looked.
Despite the fact that we
had added lots of tweaks,
this person put the Merry back
to how she used to look!
Everything was a mystery to us, but...
...for some reason, these words
remained in my heart.
I don't even know if this person actually
said it or I was imagining things...
Don't worry.
I'll carry you guys for a little bit longer.
This may sound stupid, but...
...I feel that it might've been
an incarnation of the Merry.
I bet the ship was already at her limits then.
So she might've turned into
that form to let us know it.
When I heard the assessment,
that's what I thought.
You think I'm crazy, don't you?
You don't have to believe me.
Bro?
Believe you?
This person looked like a sailor
holding a wooden hammer, right?
What...? Why...?
Do you know?
Brother...
You saw a Klabautermann.
K-Klabau...?
Klabautermann.
It's one of the legends known among sailors.
It's a fairy that dwells only on a ship
that's treated with great care.
Well, you could say it's a ship's incarnation.
They carry wooden hammers in their hands
and are dressed in sailor's raincoats.
When danger approaches the ship,
they run around inside the ship
and let people know about it.
It is said that they sometimes
help sailors quite a bit.
But to be honest, this is the first time
I've heard someone say they saw one.
The more care the ship receives,
the more it appreciates the sailors.
This ship probably wanted to somehow
carry you across to the other shore.
She was able to encounter a crew
that she wanted to carry so badly
that she'd borrow a human form to appear...
I bet she's been very happy.
Merry...
I see...
Then, the one...
...who talked to me then...
...was really you, huh?
Merry...
At any rate, for Heaven's sake...
You had a big fight with your friends
knowing your ship is at her limits, then?
It's not that simple.
How inept men are!
They're fools!
Looks like someone's here.
"Someone's here"? Who else could
it be but Zambai and the others!
Why did they take the trouble
of coming from the sea side?
Yeah... when they usually
use the upper entrance...
They might've brought Straw Hat.
Oh, that's right!
I forgot that I sent for Straw Hat
and the others with you as bait!
They won't come. We're no longer friends.
I told you so, didn't I?
Why aren't they coming in?
Okay, okay. I'll open the door now!
Okay, okay. Geez, stop ringing the bell!
Brother... Go back to your friends.
I can't do that now. I fought
a duel with my captain.
Besides, the ship stuff isn't settled yet, so...
What do you mean it hasn't been settled?
If you know that your ship can't
sail anymore, it's simple, isn't it?
Leave her with me.
I'll take care of her in a way
that you'd approve of.
What I did earlier, too, you know...
I tried to destroy the ship thinking
that it would be best for you.
Don't stick your nose
into things! It's my business!
--Hey, I'm trying to solve your problem!
--Is it Zambai?
You should appreciate it!
I should appreciate it? Give me a break!
Don't you get it?! It's a
nuisance for the ship, too!
She loves you guys so much that
she appeared in human form.
If she sinks in the middle of the sea
while you guys are on board...
Hey! If that happens, even if she dies,
she'll be filled with regret!
She won't be able to rest in peace!
Then, when your friends are dying,
can you just leave them saying,
"Well, I hope you die
without suffering at least"?!
If you put it that way,
that's a whole different discussion!
No, it's not! It's that kind of matter!
You just don't get it, do you?!
Huh?!
Mozu!
Kiwi!
Wh-Who's there?!
Pardon me... for interrupting.
It's just, these two ladies didn't let us in, so...
The secretary at Galley-La!
What the hell are you bastards doing here?!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
Galley-La! What the hell are you bastards...
We're Government
intelligence agents, Cutty Flam.
Why do you know that name?!
You've been entrusted with something
by the legendary shipwright Tom.
Now, could you please hand over your secret?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Franky's Past! The Day the Sea Train First Ran"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!