Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
but Law has been captured by Doflamingo.
Luffy snuck into the Royal Palace
to take back Law.
Sugar has passed out!!
What?!
The servants that we've been
collecting for a decade
are turning back into humans!
The spell of the Hobby-Hobby Fruit is
being removed!
We accomplished Operation SOP!
Who is he?!
Brother Kyros!
The toys were originally humans
but they were erased from our memories!
Since the Devil Fruit eater Sugar
passed out now,
we got our memories back!
He's the former commander of
the King Riku Army - Kyros!
You are...!
You're Kyros, aren't you?!
Yes, sir!
I'm sorry to keep you waiting
for a decade!
Now, I'm here to save you!
I'm here to take back the real Dressrosa!
"The Fire Fist Strikes!
The Flare-Flare Fruit Power Returns!"
A decade!
For a decade, we have suffered!
Doflamingo-sama!
Young Master!
You bastard!
From now on,
I'm gonna rip the mask off of all your deceptions!
Mingo's dead!
I was gonna kick his ass...
--There they are!
--I see them!
--You bastards!
--They found us!
Shoot!
Let's go rescue Tra-guy!
What?!
What in the world is going on?!
The toys in the Colosseum turned into
humans and animals all of a sudden!
Even I don't know how to
explain this situation...
Why is a gorilla here?!
Run!
I can't believe it!
Damn Trebol! He must've left Sugar unguarded!
That idiot!
How surprising!
Hey! How much longer are you gonna cry?!
Am I a babysitter?!
It's not that!
I just remember!
Mother-sama, I picked so many flowers!
Wow, Rebecca!
Would you like to have one?
Thank you. I would like to.
And this is from your mother to you!
Would you like to have one?
Let's eat!
Go ahead. Dig in.
Someone that I loved so much!
I'm gonna go to the palace!
Alright, Scarlet? Rebecca?
Father-sama!
If it gets dangerous here,
go to the Red Flower Field and wait there!
I'll come and get you at any cost!
Father-sama!
Father-sama!!
F-Father-sama!
What?
I...
...had a father!
Huh? What are you talking about?!
I guess that's the plot that's been
undermining the country, Rebecca.
Things always have a core.
And if you can strike it,
you can turn any situation around.
My great senpai!
Now I don't know what you are talking about!
Even the ring has one.
A core.
Let's just finish up this fight.
What the...
There are cracks in the ring!
Did Lucy do something?!
Dragon Claw Fist!
Dragon...
...Breath!
Whoa! Lucy's unbelievable attack!
The ring is sinking!
The ring has exploded!
What?
It's floating!
You bastard! What did you do?!
I gotta go somewhere! I'm gonna win this!
--Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
--Oh!
I heard a huge noise up there!
Hack?
Did he do something reckless again?!
He's gonna head underground now.
The ring has totally collapsed!
It seems like the water level is falling!
We can no longer guarantee
the safety of the Colosseum!
Everybody, please evacuate immediately!
It's driving to the center!
There must be some cracks in
the foundation of the ring!
The water is flowing down into the ground!
Give up, give up, give up!
You can't hold on to my neck! I'm choking!
This is nothing!
It's spirit! All about spirit!
That's...
I found it!
That son of a bitch!
I won't let you have it!
I got wet!
I'm losing my strength...
Don't!
We weren't gonna give anyone that prize!
Everybody's out of the ring!
I'm the winner!
What?!
You said the one who gets
this will be the winner!
The Flare-Flare Fruit!
It's all mine, isn't it?
Th...
The champion! The champion!
I know now isn't the time
but the one who got
the Flare-Flare Fruit
by taking advantage of this mess is...
...the biggest dark horse of
this competition - Lucy!
He is the champion!!
Disgusting!
I can't hold out... anymore...
Oh my great senpai! Help me, too!
You're a man.
You have to take care of yourself!
What?!
But I knew that's what you would say...
--I'm gonna make one more attack so watch out!
--What?!
Damn! He ate the Flare-Flare Fruit!
Isn't he the guy
from the Revolutionary Army?!
Ow, it's hot!
I really can generate a fire!
His clothes! I forgot I have them!
No, it's just my imagination!
It's not hot!
I am a fire now!
Ace!
I take over your ability!
You are...
Fire Fist!
THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
Damn you Straw Hats!
Tontattas!
Thank you for knocking Sugar out!
How dare you free our servants!
There's no way
I'm letting you get out of here!
Usoland!
Are you okay?!
Guys! Please look after Usopp!
Okay!
Let's run!
Don't let him lay a finger on Usoland!
You guys want to destroy the SMILE factory!
Isn't that right, Nico Robin?!
Sticky-Sticky Chain!
Wait!
A Giant!
You guys are the Little People.
Let me borrow him for a sec.
Usoland!
He's hurt so bad.
He must've fought so hard to save us...
Guys, look!
I heard some of you have been living
as a toy for a decade.
How painful is that?
"YOU" ARE HURTING ME  "DO"N'T MOVE ME
You...
Do...
If it weren't for you,
we would've lived as toys forever!
We would've lived as their slaves!
It feels like our lives have been spared!
Take a good look, warriors!
This man is...
...the hero who broke the spell on us!
Vi...
STOP MO"VI"NG ME, I SAI"D"
D...
His name is...
Captain Usopp!!
Thank you!!
Usoland!
--What happened?!
--The ceiling collapsed?!
A heavenly light!
What?!
D-D-Don't tell me
he is a messenger from heaven!
Are we...
...witnessing a miracle?!
S-So divine! He's like god!
H-Hey everybody, listen!
God Usopp is gonna say something!
You...
...people...
...will...
...be... gui...
...ded... b...
...y...
...me...
What?! Wh-What did he say?!
PUT ME DOWN, "YOU" IDIOT
You...
"PEOPLE" LIKE YOU ARE THE WORST
...people...
"WILL" YOU STOP
...will...
HEY "BE"EFY "GUY", OPEN YOUR BLIN"DED" EYES
...be... gui...
...ded...
"B"LOOD IS ALL OVER M"Y" FACE
...b... y...
"ME"ATHEAD
...me...
"YOU" "PEOPLE" "WILL" "BE"
"GUY" "DED" "BY" "ME"
"You people will be guided by me"?!
"You people will be..."
"...guided by me"!
So you really are...
...sent from heaven...
to be our savior!
God Usopp! God Usopp! God Usopp!...
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Usoland! Usoland!
Guide us, God Usopp!
What are we supposed to do?!
--He's right!
--It's our turn to help you!
We want to work for you!
Please! Guide us! Show us the way!
The action we must take!
Then, why don't you destroy
the factory behind me
and rescue our little friends?
At your command!
Usopp!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
What the hell is wrong with...
...these people?
The Fire Fist finally returns!
The mysterious man Lucy who inherits Ace's
will and power comes down into
the darkness of Dressrosa
and when his astonishing
true identity is revealed,
a new history of the three
brothers will begin!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dashing onto the Scene!
The Chief of Staff of the Revolutionary Army, Sabo!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!