Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Chopper, were you able
to find any medicinal herbs?
Yep. I've collected most of them,
but there may be even rarer ones on this island.
More importantly, something's
been bugging me for a while.
I wonder what this weird groove
is that runs down this path...
Come to think of it, yeah, I wonder what it is.
It looks as if a bicycle passed by.
We're suddenly out in a large open space.
Ahh... Hmm?
A raccoon dog?
I'm a reindeer! See? I've got antlers!
Are you okay, Chopper?!
Who the heck is this?!
Luffy, what happened?!
What's with you guys?
What's with you?!
Wh-Who's that huge guy?
Who's that guy?!
Robin...
"Navy Headquarters Admiral Aokiji!
The Ferocity of an Ultimate Powerhouse"
To think that he got Robin this shaken up...
Who is he?
He's a marine.
Navy Headquarters Admiral... Aokiji.
Admiral?!
A... Admiral? He's that high up?
There're only three officers in the Navy
who hold the position of Admiral.
Akainu...
Aokiji...
Kizaru...
The only one above them
is Fleet Admiral Sengoku, who reigns
as the top official in the Navy.
That man is one of the three men
called the World Government's
ultimate powerhouses.
Wh-Why is someone like that here?!
Why don't you go deal with big-time pirates
with several-hundred-million-Berry bounties?!
G... Go someplace else!
Hm?
Oh, my, my...
Wh-What?
Here's another sexy lady with super
big bazongas! Are you free tonight?
What's the big idea, you tall, lanky jerk?!
Pay attention, you jerk!
Hold on a sec, you guys, geez...
Did you hear what I said?
I said I just took a stroll, didn't I?
Don't get so worked up.
To start with, you guys are...
whatchamacallit... you know...
"Wh-Whatchamacallit"?
"You know..."?
Err...
I forgot. Oh, well.
You don't make much sense!
What the heck's with this guy?!
Hey, Robin, aren't you
mistaking him for someone else?
There's no way someone
like him is a Navy Admiral!
Hey, hey... Don't judge
others by their appearance.
My motto as a marine is "total slovenly justice."
That totally matches your appearance!
In any case, well...
Oh, excuse me for a sec...
Standing made me tired. Umph.
Then why were you sleeping standing up?
Anyway, to make a long story short,
I have no intention of capturing
you guys, so don't worry.
I came to check the whereabouts
of Nico Robin, who disappeared
after the Alabasta incident, that's all.
Just as I thought, she's been with you guys.
This guy sure is apathetic, isn't he?
His audacity shows he's a leader,
in a manner of speaking.
I'm going to at least report
this to Headquarters, though,
as with another wanted person, the total
bounty for you guys has now changed.
100 million... plus 60 million...
plus 79 million equals...
I don't know exactly, but I'm
sure it's not too shabby.
Why don't you calculate it?
Gum-Gum...
Hold on a sec! Hold on, Luffy!
Stop it! Stop it!
Let me go! What're you guys doing?!
What's the point in us picking a fight?!
He's one of the strongest marines!
So what?! Then are you saying we're
gonna hand over Robin without a fight?!
You jerk!
Well, you guys... I'm saying I'm
not gonna do anything, aren't I?
I'm gonna beat him up!
Stop it, Luffy!
Hold on!
S-So you're a marine...
I wish you had told us sooner.
--Hm?
--Who are these people?
Hey, get hold of yourselves.
Then this isn't an uninhabited island?
Well, they're probably the passengers
who drifted here from a wrecked ship.
About a month ago,
there was a report that a passenger
liner went missing in this area.
How are they, Chopper?
There're some injured people,
but their wounds aren't serious.
They'll be fine once I apply the medicine I have.
More importantly, it seems that
they haven't been eating well.
They're weakened.
Sanji-kun and Usopp went to get some food.
Hey! We're back!
You must've been really hungry.
You don't have to wolf down the food.
There's plenty more where that came from.
That's right! There's plenty more!
Hey, why are you eating?!
At any rate, even if this is an uninhabited island,
if you are so inclined,
you can find food, you know.
This is the problem with amateurs.
I'm surprised that you survived
after a shipwreck in the Grand Line.
We're the only ones who made it to this island.
What happened?
On our way back from a gourmet
tour to the gourmet town, Pucci...
...our ship collided with a huge frog
that was doing the front crawl
and shattered into pieces.
Doing the front crawl?! A frog was?!
Frogs normally do the breaststroke, though.
Interesting! I wanna see it, too!
--Are you out of your mind?
--It's true!
That's Yokozuna.
--Huh?
--Yokozuna?
Then, after a great struggle,
we were able to make it to this island,
yet we lived on the verge
of starvation for a month.
We rejoiced when we saw someone was coming,
but when we looked carefully,
he was riding a bicycle on the sea.
Hey, now... Under no
circumstances can one ride a...
Oh... that was me.
--Huh?
--And then, the next one
that came was a pirate ship.
Us, huh?
Then you guys are... whatchamacallit...
...you know... um... well...
Say it clearly! Clearly!
Oh, shoot! I totally forgot!
Hey, you! Don't mess with us!
--L-Luffy! Hold on! Hold on!
--Calm down!
Well, like I said...
Like I said several times already, I took a stroll.
Oh, it was a stroll? Then don't go
passing a place like this! Leave!
You don't make sense.
Luffy kinda has the upper hand here.
Well, then... Okay.
I'm going back, but before that...
You guys, get ready to depart right away.
Fortunately, there's an inhabited
island not so far from here.
You should go there to get
the treatment you need.
Hey, you guys! You don't have to
listen to this guy! He's a marine!
Is there a problem?
Oh... That's right. It's fine,
it's fine. That's right. It's fine.
Normally, marines are your friends
and we are the bad guys, huh?
It's no time for laughing!
He said he'd help those guys.
But does he have a ship?
Besides ours, I didn't see
any other ships anywhere.
There's no ship. They don't
have a Log Pose, either.
How are they supposed to
go to that nearby island?
Oh, they'll be fine.
Nothing you say sounds convincing, you know.
It's true that...
Hm?
...that man can make it happen.
All right, done!
We loaded up food and water.
With this much, you'll be fine for a while.
It's nice to work once in a while.
Yeah, it feels good! You're quite a sensible guy!
He hit it off with him after all.
So what're you gonna do?
Are you gonna swim while
pulling these guys and this stuff?
No way.
Step back a bit.
Wh-What the heck?!
A sea animal! I bet that's the
guardian of this area of the sea!
What?! Hey, you! Run!
Watch out! Gum-Gum...
Ice Age...
Devil Fruit...!
Th-The sea... froze!
This is the power of a
Navy Headquarters' Admiral.
This will probably last at least a week.
Take your time and head in that direction.
You'll get to an inhabited island in four days.
It's a little cold, so dress warmly while walking.
Is this... a dream?
The sea has become ground!
We can now cross the sea!
We can get off of this island!
Mr. Marine! Thank you!
This is a miracle! A miracle without doubt!
Well then, we'll get going now.
Yeah. I'm happy for you guys.
Be careful.
I guess there're different kinds of pirates, huh?
We can't thank you enough.
Not only did you treat our injured,
but you also shared your
food and water with us.
Don't worry about it.
They say that even a chance meeting is
due to karma from a previous life, so...
Take good care of the children
so that they don't catch a cold.
In this state, the food will
probably stay fresh for a while.
--Bye-bye!
--Thank you very much.
--Thank you!
--We'll never forget your kindness,
Straw Hat Pirates!
See ya! Take care!
Be careful on your trip!
Good, good.
Whoa, it's cold. It's cold.
This is completely like winter.
I can ice skate!
Whoa! That's amazing, Chopper!
Just as you'd expect from
someone born on a winter island!
How about this?
Whoa! That's amazing!
Why don't you try?
Boy, it's cold, it's cold!
I'm gonna freeze!
Hm?
Hmm...
What?
How should I put it... You're just
like your gramps, Monkey D. Luffy...
Wh-What?
You're free-spirited, or should
I say you're hard to figure out?
G-Gramps...
Gramps...?! Luffy's?!
Hey, what's the matter, Luffy?
You're drenched in sweat.
Well... N-N-Nothing. Um... well...
Your gramps really helped me out a while back.
The reason I came here was to
have a look at Nico Robin and you.
On second thought...
maybe you should die now, huh?
The government is still taking you guys lightly,
but if I delve into your history, I can
tell that your group has a backbone.
Although your group is small,
since it's gathering shrewd members,
it'll probably become a problem later on.
The circumstances that initially
led to your search orders...
All the actions you took up until now...
The speed of your group's progress...
I've been dealing with outlaws for a long time,
but it worries me to think how you'll turn out.
Th-That's too sudden!
You said earlier that you just
came to check things out!
The reason I especially regard
you guys as dangerous is...
...you, Nico Robin.
So you're after Robin after all!
I'm gonna beat the crap out of you!
Her bounty amount isn't just
an indication of her strength.
It also indicates the level of danger
she poses to the government.
That's why you got a 79-million-Berry
bounty on your head at the age of eight.
I'm impressed that you survived as a child.
You betrayed people and ran away.
You gained people's favor and used them.
You've survived in the underworld
by being quick to switch sides.
So this is the group that you
chose as your next hideout, huh?
Hey, you jerk! How insulting you are!
What grudge do you hold against Robin-chan?!
Stop it, Sanji!
I don't have any grudge against her.
If we are somehow connected...
...it's that I let her get
away once, that's about it.
It was a long time ago.
You guys will eventually realize it, too.
In the not-so-distant future, you'll regret
that you took in a troublesome woman.
As proof, the organizations Nico Robin
had something to do with up until today
all got annihilated... except for her.
I wonder why... Nico Robin?
Stop it, you jerk! Her past doesn't matter!
He's right! If you're worried about others' pasts,
you can't be friends with ruffians like
a pirate hunter or a former thief girl!
"Ruffians" was unnecessary!
What's more important is
the present, rather than the past!
Robin is our precious friend now!
Don't badmouth our friend!
I see... You really did a
good job befriending this lot.
Just get to the point already! If you
want to capture me, go ahead and do it!
Treinta Fleurs!
Robin! Stop it!
Oh, my, my... Maybe I talked too much.
How disappointing!
I had too high an opinion of you,
thinking you were a little smarter than that.
Clutch!
Ahhh! He shattered into pieces and died!
N-No... We're screwed...
H-Hey! Guys! Run! Let's get out of here!
That wasn't nice.
Ice Saber!
I wasn't going to kill you, but...
Slice Shoot!
All right!
Hmph! How dare you butt in, you damn cook?
The same to you, you natural monument!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
It's cold!
He froze them!
Those three... all at once...
O-Oh, no! They have to be treated right away!
If they get frostbite, their limbs
will become gangrenous!
What're you doing, Usopp?!
We have to go help those three now!
I-I really would like to,
but my body can't move.
Did I get frozen, too?
No! You're just too scared to move!
--Luffy!
--Sanji! Zoro!
Robin! Run!
You've come across some good friends.
But you're still you, Nico Robin!
No...! I'm no longer...
Robin! Watch out! Run!
I'm...
Robin-chan!
Robin!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Ahh! Robin got...!
...frozen!
Don't yell! Her death will benefit the world.
--What'd you say?!
--You bastard!
--Wait, you guys!
--Luffy!
Don't interfere in this fight!
I'll fight him in a duel!
That's fine by me, but...
err... whatchamacallit...?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Duel between Rubber and Ice! Luffy vs. Aokiji"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!