Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!!
A storm is coming.
An unimaginably big storm is...!
Out of our way!
I'm... dead.
I'm still alive after all.
I got lucky.
Are these all coincidences?
It's as if heaven is trying
to let that man live.
We'd better hurry
or we'll be in trouble!
We're gonna make it to
the Grand Line like this!
"The Legend Has Started!
Head For The Grand Line"
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
A pirate, huh? Fine by me.
What's with this storm?!
If we don't leave soon,
we'll be stuck here.
Nami-san was right when she said
we should hurry back to the ship!
Run! Run! Run!
Special Move:
My Carnival of Colors!
Pardon me!
Attacking me is a waste of time.
There isn't a man alive
who can touch my smooth skin.
For a second there,
I saw a field filled with flowers.
You're alive, Captain Buggy.
No way I'd die!
Buggy, this isn't good!
They're marines from headquarters.
There'll be no end to them!
Humph. I could care less if the
marines want to stick their nose into...
Whose nose did you say is sticking out?!
I didn't say anything like that!
What're we going to do?
Gum-Gum! Go after Gum-Gum!
Mohji and Richie should have
burned down his ship by now.
He can't get off of this island.
We'll kick his ass and
leave this island, guys!!
Yeah!!
Motor!!
Yes, Captain!
Chop-Chop Buggy! Here we go!
Igniting the bomb engine!
Set the slope!
Yes, Big Sis Alvida!
No friction...
Smooth-Smooth Tracks!
Don't let the pirates get away!
Wh... What's this smoke?!
What the hell...?!
White Out!
Smoker!
I don't have time for you, small fries!
H-He's too strong!
So that's the power
of Plume-Plume Fruit...
He took down Buggy's
gang in a split second...
Fire!
Captain! He caught
us all in one fell swoop!
How dare you, Smoker!
What's with this annoying steel net?!
Firing a weird pistol like that...
That was a "Cage Shot" developed by
the Navy to deal with Devil Fruit powers.
Dammit!
Bring my Billower Bike here!
We'll go after Straw Hat!
Yes, sir!
This is heavy!
The Going Merry is in danger!
The Navy might be
already heading toward it!
We have to get out as soon as possible!
Nami! Nami!
Can't I just ditch this thing?
No, you can't! Run faster!
I knew you'd say that.
Dammit! What's with
this sudden downpour,
when we have to burn down this ship?!
Dammit! This is bad, Richie!
We can't get a fire going like this!
One more time!
Be patient, Richie! I'll feed you later.
What're you doing?!
Mohji!
Oh, it's you, sneak thief woman.
Go, Richie!
Special Attack: Fresh Egg Star!!
You...
Damn! The rain made my hand slip!
Richie!! You're such a...!!
Now! Let's get on the ship!
Yeah!
Hold it! You have to get past me!
I'm Mohji, Vice-Captain of
the Buggy the Clown Pirates!
I won't let you take
one step on this...
Prepare to fire!
The Navy!
This is bad!
Aim!
Fire!
Contact the cannon unit!
We'll capture the pirate ship!
Yes, sir!
N-N-N-Nami!
Yeah!
Which direction is the sea?
I can't tell where we're going
because of this heavy rain!
There they are!!
What persistent bastards!
Should we stop and fight?
We don't have time for that.
Oh?
Who's that lady?!
Hm?
I didn't realize you're Roronoa Zoro,
and a pirate to boot.
You gonna take this sword, too?
You... You lied to me!
What?! What'd you do to her?!
You didn't ask my name. That's all.
It's not that I lied to you.
A rogue like you can't be
allowed to own a renowned sword!
I'll collect your sword,
the legendary Wado Ichimonji!
Try it.
I see...
You jerk! How dare you attack a lady!
Please don't interfere!
What?
This is the fight between Roronoa
and me! There's no need to step in!
You heard her. Go on ahead.
Let's go.
Hey, Zoro! If you hurt the
lady, I won't forgive you!
Sergeant Major Tashigi!
I can't let you have this
sword no matter what.
Sergeant Major Tashigi lost...
That Sergeant Major Tashigi lost...
Well, then... I'm in a hurry, so...
Why aren't you finishing me off?!
Is it because I'm a woman?!
You're lucky, Zoro. You're a boy.
It's humiliating that
you won't fight seriously
in a game played in earnest just because
men're physically stronger than women!
I'm sure you don't understand the
feeling that I wish I was born a boy!
I don't carry a sword for pleasure!
I don't like your very being!
Listen! Your face! It looks exactly like
my close friend's who died long ago!
On top of that, you started saying
the same thing she used to say!
Don't imitate, you copycat woman!
What?! Stop talking
like a child! You're rude!
I live the way I am! I don't
know what your friend was like,
but I'm the one who feels upset!
Isn't she the copycat?!
Wh-What'd you say?!
I see the exit! The harbor is up there!
Hey, who is it this time?
You're finally here...
Straw Hat Luffy...
Didn't I tell you that you can't enter
the Grand Line unless you beat me first?
Oh, yeah. I forgot about it.
You're such an airhead...
Hey, Luffy...
Sanji, go on ahead. I'll be right there.
Well, I don't know about that.
This is the end for you.
Go!
Fire!
Fire the cannons!
If we stay here any longer,
the Going Merry will be sunk!
A-Are you going to set sail?
Luffy and the others aren't here yet!
We don't have any other choice!
It's better than getting sunk here!
Right rudder full!
So what're we going to do
about Luffy and the others?
We'll pick them up somehow.
Don't let them get away! Follow them!
Nami-san!
Sanji-kun!
Sanji!
Nami-san, I'm back!
Where're Luffy and Zoro?
Can we collect those damn idiots?
Sanji-kun!
Behind you!
Dammit! This is endless!
I'll cover his back! Get closer!
No! We can't head back to land
because of the strong current.
Ahhh, dammit!
Usopp!
Bastards!
Usopp! Sanji-kun!
I'll beat you and
enter the Grand Line.
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!
Enough of your idle talk!
What?! What?! What's going on?!
I ate the Plume Plume Fruit.
So my body becomes smoke at will.
What's wrong? Finished already?
Gum-Gum Gatling!
What? Ahh, that's gross!
White Blow!
You bastard! Gum-Gum Pistol!
You get it? You can't
even enter the Grand Line.
Didn't I tell you that?
Wanted for a 30 million Berry bounty?
You're running out of your devil's luck.
Don't be so sure.
You're...
Wh-What? Who's that? Who's that?
The government wants your head.
The world is waiting for our answer.
Th-This is...
Wh-What just happened?
Luffy!
Luffy!!
Nami!
We'd better hurry up or the
ship will be swept away!
Okay!
Gum-Gum...
Wha?!
W-Wait!
I have a bad feeling...
...Rocket!!
Ahhh, I knew it!
Everyone...
That man...
What was that sudden gust?
He appeared and disappeared
like lighting on the same day
that Gold Roger was executed
22 years ago. What on earth...
I'm the man who'll be
King of the Pirates!
If that's your decision, then go!
Why? Why did you
help that man... Dragon?!
What reason would there be to
interfere with a man's departure?
Set sail! We'll go after Straw Hat!
What?
We'll enter the Grand Line.
B-But, Captain! This island
is in your jurisdiction.
I don't know what
the higher-ups would say...
Tell them I said,
"Don't give me orders."
I'll come with you!
Sergeant Major Tashigi!
I won't forgive Roronoa.
I'll capture him without fail!
Gee, that flashy gust was lucky for us.
We were able to escape like
this because I always behave well.
Where're we going now?
The Grand Line.
The Grand Line?
Yeah. This is a good opportunity. I have
to settle with that damn rubber man.
Let's head straight into
the nostalgic Grand Line...
Ugh! It's almost like
the ship's gonna tip over!
Look at that light!
Is that a lighthouse of the island?
It's a "guiding light." The entrance to
the Grand Line lies ahead of that light.
The Grand Line is ahead of that light...
What do you wanna do?
B-But there's no reason to
enter during a storm like this...
Okay, then!
Shall we hold a launching ceremony
for setting sail on the great ocean?
Hey!
Sure!
Let's do it!
In order to find the All Blue!
In order to be King of the Pirates!
In order to become
a master swordsman!
In order to draw a world map!
I-In order... to become
a brave warrior of the sea!
We're going... to the Grand Line!!
Yeah!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Hm? What's going on over there?
A flock of birds?
There must be fish under that.
Catch some, okay?
Leave it to me!
Hm? It's not fish!
It's a girl!
There's trouble! I see a Navy fleet!
D-Did they come to capture me?
Ahhh! They're firing at us!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Precursor to a New Adventure!
Apis, a Mysterious Girl"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!