Edited at https://subtitletools.com
This scent... Could it be...?
Hey, Chopper, what's the matter?!
Hey, Chopper?!
Oops!
Hey, Chopper! Are you okay?!
Hey, are you okay?!
Are you hurt?
What on earth is going on...
Starting to run so sudden... ly...
I knew she'd be here.
--Robin!
--Robin-chan!
I won't... return to you guys.
We're parting ways here... in this town...
I carry a darkness within me
that you guys don't know about.
This darkness will destroy you someday.
As a matter of fact, I'm pinning this
crime on you and planning to run away.
The situation will get worse.
Robin-chan! I don't get what you're saying!
What happened to you?!
Robin! Let's go back together!
Although I only spent a short
time with you, after today...
...I'll never see you again.
Thank you for being nice to a person like me.
Goodbye.
Wait...
Hey... wait...
I can't...
...accept this.
Wait!
Stop joking!
Wait! Robin-chan!
Robin!
I lost sight of her.
Yeah.
--Chopper...
--Hm?
You go join Luffy and the others and tell
them everything that just happened...
...without leaving a single word out.
--What're you gonna do?
--We'll part ways here for a bit.
Well, don't worry. I won't do anything reckless.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Capture Robin!
The Determination of the Straw Hats"
--Hold it!
--Hold it right there!
Don't let them get away!
What's wrong with you?!
It was going to happen eventually!
With this many people, it'd be
strange if they didn't find us!
You can't get away from us anymore!
This way!
H-Huh?
Where'd they go?
Look in every nook and cranny!
What about the alleys?!
Couldn't they have climbed
up on some rooftop?!
Dammit! They shook us off?!
But they definitely ran in this direction!
Shall we check over there?!
Then, we'll search inside the buildings!
All right, then! Let's split
into two groups and search!
Yeah!
Is it okay now?
Not yet.
Where did you lose them?!
A bit longer.
Ah...
Please...
Come back some other time!
I'm evacuating now. Stop pestering me!
Please... I've got money.
As much lumber, tar, and rope
as this amount will buy...
Also, some nails, latches, and tinplates...
I'm closing the shop.
Ah... I'm sorry, but...
Tsk... Okay, then.
But you can't buy that much
with this little money.
Th-Then, to make up for the rest,
I'd like to exchange my tools.
Hey, hey, don't be ridiculous! Stop it!
I only sell. To think you're tryin' to barter...
What are you, a bumpkin?
Geez... You win.
H-Hey! Are you okay carrying that
stuff when you're injured that badly?
Surely you have friends, right?! Hey!
See, what did I tell you?
Hey, hold on a sec, lad!
I'm okay. This is nothing.
--Hey!
--What is it? Are you gonna...
No...
Here. Take these. You're hungry, right?
Thank you.
Sure... Be careful going back.
Be careful going back!
These're good.
These're really good.
What a considerate pops he was.
The waves are getting quite high.
Don't worry. It'll be okay.
You're a ship... that flew in the sky!
Don't worry!
What's the matter, all of a sudden?
What's wrong, Franky?
Bro?
I'm getting ticked off!
Maybe it's about time to
go on another rampage!
Bro! Wait for us!
Thanks for the drink, Blueno!
What happened to Franky
all of a sudden, Kokoro-san?
Beats me... How should
I know... how idiots think?
I guess things have finally calmed down.
"Finally calmed down"?!
You had all those shipwrights chasing after you!
That's why we ended up
getting dragged into it, too!
I said it was unavoidable, didn't I?
At any rate, Chopper, I'm surprised
you found out where we were.
--Your scent.
--Oh, yeah.
Hm? Come to think of it, where's Sanji?
Well...
Did Robin really say that?!
Yeah.
We all... were prepared for it, right?
Even though it was for a
short time, we let Robin,
who showed up as an enemy, come on board.
It'd be embarrassing if we ran
away because we got scared.
Isn't it about time for us to settle this matter...
...as to whether that woman is... foe or friend?
The situation will get worse.
After today... I'll never see you again.
So you're sure that Robin said that, Chopper?
Yeah.
She said she wouldn't see us after today.
It also sounds like she's
declaring that she'll do something
that could worsen the situation
before the day is over.
Look at how big a fuss
the attempted assassination of
the mayor caused in this town.
If it's possible to make the situation worse,
there's only one thing she can do.
This time for sure... Assassinate the mayor...
It's natural to think that way.
But we know that she's pinning
her crime on us on purpose,
so it's possible that this could be a trap
to lure us out to the scene of the crime.
Trap...
If we're at the spot of the
assassination carried out tonight,
the crime will easily be pinned on us.
Hey! You already sound
like Robin is really our foe!
I'm talking about the possibility.
It's not that I've decided on either.
If I already decide either to believe her or not,
if the truth turns out to
be the opposite of that...
...it'll slow down my reaction.
If something is to happen,
it'll be tonight. Are we going?
We are.
I don't mind going... but there's a problem.
Sanji-kun saw Robin walking
with someone, right?
Iceberg-san said the same thing.
She was with someone with a mask on.
"Mr. Iceberg Falls Victim to Assassin"
But it wasn't any of us.
He must be the reason why
Robin suddenly changed.
Isn't he making Robin do bad things?!
That would be fortune.
If this guy is Robin's real friend,
then that would be misfortune.
But "someone with a mask on"
can't be a clue. That's the problem.
What's our goal?
We'll capture Robin.
Otherwise, we won't know anything.
True. Thinking about it is a waste of time.
But, come to think of it...
...the World Government has been trying
to capture that woman for twenty years,
and yet, it still hasn't happened.
But if we wanna know the truth,
that's the only way.
Okay, I'll do my best, too!
Well then, let's go...
...to Galley-La Company!
Dammit! The night is coming at last.
Paulie-san! This is it! The backstreets
will become dangerous soon.
Yeah. Let's go back.
I'm gonna head to the main office.
Okay!
Hey, guys! We're going back!
Straw Hat! Show yourself!
Where're you hiding?!
Straw Hat! That bastard...!
I thought the guy had at least a bit of mettle.
But he doesn't even show himself.
But Bro, the entire island holds
a grudge against them right now.
She's right. They must be
running from place to place.
By the way, what's the matter?
What're you guys doing?
We're vulnerable to strong winds from the front.
More importantly, Bro, the way you're
raging today is different from usual.
Letting stuff build up inside you isn't like you.
Shut up! I'm like that this week!
--Bro!
--Hm?
--Bro! Bro!
--That's Zambai and the others.
Bro! Did you beat up those bastards?
No, not yet.
There was some crazy
interference. They got away.
What?!
They got away from you when you were angry?!
What strong luck they have!
I see... Since that weak long-nosed guy
was fixing their ship all by himself,
I just assumed that you beat up the others.
Huh? You found one of them?!
Y... Yes, on their ship.
If you've found one of them, that makes it easy.
We can use him to drag them all out!
B-Bro is showing his bad guy face.
Well then, you guys! Starting now,
march throughout the town...
...shouting, "We've got Long-nose!
If you don't want him to sink in the sea,
come to the warehouse under the bridge!
Franky sends his regards!"
To make it true, I'm gonna
go kidnap Long-nose.
Okay, Bro! Leave it to us!
You're big, but your baggage is big, too, huh?
This is my special bed.
Aqua Laguna! Aqua Laguna!
Aqua Laguna is coming!
We're Aqua Laguna!
Run!
So what's going on with those culprits?
I heard that they haven't been caught after all.
How disturbing. Ahh, what a pain...
It's said that they might attack again
tonight in the confusion of the storm.
Aqua Laguna is here!
But it'll be crazy tonight.
I heard that all the craftsmen
will be guarding the main office.
Whoa! That's pretty serious!
How many are there in the Straw Hat Pirates?
Some people said 50. Others said 100.
The captain's got a 100 million
bounty on his head, after all.
Some said that 3,000 of his men
would advance from the sea!
That sounds totally dangerous!
Galley-La Company! Form a line,
and don't leave any openings!
Yeah!
Don't allow even a single rat inside!
Bring it on!
Shut up, coo coo! Be quiet, Tilestone!
I was told that they weren't on the sea train.
Then they're still somewhere
on this island, huh?
But they're fools if they really
appear with all these guards around.
I heard that an idiot plunged in here
in the middle of the day today.
Don't think using your common sense.
Well...
They don't have to go this far.
They're doing it voluntarily.
They're treating me like a king.
By the way, why did you put up Nico
Robin's wanted poster in your room?
Are you curious?
A little.
It's better if you don't know.
She is... a devil.
Tons of people are guarding the place.
It's a little far.
You can just stretch your arm
and go flying there, right?
But after the commotion starts, okay?
Yeah. If we cause a commotion before
they do, they'll just take advantage of it.
Listen up!
Don't miss even the slightest movement!
Yeah!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
What was that explosion?!
So they've finally started taking action.
The craftsmen are being
attacked by weird people!
Robin is definitely in that commotion.
Listen. Think that we'll never be able to
see Robin again if we miss this chance!
I know. We'll definitely
capture her. Just wait, Robin!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Cannon Fire Is the Signal!
CP9 Goes into Action"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!