Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
With Wyper leading the charge, the Shandians
take the fight to Upper Yard,
taking advantage of the fact
that the priests' eyes are focused on Gan Fall.
No matter what, head for "God's Shrine"!
Don't fear Eneru!
The Great Warrior Calgara is
our one and only Preserver!
Yeah!!
So you've come, Shandians!
After defeating Satori, Luffy and the
other two headed for the sacrificial altar.
The wounded Gan Fall,
and drowning Chopper...
Believe it or not, the one who rescued them
was a bird that was also found in Jaya.
There's a bunch of South Birds... But why...
Why are they this huge?!
So you're the ones that saved us?!
What?! He's God?!
Around that time, Nami, Zoro and Robin,
who reached the seashore,
discovered the shocking
secret behind Upper Yard.
This is the other half of the island that
was ripped up. This was part of Jaya!
The "city of gold" that once existed
on the ground and was seen by Noland...
...didn't sink into the ocean.
For 400 years... this part of Jaya has been...
...flying in the sky all this time!
"Jaya, City of Gold in the Sky!
Head for God's Shrine!"
Yahoo! Thank you, God!
I can't believe that the sky island we reached
after all this trouble was the city of gold!
This must be a reward for
behaving myself, right, God?
Hey, I thought you were
scared of this island's God?!
Hm? God? Oh, what's the big deal?
Is he worth more than gold?
But, you just said, "Thank you, God!"
She's not making any sense!
It's useless.
Hey, what is this place?!
I'll bet that this is the next ordeal area.
Another priest will appear. Be careful!
Aw, man... Come on, one ordeal is enough!
What is it gonna be?! String? Iron? Or Swamp?!
It looks like an ordinary grassy plain.
It's not ordinary! Open your
eyes and take a good look!
Those sticks all have skulls on them!
Oh, you're right! What the heck?!
Another one of those monstrous
priests is gonna show up?!
I'm excited! I wonder what kinda ordeal it'll be?
Are you nuts?! If the priests win, we'll
end up like the heads on those sticks.
There's no doubt about it!
Don't worry! We're not gonna lose!
Something's coming this way.
What?! Iron, String, Swamp...
Are they all coming together?!
That would save us a lot of time.
Ahhh! Here they come!!
You dirtbags! Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!!
What was that?!
Paramythia! He probably has the
power of the Super-Power Devil Fruit.
Wyper, are we gonna fight them?!
No, don't bother!
That guy...!
Hey, you! What're you doing?!
You ready to take us on?! You bastards!
So you were the Blue Sea
people acting up in Skypiea...
Hey, Luffy. That guy's the masked
guerrilla that we saw on the White Sea!
What's wrong with you?
He's running on the clouds!
Hey, stop! What do you want?!
To eliminate you!
Looks like he wants to fight.
Fine by me!
What's going on?!
They're scary! Sky islands are scary!
If you don't want to die, go back
to the Blue Sea immediately!
If you've got any funny ideas about
doing something on this island...
...we'll eliminate you along with Eneru.
So they're trying to kill Eneru?
Then does that mean the
guerrillas and God are different?
They're not priests?
Then let's leave them alone,
and get through here quickly, Luffy!
What'd you say, you dirtbag?!
C'mon! I'll beat you up!!
Ahh! Stop it! Please stop!
I'm coming over there, so stay put!!
I'll pay you back for earlier with interest!!
I told you, "Go back."
Whether or not you have the
ability to go back is another story.
What's their story?
Well, we learned that they're enemies
with God Eneru and us as well.
Dammit...! What's with this island?
We're gonna move on.
My "Can't Go into Jungles" disease is...
Oh, I'm hungry.
How could you be hungry? I've had it!
Oh yeah, Luffy, let's sing Sanji's
song to bring our spirits up!
♪ Take my hand... ♪
No, it goes like this!
I'll cover you!
Save our comrade!
Now!
Something's gonna happen!
Something's definitely gonna happen!
There's no way that we can
get through this safely!
We've got zoro, er, zero chance... zoro...
I wonder how Zoro's doing.
We've come quite a ways, haven't we, Sanji?
Haven't we, Sanji?!
Yeah, and that grassy plain
earlier turned out to be nothing.
Now that we've come this far,
I hope we can keep on going safely.
Yeah! We can! We definitely can!
What is it this time?! What the heck?
Look, Usopp!
This is fun!
Is there any point in winding the canal?
I'm getting dizzy!
This is fast!
Or rather, we're falling!!
Milky roads are fun!
Oh... I feel sick.
Hey, we've come really far.
I wonder if it'll be like this
the rest of the way to the altar.
The sun will set soon.
I can't see the sunset because of the clouds.
So they have twilight on the sky island, too.
Wyper! Kamakiri and I will fight here!
Help them over there!
Got it!
Chopper!
Where are you?!
What happened, Chopper?! Say something!
Hey, the Merry's mast is gone.
What kind of changes did he make?
You can't be serious! The ship was attacked!
Chopper! I'm sorry it took so long!
It's safe now to come out!
You're there, aren't you?!
Stop hiding and say something, Chopper!
I wonder if he was torn limb from limb.
Stop saying scary things!
Hey, Chopper! Are you there?!
Did something happen?!
Say something!
No--
Nothing scary happened!
Okay, okay... You're strong.
So tell us everything that happened.
Whoa! We're going up
another tree! This is a big one!
Hey, this is no time for idle chit-chat, Luffy!
What is this? What's this feeling?
Don't you think there's gonna
be something at the end?
The priests might be waiting in surprise
for us at the end of the milky road.
This thing is so tall! I'm so excited!
Are we gonna spin around again?!
Hm? There're something there.
There they are! Are they priests?!
No, they're skysharks!
Oh, just skysharks, not priests.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, seriously?!
Ahhh! They're huge!
We're gonna be swallowed!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!!
We're soaking wet!
Oh! Hey, look!
We found it! The Going Merry! That's the altar!
Yahoo!
Ahhh! Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Sorry to keep you waiting!
I've overcome the love ordeal to come here!
Aw, was that it? That was the ordeal?
Were you guys scared?!
Now that Captain Usopp is here, you'll be safe!
Looks like they're okay, too.
Phew, I'm relieved.
The mast is... gone...
U-Uhm... Usopp... I'm sorry.
I fought really hard...
...but a lot of things got burned.
Are your wounds okay?!
What?
Yes.
What a scary guy, using a
spear that can burn things.
I'm glad that it wasn't you that got burned.
We'll think about the ship later.
I'll become a more dependable man!!
Hey, Chopper! How did you
get rid of one of the priests?
I used the whistle.
The Sky Knight came to rescue me.
Oh? Where's that weird old guy?
"God"
So he fought this hard, even though
he gave us this whistle for free.
If it wasn't for the Sky Knight, both
the ship and I wouldn't have survived.
There're many things we'd like to ask him,
but we'll wait until he wakes up.
Thanks to you, too.
Luffy!!
Since the ship is in this
state and the sun's setting,
it looks like we won't be able to head
back to Angel Island until tomorrow.
In any case, let's head to the
forest and camp at the lakeshore.
Why?
The ship will get destroyed if
we have to fight here, right?
Use your head!
Also, it's probably a little
easier to fight on the shore.
Yay! Alright! Camping! Party time!
Yay!!
What? Hey, wait! We're in enemy territory!
You wanna camp?!
Alright! Then, let's start by
barbecuing those skysharks!
Yeah, this is yummy!
Geez, you'll eat anything.
Hey, this is pretty good.
Quiet! We're in the middle of reports.
We encountered Satori from the Illusion Forest,
a priest who uses surprise balls.
While the surprise balls made
the fight tough, the toughest part
was that he predicted our movements using
a technique called Mantra or something.
The priest Shura, who appeared out of
nowhere, uses a spear that burns anything.
Also, he seemed to predict my movements, too.
Although I tried to attack him
many times, he dodged each time.
The bird he was riding blew flames
and burned the main mast.
The Sky Knight was defeated, too.
You guys had a really hard time.
But we discovered that this
island is the other half of Jaya.
The city of gold didn't sink in the ocean,
but it flew up into the sky!
Alright! Well, everyone, thanks for your reports.
Based on your reports,
we've learned many things.
"The bird blows flames!
The spear burns things!"
"The sky island is actually part of Jaya, which we thought sank in the ocean!!"
However, the biggest discovery is this!
Believe it or not, this island is the city of gold,
the one that the Saruyama
Alliance was searching for!!
Really?!
I already said that, didn't I?!
So, what is this Mantra thing?
I don't know. Maybe it's like
an intuition or something.
Intuition, huh?
Hey, Chopper! Should I ground more?
Yes. Make it so that he can swallow.
His digestive tract is a little damaged.
Gold, huh? I've been waiting
for an adventure like this!
I can't wait!
That's what I wanted to hear!
This simplifies things!
Hey, hey, Luffy. Have you forgotten
the guerrilla's warning from earlier?
God's gonna get angry. He's scary!
That sounds fun.
Well, as pirates, we can't back off
when there's treasure close by, can we?
We've got enough enemies.
It's gonna be a survival game.
Sounds fun!
You guys... Shouldn't you be
at least a tiny bit afraid of God?!
I'm not responsible for this.
You'll be punished, seriously!
Alright! Let's do it! Gold hunting!!
Even if we're far apart
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
You have a friend here to share the pain
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
I won't let it just be a dream
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Oh, I can't wait to see the treasure!
Don't be so hasty. At any rate,
we'll start in the morning.
We'll start after eating dinner and breakfast!
That's what you always talk about!
If I'm not mistaken,
it's in the shape of a bell, right?
A golden bell? How gorgeous!
Alright! We'll get the gold!!
Yeah!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Festival on the Night Before
Gold-Hunting! Feelings for Vearth!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!