Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Hold Land of Marie Jois
Bartholomew Kuma-sama has returned!
Don't be ridiculous!
Bartholomew Kuma, you're telling
me they escaped your powers?
Give me a better excuse than that!
I'm the one who has to
report this to the top!
That's my grandson for you!
Quiet, Garp!
You were assigned a special government
mission to eliminate them all,
yet you couldn't even bring back the
head of Luffy of the Straw Hats?
You're a disgrace!
Don't worry, Sengoku.
Luffy isn't the sort of man who'd go around
telling the world that he defeated Moria.
Kuma, you didn't take pity on those pirates
because they were injured, did you?
Even if you let them escape,
we will not stop pursuing them!
They're following the Log toward
the Navy Headquarters as we speak!
Oh, that's right!
Tea
I brought fresh tea leaves!
Bring some rice crackers!
Damn it, Garp, shut up!
"Halfway Across the Grand Line!
Arrival at the Red Line!"
What the heck is going on?
It's hopeless.
Oh, dear...
We're not catching a thing.
This is weird.
Times are tough...
Man, this is boring!
Now, let's be patient.
Hey, Nami!
Aren't we at Fishman Island yet? Huh? Huh?
Oh, give it a rest! I'm
sure we're getting close!
Fishman... Mermaids!
Oh, beautiful mermaid!
Where is the mermaid I have dreamed of?!
Gah! I'm sick of this!
Sanji! I need food!
Is that...
Incredible! A huge school of fish!
You see? With some patience,
everything works out!
Fish 'em all up!
They're coming this way!
Want to try it too, Nami?
What is it?
Something isn't right.
Huh?
Hey, wait up, fish!
That's...
This is...
What is that obviously
foreboding look on your face?
Serpent Currents!
Serpent Currents?
Everyone, be careful!
It's almost like they're alive...
This looks a little dicey.
Well, this is quite...
Cool!
Sanji-kun!
Leave it to me, Nami-san!
It won't budge!
Weapons...
Left!
Hey! What are you doing?!
Steer the ship!
Shut up!
In these waves, it won't
do what I tell it to!
Gum-Gum...
Pistol!
Are you all right?
Yeah! You saved us!
Serpent Currents...
They certainly do move like serpents.
They're very aptly named!
Hey, you! This is no time to be impressed!
Gum-Gum...
Gatling!
Star Shield!
We keep cutting them down,
but there's no end to them!
How long are these currents gonna last?!
How much farther do they go on?!
Should we fly out of here with Coup de Burst?
Oh, yeah! That's one way!
It won't work!
I can't see any end to the currents.
Even if we fly away with Coup de Burst...
We can't escape them.
What?! No way!
Shall I play a song?
Huh?
At times like these, we need to boost morale!
All storms and currents
will eventually recede.
Let's just be patient.
Sounds good, Brook! Go for it!
Then—
We're in the air!
Hey, we're...
...gonna fall!
Chopper!
I thought I was gonna die...
Hey, look!
That's...
I see it... I see it!
It's the Red Line!
The Red Line!
We finally made it this far!
There was a nasty storm that day, too...
I'm gonna find the All Blue!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
I'm gonna be a great swordsman!
I'm gonna make a map of the whole world!
I-I'm gonna become a
brave warrior of the sea!
Let's go!
To the Grand Line!
Hey! I can see the Mystery Mountain!
It's gigantic!
The entrance to the Grand Line...
So that's the Red Line!
I-I can't even see the top
through all the clouds!
It has taken me 50 years...
Let's go, everyone!
That's...
It's huge!
Make sure you steer.
I don't want you giving me orders.
Should we use the paddles to retreat?
There's no time.
Sanji-kun! Get us on that wave!
You got it!
Wait, "get us on" it?!
Leave it to me!
I dealt with bigger stuff than
this when I was on the Sky Island!
The Knock Up Stream, huh?
Yeah, that was really fun!
That wasn't fun at all!
Of course, there's no way
this time is gonna be...
Go!
Now we can use Coup de Burst!
Lower the sails, everyone!
Here we go!
Coup de Burst!
Whew, we're saved!
Man, that was a close one.
We're here!
We finally made it here!
I can't see the top...
It's huge!
So this is the Red Line...
It's kind of nostalgic... Makes
you feel really emotional, huh?
I wonder if we've grown
a little since then...
I feel like crying!
So much has happened!
Anyway, we're halfway there now!
The Twin Capes, where we met Laboon,
are connected to this wall on
the other side of the world.
I'm glad we all made it here together!
Apparently, I crossed Reverse Mountain from
South Blue before I was old enough to remember,
but I guess that was more than 30 years ago.
I entered this sea five
years ago, from West Blue.
Once we go around the
second half of the world,
we'll get to see this wall
again, and when we do...
I'll be King of the Pirates!
We have to remain alert.
We're right next to Marie Jois,
the holy land of the Navy HQ
and the World Government.
This surprise pool is the best!
I'm not good enough...
Just try it.
Hey, you're alive?
Where is he?
What happened here?!
Nothing...
Nothing... happened!
I have to get stronger!
I'm still weak!
I'm still...!
How does it look, Robin? Brook? Luffy?
Not good. It's pitch dark.
It's pitch dark!
Hey, I just saw something flash!
Y-Y-You think it was some monster's eyes?!
M-Monster?!
W-We're gonna die!
Wait, I'm already dead!
Oh, right. Nami-san, pardon
me for asking, but...
What kind of panties are you wearing today?
Shut up! Be serious about this!
Scary!
He's got some guts.
Hey, you guys!
The Shark Submerge III can't
dive deeper than 5,000 meters!
Be careful!
Hm? The hull seems to be creaking...
Yes, because...
We're more than 5,000 meters under.
Ah, so that's why.
Wait! That's a bad idea!
The pressure will crush us!
Hey, that monster from
before is still around!
It sure has a big mouth!
That was close!
It's gonna eat us!
It's coming again!
Looks like this isn't gonna go well.
I never want to ride in the Shark Submerge.
Ditto.
Nami-san!
My tart made of horror pears
from Thriller Bark is done!
Wow, it looks delicious!
Behind us! Behind us!
Here it comes! We're gonna get eaten!
This is a problem, though...
Wow! This is great!
Yum!
Looks like another dead end,
just like at the Sky Island.
That's right.
I know which way we need to go, but
I don't know the means to get there.
How do we get to Fishman Island?
We're out!
That was fun!
Welcome back! Good job!
It was no good. We couldn't
see the sea floor.
You sure Fishman Island is really here?
That was my first time riding a submarine!
If it's any deeper, we'll
die before we get there.
I'm sure the Log Pose was
pointing right beneath us...
What a problem. I should have
talked with Lola about it more.
It's the thing from before!
It followed us back!
Don't think you can beat me
when we're above the water!
Gum-Gum Rifle!
It actually didn't seem all that huge.
Yeah, since we've seen Oars. We're okay now!
It spit something out.
Huh? A fish?
A person?!
No, it's not.
That's a...
It... It couldn't be!
Nailed it!
You saved me!
That was awesome!
You're not supposed to be impressed!
We were about to be digested!
You just had to stroll right
by that monster, didn't you?!
Well, I didn't see it there...
How do you miss something that huge?!
Hey, not that it matters, but
you're sitting on something.
Huh?
Gah! I crushed a human!
I'm sorry! Are you okay?
Oh, no, it's okay... More
importantly, are you...
Please snap out of it! Are you okay?
Is that...
...a tail fin?
No way... It's really...
A mermaid?!
Please save my friend, Hatchin!
Leave it to us!
We just have to knock out
that guy in the mask, right?
He's the boss of the Flying
Fish Riders, Duval!
I've been waiting.
I'll kill him.
I'll kill the man who ruined my life!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hatred for the Straw Hats!
Iron Mask Duval Appears!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!