Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal,
they landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts,  one
burning, the other frozen.
A branch of the Navy - G-5
- led by Smoker reached
the island while chasing after the Straw Hats
and got into a fight with Trafalgar
Law who appeared out of nowhere.
Scalpel!
My heart!
The Master was our warm-hearted savior!
Master!!
Punk Hazard is our Master's property now!
Rejoice!
The Master is still doing research
today for the future of mankind!
He needs only a few guinea
pigs and you can become one!
You can't get away!
"Chopper's Fury! The Master's
Inhumane Experiment!"
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST
AND SECOND LABORATORY
Master!
What a great guy!
Yes, the Master is a wonderful person.
The Master is super!
--He's merciful!
--The human race's last hope!
We don't know him that well.
Hey, are you listening?
--We!
--Love!
Master... Wow!
What the hell?!
I got puffed up!
A fuzzball!
That's Guard Boost! You can
turn into six forms at will.
--What an unstable body!
--Get used to it.
You fools! Stop playing with my body!
What?! The samurai left?!
Yes.
Damn! I thought he was too quiet!
When I said I saw a torso earlier,
he asked me where in detail.
I told him I lost it around the
lake and he went storming off.
I wasn't paying attention being
fascinated with Nami-san's sexy body!
Why does it matter to you?
He was only a head and couldn't move.
I'm the one who brought him with us.
I couldn't leave him alone
so I'm responsible for him.
If something happens to him, it's my fault.
I see. Although he is a samurai,
he can't use a sword without his
torso so all he can do is run.
Do you wanna go honor your responsibility?
Boy, that fool!
Luffy, I'll be right back, okay?
Yeah, okay!
I'll show you the way so...
can I see your panties?
Of course! Oh yeah, let's get a camera!
Wait, you fools!
Zoro, you gotta go with them!
If Zoro is there, Sanji-kun will
be arguing with him all the time!
Because you're such an idiot,
I was forced to go look for the
stinking samurai, too, you perv!
Do you think I wanted this?!
I don't wanna be with a dumb-ass who
I can't share this happiness with!
She only hit me.
Are you all worrying if my bones got broken?
No, the only thing that was broken
is my will to see panties.
They look so happy.
Yeah, they're full of energy.
They don't look like they're sick at all.
I'm gonna look into their sickness.
Is there anything I can do?
There is. I need samples of their sweat.
Can you collect some for me?
All done!
Sis.
Mocha.
Do you think I'm gonna get better?
Do you think I can see my dad and mom?
Don't worry.
I will take you back to
your family at any price.
Uh-huh.
Now, let's talk about what we are gonna do.
First of all, get us back to
normal as soon as possible!
I don't wanna be a pervert anymore!
Hey, hey, you're overpraising me!
Don't ever smile like that
with Chopper's face! Ever!
But what should we do with those brats?
They're such a pain in the ass!
Franky, I don't want you to say a
single word while you're in his body.
Ever!
Let's have a snowball fight, Synd!
What's the matter? Are you okay?
I can't breathe...
What's wrong? Synd, you're acting strange.
No...
This can't be!
How is it going, Racoon-chan?
Well, we'll see soon.
What?! This is...
What's wrong, Synd?
Are you in pain?
Are you okay?
What? What?
I can't breathe!
Chopper, he's saying he can't breathe.
Help him.
Mocha!
What happened, everybody?!
Dolan, too?!
They're collapsing! Mostly the giant ones!
What's going on?!
Chopper, what was it? Are they really sick?
No.
What?
Synd, is there something you want now?
What do you usually do at this time of day?
Usually?
We have a checkup and...
...after that...
What do you do after that?
I get a candy.
A candy?
It tastes good.
We all love that candy.
And it's fun, too.
What?
Because smoke comes out of it.
Oh yeah... When I eat that candy...
When I eat that candy,
I... I feel happy so...
...that might help me now!
Was your name Brownbeard?
What do you know about this?!
These children are not sick!
What are you saying?
I work outside so I don't know much
about what's going on in the laboratory
but those brats have an intractable disease!
Kids, stay with us!
Hey Chopper, even the smaller
ones are suffering now!
What the hell is this Master guy thinking?!
What do you mean by that?
Do you have a problem with our Master?
The merciful Master was
kind enough to take them in
and try to save them with
his medicinal skills!
He's a scientist of love!
--I can't breathe!
--Ally!
Look! In fact, they're suffering now
because they left the laboratory
and they haven't gotten
their treatment for today!
You're wrong!
Chopper, did you find out something?!
NHC10.
I detected it in their body.
Although it was just a trace amount, it's...
...a drug!
A drug?!
Only select doctors in a few
countries are allowed to use it!
I knew about it because
Doctrine was using it.
Even for its intended
purpose - to cure diseases,
it's used sparingly because
it's highly addictive!
These children were taking a
small amount of it everyday
and became chronically addicted.
They crave another dose to ease the pain.
Why is he doing this to
these little children?!
So they can't get out of the lab?!
What does your "savior" want to do...
...with these poor children?!
Hey, stop slandering our
Master or I'll beat you up!
Chopper! What should we do?!
The kids are collapsing one after another!
The candy...
Do you want a candy?
Do you want me to go get it from the lab?
No!
We can never let them eat that candy again!
I guess they were ingesting the
drug like that without knowing!
Straw Hat bro!
Are you gonna go get me the candy?
No, I can't! If Chopper says "No," I can't!
He is our doctor. Trust him!
Why?
Why?!
What happened to you, Synd?!
I'm scared!
You said you're gonna go get it for me!
You said you're gonna get it!
You said you're gonna go get it for me!!
Luffy!
Where is this strength coming from?!
Synd, stop!
I've never seen Synd get so violent!
What power!
It's no wonder if he's a Giant!
That strong?!
Why can't I have the candy?!
--Synd is not a Giant!
--What?!
When we came to this island,
we were all normal-sized.
I thought we had a disease
which makes us grow too big.
There's nothing wrong
with us other than that!
There isn't such a disease that'd
turn an ordinary person into a Giant!
Big people are big from the beginning!
Those of us who've been here
longer have a bigger body!
That means...
...they didn't always have a problem with
the oversecretion of pituitary hormones.
The candy!
These children are...
…test subjects!
The candy!
Don't lose your mind, Ally!
I want the candy!
What does the Master guy want?
By manipulating such little
children with drugs?
The candy!
Other kids are losing it, too!
We can't do anything!
Nami!
--Synd, don't!
--Hey, can I stop him?!
No! Move out of my way, Luffy!
Usopp, don't hurt them!
Dammit! I know!
Special Attack - Sleep Star!
All right! They are all sleeping now.
So they were all kidnapped as I thought.
Get us out of here!
I want to see my father and my mother!
Luffy.
These kids are going through
such a horrible ordeal...
...without knowing anything
and it breaks my heart!
They said they want to go
home and see their parents!
We've got to help them!
Luffy! I wanna help them, too!
Alright, let's take them
all to their parents.
Fool! It's not that easy! We
have a mountain of problems.
He's right. Plus, it's just speculation now.
Nothing can be solved until
we see the ringleader.
The Master guy, huh?
But Zoro, Sanji, and Brook went
out looking for the samurai so...
Well, that's okay!
All right!
Let's go to the laboratory to see the Master!
--I'll stay here.
--What?
I really can't stomach what
the Master guy is doing
and I wanna kick his ass!
But I can't leave these kids
here. I have to look after them.
Y-Yeah, h-he's right!
Then, I'll stay here, too!
Hey, Nami! That's not
fair! You're just scared!
But it'll be crazy if they go wild again.
Let's leave the big ones like this.
I feel a little bad about this.
We have no choice. They go wild
like heavyweight fighters.
And we don't know when they're gonna wake up.
What should we do about the
body shuffle situation?
I assume we can't go back to
normal unless the four of us
see Trafalgar together.
Why bother? Just leave it like it is.
No way! You gotta make it right!
The Master is a warm-hearted savior.
I trust you, Master!
Hey! Samurai-san!
Where are you?!
If only we could find traces
of his wooden clogs.
So heavy!
My breasts are heavy when I run!
I thought you wanted to save that samurai!
Oh no!
How romantic!
No, fool!
I don't care if you fall down!
You jerk! Treat Nami-san's
body more carefully!
Hey, you two! Take a look at this!
There is a footprint!
A trace of his wooden clogs?
It's nothing like that!
Then, it must be some centaur's footprint.
No!
Th-This is...
The Navy G-5 Vice Admiral Smoker's heart!
What a nice gift, Law.
The fight is over.
Since they lost their warship,
they will come to steal our
ship here to make a report.
Of course, that's already been taken care of.
What about Straw Hat-ya's group?
Don't worry about them, either.
We will get rid of them soon
and take back those kids.
I mean, I know those brats will have an
urge to come back here even
if we don't do anything.
But since Monet told me to be
careful with the Straw Hats,
I sent those two just to make sure.
They never miss their target!
The Snow Mountain Killers!
Yeti...
...Cool Brothers!
There are six more.
I thought they would be stronger than that.
Let's just finish them all off.
Like we took down those three...
We'll do it in a cool way!
Luffy and crew hurry to the
laboratory to see the Master.
In their absence, Nami and Chopper
stay behind to watch the children,
when suddenly, invisible assassins attack!
By the time Luffy realizes what's going on,
the two are facing a life-or-death situation.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To Annihilate the Straw Hats!
Legendary Assassins Descend!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!