Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that's what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
Wanted->means Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
we go!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and were drawn into a climactic
battle on Punk Hazard
which ended with Caesar's capture.
Then, they left the island
along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Law. However...
Law is different but Straw Hat
is just an ordinary pirate.
Where did they go, you bastards?!
Come to think of it,
you were talking on the
Transponder Snail earlier.
Who were you talking to?
That was Doflamingo.
His underground alias is Joker.
And Joker's most important
business partner now is...
...one of the Four Emperor -
Kaido, the King of the Beasts.
Our target.
There is no way to find
out who knows what.
That's why, Law, Straw
Hat, and you soldiers,
I'm gonna kill you all!
No!
Whoa-whoa.
Excuse me, young man.
Could you step aside?
He is my...
...friend.
"Intense!
Aokiji vs. Doflamingo!"
Is that the former admiral - Aokiji?!
I thought he disappeared
after Akainu beat him!
Young Master!
Young Master-sama!
Th-Thank god-dasuyan!
He didn't get frozen to the bone!
Young Master-sama!
Smo-yan!
I'm not interested in fighting you.
But if I can't silence that guy,
I have to change my plan.
Can I ask you something?
What is your...
...current status, Kuzan?!
Your reputation is sullied.
Hey, treat him already!
Y-Yes, sir!
There is a difference between
the look of an ordinary vagabond
and that of a determined man.
I never thought that the World
Government was almighty.
There are things I can do
without belonging to the Navy.
There are things I can see now
because I'm not part of the Navy.
I was dead for a moment.
Maybe I was fated to come here.
What brought you here?
I came here to see you.
How did you know that I'd be here?
Don't tell me
you have something to do with
the underground community now.
Th-The former admiral has
something to do with...
If you're done with the
treatment, go away!
I'm still me, Smoker.
Then I have no qualms.
Anyway, you guys should
keep an eye on Doflamingo.
He's a Warlord and the
king of Dressrosa.
He's an unusual pirate in many ways,
but not like the Snake Princess of the Kuja.
Tell Sakazuki and get the
admirals into action.
In the worst-case scenario,
things could go very wrong, very quickly,
and it would become the most
serious matter Sakazuki faced
since taking over Navy HQ.
I warned you.
Hey, guys!
You have to keep it...
I mean, you know.
What was it?
I forgot. Who cares.
Yes, we'll keep it
secret that we saw you!
Doflamingo.
Joker.
His underground alias is Joker.
And Joker's most important
business partner now is...
...one of the Four Emperor -
Kaido, the King of the Beasts.
Our target.
What?! K-Kaido?!
Kaido?!
What's the matter?
Never mind. Go on.
Why is there a dragon here?!
Where did Momonosuke go?!
That's him.
Th-This dragon is Momonosuke?
Uh-huh.
What?! What happened to you?!
Kaido of the Four Emperors.
In order to take him down,
we have to weaken his forces.
Kaido is buying a large amount
of fruit from Joker now.
It's a Zoan-type, man-made
Devil Fruit - SMILE.
M-Man-made?!
If such a thing exists,
the number of Devil Fruit
eaters will keep multiplying!
That's right.
Don't say it so casually!
Since it's man-made, however,
it seems like there are some risks involved.
But, in fact, Kaido has
more than 500 Devil Fruit
eaters in his pirate group.
Who doesn't wanna do this?! I don't!
--I don't!
Shut up.
But Devil Fruit eaters
won't multiply anymore.
Really? Him?
Were you making a substance
for the man-made Devil Fruit?
How cool! SAD!
I can't believe it.
Don't praise him!
Is it that hard to make the SAD thing?
He just put Vegapunk's discovery
of "lineage factor" into practice.
So Vegapunk is the smart one.
He's just a piece of shit.
Shut up, you bastards!
Can you fools even make it?!
Don't ever call us "fools"!
Joker is finished.
We're gonna go onto the next move.
There is a factory manufacturing SMILEs
somewhere on Dressrosa.
We should just find it and destroy it?
That's right.
Then, Kaido's forces won't strengthen.
However, he's a professional
businessman.
I'm sure he'll retaliate.
Dressrosa, huh?
Is that where you wanna go, Kin?
Indeed!
They're keeping one of
my comrades prisoner.
Oh, something is falling.
What are those clouds?
It's gonna start raining.
It's not rain, it's hail (arare).
Oh (ara).
This is...
Nami!
What's wrong?
Is there something to those clouds?
Franky, prepare for Coup de Burst!
Okay, I got it!
Somebody, take the helm!
I'll take it!
We gotta furl the sails!
I wonder what those clouds are.
Hard aport! Coup de
Burst toward 9 o'clock!
Head for an area with no clouds!
Alright!
No, don't! No, no, don't!
Coup de Burst!
That was close!
W-We're flying!
We got away!
That was close!
Thanks, Nami-san!
Are you guys trying to kill me?!
Oh, that was fun!
Momo, did you like it?
Don't you think this ship is cool?!
I-It is cool!
Nothing is impossible
for the Thousand Sunny that I built!
It's super, isn't it?!
It is super!
Momo-chan, do you wanna
look around the ship?
I'll give you a tour.
Really?! Alright, you may!
When did you turn back to yourself?
Let's go!
All right!
It's already late! No one has come!
Yes, sir! I didn't see anybody!
Uh-huh. Good job!
Thank you, sir!
Hey, do you think they
can still find us?
How many people are looking for us?!
Tens of thousands?
I can't stop worrying
since I heard you blackmailed Doflamingo!
Me, neither, you fool!
Kin gave us armor and some helmets.
Just let it go!
Resign from the Warlords
or fight one of the Emperors.
Nobody can choose between those options.
He'll just come to kill us.
I'm scared!
You bastard! Fight me squarely!
Stop!
I said it's a long story!
--Cut it out!
--Stop!
Come on! It's dangerous
to fight on the ship!
Oh, are you playing samurai?!
Fight, fight!
You should be ashamed of yourself!
The whole country was left heartbroken!
The grave of the Wano Kingdom's hero,
left plundered by a thief!
That was you!
I said I didn't do it!
You must have! You have
legendary swordsman
Ryuma's great sword Shusui on your belt!
Come on, come on! Fight, fight!
Just cut him already!
Who wants to eat a midnight snack?
Oh! What is it?!
Pizza.
Pida?
I don't know what that is
but if he cooked it, it should be good.
Momonosuke went to bed already?
He's taking a bath with Robin.
What?!
You haven't taken a bath
for days, have you?
Nope.
Did you get all warmed up?
Uh-huh. Not bad.
You came at just the right time!
Kin'emon-san, he needs a kimono.
What are you doing, you dirty brat!
It's not fair!
You're taking full advantage
of being a child!
Just cut off your top-knot!
Hey! Why did you gang up on a child?!
No, it's not what you think, Nami-san!
Men are all...
I was scared, beautiful princess!
Beautiful princess?!
Don't be so honest!
You're such a lovely boy!
You sleep in our room, Momo-chan!
What?!
They'll let him in the girls'
room - the secret garden?!
What?!
You're the worst, you brat!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Clank.
Oh really? You found them?