Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fish-Man Pirates.
Luffy finally defeated
Hordy in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot.
There's the Sunny!
Franky's there!
Looks like he's ready to go!
Here we go finally!
"Finally Time to Go!
Goodbye, Fish-Man Island!"
THE FISH-MAN ISLAND--CORAL
HILL "MERMAID CAFE"
Madam Sharley,
Luffy-chin and his friends
are leaving the island.
Oh yeah? Why don't you go and send them off?
Okay!
Madam! Can we go, too?!
What? We'd need to close the cafe then.
Tourists will start coming back
since that stupid Hordy is gone.
So I need you to give your best
for the cafe like before, girls.
You can count on us, Madam!
What? The crystal ball?
Don't worry. I won't need it again.
I will never again try to see the future.
Straw Hat destroying the Fish-Man Island...
I never wanted to see such a horrible future.
I'll be so happy if my prevision
is not accurate this time.
She is more afraid than anybody because
she knows it was always accurate.
The future she saw may not happen soon.
It could be a year from now or more.
There is no reason to
believe it wasn't accurate.
But, Madam, Luffy-chin and his
friends would never do such...
Camie!
Forgive me for suspecting your friends.
I know what you want to say. I can
trust the Straw Hat boy, right?
Uh-huh!
These are some gifts! Take them!
Yeah, thanks!
Luffy-sama and everybody, are
you really going to leave now?!
We just became friends! Stay
here at least one more day!
No! A week!
No! Just one more year!
You've been crying since the
first time we met, Yowahoshi!
I-I am sorry!
I will stop being a crybaby!
I never thought the day like this would come!
The Mermaid Princess of the Fish-Man Island
who I've dreamed about is
crying as we're leaving!
Sanji-kun!
I wanna live here for a year or two!
Yes, me too!
I sing about a dream life on the
Fish-Man Island on my latest single!
When you wake up in the morning you
say "Good mor-ningyo (mermaid)!"
--In the cafe at the night, you say "Good eve-ningyo!"
--Oh, my Mermaids!
That's a good idea!
Why don't you stay here, Nosebleed-kun?
What did you just call me, Moss Head?!
Who are you calling Moss Head, you fool?!
Your Majesty.
We have to tell them.
About the Tamate Box that
they gave to Big Mam.
When someone opens it, there
will be a huge explosion!
But, look at that!
We're doomed! One of the Four
Emperors wants to kill us!
We're gonna go to the New World just to die!
Do you think she'll forgive us
if we send all the treasures
that we get from now on?!
We cannot tell them that they
already sent her a bomb!
But those explosives are 10 years old.
Maybe they won't explode,
Minister of the Right.
Your Majesty, you are so positive!
Yes, the Ryugu Palace is very humid
and we don't even know if Big
Mam is going to open it herself!
Then let's just hope for their safety!
What are you two whispering about?
What is this?
It's a Log Pose for the New
World. Take it with you.
I cannot believe you were going to
go there with a single-needle one!
Oh, what's that?
A new Log Pose? Wow, that's cool!
There are 3 needles. Why?
Look at the Log Pose that
you have been using.
It's still moving a little bit! I thought
it gathered enough logs already.
It did. And from now on, it would
take only half a day to record logs.
On the first half of the Grand Line,
you let the Log Pose record the
magnetic waves of the next island
and navigated your ship as it told you.
But on the second half of
the Grand Line, on top of the
sea current and the climate,
there are some islands that change their
magnetic waves, the only thing
you can normally count on.
And for some islands, the
magnetic waves just disappear.
What?! Then we can't reach those islands!
If you only have one
needle, you will get lost.
But what if you have 3 needles?
One of them is moving just
like the old one but...
…the other two look settled.
They each record the magnetic
waves from different islands.
That means you can choose whichever
your gut tells you and advance.
Whether you live or die hangs on that point.
A good navigator can tell
which way is safer to go
by looking at slight
movements of the needles.
What it basically tells you is
the wilder the needle moves,
the more dangerous the island is!
Something is happening on the island
that is causing the change
in its magnetic waves.
What?! I don't like this! I'd
rather not know about it!
You'll see if it's dangerous?!
No way! Break that Log Pose!
Why? You have to navigate
safely in order to stay alive.
Let's see.
D-Dammit!
No!
The one in the middle is wobbling a
lot! That must be where the party is!
H-H-He was listening!
Luffy! You stay quiet!
I'll choose which way to go from now on!
No way! I'm the captain!
Please Captain! Listen to what
the navigator has to say!
Nami-san's so cute when she gets frightened!
So cute! So cute...
The B-side of the single
is "The Requiem for Us"!
All right, guys!
We're ready to go!
Den-san taught me how to ascend too!
Shall we go?
Okay!
Let's go!
Luffy-chin!
Straw!
I'm gonna help with repairing the factory!
Are you gonna be okay without a guide?
We're fine! We had a lot
of fun on our way here!
Yeah, he's right! We don't need a guide!
Man's journey always ends up in hell!
Yeah, yeah! We want a war, you bastard!
How desperate.
Everybody! Come visit someday!
I'll come back!
You're the "All Blue" of my heart!
What a cheap dream.
All I want to say is "Thank you"!
I will pray for your safe trip!
Uh-huh!
Next time we see you, we will lead
the strongest army on the seafloor!
Ooh mambo!
He's right!
We will become greater than the
Great Knight Neptune-mi-fa-so-la-ti-do!
Can't wait!
Um, where is he?
There you are!
Jimbei!
All right! Spread the sail!
Let's set sail!
Straw Hat!
See you, Fish-Man Island!
Alright, here we go!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Come to eat sweets and meat anytime!
I like humans now!
Racoons and robots too!
Like I give a damn, you jerk!
Huh? Oh? What about bones?
Take care, Luffy-chin and everybody!
Come to eat octopus balls again!
You guys! I love you all!
1, 2, 3!
We like bones too!
Thank you for your concern!
Princess-sama!
Luffy-sama!
Yowahoshi!
Shirahoshi-chan!
If I can see you again someday,
I promise I won't be a crybaby!
Take me out for a fun stroll again!
A stroll? Do you wanna go to
your mother's grave again?
No. I want to go somewhere further next time!
I want to go to a real forest above ground!
Oh yeah, you've never been
out of the sea, have you?
Okay, fine!
I'll take you there next time!
Will you promise?
Yeah, trust me!
I promise!
Hey, Luffy! We have to help
you keep that promise.
Luffy-san, a promise is something
you have to keep at any cost.
Then, Shirahoshi, I promise you too!
Nami-chin-sama!
Me too!
Okay, me too!
Me too, of course!
We all promise her so...
...We won't let her down!
We promise!
E-Everybody!
So don't cry anymore!
Okay!
Do not ever forget their kindness.
Of course!
Hey, Dad, Dad!
Buy me a straw hat! I wanna
pretend I'm the hero!
What? They only sell it above ground!
Buy one above ground then!
No way!
There are horrible humans
who hate Fish-Men above...
What?
Oh, I mean, I heard some
of them are like that...
Of course, there are good and
strong humans like Straw Hat, too.
Oh, Boss Jimbei! You came at the right time!
I heard what you were talking about.
I will tell a merchant to get
his hands on some of those.
Really?!
Yes, what you want is that hero's hat, right?
Uh-huh!
I had a wonderful time!
The Mermaid Paradise!
Now everybody, pull yourself together!
There is no safe place once we sail out!
We have to pass though the dark water again.
What is that, Franky?
I'm gonna make the ship float with
buoyant square logs of hollow Banyan.
I can adjust the speed by how many I put out.
What's the matter, Luffy?
If we ascend here,
we'll be at the sea where Shanks is!
I wanna see him!
In that case...
...I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Come bring it back to me someday!
Once you've become a great pirate!
There is one thing that makes me wanna stay.
That is my desire to see
you fulfill your dream.
But I'm sure that you can do it!
Because you're my brother!
Don't just think about the ones you've lost!
You can't get back what you've lost!
What is it that you still have?!
Rise to the top!
Luffy-san! Do you know what they call
the second half of the Grand Line?
People call the final sea beyond
the Red Line by another name.
"The New World."
It's the sea where pirates who will open
the way to the next generation gather.
The pirate who conquers the sea will
become the King of the Pirates!
Once we pass through this deep sea,
we'll get to the ultimate sea!
Finally! I'll cut everything away!
Wait for me, Laboon! One more half to go!
Count on me! I'll navigate
you anywhere you want!
That's right! The Sunny can do it!
I'll heal you no matter how wounded you are!
You'll never go hungry while I'm here!
You've got the warrior of the sea here too!
Let's go!
Guys!
To the New World!
Yeah!
The Straw Hats depart Fish-Man Island
and rise up out of the sea.
But it's the harshest
ocean of the Grand Line.
On the voyage up to the New World...
...they come across hardship after hardship.
As the crew is tossed about...
...by a killer underwater whirlpool...
...an unimaginable sight appears before them.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To the New World! Heading for the Ultimate Sea!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!