Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has made it aboard a Navy ship
in order to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been taken to the Navy HQ!
There is nothing but despair ahead for you!
You can't get away no
matter how you struggle!
Can't you see that it's no
use? For pirates like you...
...The Gate of Justice won't open!
Are you sure about opening the gate?
Warden Magellan!
Bon-chan is...
It's me!
Bon-chan!　Bon-chan!
Bon-chan, the gate's closing.
We...
...have to go.
Thank you!
--The gate is closing!
--We gotta sink them!
Do you wanna say something before you die?!
This is what I wanted!
Luffy has broken out of the world's
greatest prison Impel Down!
But the end is nowhere in sight...
"To the Navy Headquarters!
Off to Rescue Ace!"
Why do you want to live so dangerously?
If I hadn't come here with an antidote,
LEVEL 4 BURNING HEAT HELL
you guys would be dead.
You can't underestimate Magellan.
But we're alive!
The fact that you came down
here is a part of our fate.
But you're right! I thought
I was going to die!
We are...
...lucky.
Whether you die or not--it's up to God!
Those who harbor fear will lose!
We just need to live in the moment!
Don't we, Shiryu?!
I'm grateful for your
help! You have my thanks!
And again, welcome to our gang! I think
that we're gonna make a great team!
My future here is predictable.
I've been waiting to meet someone like you.
THE SHIP ROUTES OF THE WORLD
GOVERNMENT TUB CURRENT
All right, everyone!
Let's toast to our unprecedented
unheard-of breakout of Impel Down!
--Cheers!
Oh, that's good!
We'll have to do it without
Inazuma from here.
What?! The infection is really that bad?!
I was infected with just
one kind of poison and...
...got it out of my system using my
Healing Hormone and Energy Hormone.
Heehaw!
But it's complicated because...
...one will take years off my life but
the other causes severe side effects!
It's better if he can rest
and recover naturally.
Nothing can help you to regain
years lost by using the hormone!
Inazuma is an indispensable New
Kama of the revolutionary army!
We shouldn't allow him
to push himself too hard!
When I think about it, he
wasn't a bad guy after all.
I was looking forward to seeing him again...
But once more, he rushed to our aid!
Bon-chan!
--Brother Bon!
--Bon-chan!
Bon-chan!
Hey, how long are you gonna
mourn like that, guys?!
He was great but he's dead
and nothing can't change it!
Let's just party!
It's a breakout party!
Oh yeah, let's celebrate it
as a funeral for Mr. 2...
I knew I'd fall into the red!
We don't know if Bon-chan's
dead yet, you, big nose!
What did you just say?!
Your nose is red, round and stupid!
Well, your face is rubbery,
stretchy and stupid!
What'd you say?!
I couldn't care less about them...
I thought that talking to fish was
the special ability of Mermaids only.
But you can call out to sharks, too.
Is it so weird for a Fish-Man
to be a friend of fish?
Well, I can say that it's not normal.
I guess that you're a misfit...
...of the violent species.
I take it as a compliment.
I can't deny the fact that
Fish-Men are violent.
Bon-chan's not dead!
Oh! Captain Buggy grew another red nose!
Luffy-kun.
You gave me an opportunity to save Ace-san.
I owe you a great debt.
Don't think of it in terms like
that. There'd be no end to it!
For me, it's just encouraging to
have you along! You're so strong!
I want to thank you and apologize
to you for the other case before this.
But, not today. There is
something more important now.
You can call me Jimbei!
I'm a Warlord but I'm sure
they'll revoke my title!
So let's run wild at the Navy Headquarters!
We have to live up to the expectations of...
...that Queer-kun and rescue
Ace-san at any cost!
--A Warlord?
--The Navy Headquarters?
What?!
Hey you! You're a Warlord?!
No wonder you're so strong!
Sorry that I hadn't introduced myself yet!
Everyone else knows that.
Hey! What's that about
the Navy Headquarters?!
Don't tell me that we're heading
to the Navy Headquarters!
--Yes, we are!
--No!
I know that you guys know about the
war between Whitebeard and the Navy!
--What'd you say?
--The Navy HQ?
It's obvious. It's your faults
for being so clueless.
What?!
We passed through the Gate of Justice.
That means our destination must be
either the Navy HQ or Enies Lobby.
The Tub Current that we're on
is exclusive to the Government.
It's a giant whirlpool that connects
the Government's 3 major facilities
We wanted to break out because
we have a role in the war.
Yeah! The real fight is on its way!
"The real fight is on its way?!"
W-We didn't know about this!
--Stop the ship right now, you bastard!
--Stop!
We can't stop because we are on the current!
Why don't you guys get off?!
--Okay, bye!
--Yeah, bye!
No, we can't!
Devil Fruit eaters
like us will definitely be killed!
The Navy HQ and The Seven Warlords
versus the Whitebeard Pirates?!
That's more horrifying than hell!
I wanna go back to the prison
rather than entering this war!
Us from the Kama Land knew it.
Why didn't you tell us then?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
We can't escape death this time!
Mom!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Hey, do you hear something?
--It's a Transponder Snail!
--Who's calling?
Don't you get it? This is a Navy ship!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Why don't we just pretend we're not here?
--Clank!
--Hello?
He picked up!
This is the Navy HQ.
Oh, this is Luffy.
Don't give your name like that!
We know that the ship has
been taken by escapees.
We received a report from the
Fleet Escort Force at Impel Down.
We determined who the two main suspects
of this great escape case were...
...from the insider information
before contact was lost.
Two?
A pirate--Straw Hat Luffy!
And another pirate Buggy the Clown!
-- What?!
-- W-What?!
No way!
Captain Buggy is the main suspect
although there're Warlords here?!
Who the hell are you?!
Why me?!
--Let me see the documents.
--Here you go.
We thought that you were
just a nameless pirate.
Buggy the Clown, I can't believe that...
...you were a crew member under
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
How'd you know that?
What?!
--"The ship" - that means Oro Jackson?!
--He's kick-ass!
He's a star! A star among pirates!
We also know that you're a sworn
brother of "Red-Haired" Shanks,
one of the Four Emperors.
What?!
How could someone like this
have laid low until now...
...without raising any alarms.
But now, you've made yourself known.
Well...
We can't see clearly your
connection with "Fire Fist" Ace
but we're sure that your goal is
the same as Straw Hat Ace's rescue!
Well... I don't really...
We know that you have
Jimbei, Crocodile, Ivankov,
and more than 200 ruffians who
are also escapees on board.
I warn you.
As long as we don't open the Gate of
Justice, you guys can't get to Marineford
or even get out of the Tub Current!
There is no sea for you all
to get away to or to live on!
Better make yourselves
comfortable! That's it.
Hey wait, Navy!
I'm gonna rescue Ace at any cost!
"Wash your potatoes" and be ready for us!
Potatoes?
Clank!
The expression should be "watch your neck!"
You don't wash your potatoes and
boil them at a time like this!
First of all, why did he try to
pick a fight with the Navy HQ?!
Wait, before that... Captain Buggy!
Were you really a member of the crew?!
And a sworn brother of "Red-Haired?!"
Our savior is a hell of
a pirate as we thought!
Oh, well...
Damn! If word gets around, the
Government will keep an eye on me!
So that's his background!
And yet, he's so weak.
With such a pedigree, how
could you be so dirty?!
So every ship has at least one blemish!
Shut up!
I didn't know that. But I remember...
Have you also heard of the East
Blue pirate known as Buggy?
The Vice Captain old man was saying that.
Huh? The Vice Captain?
The old man called Rayleigh,
I bet you know him.
What?! Have you seen Rayleigh-san?!
I miss Vice Captain! Where'd you see him?
They're talking about "Dark King"
Rayleigh! What a conversation!
Captain Buggy! I knew you were something!
No no, wait a second! It's all true but...
...if you spread this around, it'll
be bad for my future as a pirate!
It's amazing that you were the
member of the legendary pirates!
Buggy! Buggy!
H-Hey, you fools...
Stop it! I was an apprentice to be exact!
I don't want you to make
a lion of me with that...
Hey, you got the wrong idea!
Well, I don't feel so bad...
Oh yeah, wait a minute!
The Navy has overestimated me for
sure but it's not such a bad thing!
Yeah! Because it's all true!
I'm developing a reputation here!
If by some chance, I could...
If I could beat Whitebeard,
then I'd become the one of...
...the Four Emperors!
Oh no no no... I'd go way
beyond that and become...
...the King of the Pirates!
Yeah! These guys might have
higher bounties than me!
If I play my cards right...
...I can do this!
Captain Buggy! We'll follow
you the rest of our lives!
Give us an order!
Let's steal this ship from the ones
who want to go to the Navy HQ!
And then, we're gonna be free!
Well, Straw Hat! You need to
give over this ship to us!
After breaking out, we don't
wanna go to the Navy HQ!
We got Captain Buggy on our side!
Go ahead, Captain Buggy!
--Buggy! Buggy!
--This is no good.
It's better to just kill them all.
Yeah, I feel like I can do it!
Be quiet, you flashy fools!
You guys are all full of whim and fancy!
This ship won't stop!
We're
heading to the center of the war!
And you guys are already on board!
Brace yourselves and think about it!
Soon, the man at the top of the
world is gonna show up in our midst!
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance.
If you guys are real men, why don't
you live out a dream with me?!
Today...
I'll beat Whitebeard which means
that I'll conquer the world!
Yeah! Captain Buggy!
Captain Buggy!
We were devastated by the darkness of hell...
...And we almost lost the
most important thing!
Losing the jewels of our hearts
that we once had - called dream!
I will follow you!
I don't want a peaceful life!
That's right!
Let's go, guys! To Navy Headquarters!
Looks like it's over.
He has this kind of ability at least.
Captain Buggy! You should lead the world!
I'll follow you to the end!
Yeah, follow me!
I hope they are having fun.
The ship that carries Portgaz D. Ace
will arrive at Marineford shortly!
Here he comes, finally!
Relax and go on board!
There's room for everybody so don't worry!
Be prepared for the arrival!
NAVY
The sky island, Weatheria, still carrying
Nami, continues toward the Grand Line,
but it's traveling far too slowly.
Will Nami make it back to her friends?
And will Franky, now a gentleman,
ever return to his old self?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! The Weatheria
Report and the Cyborg Animals!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!