Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can't stand still, I can't stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
your toughness, that's what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
After leaving Punk Hazard,
the Straw Hats headed to Dressrosa.
But a mysterious man,
Breed, who leads a pack
of sea monsters made a raid on them
and kidnapped Caesar.
To take back Caesar, Luffy, Law,
and Chopper snuck into the enemy's ship.
There, they happily reunited
with a Kung Fu Dugong
who had become Luffy's disciple in Alabasta.
Pull your arm back all
the way - like this!
And use the lower half of your body!
However, Breed's Peto-Peto
Fruit power controlled
the Dugong and the others.
Breed gained control of Chopper, Luffy,
and even Law with his mysterious power.
Pet-peto!
Dammit!
I can control any living thing
and bring out all of its power!
You will see how deadly it is!
"Luffy Dies at Sea?!
The Pirate Alliance Comes Apart!"
Damn! I can't take it off!
Luffy, look up!
I can't control myself!
Damn!
Watch out!
Wait!
Chopper stopped!
You're just the bait.
My main target was you
two from the beginning.
What did you say?!
Wait!
Oh? I can't move!
Roo...
Wait!
You guys are going
to be eating out of my hand forever.
As long as I hold you two as my slaves,
there's nothing to be afraid of!
Straw Hat! Trafalgar!
Sit!
Dammit!
Shake hands!
Son of a bitch!
See what I'm capable of?!
This is the power of the Peto-Peto Fruit!
Whether you're a Warlord
or a rascal pirate
with a 400 million bounty,
you're powerless before me!
If you were an animal, you
could've become my pet.
But stinking humans like
you will become my slaves!
How cute!
I didn't realize because you
had a strange outfit on before!
Your blue nose is so cute, Raccoon-kun!
I've never had a pet like you before!
I'll dress you up right away!
Don't!
Oh, good boy, good boy, good boy!
Hey, get your hands off of Chopper!
Shut up! You two are
gonna get locked up!
Put Sea Prism Stone handcuffs on them!
It won't be long.
It won't be long
before my dream kingdom becomes reality.
Hey, Peto-guy! Let us out!
Give us back Chopper! Dammit!
You...
I'm losing my strength...
I guess the cage is...
...Made of Sea Prism Stone.
You guys are so pathetic.
Caesar!
Hey, let us out!
Shut up! Why does everybody
give me orders?!
Did he take control over you?
Yes, he did. A collar and a leash!
I feel like a pet!
But I'm a great scientist!
He said he's a Peto-Peto Fruit eater.
And with that power,
he can make people obey whatever order he gives.
Caesar, is he one of
Doflamingo's associates?
Are you stupid?
If he were, why would I be held captive still?
As far as I know,
Doflamingo doesn't have
any subordinates like him.
That guy told me he wants to create
a dream kingdom or something.
What kingdom?
How do I know?! Dammit!
It's so humiliating...
...for me to take that whip fool's orders!
Screw him!
Caesar!
Lie down!
Hey, Caesar!
I said "Lie down"! Can't you hear me?!
Dammit! That asshole! I can't take it!
You guys can't get away from me!
Now,
it's all ready!
What should I make them to do for me?
Peto-guy!
Give us back Chopper...
You shitty humans never learn.
Don't worry. Chappy's here.
Chappy?
Chappy!
I'm not Chappy!
Chopper!
Chappy!
I'm Chopper!
Chopper, what are you wearing?!
Hey, Luffy! Stop laughing!
Oh... I'm exhausted because
of the Rumble Ball...
Are you shy because you're dressed up?!
No...
Oh, somebody's in a bad mood!
Stop!
Luffy!
Don't push your luck.
You must be happy when I pet you.
Submit to my demands!
Are you okay, Chopper?!
Yeah.
Chappy, get on your knees!
Lower to the ground!
Now, it's time for discipline!
Hey, stop!
I said "Stop"!
What are you doing to my friend?!
"Friend"...
"Friend"?
"Friend"!
"Friend"!!
Cut the "friend" crap!
I don't believe in friendship!
It's not worth a damn!
Listen! All I need is...
...loyal followers - tools -
who just work for me!
I have no need for insubordinates!
Everyone should just do as
I say without complaining!
Worthless humans always
stand against me!
That's why I have no need
for their friendship!
I don't need them!
But animals... pets are different!
They just follow my orders
quietly and submissively!
Animals! Pets! They're the best!
That's why I need you.
Caesar.
To make...
...this!
Is that... SMILE?!
Where did you get it?!
I have a connection
with the underground.
I'm gonna use this Zoan type,
man-made Devil Fruit...
...to turn humans to animals forcibly!
Then there will be no more detectable,
pathetic humans in the world!
You bastard! What are you really up to?!
A kingdom.
I will create an animal-only kingdom -
without a single stinking human!
And I will conquer all the animals
using my Peto-Peto power!
I will turn them to loyal pets!
That's my dream kingdom!
Suit yourself!
But you can't make me follow anybody!
What are you talking about?!
Didn't you see what I'm capable
of with the Peto-Peto power?!
It means nothing to me!
You silly human!
Worthless humans like you should just
shut your mouths and follow my orders!
Stop resisting!
I'm a pirate!
I'm not gonna follow anybody's order!
Pirates should be free!
"Pirates"? "Free"?
I hate humans like you the most!
Alright.
I was gonna spare your
life and enslave you.
But all you damn humans
deserve death after all!
What is this place?
Where are we?!
It's showtime!
I'll show you the terror
of my Peto-Peto power!
Alright, Trafalgar, here
is my order to you!
Kill Straw Hat!
Tra-guy!
Straw Hat, I want you to kill Trafalgar!
Dammit!
No!
This is outrageous!
Go ahead and kill each other!
You can't use your Devil Fruit power though!
Punch each other to death
like idiots - just as you pathetic humans are!
Now, the bloody show begins!
Luffy! Law!
I can't believe this!
Tra-guy, it's no good!
I can't control my body!
Dammit!
Yes! This is the greatest show ever!
Damn! I can't stop myself!
I don't wanna fight you like this!
Dammit!
Get away from me!
Destroy each other! You foul humans!
The leash!
Keep fighting!
Tiptoe, stealthy steps... Goodbye!
What a fool.
He still doesn't understand
that nobody can get away from me.
Well, I'll let him go for now.
I'm enjoying this bloody show!
Seal, watch out!
Hey you, stay out of it!
Do you wanna get whipped?!
What?! Stop barking!
You fool!
Don't tell me you're
speaking against me!
Damn you!
Damn! Damn! Damn!
You idiot!
Stop!
Dugong!
Do you want to help them so bad?
Alright, if you insist, I'll stop them.
Straw Hat, Trafalgar, wait!
My body stopped.
Instead,
you do it.
Since you like them so much,
it'll be far more interesting
to see you beating them up!
Kill those two, Dugong!
Now, go!
That guy's terrible!
Seal, I'll be alright!
Do you realize what happens
if you disobey me?!
Now, throw them into the sea!
Seal!
I told you to use the lower half
of your body and pull your
arm back all the way!
But you sure got stronger!