Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
But his struggle ended in vain
and the historic War of the
Best in Marineford has ended.
However, 10 years ago, in the East Blue...
Luffy, this is Ace.
You're gonna live here with them from today.
Take me with you! Let's become friends!
It's the end of the forest.
"Here Comes Sabo! The Boy
at the Gray Terminal!"
I can't believe we earned this much!
Porchemy-san was right!
That greedy merchant begged for it when we
said that it was treasure from the Grand Line!
In fact, it was just junk that
we found washed up on the shore!
We were lucky that he was just a
coward who has never gone to sea!
Well, we've never been to sea, either!
Wow! What is this place?
There is a place like this on the North side
of Mt. Corvo where the Dadan family lives.
It is a smoky pile of discarded junk.
Unwanted things ended up here.
And here live rogues who were
shunned from mainstream society.
Unsurprisingly, it's a lawless area.
Crime and disease abound
since there are no doctors.
This place is called Gray Terminal.
Ace!
What's that?
He's not here.
Hey! Where did you go?!
Ace!
It's afternoon already.
Treasure, treasure! Is there
anything valuable here?
Here's something!
--Give it to me!
--That's mine!
Stop it! I found it!
Don't touch it, you fools!
Let me cash it in for you!
--You can't have it!
--Stop!
--Damn you!
--Give it to me!
You wouldn't have gotten hurt
if you'd just given it to me!
Thank you very much!
You asshole!
Thief!
Outta my way, brat!
Hurry up! Or I'm gonna...
He went that way!
"THE FOREST IN-BETWEEN"
MT COLVO AND GRAY TERMINAL
Sabo! Sabo, are you there?!
Oh, Ace!
Sorry I'm late.
You sure are.
I've already done some work in the city.
SABO [10 YEARS OLD] (A BOY WHO
LIVES IN THE GRAY TERMINAL)
Oh yeah? Well, I did, too.
At once!
Whoa! You got a lot! Way more than I did!
That's a lot of money! How'd you get that?
I robbed some thugs near the main gate!
Damn! You won again!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose.
It's been 5 years since we started
to put money in our "pirate savings".
We worked hard for it.
Yes, we did.
We're gonna leave the East Blue and go
somewhere these people have never dreamed of.
It's exciting just to think about it!
Now put it away. We can't
let anybody to see it.
I wonder how much we need
to get a pirate ship.
I don't know. 10 million
or 100 million maybe?
Long way to go.
"A pirate ship"?!
You guys! Are you gonna become pirates?!
I'm gonna become one, too!
--Be quiet!
Ace! I didn't know that you
travel this far everyday!
Shut up!
Is this the Luffy that
you were talking about?
Oh, you told him about me?!
I told him how annoying you are.
He also told me that you're empty-headed.
Oh yeah?
You don't realize that
we're dissing you, do you?
He finally got me here although I
didn't take any walkable routes.
Are you a friend of Ace's?
Be my friend, too, buddy!
Shut up! You can't call me "buddy"!
--Then what's your name?
--Sa...
I'm not telling you!
This is why I told you to live here with me!
The daily round trip--training on the
mountain road turned out to be bad!
What should we do?
He found our secret. He's gonna
tell somebody if nothing is done.
We gotta kill him.
Alright, let's do it.
What?!
Don't kill me!! Help me!! I don't wanna die!!
Shut up, you fool!
Sabo, kill him already!
What?! You do it!
I've never killed anybody before!
Me, neither! And I don't know how!
Don't throw me into water!!
--Okay, let's head to the river!
--Why did he tell us that?
He's stupid!
Help me!!
--Shut up!
I don't wanna die!
I hear a voice from the forest!
A kid's voice!
Oh no! Somebody's coming!
Set him free for now!
We gotta move from
here or they're gonna find our treasure!
Everybody knows those kids
around here. Ace and Sabo.
CREW MEMBER OF THE BLUEJAM PIRATES PORCHEMY
Are you sure that it was
Ace who took the money?
Yes. We're sorry. We shouldn't
let our guard down.
How outrageous that kid is!
He can't just steal our money!
If Captain Bluejam finds out about
this, he's gonna kill all of us!
Dammit! I didn't know that those
thugs were working for Bluejam!
You mean that you stole the money from them?
I shouldn't have taken that money...
He has a real sword. That's
Porchemy who works under Bluejam.
He's crazy. Did you know that?
He strips off your scalp alive
after you lose a fight with him!
Let's just let them pass for now...
Oh? Where is he?
--Let me go! What do you want from me?
--How could you get caught?
Let me go! You bastard!
Who is this little shit?
Help me! Ace!!
Help me, Ace!!
--That fool! He's calling my name!
--Help me! Ace!!
Did you just call for "Ace"?
So what?!
Do you know Ace?
I'm his friend!
Oh, but he just tried to kill me.
That fool! He's such a big mouth!
I don't know if you know about this but
I heard that Ace stole some
money from us and ran today.
You don't know where is it now, do you?
Oh no! They're gonna take
all our treasure away!
I hope that fool doesn't tell them!
So? What do you say?
--What?!
--Huh?!
I-I don't know...
A terrible liar!
Alright, alright! It can't be
helped that you don't know.
Don't worry, I'll help you
bring back the memory!
What are you doing?! Let me
go! Where are you taking me?!
Dammit! Stupid! Let me go!
You bastard! Let me go! What
are you doing, bastard?!
What should we do?!
You know what we have to do...
Let me go!
I'm not gonna tell you anything!
You little shit!
I told you that my body turned to
rubber after I ate the Gum-Gum Fruit!
Shut up!
The Devil Fruit, eh?
Looks like you had the real one.
Get me a pair of gloves.
Y-Yes, sir!
Hurry up, hurry up! We're
screwed if they come back!
We gotta move our treasure somewhere else!
It's a matter of time
before Luffy tells them!
They'll take not only what we stole from them
but all of our "pirate savings" that
we've spent 5 years collecting!
Listen, you little shit.
The money that your friend Ace stole
is very important to our pirate crew.
And you know where it is.
So I need you to tell us.
No!
It worked!
You don't wanna make a pirate mad!
Our captain Bluejam is very brutal!
It hurts! I'm scared!
Help me!!
Guys, go look for Ace and Sabo! We
don't have time to stand around!
Y-Yes, sir!
You're asking me if I know Ace and Sabo?
You guys must be hooligans from the city.
You don't wanna mess with those two.
They're kids but you
can't underestimate them.
They're like mad dogs
that'd kill even a tiger.
Ace and Sabo? I haven't
seen them for a while.
Anyway, young men, why don't you
leave everything valuable here?
--C-Come on, man!
--We'll ask someone else!
They still don't know where we are?
I thought that they'd know by now...
Oh no!
I didn't realize that it's almost night.
Yes! It's finished!
We moved all the treasure!
What's wrong with that kid?
Ace!
Sabo! What's wrong? Have they
shown up to look for the money?
No, they haven't!
And I bet they won't!
What do you mean?
That kid, Luffy...
He hasn't told them anything!
I'm sure that they're torturing him!
I thought that he'd just tell them
because he's dumb and cries so much!
It doesn't make sense!
If nothing is done, he'll...
GRAY TERMINAL "THE COVE OF PIRATES"
It's so late!
Who is in charge today?
It's Porchemy, Captain Bluejam.
It's almost sunset.
I'm sure that they've already
cashed it in by now.
CAPTAIN OF THE BLUEJAM PIRATES BLUEJAM
Maybe he's running away with the money.
No way! I don't think that he would risk
getting killed trying something like that!
I don't think so, either!
Spit it out already!
P-P-P-Porchemy-san!
It's no use doing it anymore!
He doesn't have the energy
to even scream now!
I bet he won't say anything and to be
honest, I can't stand watching it--it's too cruel!
Show some mercy!
Look for Ace and Sabo if you
have time to speak for the kid!
We're the ones that are in danger
of death! Can't you see?!
We're already too late to give
that money to Captain Bluejam!
How could they do that to the little
kid? Should we call sheriff in the city?
It's no use. This area is not
covered by the country's law.
Plus, he's a member of the Bluejam Pirates.
And they're paying money to the Nobles.
They'll be overlooked for any crime and
murder they commit in this country.
One more dead body will draw
no one's attention here.
Answer me!
I won't say it.
You little shit! Stop trying to
keep a secret like a grown-up!
Say it!!
I won't say it!
I won't say it!!
Fine. Enough.
Then you die.
Don't!
Ace and Sabo raid Porchemy's hideout to save the captured Luffy.
Despite the overwhelming strength of the pirates,
Sabo finds a moment's opportunity to free Luffy and makes a run for it,
when Ace shares a surprising resolution...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Won't Run! Ace's Desperate
Rescue Operation!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!