Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
saa yukou
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
"To Live Up to the Promise!
Departures of Their Own!"
Late in the day
on which the Celestial Dragon's
ship arrived at the Goa Kingdom,
at a small village somewhere
in the East Blue...
Did you see the person with
the gigantic face today?
Yeah, I've never seen someone like that!
Look, the ship is huge, too!
580... 581...
582... 583...
584...
You're late, Dragon! I got tired of waiting!
Sorry.
What happened?!
--Oh, that's very bad!
--Hey, treat him now!
Roger!
Honestly! Where have you been?!
I was watching the ceremony
for the Celestial Dragon.
How could you do that without telling me?
You attract too much attention.
M-My face, you mean?
We have to prepare as soon as
possible for what will come!
Do we have enough food?
They gave us some at the
training hall in the village.
Let's leave here! Head back to Baltigo!
Meanwhile, in the Goa Kingdom
after the observers from the
World Government left...
Here comes some junk!
People are doing exactly the
same thing they did before
accumulating another mountain of junk.
Here I come, Ace!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
What are you doing?! You're no match for me!
No matter how strong you are,
it's nothing if you can't hit a target!
Rubber is not useful in
fighting just as I thought!
Shut up!
What?! I'm telling you the truth!
All you can do is bounce back
attacks  and sink like a rock!
Stop making fun of the Gum-Gum
Fruit! I'll make you cry someday!
I've been creating new attacks
stronger than the pistol!
Luffy, that was great!
Your arm stretched farther than yesterday!
Sabo! You're too easy on Luffy!
I'm stronger than yesterday as I thought!
--Don't you think so, Sabo?!
Sabo was a good brother...
What?! You mean it'd be
better if I had died?!
I didn't say that!
You meant it!
Ouch!
Sabo didn't hit me like that!
--What?!
--What?! Be nice to me!
No way!
Ouch.
I HEREBY ESTABLISH AN INDEPENDENT COUNTRY
I hereby establish an independent country.
Country?!
ME TOO
Me too!
ACE'S KINGDOM--
LUFFY'S KINGDOM
ACE'S KINGDOM    LUFFY'S KINGDOM
What do you want this time?
We need to be strong enough
to live on our own!
You guys belong to Dadan's Kingdom!
Let me use your bath sometimes.
Ace! You gotta help me! It's a bear!
I thought that you wanted
to live on your own.
Dammit!
Luffy!
Hey, anybody there in Dadan's Kingdom?!
Luffy got hurt! Please help him!
Magra! Please! Treat Luffy!
Okay, okay, come in now!
Well, well, it was no joking matter.
He might have died if the
cut was a little bit deeper.
You three fought those beasts
together, didn't you?
It's my fault!
I knew it doesn't prove that you're
strong by fighting on your own!
I'm not good enough!
I'm not good enough at all!
Ace...
I'm sorry, Luffy!
I'm sorry!
Hey, guys!
Makino came all the way bringing us sake!
How to pay respect to other people?
Uh-huh.
What's gotten into you?
Since I'm Luffy's brother,
it's my job to go see the captain
of the Red-Haired Pirates
who helped Luffy in order to thank him!
Do you have something to say?!
I'm sorry. Alright, I'll teach you how.
Okay, this would be the first one...
They didn't pay!
Stop!
Oh, we forgot to do it!
Oh yeah!
--Thank you for the meal!
Shut up, you brats! You got to pay!
I'm gonna win today!
--We did it!
Bear meat stew tonight!
7 YEARS LATER
ACE, 17 YEARS OLD
LUFFY, 14 YEARS OLD
Take care, Ace!
Yeah. See you, Luffy! I'm going now!
Uh-huh! I'll be a lot stronger
when I leave here in 3 years!
Good luck, Ace!
Take care!
Don't catch a cold!
You just wait! I'll make my name soon!
Ace, the son of the King of the
Pirates, has grown up secretly
and he quietly departed from
the shore nearby Mt. Corvo.
He's gone!
Honestly! I wonder what Garp would say.
You must raise him, Dadan!
No way! Whose baby is this?
Boss!
Ace is gone!
Oh good. But I can see that
Garp will be mad at me.
He was such an useless little shit!
Oh, Ace left a message for you.
What?! He still has something to
say to me even at the last minute?!
He said "Thank you for taking care of me!"
He can't do that! That fool!
Oh? Boss, are you crying?!
I'm not crying, you fool!
I have to wait 3 years more.
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Damn! I missed it by a little.
You almost got it, Luffy!
Why don't you keep the
center of gravity lower?
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
I wanna become stronger!
A FEW MONTHS LATER
Luffy!
Look at the newspaper!
What is it?
Look here!
Wow! Ace made his name!
He got his own ship and crew!
He's great! Ace is great!
But I'm gonna top him!
3 YEARS LATER - LUFFY, 17 YEARS OLD
Hey, guys!
I'm leaving now. You're not gonna see me off?
How annoying.
The mayor and Makino won't mind,
but the people in the Windmill
Village will be scared of us.
But...
Why don't you just go already?!
Alright. Then you guys,
thank you for everything!
Don't say it - I feel awkward!
Well, well, take care!
Yeah, okay!
Oh yeah!
Dadan, I don't like mountain bandits...
Shut up, you brat!
...but I like you guys!
Stop talking nonsense and go
away already, you bastard!
Dammit! Why am I surrounded by such fools?!
Oh, you crying?
I'm not crying!
Windmill Village at the edge of
Goa Kingdom on the Dawn Island.
Hey, why don't you take my
old fishing boat, Luffy?
That thing is gonna sink any minute!
That's a small boat...
This is fine! This is
what I wanna start with!
Sabo!
Watch over me! I'm gonna go out to sea now!
Sabo was first and Ace was second.
And I'm third but I'm gonna
top them!
Wait for me, Ace!
I'll catch up with you soon!
What are you doing screaming and mumbling?
Is it some kind of incantation?
No, it's not! It's a challenge!
--Who's Ace?
--No idea.
Alright, I'm going now!
He's finally leaving,
mayor. I'm gonna miss him.
It's a dishonor to the
village to become a pirate!
What nice day for setting sail!
Th-That's...!
Here comes our local sea monster!
You don't know who you're messing with.
Look at this technique I've
been training for 10 years!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
That will learn ya, stupid fish!
Wow! He beat the sea monster
with a single blow!
He's become quite strong!
Let's start with finding a crew!
I want at least 10 of them.
And the black flag!
Alright! Let's go!
I'm gonna become...
...the King of the Pirates!
And now,
Luffy mourns the loss of his brother Ace.
Luffy-kun...
The King of the Pirates?!
I'm...
I'm too...
...weak!!
As Garp returns to Windmill Village,
Dadan greets him in outrage.
Meanwhile, Luffy is lost in his grief
and helplessness after losing Ace.
As he watches Luffy writhe in despair,
Jimbei recalls the words of Ace...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Want to See Them! Luffy's Mournful Cry!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!