Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight fierce battles
among other tough contenders from the New World.
"Chinjao the Drill."
That's what they used to
call me but not anymore.
Answer me!
Do you know what Garp has done to me?!
I told you - I don't know!
Since you're that bastard Garp's grandson,
I can't just let you walk away
because you have no idea!
For 30 years,
I've been holding a grudge!
Say it, Straw Hat!
What has Garp done to me?!
What did he take away from me?!
Hey soldier, what's your point?
What's going on here?
What I wanted to show you is...
...this country is filled with both
the forgotten and those who forgot them!
All of us toys were once humans!
What?!
A Devil Fruit eater who Doflamingo
brought 10 years ago,
turned us to toys!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
What is she doing?! Pick up already!
You have no mercy!
I'm all thumbs so...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Why is she not picking up?! Nami-ya!
I know I'm not calling the wrong number!
It's Usoland's Haki!
So powerful!
Look, my body trembles with excitement
so the ground is shaking!
How awesome!
He's unbelievable!
By the way, Leo,
you people keep saying "fight" but...
...why do you wanna fight Doflamingo?
What?
The hero's very funny!
We want to rescue the 500 friends who are
forced to work
at the shady factory, of course!
The battle will take place in Dressrosa!
Underneath the Colosseum!
At the shady factory!
Let's go, everybody!
Yeah!
"Making a Sortie!
The Legendary Hero Usoland!"
THE TONTATTA KINGDOM - UNDERNEATH GREEN BIT
Usoland! Usoland!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!...
Going underground?
That's right.
There is an underground passage
between Green Bit and Dressrosa.
So we're gonna go through the passage
and meet up with your friends?
That is correct!
Are they really gonna fight Doflamingo?!
Here we are! At the airport!
An army of bugs!
How cute!
Yellow Cub 43 through 48
are prepared for takeoff.
Keep standing by.
Pink Bee 21, 22, 25, 26, proceed to Runway B.
This is Yellow Cub 43. Ready to takeoff!
43, cleared for takeoff.
Pink Bee Squad, ready to go!
Pink Bee, roger that.
All bugs, stand by and wait
for further instruction.
Oh, Usoland, watch your step!
Sorry!
Cub-san! Bian!
Leo, you're late!
CUB - A LEADER OF YELLOW CUB SQUAD
(BUG-BUG FRUIT, MODEL RHINOCEROS BEETLE)
We're ready to go!
BIAN - A LEADER OF PINK BEE SQUAD
(BUG-BUG FRUIT, MODEL HORNET)
We're gonna fly at high speed!
I'll be counting on you two!
Leave it to us!
Squad members have been
training so hard for today!
To save our friends and Princess Mancherie,
we had no other choice!
Yeah!
Uh-huh!
I've never seen this kind.
I wanna show it to Luffy!
Usoland! Robiland!
You two are big so take the 20 passenger bus.
Come on, Linear Foxes!
LINEAR FOXES - TWENTY-MAN BUS
(KON EXPRESS)
This is nice! It's like a couch for a king!
They're fast when they run.
Such beautiful hair!
Alright, everybody! Let's get going!
With our hero Usoland!
To take back the 500 friends
who are held captive!
Yeah!
It's really fast!
I think I have to tell you two...
...why we want to do this.
Where're you coming out from?!
Gancho-san!
Boobie-morning! I'm the Tonta-chief - Gancho!
Thank you for doing this!
I want you to know since you're gonna risk
your life fighting for us.
No, I'm not gonna risk my life...
Don Quixote Doflamingo has
been causing us Tontatta Tribe
a lot of pain recently.
But our connection with him
goes way back before last decade, actually.
It goes back about 900 years ago.
What?!
Here in Dressrosa, there
is a vast sunflower field.
Somewhere in that field
of blooming sunflowers,
at a place no one knows,
there is a secret entrance.
Descend the stairs there,
and you will hear energetic voices.
Where's this connecting to?
You'll see soon.
Let me introduce!
Commander!
We've been waiting for you, Commander!
Thanks, you all!
AN ANTI-DOFLAMINGO COALITION -
"THE KING RIKU ARMY" HEADQUARTERS
He looks like a strong toy man!
What kind of Big Human was he?!
It's good to have him on
the day of the battle!
We're gonna fight with them!
They're Little People from the Tontatta Kingdom!
Little People?
They're as strong as you are.
They move so fast that
people can barely see them.
So they call them "fairies" in the town.
So the one who stole Zoro's sword was...
Let's go!
I thought that you wanted
to go back to your ship!
Hey, don't let him attack you, Luffy!
Young man, I can't see!
Zoro!
It was such a pain just to get here!
Let's get going!
Let's go to your ship!
You're some kind of idiot
like I said, aren't you?!
Damn, that bastard!
If there is an event like
this, why didn't he tell me?!
I wanna fight with my swords!
Oh, Commander!
Oh, Franky!
What are you doing here?
Commander, we already sorted out the intelligence
from the scouting unit!
We know what the enemies and Sugar are doing.
And, no big surprise, with
the battle close at hand...
That's right!
Some legendary heroes have appeared at Tontatta!
Their names are Usoland and Robiland!
They say they're on their way here!
On top of that, they have
some friends with them
and their names are...
...Luffyland, Zoroland, Namiland, Sanland...
...Chopperland, Fraland, and Boneland!
Must be Usopp!
Why did he tell such a lie?
Um, I think I'm Zoroland.
I'm Fraland! Nice to meet you!
What?! Great!
They're so naive.
Oh, I don't have time for this!
I gotta get back to the Sunny!
Nami and the others are in danger!
I kept telling you so, didn't I?!
The Sunny?!
Lucy fended off this one easily, too!
The champion hopefuls -
Sai, the 13th leader of the Happo Navy,
and "Destruction Cannon" Ideo
have surprisingly been eliminated!
Will the legendary gangster
- Don Chinjao win?!
Or Lucy, the unknown powerhouse
who keeps going strong?!
You annoying grandson of Garp!
Eight-Impact Fist!
Head-Arms Spin!
That technique again?
Damn you!
Gum-Gum...
Take this and fly away!
...Jet Cannon!
Gum-Gum...
Take this and fly away!
...Jet Cannon!
What?!
What just happened?!
Jet Whip!
DRESSROSA - SANJI AND KIN'EMON
Go! Luffy-dono!
Why're you cheering with the others?!
But, Sanji-dono, when a man fights,
he has to win!
Isn't your friend captured at the Toy House?!
Are you gonna forget about him?!
That's right!
Burgess!
I heard that it's getting interesting!
Who is that little guy?!
GREEN BIT
What are you gonna do?!
There's nowhere to run!
Hey, Joker!
Before you kill him,
I need you to take something back for me!
It's my heart! Law took my heart!
I don't know what he's gonna do with it!
Room!
Shambles!
That bastard!
It's no use!
Nobody can stop art!
Blow Kung-Fu...
...Art!
This is just smoke!
Here I go! Weather Egg!
Come on out, Snow Clouds!
Ewww! Disgusting!
You turned my Clima Takt into a toy!
What an insult!
Who did you call a super model?!
I didn't say that!
"Turned it into a toy"?
Don't confuse it with a toy!
You have no taste!
Yes, we have a Devil Fruit eater
who can turn people into toys in our family.
But I'm an art human who
ate the Art-Art Fruit!
You people have been turned into art!
"Art"?!
Damn! Nami got defeated, too!
But my antlers and hooves are useless!
Hey, Bone-kichi, she's trying to kidnap me!
I know! I'm not gonna let her do it!
But look at this.
My Soul Solid looks like this!
Why are you moaning like you're a victim?!
You should be happy that I made you artistic!
More importantly,
look what you did to my submarine!
And to my men!
To avenge them,
what kind of artistic death
should I bring to you?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
--Ring, ring... Clank.
--Hello? It's me! Who is this?!
We're in big trouble right now! Help us!
Who said you can pick that up?!
Chopper-san, way to go!
Is this Tony-ya?!
I don't care what's going on over there!
Listen carefully!
What?! Is this Tra-guy?!
Is it Law?
What are you doing, Tra-guy?!
Come to the ship now!
We got turned into art! Help us!
I-I'm just fine!
Listen, I need you to...
....sail the ship to Green Bit now!
I wanna leave Caesar with you guys!
I've got no time to fill you in!
Come to Green Bit now!
--Clank.
--What?!
Whaaat?! He asked us the
impossible and hung up!
I thought he already handed Caesar-san over!
What's wrong with him?!
He just talked
without hearing what we had to say!
Is he Luffy?!
I... h-h-have no problem!
I have nothing but a bad feeling!
What's going on out there?!
I can't take it anymore!
Bullet String!
It's no use, Law!
Who did you just call for help?
Give me back Caesar's heart already.
It's so meaningless for you
to keep hanging on here.
Your partner - Straw Hat has already
walked into the trap that I set up.
He's now fighting in the gladiatorial contest
at the Colosseum.
Tough contenders from all over
the world come to fight in
that outlaws-only, deadly competition.
When someone loses,
it's a one-way ticket to hell.
He will never come out
alive from the Colosseum.
It's the end of your alliance.
Law!
Just give up!