Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
After being separated
from his friends,
Luffy comes to the rescue his brother
Ace who has been captured by the Navy
by sneaking into Impel Down -
the greatest prison in the world!
He heard from some prisoners that Ace
would most likely be held on level 5
and ran into an
unexpected acquaintance!
I'll change my plan!
Now for some chaos!
I'm with you!
"Break through the Crimson Hell!
Buggy's Chaos-Inducing Plan!"
Gum-Gum...
Whip!
Stop! Stop, stop!
No!
Just kidding!
Chop-Chop
Emergency Escape!
Prepare to fall and have
your head crushed!
Aerial Tailspin Big Top!
How d'you like that,
you sea gorilla?!
No damage at all?!
D-Don't! Stop punching me!
Looks like you've gotten
stronger since we last met!
They're tough! What
kind of animal are they?
They're fighters from the sea called
Blue Gorilla known as Blugori!
Stay sharp! There're
still 4 more...
Well, then! I see you've
taken care of them already!
But I don't have time to
mess around with these!
Wow! He kicked a
lot of Blugori ass!
--Hey you! Who are you?!
--Let us out!
What's up?
I thought there was
only one escapee.
Yes, there's just one.
I could be wrong
but I saw two guys.
Anyway, 5 Blugoris have been beaten
in front of community cell #10!
5 of them? It can't be true!
We don't have any prisoners on level 1
who stand a chance against Blugoris!
Whaaat?!
You wanna rescue Ace?!
Yeah.
Shh! Be quiet!
You're the one
who's screaming!
Hey guys? The key? Please...
Shut up! Keep
your mouth shut!
Do you know Ace?!
Yeah. Unlike you, your
brother was very polite...
Is this really a time
to be partying?
How can you attack Luffy if you
don't even know where he is?
Don't be such a
spoilsport, Alvida!
Let us enjoy ourselves!
Huh?
Do you wanna see Luffy?
I know where he is!
See? He knows
where Luffy is...
Who the hell are you?!
Hello! Excuse me for
interrupting your banquet.
I was drawn here by the
smell of all this good food.
My name is Ace.
Nice to meet you!
Oh no no, you don't have to be that
polite. The pleasure is all ours...
That's not what I asked!
I don't care about your
name! Don't mess with me!
Captain! Captain,
he's the "Fire Fist"!
"Fire Fist" Ace! Whitebeard's
Second Division Commander!
Whitebeard?!
What?!
Oh! You know my father!
That's very...
He's sleeping!
Then we hit it off and
became drinking buddies.
So I feel very sorry about
what happened to him.
That's the foolishness of the Navy
to mess with Whitebeard's crew.
I wanna get to level 5.
That's where Ace is, right?
I don't know! Go by yourself!
I'm no friend of yours!
I'm not going to that
hell hole! See ya!
If you're not willing to
escape, I'll do it on my own!
There's 10 or more navy ships out
there. Are you sure you can make it?
10 or more?
Oh, I get it! They must be
preparing for Whitebeard's attack!
Now isn't the best time.
I'll just kill some time and...
What?!
Oh well, I'll just ask
somebody else!
The key!
No no, it can't be!
It's stupid to even think it!
But maybe...
Alright then, good
luck with your escape!
I'm sure it is!
Wait a minute, Straw Hat!
--What're you...
--There he is!
--Up there!
--They found me!
Why did you yell?!
H-Hey, that's a beautiful
armlet! Can I have it?
Why're you so interested all of the
sudden?! This was a gift from Nami!
I'll tell you where Ace is!
Really?
Yes! If you give it to me.
Yeah, in that case!
Yeah!
Okay, first, let's
lose our enemies!
Hold onto my feet!
Your feet?!
Run, Straw Hat!
Don't drop those, Straw Hat!
Let's see how Buggy the Clown's
Chop-Chop power works!
He can chop apart his body and
control each part as he wants.
But the pieces are controllable
only in a limited area and to use his power,
his feet must be on the ground.
Yes! How lucky I am!
I can't believe that I found the treasure
I was looking for in hell like this!
Captain! Captain!
What do you want?
Are you really
sure that this is it?
Is this the cave
where Captain John
who acted so cruelly to
protect his treasure hid them?
Yes, it is! Proceed carefully!
O-Okay.
Listen, where there are treasures,
there are usually traps or guards!
One false move
and you're dead!
Maybe there will be
some kind of monster
or bloody traps like
you'd see in hell!
Alright, let's continue with
the tunnel construction!
Yes, boss!
Oh? You guys must
be the new crew!
Yeah! Boss, I love this job!
Right! All our sweat turns into a part of
the tunnel that will make people smile!
And beer tastes so much
better after hard work!
Enough of this
goody-goody laborer crap!
We kept sailing here and there in the Grand
Line looking for the treasure after that
but we couldn't
find it anywhere!
To top it all, I was caught in a navy
post while I walked in by mistake
and was shut up
in this prison.
But my luck has
not run out yet!
Run as fast as you
can, Straw Hat!
I'll lead you to the
entrance of level 2!
Level 2? Aren't you listening?
I wanna go to level 5!
Listen to me, Straw Hat! You'll be
unable to go straight to level 5!
In Impel Down, this first
basement is what they call level 1
and as you go down to
level 2, level 3 and so on,
you encounter more vicious
criminals who have been captured.
I've only ever been to level
4 to be tortured by fire,
so I don't know about
the floors below.
But level 5 holds the
extraordinary criminals with bounties
of hundreds of millions or more!
But I heard from some prisoners
that there are more floors below!
They said that there are heinous
monsters whose existences
have been deleted from history!
It's just a rumor but maybe
that's where Ace is!
Anyway, I can only
lead you to level 4!
Alright! Suddenly you're
not such a bad guy!
Yeah, because you said
you'll give me the armlet
that will tell me where
Captain John's treasure is!
I-I shouldn't have
opened my big mouth!
You're a...
Yeah?
...a pretty crappy pirate
to have been caught!
Shut up! Leave me alone!
H-He wasn't even paying attention!
Thank god he's such an idiot!
I didn't know that this armlet
functions as a treasure map!
I had no clue at all!
You were paying attention!
Damn! Then I have no choice!
Alright then, you
can have it now!
You know that it's a treasure map
but you're still gonna give it to me?
Yeah! Rescuing Ace is
more important to me!
And don't you think that I may just take
off with it if you give it to me now?!
No! Because you gave your
word that you'd lead me to Ace!
Don't look at me with
those trusting eyes!
I'm a sly and worthless man!
You shouldn't
believe a guy like me!
I finally have Captain John's
treasure mark after all this time!
Thank you, Straw Hat!
Now, how the hell
do I get out of here?
Oh! Is it faster to break
through the wall? I got it!
No, that's not what I...
I wonder how Luffy's doing.
I warned him not to
get into any trouble...
They built this place as a
fort that locks people in.
Don't get in any trouble.
Once they catch you, you'll
never be able to get out.
I know that you're strong
but promise me that you
won't get in any trouble.
Alright! I promise!
Thank you so
much, Hancock!
Hancock...
Hancock ...ncock...
Oh, Luffy! I can hear your
heavenly voice in my heart!
Okay, it's about time!
Mmm! What a
pleasant scream!
Seems like jailers
doing pretty well.
Did you like it,
Hancock-dono?
Oh, you didn't hear it?
Sorry about that!
But there is one more
chance so please do enjoy it!
I don't care about screams! I can't hear
the voice in my heart because of you!
I don't know what I did wrong
but she's stepping on me!
Why? I'm a vice warden!
Don't do that, Hancock-dono!
But I'm kinda enjoying this!
What?
Oops! Did I say
that out loud?!
Who are they?!
That's Buggy the
Clown who escaped...
And who is the other one?!
This is the jailers' room!
Then we shouldn't go this way!
Stop! Straw Fool!
What the hell is this?
A forest in the prison?!
It's a crimson forest!
There are so many people!
They're prisoners!
This is not just a forest!
Leaves are as sharp as blade
because they're Blade Trees!
The grass is actually needles
which prick  your body!
It's called Spike Needle Grass!
Chased by loosed venomous
spiders and jailers,
prisoners run around the forest
and get cut by leaves and
grasses which shed their blood
causing them to agonize!
This is level 1 -
the Crimson Hell!
That is Impel Down!
"The Underwater Prison - Impel Down - Level 1
Crimson Hell"
Help me!
I can't stand it!
This is a real hell! Is this the kind
of thing they're doing to Ace?
Yes! Let's just keep falling!
Why?! We're gonna get cut!
I'm not gonna get cut!
Just shut up and hang on!
Straw Hat! My feet! Throw
them to the ground!
Your feet?
Ah! Okay!
W-What is that?!
Augh! Watch out!
Once I get my feet on the
ground, it's a piece of cake!
We don't need to use stairs
to go down from this floor!
We don't need a key to
open the door to the stairs!
I just remembered that there's a way to
escape the agony of the Crimson Hell!
There's a way out of hell?
Look! This is it!
It's a hole!
Wow! It's as dark as night!
This is the way out but nobody
wants to escape from here.
Do you know
why, Straw Hat?
Because this hole is
connected to level 2
which is an even
more terrifying hell!
There may be people who try to
escape from hell back to earth
but there aren't people stupid
enough to descend deeper into hell!
Well, this is good for us!
We can just jump down!
Yeah but down below,
there's... No, wait! Hey!
Wow, it's deep! I wonder
what's down there!
Ha! What a hotfoot!
He isn't afraid of anything?
But at least now he can't
stop me if I just take off!
Now I'm free! I finally got the treasure
mark that I always dreamed of!
Find your own way!
Good-bye, Straw Hat!
Down to level 3 or level 4 - it doesn't
matter either way you're a goner!
Stupid Blugori! You can't chop
me because I ate Chop-Chop fruit!
That's...
...my feet!
No! You got to
be kidding me!
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow...
Surveillance Room!
There is another guy!
They just fell down to level 2!
Can you look for them?
I got it!
"The Underwater Prison - Impel Down - Level 2
Floor of Wild Beasts From Hell"
W-What's going on?
The beasts unusually agitated!
Are they hungry or something?
I have no energy
left to be afraid.
Either way we're
gonna be their dinner.
Luffy and Buggy fall down to level 2,
where beasts of fearsome strength roam.
This is the floor of the wild beasts of hell.
Meanwhile, Hancock reaches
the heart of the prison,
where she encounters Warden Magellan.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Strongest Man in the Prison!
Poison Man Magellan Appears!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!