Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
saa yukou
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards finally got over the
encircling walls to make it to the scaffold!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
Luffy runs toward Ace with
the Whitebeards' assistance!
You guys!
Pops?!
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
...with all your strength!
They made a path!
I'm here, Ace!
Grandpa! Move out of my way!
I'm not going to move!
Because I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting against pirates
since long before you were born!
Old man!
If you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Because of the path you two...
...have chosen to live!!
"Each on Different Paths! Luffy vs. Garp!"
Please, grandpa! Just let me go by!
Luffy!
C-Coby! S-Stay with me, Coby!
Damn Straw Hat!
How could he do this to Coby without mercy?!
I'll make him pay!
I-I have to become...
...much much stronger...
Y-Y-You are alive! I'm so relieved!
Where's Luffy-san?
That damn Straw Hat is...
...being blocked by Vice Admiral Garp!
Are they really gonna fight?!
Luffy-san!
Straw Hat is heading to the scaffold! Dammit!
It's easy to get him from this distance!
Aim at Straw Hat Luffy!
You impertinent fools!
Stand back!
Slave Arrow!
--We...
--Love...
--You...
Pirate empress! Whose
side are you really on?!
Of course, Luffy's...
...but what if you hit Vice Admiral
Garp with a stray bullet?!
--What?!
--N-No!
Vice Admiral Garp! He is none other than...
...my grandfather!
--Your grandfather?!
--Vice Admiral Garp?!
If I get married with Luffy, then of
course, he becomes my grandfather!
--It's just...
--...In your head!
You gotta find a way, Straw Hat!
Hurry up before the bridge collapses!
Straw Hat!
Luffy-kun!
Luffy! Straw Hat Luffy!
Like I said, if you wanna pass through
here, you have to kill me first!
Ouch!
You bastard!
Grandpa!
Why do you want me to fight with these guys?!
That's your training!
My training?!
It just makes me hungry and I
don't wanna get hit anymore!
Don't be such a baby!
You got to become the strongest Navy soldier!
I'm gonna become a pirate,
not a Navy soldier!
Huh?
You fool!
Ouch!
Nothing's more painful than grandpa's fist!
Gum-Gum...
What a fool...
I gotta tell you something!
What is it?
I'm not gonna become a pirate!
You finally got it!
I'm not gonna become just a pirate,
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
You can't be influenced
by "Red-Haired" like that!
You're dismissed! I got to
beat some character into him!
Grandpa!
I'm not gonna let you become
a pirate at any cost!
Although you're worn out and sleeping,
your stomach is active as always.
I guess you must hate a grandpa
like me; so intimidating.
But Luffy,
the reason that I'm training you
so harshly to become a Navy soldier is...
...that I don't want you to stray
from the right path at any price.
That is my wish.
Luffy, we'll have a great dinner tonight
because I swiped plenty from the Navy.
You can eat as much meat as you want!
Grandpa...
I can't do it, grandpa! Move out of my way!
If you can't, Ace will die!
No way!
Things don't always go as you want!
I'm not gonna have mercy on you!
Luffy, I consider you...
...my enemy!
Luffy!
Garp!
Dammit! My mind is so warped!
It's not the right time for this!
Pops and brother and friends are...
...going down one by one bleeding, but...
I'm so happy that I can't hold back my tears!
At this last moment, I'm starting
to think that I wanna live!
Vice Admiral Garp!
Old man!
You're their parent after all, Garp.
He is about to get to the scaffold!
You called him a reckless piece of crap!
He is reckless!
I wonder how he can set "Fire Fist" Ace free.
Get lost! You fool!
You're not careful.
Pops!
Finally... finally...
I made it!
Luffy!
You're so...!
Ace!
Hold on!
Take this.
It's your brother's handcuff key.
I have the key!
Luffy, how did you...?!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
--Look! Fleet Admiral Sengoku is using his power!
--I've never seen it before!
You can't get away from me!
Sengoku!
A giant Buddha!
I can't believe that you even have
such a thing, Straw Hat Luffy!
Oh no, the key!
Get ready!
Aim at them and be ready to
fire at a moment's notice!
No way, the key...!
Straw Hat Luffy!
You're a serious criminal who
should be punished by death, too!
I'm gonna execute both of you
brothers with my own bare hands!
What was that? I passed
out all of a sudden...
Straw Hat... Oh!
San! Why are you here?!
What is that?!
Hey, San! Protect Ace with a wall!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Balloon!
Candle Wall!
Is he expanding?!
--The scaffold is collapsing!
--What happened?!
Ace is still alive!
We're falling!
I'll make the key! Uncuff him right away!
Alright!
Captain Buggy! There's brother 3!
What?! What is he doing in
that ridiculous costume?!
I thought he ran away from here already!
The execution of "Fire Fist" Ace has
to do with the prestige of the Navy HQ!
We have to finish it!
That was...
...the executioners!
Ring, ring, ring... Clank!
Oh, that's good! Admiral Borsalino
stopped Straw Hat in the plaza!
Straw Hat?!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
Mr. 2...!
Okay, what should we do now?
We're gonna rescue Straw-chan!
Because I'm his friend! I
don't need any other reasons!
Friends?
Bon-chan, the gate's closing.
We... have to go.
Thank you!
Straw-chan!
--Bon-chan!
--Straw-chan!
You gotta save your brother at any cost!
He never ran away.
He honored his friendship with Straw Hat!
Okay guys, hurry up and get ready!
Yes, sir!
Where's the other guy?!
What's taking him so long?!
Since it was such short notice, he's
having trouble getting ready...
Hey, hurry up!
Alright, let's go!
If I tell you that I'm here out
of respect for my late comrade,
are you going to laugh at me?!
No, I won't!
Fire! Blow them away!
Save your brother, Straw Hat!
Okay!
Oh no!
Straw boy!
No way!
Ace!
--Brother 3!
--They all got hit!
"Fire Fist" can't use his power because of
the Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
He's dead!
And we got Straw Hat, too!
There's a tunnel of fire in the smoke!
You've always been like this!
Luffy!
You've never even listened to me...
...and always done such crazy things!
--Good!
--Oh my!
Ace!
I-I can't believe it!
Straw Hat and brother 3 are alive, too!
Ace!!
Ace is free at last!
Seeing Ace and Luffy taking on the Navy
in such a well-synchronized combination
raises the morale of the Whitebeard Pirates.
But Whitebeard, looking to a
future still farther ahead,
comes to a decision of his own.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Ace Rescued! Whitebeard's Final Order!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!