Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Fight, shake it off, act strong
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
negai wo tabanete
Put all our wishes together
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
hikari no saki Make my day
Beyond the light, make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
Gravity Blade!
Raging Tiger!
This jerk! What is he up to?!
It's an all-or-nothing gamble.
I'm determined to bet my life on it.
Father-sama must be
somewhere on this battlefield, too...
Somebody made it here, huh?
It's you...
We can go straight to the fourth level this way!
Let's go, Tra-guy!
Go!
I'm gonna go first!
Oh, wait, Soldier!
Luffy, dodge!
Let me take care of it!
Hey, Bartolomeo!
If it helps Luffy-senpai...
I'm happy to die!
I know how you feel...
Rooster-kun.
Our captain is...
...worth risking...
...even our lives!
"A Tearful Reunion!
Rebecca and Kyros!"
Damn!
I gotta hurry or
Soldier will kick Mingo's ass first!
Straw Hat-ya!
What?!
It's still here!
It's no use fighting it!
We're almost at the fourth level!
Shake it off!
Okay!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 4
THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
What did you come here for?!
Don't tell me you're here to kill Doffy.
That can't be it.
You recklessly challenged me
with that blunt-edged sword
and disgraced yourself pathetically!
So you know you have no chance against Doffy!
Or...
...you came to challenge me again
believing in some miracle?
To avenge your mother...
...on me!
I like the look in your eyes.
I... I couldn't protect her!
Sure! If you wanna challenge me,
I accept!
Listen to me, Rebecca!
I promise I'll kick Doflamingo's ass for you!
Shame on you, Rebecca!
What's the matter?! Why are you running?!
Why aren't you fighting?!
You're a gladiator!
I thought you came to kill me!
I know I'm no match for Diamante.
What I have to do now is
hand this key over to Lucy and the others!
At the Colosseum, I managed to put on
some good shows using you but...
...if you can't fight,
you've served your purpose!
I'll... put an end to you now.
No, wait...
You prefer a gun, don't you?
Because Scarlet...
...got killed by a gun!
Help!
Soldier-san!!
Rebecca!!
You're...
Kyros!
Won't let you take away...
...another member of my family
from me!!
This man was a legend.
He was the strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum.
Although I couldn't protect your mother,
I'm gonna protect you to the end,
with my life!
Let me teach you how to fight.
My mother said I shouldn't hurt anyone!
I'm gonna teach you how to not get hurt!
I'm a toy.
Rain and wind will rust my body!
I don't know how long my body's gonna last!
Be strong!
Rebecca!
Father-sama...
I'm sorry, Rebecca.
As a toy with no future,
all I could do was teach you how to fight!
Even though you're a gentle person
like your mother!
But it ends today!
What?
You...
...don't have to fight anymore.
Uh-huh! Uh-huh!
Uh-huh!
What do you mean by that, Kyros?!
It means, today,
I'll settle my score with all of you!
That means...
...it's the end of all of you!
You monster!
Rebecca!
Is this...!
Rebecca!!
Lucy!
The key!
Great! We both made it!
Give it to me now!
Here it is!
Hurry up!
Rebecca!
Room!
You jerks!
Here they are.
Finally, we caught up with him!
Finally... I'm free!
We're here!
The fourth level - where Mingo is!
Is that where he is?
Yeah.
Law! Straw Hat!
Diamante.
I'm sorry, you two...
My hands are full with this guy.
Could you take care of Doflamingo for me?!
Of course!
Then, I'll leave that guy up to you, Soldier!
Got it!
--Let's go, Straw Hat-ya!
--Okay!
Oh yeah, Rebecca!
I bet you're happy to see your dad!
Uh-huh.
Thank you for the key!
See you!
Hey, Lucy!
Are you really going to...
Are you really going to
take down Doflamingo?!
I'm not Lucy.
My name is Luffy!
The man who'll become the King of the Pirates!
So don't worry!
The King of the Pirates?!
You're fighting me, Diamante!
Don't get in my way!
What annoying bastards!
I won't allow you idiots...
...to get to the Palace!
You tremendous idiot! Traitorous brat!
Room!
Shambles!
Dammit!!
Is this... the palace?
Yeah, we finally made it.
What a useful ability!
It is but it also eats up my energy.
Maybe, having those Sea Prism Stone cuffs on
and getting carried by you to this
point wasn't so bad after all.
I was able to save my energy.
Scalpel.
What's wrong?!
I operated on myself.
He purposely used lead bullets...
That jerk!
You okay?
--No need to worry.
--I see.
All right!
Let's go and kick Mingo's ass!
Wait!
What?!
Doflamingo isn't someone that you can
beat just by force of will alone.
You need to cool down.
What?! How can I cool down
after getting this far?!
I'm saying, if you don't,
you can't defeat him!
I promised Rebecca!
Stopping here won't change anything!
Law and Straw Hat have shown up
in the yard...
...nearby the pool.
--Roger that.
--Clank.
10 years... For 10 years.
I spent such a long time,
increasing their number little by little.
Those tens of thousands of toy slaves.
But that idiot...
...brought it all to naught in an instant!
Not yet, Kanjuro?! We have no time!
It's almost done!
Revenge is easy.
Just touch them with this hand.
Straw Hats...
Now I'll bring...
...your existences...
...to naught!
A vengeful Sugar closes in on Luffy and Law.
"Won't let her turn him into a toy!"
With this passionate thought in his mind,
Usopp takes aim at Sugar in the distance,
beyond even his line of sight!
Suddenly, everybody's fate depends on
Usopp's skill!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"One Shot One Kill! The Man
Who Will Save Dressrosa!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!