Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Zoro...!
Where is Luffy?
Did Luffy get cut down by Zoro?
Don't tell me... It can't be...
Where's our captain?
You damn swordsman...!
If you're gonna harm the ladies,
I'll be your opponent.
He said, "I still haven't
played my trump card yet"!
"The Last Counterattack by the Memory
Thief Who Revealed His True Colors!"
Oooh! All right! I'm... me!
Ahhh! I'm me!
Excuse me, but aren't you one of the guests?
That's right! I'm a guest!
Why am I dressed like this?
What're you doing, manager?!
Please come to the front desk right away!
So I was right... I'm the inn manager, aren't I?
M-Mom! Where have you been?!
I'm sorry. Are you okay? How have you been?
All right! Our memories...
Our memories are back!
E-Everyone! There's trouble!
Oh, it's you, Drim.
Don't scare us like that.
Drim... Drim...!
Mom! Mom!
So you're okay.
Looks like everyone's memories are back.
Good, good.
But how did something like that happen?
Everyone! There's trouble!
The one who took our
memories away is in the forest!
--What?!
What's it saying?
"T-Take them out, Roronoa Zoro!"
So he said.
S-See? He's being controlled by that thing!
Hey, someone, do something...
Geez... You damn swordsman,
you're always bringing in trouble...!
Ahh, Sanji! Be careful!
Hm?
"Now this will buy me some time"?
Collier!
Huh?
Don't interfere...
...you idiot cook!
Oh? There he is!
Zoro!
So you're okay!
Luffy! What'd you do that for?!
Zoro, did you just... say "Luffy"?
Tsk.
So your memories are back?!
Of course.
Your face is scary! If your memories are back,
then approach us with
a smiling, kind face like this!
Argh! Shut up!
Ow!
Hm? Who am I?!
--Huh?!
--Hey! Don't make it more
complicated than it already is!
Ah, Zoro! How dare you do that earlier?!
Geez, do what you want, you guys...
Good! Now we're all back to normal.
Robin-chan really is wonderful, to figure out
that that sea horse horn is the real culprit.
What?! So that was it?!
You were the first one to
get your memories back.
Why didn't you notice it?
How rude! I'm better than Zoro!
So where did that thing go?
Ah...
Did it get away?
No...
...it's so obvious where it is.
You're right. It turned pale.
It should've hurried up and escaped.
Does it think it's hiding wel--
You bastard! How dare you manipulate me?!
I'm gonna catch and fillet you!
Oh, his feelings are hurt in his own way.
"Now, catch me if you can!"
"You really piss me off! Hold it!"
"Hahaha! You can't catch me!"
"Then how about this?!"
"I'm right here!"
"What?! No way! Now, I'm getting serious!"
"There, I've caught you!"
"I'm not gonna let you go!"
You're next, Usopp!
"I'm going to play my... trump card"?!
What?!
C-Can't be...!
Bellemere-san... is that you?
Doctor...!
Kaya...!
Are you better now?
Whoa!
Whoooa!
How have you been?!
These are...
...afterimages of their memories...
You wanna fight, you jerks?!
I'll kick all your asses at once!
What's going on?!
Shoot...!
Dammit! I can't move!
What is it saying?
"Thanks to you guys, I even lost all the
memories I collected from the villagers.
But if I can obtain all your rich memories,
I can become one!"
Become what?
I don't know.
"I'm not going to miss this opportunity!"
What the heck is that?!
And...
...who am I?!
Who are you guys?
Who am I?
Hey, the one who's drowning over there!
--Huh?
--Do you know?
How would I know?!
"All right! I was able to
become a Millennial Dragon"?
--You...!
--Amazing! You can understand what it's saying?!
--Err...
--Hey... This raccoon dog talks!
Ahhh! Am I a raccoon dog?!
A talking raccoon dog and a Millennial Dragon...
And a damn bastard who almost drowned...
What the heck...?
Just watching that dragon...
somehow gets me pissed off! Why?!
What happened? How? Why?
Strange... Why am I here?
Amazing!
A dragon, huh? I wanna ride it!
Are you an idiot? There's no
way you can ride it from...
You don't know until you try... Ahh!
What the heck is he?!
What's going on?! My arms and legs stretch!
This is fun!
He really jumped on it...
Wait... What's with his body?!
He's a monster.
It's dangerous! Hey, keep still!
Somehow that thing looks like it's in pain.
"Let go of me! Hey! The memories
are going to leak out"?!
Memories?
Again and again...
How dare you steal our memories?!
You bastard!
What is it saying?! Chopper!
Chopper? M-Me?
Who else could it be?! Right?!
Yep!
"I was finally able to become a
Millennial Dragon! Don't interfere!"
Oh, yeah?!
People's memories aren't yours to take!
If you wanna become a Millennial Dragon,
become one by making your own big memory!
"Shut up! Take this! This is it!"
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
If you wanna fly that bad...
I'll send you flying!
--Hey...
--Hm?
You're gonna catch a cold.
I kicked its ass!
At any rate...
...if I remember right,
don't Millennial Dragons hatch from eggs?
Yeah. You can't become one
just by eating memories.
Is that right?
Yeah, you probably don't know it,
but we saw it with our own eyes
before we entered the Grand Line.
Really?
Well, forget that. People must be
making a racket in the village by now!
After all, we're their benefactors who
got all the villagers' memories back!
No doubt they're gonna treat us like heroes!
First all-you-can-drink party
we've had in a while, huh?
There's something you wanna forget?
Shut up.
Seems like we can expect
them to reward us good!
I want a bronze statue.
I'm gonna be so popular
with girls, huh? Not bad.
What about you, Robin? If you're able
to get something, what would you like?
Books, as expected?
Yeah. If possible, maybe books
on this island's history.
I knew it! I want a medical book--
one that's this thick!
We can see the seashore now.
Hey, ladies and gentlemen!
Thanks for coming to greet us!
Huh?
--What?!
--Why?!
U-Um... H-Hey...
I-It's them!
Everyone! Attack!
Ahhh! What's going on?!
Usopp! Aren't we supposed to be heroes?!
Beats me! I wanna ask that question myself!
Nami-san! Where's the waver?
This way!
Hold it! Stop right there, pirates!
You damn memory thieves!
You damn girl! Pay your bill!
What's with them?! They think we did it!
Looks like it.
Well, we're pirates. It can't be helped, huh?
Now that it's come to this,
we're to the point of desperation!
Hey! Hold it! Stop it!
What pirate would stop just
because they're told to stop?!
I'm glad we made it back.
A big bronze statue... It was so close...
...to being built... A big, dark statue...
At any rate...
To think that losing memories
would turn into such a big fuss...
Yeah, I totally agree.
There was even some guy who
schemed to make us his pirate crew.
Well... Sanji-kun... I just got
carried away... I just got carried away.
On the other hand,
there was a damn simpleton
whose body and soul got taken over.
What'd you say?!
To start with, if you were
actually standing guard,
this racket wouldn't have happened,
you idiot moss-head!
Shut up! I was sleepy!
If you wanna sleep that much,
sleep for the rest of your life!
Argh! Shut up! That's enough!
Or would you like to lose your memories again?
Oh, Nami-san! Please don't say things like that!
My memories...
If I hadn't gotten my memories back...
...what would I have...
What's wrong... Robin?
What?
I'm okay.
I'm a little sleepy, that's all.
It's just natural. Robin-chan hasn't
slept much because of this racket.
--Oh, that's right!
--All right then!
I'll make a special healthy dinner with
a mixture of herbal medicines tonight!
Ah, food! I forgot about it!
Sanji! Food!
I'm gonna make it now, so just wait quietly!
--Say, Luffy.
--Hm?
Why didn't you come back
with Zoro at that time?
Oh... Well, I got stuck
under a rock Zoro cut down.
--A rock?!
--Yeah. That was one huge, hard rock.
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Now, things have been settled.
To the next island, full speed ahead!
Geez, you're full of hot air!
I think with this incident, you've all
learned how important memories are.
What are you trying to summarize for?
Hm? I feel like I just saw something
I don't wanna remember.
Oh, that Split-Head is...
Boss?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Proud Man! Silver Fox Foxy"
Him again?