Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
As I promised, I'll kill you in
an instant. Die without pain.
Too bad. If you'd stayed connected with
that shepherd and had him protect you,
you would've been okay.
Now, this is it for you!
Don't kill him! Please! We don't need your key!
Now, die!
Usopp!
Who the hell are you?!
A hunter.
I-I'm sorry, Sanji-kun.
I...
After all... I...
You're still alive. That's all that matters.
Everyone has things that they
can do and things that they can't.
Sanji...
Look outside, both of you.
No way...
The Gates of Justice are about to open.
Robin...!
Once those gates are opened
and Robin-chan goes through there,
the sea beyond hosts a nest of Sea Kings
and we have no means to cross it.
Past that, there's a large
prison and Navy Headquarters.
Soon Robin-chan will be taken
to a place beyond our reach.
Oh, no... Luffy didn't make it in time?
Teach her a lesson, Funkfreed!
Luffy is just ahead.
Don't hit her vital spots, got that?
Ivory...
...Dart!
I won't let you escape, you dumb woman!
Don't underestimate me!
Now, let's go through the
doors to our dreams together.
Leave getting his key to me.
Are you changing fighters? That's fine by me.
I'll do what you can't do.
And you do what I can't do!
What?
Think carefully.
Grasp the situation!
As long as we have you, we can
save Robin-chan for sure! Usopp!
I want to live!
Wh-What I can do...
"Fiery Kicks! Sanji's Full
Course of Foot Techniques"
As long as they have me... we can save Robin?
What's that? What does that mean?
Shave!
Go!
O-Okay! Usopp!
Ow, ow! My wounds hurt!
Bear it! It's better than
being killed here, right?!
Good point.
Iron Body Kenpo!
Wolf Repel!
Some hunter you are. You just talk big.
Oh, that's right. I get it!
What is it?
We can save her... As long as they
have me, we can save Robin! Dammit!
"Dammit"?! You don't have
to get upset or anything!
Let's hurry, Nami-kun!
Hey, wait up!
I got it! I got it!
Hey, be quiet. That wolf's gonna come after us!
Maybe I should kill them after all.
Now you've gone and done it...
Ten Finger Pistol!
Troisième... Haché!
Iron Body!
That doesn't work on me, you fool!
What's with his kicks?
That technique you guys use
to make your body like iron...
...is really a pain in the ass.
Tempest Kick Lone Wolf!
Basses Côte!
Longe!
Tendron!
Flanchet! Quasi! Queue! Cuisseau! Jarret!
Veau... Shot!
Iron Body Kenpo!
I said your kicks don't work on me, didn't I?!
Wolf Fang!
Now that attack worked, didn't it?!
That was Iron Body Kenpo! Wolf Fang Stance!
I'm the only one of the Six Powers Masters
who can move around while using
Iron Body on my entire body.
Stop your rambling!
Deuxième Haché!
It appears to have worked,
but it actually didn't?
Well, did it or didn't it?!
Well done.
I've been waiting for a man like you.
Hm?
Would you save her... Save Robin?
What?! What're you saying?
I kept quiet about this, but... Robin is...
...actually my little sister... whom I
was separated from a long time ago.
What?!
Is that true?!
I didn't know.
She never told us anything like that, so...
That's just natural...
...but it's true.
It was over twenty years ago.
I'll never forget.
On an island in the West Blue,
on a sunny, pleasant summer day,
Robin and I went to a beach to play.
--Big brother!
--My sister and I were close.
--Robin!
--So we always played together.
--Look!
--On that day, too, we both were happy...
...until those guys came.
When I took my eyes off of her for a second...
...those pirates kidnapped Robin!
Robin! Give Robin back!
After that day, I never saw her again.
When I found out that she
escaped from those pirates,
--Robin...
--...it was too late.
It was all my fault.
So I wanna save her at any cost,
but I can't do anything due to
the position I'm in right now.
So... I'll entrust everything to you.
Please, save her!
Okay, I got it. Just leave it to me.
I'll take this key and save her without fail.
You think I'd buy that crap?!
Robin-chan is your little sister?
You dumbass! If you're gonna lie,
try to make it more believable.
Seriously, after coming this far,
you're still causing me trouble,
you dumb woman!
Dumb! Dumb! Dumb! Dumb woman!
I'm getting pretty exhausted because of you!
Walk on your own, bitch!
Don't make me repeat it.
There isn't even a shred of hope left for you.
I heard some voice in the passage earlier,
but no one showed up after all, did they?
Lucci might be killing him right about now, huh?
You bitch! You made me
have to do all that coughing!
Dumb! Dumb! Dumb! Dumb woman!
Dumb! Dumb! Dumb! Dumb woman!!
You should have realized by now.
No matter what tricks you play,
you can never go through these doors.
You're wrong! I'll do whatever
it takes to go through there!
It seems that we disagree.
I guess there's no point in discussing it.
I don't have much time, either.
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Stamp!
Whip!
Spear!
Did it work a little this time, wolf?
Whoa! You bastard! The key...!
You gave it to me!
How dare you...?!
You still haven't learned your lesson?
Iron Body!
--See ya!
--Ahh! Hold it!
I'm the one who has the trademark on foul play!
How dare you mock me?! Shave!
Party Table...!
Iron Body Kenpo!
Hm?!
Cuisseau Shoot!
Brochette!
Dammit! I'm pissed!
If you wanna get hurt that badly... that's fine.
I'll show you the true power
of my Iron Body Kenpo!
Iron Body Kenpo! Wolf Plantain Stance!
Wolf Hunt High-Speed Scratch!
Whoa! A slashing attack?!
Don Po Ro!
What do you think of the
power of an Iron Body punch?
It's incomparably powerful, isn't it?
Moon Walk!
Tempest Kick! Lupus Fall!
You were naive to think that you
could steal the key from me and run.
I'm a wolf. I'll keep going
after you until I chew you up.
Oh? You're still alive.
I don't intend to run...
I don't intend to be killed...
And I don't intend to forgive.
Forgive?
Are you sympathizing with Nico Robin?
A distracted mind just creates
openings during a fight.
If you have time to pity that ill-fated woman,
you should think of a way
to save your neck here.
Watch your mouth.
I'm the kind who heats up with anger.
If you're under strain, there's no
chance you can bring me down.
I'm sure my attacks have done
quite a bit of damage to you by now.
If that wasn't enough, then...
Iron Body Kenpo! Devil Wolf!
Go ahead and laugh while you can.
Hm?
I don't know what's so fun
about spinning like that, but...
Hm? What's with him?
One of his feet is now red!
Devil's foot...
Diable Jambe!
The heat generated from spinning
will make my fast kicks even more...
It's glowing!
Ow, it burns!
Its destructive power is just like that of a devil.
It burns! Ow, ow, ow...!
I-I got burned! Even my bones
feel hot! They're broken!
Iron Body isn't working at all!
What's with that kick?! Dammit!
How stupid!
To think that he jumps into the air
when he's fighting a Six Powers Master!
Diable Jambe!
--Première Haché!
--Moon Walk!
How stupid!
You're really stupid!
You got carried away and became
hasty trying to finish the fight!
I win!
Take this! Moonlight Ten Finger Pistol!
One of my hands got repelled.
You were close, huh?
If you were fast enough
to get another kick in,
you could've completely
stopped the Finger Pistol.
Well, I couldn't help it...
...because the other kick is...
for finishing you off!
Diable Jambe!
What? W-Wait!
Flambage...
...Shot!
God creates food...
...and the Devil creates spice.
I guess I made it a little too spicy.
What're you doing?
My attack has already started.
--What?!
--Kirin Shower!
I can't block them!
I'm just starting to show a
giraffe's real wild strength!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fierce Sword Attacks! Zoro vs. Kaku,
Powerful Sword Fighting Showdown"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!