Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"An Ancient Island!
The Shadow Hiding in Little Garden!"
I wonder if it's not gonna snow anymore.
There's no way it would.
Does too. You don't know since
you slept through it last time.
Hmm?
Hey, do you think it'll snow again?
It could snow, but the sea
we were in first is special...
...since the seven magnetic forces from
Reverse Mountain mess everything up.
That doesn't mean you can relax
your attention here, though.
It'd be rare for this sea to
be wild like the first journey,
but it's still true that this sea is a
lot more difficult than ordinary ones.
Never underestimate this sea.
That's the ironclad rule.
Hey guys!
Wanna have my special drink?
Yeah!
Thanks!
Say, Usopp. Make a fishing tackle for me.
Fishing, huh? That's a good idea!
Okay. Then I'll make an
artistic fishing rod for you.
Hey, it goes like this.
Wow, you sure can drink.
Hey, is it good?
Whoa! Amazing!
Is this really okay?!
Here, this is for you.
What?
I think it's fine.
They'll work hard if it storms...
since they don't wanna die.
That's true, but it makes me feel
like I'm worked up over nothing.
This ship makes you feel like you don't
have to worry about anything, right?
Attaboy! Go, go, go, go...!
Stupid Karoo!
Yes... it's a lot easier this way...
Hey, everyone, look!
It's a dolphin!
Whoa! He's cute!
It's huge!!
Get out of here!
Let's go!
Okay!
Yep!
Alright!
Take that side!
Got it!
Everyone...
Completely unfurl the sails!
Okay! Ride the wave
and shake him off!
Nami! Which direction
should the ship take?
Hold on a sec. Let me check.
Turn to port, full!
Okay!
Whoa!
There's no mistake.
That island and Cactus Island
are pulling against each other.
Our next stop is...
...that island!
So that's the one!
Our second island in the Grand Line!
Mr. 3...
What is it? Hold on...
There's just nothing like Earl Grey.
I'm bored.
You say you're bored, but you
don't like working, right?
Right.
Then, why don't you try enjoying
this joyous free time a little?
Being able to take a long vacation
like this is a privilege to officer agents.
And...
stop calling me by my code
name in public like this.
People will find out that I'm Mr. 3.
You think?
By the way, you've been looking at that
piece of paper for the past few days.
What on earth is it?
An order from Boss.
You should've told me sooner!
Apparently, Mr. 5 has been taken down.
Humph! If someone had to get taken down,
I wish it were someone like Mr. 2.
Then you could get a promotion.
Mr. 5 being taken down isn't
worth making a big deal over.
After all, that man is just an
"idiot with devil fruit power"
who was overconfident
of his own position.
No matter how amazing the
devil fruit power one gains,
if he can't fully utilize it,
his existence is a total waste.
Superb criminals execute their
crimes using their superb brains.
Let's teach whoever beat Mr. 5...
...the terror of making a criminal
organization their enemy.
So this is Little Garden!
What's "little" about it?!
This place doesn't quite fit its cute name.
Ahh... It's like a terra incognita.
It's a thick jungle!
We have to be careful.
I'm worried about what
Miss All Sunday was saying.
But what's even unluckier is
the course your Log Pose indicates.
The name of the next island is...
...Little Garden.
We don't even need to do anything;
you'll be wiped out long before
you can even reach Alabasta.
A-A-Are you saying
a monster may appear?!
Who knows?
Let's go to our next destination
without going ashore on this one!
But the Log can't be stored so quickly.
Also, we have to stock up on food soon.
We didn't get anything in
the last town we were in.
There's a river mouth there.
What? Really?
I hope there's a BBQ restaurant in here.
As if there'd be one!
But you said we were going
to stock up on food.
We'll collect food to cook later!
Geez, what're you thinking?
But it's dangerous to go ashore.
Just take a look at the
plants here to start with.
I've never seen anything like them,
even in encyclopedias.
Ahh!
How cute!
You mean me?
Obviously I meant Nami-san!
What was it I just heard?
It's all right. It's just a bird.
And this is just a jungle. Don't worry.
What's the matter?
What was that for, you damn bird?!
A lizard... I wonder if it tastes good.
Is that a kind of noise you
hear from just any jungle?
That sounded like a volcano erupted!
A tiger?!
It's too huge!
Ah!
What?! What happened?!
This isn't normal!
This is definitely not normal!
Why does a tiger, king of the jungle,
fall covered in blood?!
Ah! It's decided that we're not
gonna go ashore on this island!
We'll quietly wait on the ship
until the Log is stored and...
Right!
...leave this island as soon as possible.
W... We have to go to Alabasta quickly...
Hmph!
Sanji! Make lunch for me!
Lunch?
Yeah! For replenishing energy!
A "pirate lunch" with
lots of meat and no veggies!
I can smell adventure in the air!
W-Wait a sec! Where're you going?!
Adventure!
Wanna come along?
Adventure! Adventure!
It's useless... I can't stop him.
He's too enthusiastic...
Is he crazy? There's a monster
that beat up a huge tiger in here!
Sanji! Make lunch for me!
Okay. Hold on a bit.
Say, can I come with you?
What?!
Sure! Come, come!
Not you too!
Yeah... If I just sit around here, I may
start thinking about all sorts of things.
I'll go out to take my mind off
things until the Log is stored.
No way! It may be okay for Luffy,
but it's too dangerous for you!
I'll be fine since Karoo will be with me.
He's too shocked to say a word, though.
Then, I'll make a lunch
of love for Vivi-chan.
Could you prepare something
to drink for Karoo?
Of course! Please leave it to me!
Okay.
Now you're all set. Two pirate
lunches and a special drink for Karoo.
Okay!
Well, then. See you later!
All right! Let's go!
We'll be back in a little while!
Miss Wednesday sure is brave.
As may be expected from someone
who infiltrated an enemy organization.
Well, I'm bored too,
so I'll go take a walk.
Take a walk?!
Heave ho!
Ah! Hey, Zoro!
Wait!
Hmm?
We're short of food.
If you see animals that
appear edible, bring them back.
Okay, got it.
I'll bring back one that
you can't possibly capture.
Wait, you bastard!
Hmm?!
I can't let that remark go unchallenged!
You can capture a bigger
one than I can, you say?!
Of course.
Then, it's a hunting match.
Look! We'll compete over how
many kilos of meat we get.
Didn't you mean to say how many tons?
You can talk cocky once
you've brought back some prey.
Humph! I'll take you up on that!
I wonder... why they're all like that?
I understand how you feel.
Don't cry. I'm on your side.
We're sitting ducks...
That's my line!
But wait a sec...
W-W-What's the matter?!
N-N-N-N-Nami?!
This isn't it... This isn't, either.
Ouch! Ow, ow...! H-Hey, Nami! Nami!
Hey... what the heck
are you looking for?
I remember reading about it in a book.
A... About what?
Little Garden.
Oops!
What's the matter?
Here, look at this!
There's a shellfish like a squid.
A squid shellfish!
It looks a lot like the ammonite.
It's a squid shellfish, right?
I feel like someone's been
following me for a while...
Well, it must be my imagination.
How dare you mess with me?!
Collier Shoot!
Hm...
What the hell is this? Is it edible?
Let me see... which one was it?
I think I read it recently,
but it slipped my mind.
Oh? Why is there a Sea King on the land?
A dinosaur!
A dinosaur?!
Then, this is an ancient island!
Huh?
The land here is stuck in
the time of the dinosaurs!
Hmm?
Since there were no exchanges
among islands in the Grand Line
due to the difficulties with sea travel,
each one established its unique culture.
There are islands that have an
extremely sophisticated culture...
and there're some others
that remain in the same form
without progressing for several thousand
or tens of thousands years...
The random climate in the
Grand Line makes it possible.
That's why this island
exists in the dinosaur time.
Amazing!
Luffy!
Don't jump on it!
Usopp! Usopp!
What? What's the matter?
Did you find the book?
Yeah...
Humph! What a rude guy...
So we both use the Three-Sword Style...
This is bad. On this island...
On this island...
Ah!!
What? It felt like
Nami-san just called me...
"To those residents,
this island is as if a 'little garden.'
Little Garden...
That's what I'll call this place."
Louis Arnote, explorer.
You've got me!
Ah, gentle song
Make it there for us
After a wave washed away
that little sand castle
You looked up at the passing
clouds with a sad smile
If you find the world is full of enemies,
I've got your back
Don't lose faith
You've got me!
Ah, my love
I'll hold you in my arms forever
You've got me!
Ahhh! A giant!
Pretend we're dead.
Doesn't that only work on bears?
Whoa! It's huge!
Are you a human, old guy?
With a big catch like this...
In this hunting match...
I'm the winner!
Hey, old guy. Where're you going?
Duel?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Huge Duel!
The Giants Dorry and Broggy"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!