Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen
and were held captive by Caesar Clown...
...to be used as guinea pigs for Shinokuni,
a weapon of mass destruction.
But the counter attack has begun with their ally - a Warlord - Trafalgar Law!
Franky...
...Fireball!
The ship is on fire!
Put out the fire!
Now that we are not being picked up on Caesar's Video Transponder Snail.
White Chase-ya, I have no obligation to save you
but if letting you go back to the base safely makes Vergo lose his footing,
it work out well for me.
However,
you need to forget everything that you heard about me and Joker.
I'm not asking you a favor.
It's a condition.
For sparing your life.
Hey, Kin'emon!
Can you cut iron?
That's not so hard to cut!
Brownbeard, keep charging like this!
I'm gonna charge!
"Get to Building R! The Pirate Alliance's Great Advance!"
What have you done?!
Oh no!
It's good that we made it in but the poison gas will come in, too!
Screw you guys! Are you trying to get us all killed?!
Everyone, try to plug up the hole!
Or we're all gonna die!
I guess we're safe now.
It's the end!
There is nowhere on Punk Hazard that is habitable!
It's still pretty dense.
One foot out the door and it will kill you.
How was it, Brook?
Yes, it was like a land of dead.
When I think of what would've happened if we couldn't plug the hole,
it terrifies me.
You terrify us, too!
Okay!
It's not okay!
We all could've died because of you!
We plugged the hole, too!
You guys are way more annoying than I expected!
Give it up, Straw Hats! You too, Brownbeard!
Now we're cornered?! We have nowhere to run!
We don't need to run.
Well, this is so predictable.
They shouldn't do that.
Th-They knew my name!
Oh, it's starting down there!
You two, don't stand in my way - or in his people's, understood?
Yeah.
Oh, Tra-guy! Hey you!
Now is the chance! Hurry up!
Switch us back!
You don't have to!
Hey, what are you saying, Sanji-kun?!
--Oh, it's nothing!
--No, we have to switch back!
Room.
--I want my body back! I want it back!
--It's not necessary...
Shambles.
Oh, damn! The dream is over!
I'm back!
But, oh?
Sanji-kun?
Why am I wearing a different coat?!
You took my clothes off, didn't you?!
I can explain...
Sanji, are you okay?!
Oh? My body...
But it's not just because of that punch.
Nami was beaten badly in that body by Caesar.
What?
H-Hey, what's the matter?!
I'm so glad that it was my body that got hurt!
You're so noble!
Everybody here, listen!
Law!
Now, outside of this laboratory is filled with the poison gas
but there is one passage that
could lead you directly to the sea bypassing the air outside!
This laboratory consists of multiple buildings.
We're in Building A now.
If you go through the gate at the back of this building
and pass through Building B, the central part,
you'll find Building R.
There is a big door marked "R-66"
that is an entrance to the passage to the sea.
I'd rather not have to create a massacre but I can only give you two hours.
Those of you who stay longer than that,
I can't guarantee your safety.
What?!
Hey, what do you mean by that?!
--Hey!
--Screw you!
Is something gonna happen to the lab?
Depends on how things go.
I just have to do what I have to do now.
Hmm, I see.
Robin, could you do me a favor?
What is it?
G-5!
Smo-yan!
There are children who were kidnapped two years ago in this laboratory!
Retrieve them and head for the "R-66" door!
If he is right, you'll find a harbor there.
Steal a ship and let's escape from Punk Hazard!
Alright!
I wanna leave this shitty island already!
Children...
Everyone, let's split up and look for the children and take them to the passage!
It's "R-66"!
Okay!
Zoro! You can't go alone!
Wait for me, Momonosuke!
I'll save you at any cost!
Okay. I got it.
Thanks. Well then...
Wait for me, Caesar!
I'm not gonna get suffocated this time!
I'll beat you up and kidnap you!
You see? This is a great open experiment!
The Straw Hats, Trafalgar Law, the Navy G-5...
They all sacrificed themselves for me
to prove how powerful Shinokuni is!
What happened?
What's going on?
Why I don't see any G-5 soldier at the main entrance?
Why I don't see any solidified bodies?
I can't prove the power of Shinokuni without them.
The Straw Hats, Law, and Smoker... Did they die for sure?!
What do you think, Vergo?
One thing is clear.
They are not in that cage anymore.
What? What do you mean by that?!
G-5 is a group of rough meatheads.
I don't think they are smart enough to
get away from the gas on their own.
Which means?
I guess the Straw Hat and the others
broke out of the cage and helped the G-5 soldiers escape.
What?!
Let's go!
Tashigi, I want you to lead the G-5 soldiers.
Where are you going, Smoker-san?
Don't tell me you're going after Vergo!
I can't forgive him!
The law can't settle these matters, Tashigi!
I have to do it myself! He was messing around with the Navy!
Take me with you, then!
He... Vergo is so strong!
If something happens...
Who's gonna protect our men?
Help those fools escape. The children, too.
Smoker-san...
Is it true? Luffy got beaten by Caesar before?!
Yeah, we got caught off guard and suffocated, too.
He can manipulate gas! He's such a pain in the ass!
He can remove the oxygen out of the air!
We had been put to sleep by the yetis, too.
That's no good.
That's really no good!
We spent those two years for what?
Whoa, whoa, we're both still alive so...
Screw that!
Being caught off guard could cost us our lives from now on!
H-Hey!
Don't let them pass through!
Luffy!
Get out of our way already.
What is the Moss Head doing?
Hey, Luffy!
Zoro?
Get a grip!
This is just the beginning of the New World!
He's so tough on himself.
Yeah, sorry! I won't drop my guard again!
It's Straw Hat!
I don't know what he's up to but take him down!
Gum-Gum...
...UFO!
I'm just gonna go!
Take it more seriously...
Master!
What's wrong?
With the pirate - Straw Hat Luffy in the lead,
all of the enemies have entered into the lobby of Building A
and they are advancing!
What?!
They got inside?!
How did they open that solid shutter?!
How did they break out of the cage?!
We don't know yet!
In any case, it's not good to have Law loose.
I have to kill him myself depending on what his purpose is.
Outta my way!
Let's go!
Inside the sealed-off lab...
...Luffy and the others frantically run
from the encroaching Shinokuni.
Facing instant death if unable to make it through the gate in their path...
...G-5 displays the Navy's pride!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Tashigi's Tears! G-5's Desperate Breakthrough Plan!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!