Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Oh, that's right. I get it!
What is it?
We can save her... As long as they
have me, we can save Robin! Dammit!
"Dammit"?! You don't have
to get upset or anything!
Let's hurry, Nami-kun!
Don't make me repeat it.
There isn't even a shred of hope left for you.
I heard some voice in the passage earlier,
but no one showed up after all, did they?
Lucci might be killing him right about now, huh?
It seems that we disagree.
I guess there's no point in discussing it.
I don't have much time, either.
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Stamp!
Whip!
Spear!
I'm a wolf. I'll keep going
after you until I chew you up.
Oh? You're still alive.
I don't intend to run...
I don't intend to be killed...
And I don't intend to forgive.
Forgive?
Are you sympathizing with Nico Robin?
A distracted mind just creates
openings during a fight.
If you have time to pity that ill-fated woman,
you should think of a way
to save your neck here.
Watch your mouth.
I'm the kind who heats up with anger.
Its destructive power is just like that of a devil.
Diable Jambe!
What? W-Wait!
Flambage...
...Shot!
God creates food...
...and the Devil creates spice.
I guess I made it a little too spicy.
"Fierce Sword Attacks! Zoro vs. Kaku,
Powerful Sword Fighting Showdown"
Oni... Giri!
Whoa! Damn that giraffe and Moss Head!
Are they trying to destroy this tower?
This is...
"Gates of Justice"
"Underground passage"
Gates of Justice?
So I can get there by following this?
I hope Nami-san and Usopp are
already headed to Robin-chan by now.
I have to hurry up too
and bring this #1 key to her.
I'd better get going!
You bitch! Come on already!
We're finally on the Bridge of Hesitation!
Look, Nico Robin!
You can see the opened
Gates of Justice, can't you?
It took a long time... It really took a long time.
But I'm finally here.
Once I've gone through those gates,
I can be the Government's...
No, the world's hero!
The bridge that continues onto the other
side of the doors has indeed risen up,
and is now waiting for
the hero to come and cross.
This is wonderful! Just take a look
at the path to my bright future!
Well, for you, I guess it's the path to hell, huh?
Right? You think so too, right, Nico Robin?
--No!
--Hey, what're you doing?!
Ow!
Hey! Stop!
You... Enough already, you bitch!
You still don't get it?!
It's pointless to try and struggle!
Do you really get who I am?!
I'm the world's hero. I'm the
world's hero, you got that?!
You're in the worst situation without a
shred of hope left! I'm different from you!
I have a bright future full of hopes and dreams!
Do you get it, you dumb woman?!
Dumb! Dumb! Dumb!
Luffy...
Everyone...
Everyone...!
Gotta hurry! Gotta hurry!
It'll be meaningless if I
can't make it in time! Hm?
I can see something up ahead!
We'll reach our destination
in about ten minutes!
Hurry up and check the formation of all ships!
Yes, sir!
Hey! Stand up already, you bitch!
Now, let's go, Nico Robin!
Is this the exit?!
You... Straw Hat!
Ah! Franky!
What're you doing here, you jerk?!
You idiot! Enough with the attitude already!
I'm on your side right now! Just give it up!
Lucci, huh? So you're having
a tough time against him?
Where's Nico Robin? I brought two keys.
Shall I give you a hand?
No. More importantly...
...please stop Robin.
You can get to the Gates of Justice
through the doors behind the pigeon guy.
Robin has already been taken away.
I'll restrain him.
Just super leave it to me, you jerk!
I'm saying that if I had to choose,
I like meat better!
And I'm saying it doesn't matter, herbivore!
Hm?
In any case, I'll hurry up and take your key.
If I can't make it in time,
it'll be the same as defeat.
Two-Sword Style... Nigiri...
You get stronger when you
wear a towel on your head?
Who knows...?
Tower Climb!
Tower Climb Return!
Flash!
Ripple!
If you jump, you'll have blind spots.
Giraffe Scythe!
Iron Body. No Blind Spots.
What?!
I've become square with no blind spots.
Shut up! What the hell are you doing?!
You're so naive.
Have you not noticed...?
What?
Giraffes have four legs.
Tempest Kick!
Like I said, are you gonna fight or not?!
Where are you looking?
My attack has already started.
The slash attacks I directed upwards...
...will deflect off the ceiling...
...and pour down on you!
Giraffe Shower!
Iron Body.
Slash attack pellets...
Dammit! I can't block them!
Nose Pistol!
You bastard...!
What a tough guy you are.
I'm flabbergasted.
I've trained my body, you damn gi-riff-raff!
Gi-riff-raff? I am a giraffe!
Gi-riff-raff.
That's wrong! I'm not gi-riff-raff!
--Shut up!
--Hm?
Gi-riff-raff... Gi-riff-raff...
Stop rambling... I could care less!
If you're mocking me, you'll pay for it.
Likewise. You'd better prepare
yourself. Playtime is over.
First, I'm gonna break through... that Iron Body!
You sure do say funny things.
You are going to break through Iron Body?
You think you can do it?
Yeah, of course.
Want me to try?
One-Sword Style...
...Lion Strike!
Tempest Kick!
Dragon Cut!
Would you have been able to cut if it was iron?!
It's my call as to whether or not I
use Iron Body to block your attack.
I see. I guess it's not that simple, huh?
One Gorilla!
Two Gorilla!
Now, bring it on!
Three-Sword Style...
A strength contest this time?
How interesting.
Nose Pistol!
Two Gorilla Slash!
What strength...!
You speak in an arrogant manner.
You're the type who can't even
imagine your own fall, aren't you?
How haughty you are!
So are you!
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Paper Art.
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Shave!
Straw Hat!
Tsk!
Tempest Kick!
Weapons Left!
Shave!
What?!
Gum-Gum... Rocket!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
Straw Hat!
Okay, stay like that and don't move!
Wait!
Don't waste your time on this guy. Go already!
I said I'd restrain him, didn't I?!
Restrain him?! But you're barely
holding your own against him!
We should work together and...
Franky!
He's my opponent! I'm the
one who has to restrain him.
I'll say it one more time.
Hurry up and go to Robin!
And stop her!
Or she'll be gone forever!
We won't be able to get her back!
You...
Stop! Sea Train!
Give Tom-san back to us!
That's not possible.
I won't let you get away.
Straw Hat!
Hurry!
Go!
You...
Okay!
I thought I said I wouldn't...
...let you get away!
Moon Walk!
Shave!
What?!
Finger Pistol!
I thought I told you.
I'm your opponent!
I still haven't shown you...
...a giraffe's real wild strength!
Stop talking! Just show it to me.
Sure thing!
Have a good look at the giraffe's power!
Giraffe Cannon!
There's no giraffe like that.
Extreme Nose Pistol!
Giraffe Blast!
It stretched?!
See? What did I tell you?
That long neck is your weak point.
That's not totally true. Tempest Kick!
Spinning White Blade!
It's you who has an opening.
Tsk! Just what kind of creature is he?!
I won't miss next time.
Giraffe Cannon!
Wha...
Oh, shoot! I pushed my neck in so
much that my arms and legs got longer!
What kind of setup does your body have?!
It's as if flour got crammed in
and got pushed out as noodles.
Just like a pasta machine!
Hm?
Pasta Machine!
Don't just make that into an attack name!
I like my long neck, but long arms
and legs are easy to use, too.
I'm an expert at fighting who turns
an unexpected situation into a chance.
Just watch... The technique
using this long reach...
Giraffe Blast!
You couldn't come up with a new attack?!
Enough is enough!
Three-Sword Style...
...Dragon Twister!
Iron Body!
How powerful...!
Shave!
Moon Walk!
What?
He jumped into the upper floor!
Pasta Machine!
Thanks for waiting!
Arms, legs, and neck...
If I can control their reach at will,
I can swing my swords vigorously!
I'm a Four-Sword Style swordsman.
I can now make full use of the giraffe's power!
You no longer have any chance against me!
The giraffe's power is very strong...
You can store your obstructive neck away...
You use the Four-Sword Style...
Hmph!
What?!
He stopped my sword attacks?!
None of those things...
can be a basis for my defeat.
I'll use my strongest Tempest Kick, Sky Slicer,
and cut down that useless retort of yours!
You have nowhere to escape.
Hardships are fine by me!
I choose to walk the path of Asura!
What's that illusion?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Demon God Zoro! An Incarnation
of Asura Born from Fighting Spirit"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!