Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
Everyone! Hold on tight
to the ship or get inside!
The ship's going up!
--Spread the sails! Right away!
--Eh?
If we're dealing with wind
and sea, I can navigate it!
Who's this ship's navigator?!
You are, Nami-san!
Awesome! The ship is flying!
What could be up there?!
Let's plunge through
the cumuloregalis clouds!
"Sail the White Sea! The Sky Knight
and the Gate in the Clouds"
Can't breathe...!
Drat! They got away!
They're lucky...
You're pretty carefree, after our
prey just got away from us!
Do something, Captain! Let's go
after 'em and take 'em down!
Don't fret, Burgess!
They haven't left this world!
We'll run into 'em soon enough!
As long as we're on the Grand Line!
Exactly.
All things in this world are cogs
that move in tune to strong desires.
--See?!
--You're so right!
Damn... What happened?! Is everyone here?!
Hey, guys! Look outside the ship!
What is this place?!
It's pure white!
--Clouds?!
--We're in the clouds?!
How are we staying on them?!
Of course you can stay on them! They're clouds!
No, you can't!
Oh, no! Usopp isn't breathing!
What?! Do something! CPR!
Okay! I'll give Nami-san CPR!
--Moron...
--Usopp! Say something!
Usopp!
Clouds... What?!
These are clouds! No, there's
too many! What is this?!
Basically, this is an ocean in the sky?
An ocean... in the sky?!
But look! The Log Pose is still pointing upward!
It seems we're in the middle section
of the cumuloregalis clouds.
We need to go even higher? How?
That, I don't know...
--Did you call me a moron?!
--I forget.
An ocean...!
In Swimming Lane #1, Captain Usopp!
--You can do it! Good luck!
--Yay!
Hey, now! Don't be reckless!
This ocean's still a mystery!
An ocean's an ocean!
--Awesome!
--He's so brave!
There's so little resistance...
But it's hard to see anything at all...
Oh! I'm going deeper and deeper! So easily...!
Usopp's so lucky! If only I could swim, too!
I bet it's so fun...
Hey.
He's... not coming back up.
I was just wondering... Do you
think this ocean has a bottom?
--You don't mean...!
--Did that bastard fall from the clouds?!
Usopp!
That moron! I tried to tell him!
Stretch your arm as far as you can!
--But I can't see down there!
--It's all right. Leave it to me!
Ojos Fleur!
--There he is!
--Eh?! Where?!
Veinte Fleurs!
Okay! Pull him up!
You got him?! Okay!
Is he heavy?!
--He shouldn't be.
--Luffy! You can do it!
You can do it!
Yes! He's back up!
Things came with him!
They wanna eat Usopp!
It's nothing to be that afraid of!
Huh?!
But it sure is hard to breathe here...
This is one strange creature...
I'm not even sure if it's a fish...
That octopus was like a balloon!
It's definitely an animal. It was moving.
I can't believe things live in clouds...!
Perhaps we should think of this
as an ocean rather than clouds.
What's this flat snake?
A flounder! Because it's flat!
So this is a flounder?!
Dammit! What is it this time, Usopp?!
My pants! There was something in 'em!
Usopp!
Sky island scary, sky island scary...
What an unlucky day.
These are skyfish! The odd fish
described in Noland's logbook.
They must have evolved to survive
in this bottomless sky ocean...
So they turned all
balloon-like and flat and stuff?
To be even lighter...
The buoyancy here is weaker
than in the oceans below.
They have scales like feathers,
and weird carnivore-like mouths!
I tried sautéing it.
--This is good!
--We're still investigating it!
What're you guys thinking?!
Oh! It really is good! What is this?!
I've never had anything like it!
Is it to your liking, Nami-san?!
Let's eat that big one, too!
That one looks like it'd be a lot of work...
Where is the sky island?
Oh! A ship...
A ship! Hey, guys! A ship... and a person?
Eh?
Eh?!
Hey. What's wrong, Chopper?
Is there a ship out there, Chopper?
No, uhh, there was, but not anymore...!
Huh?
--And there's a bull, and it's
running straight here, it's on...
--You're not making sense! Calm down!
What's wrong with you?
It's a person! Someone's coming!
He's running on the clouds!
Hey, stop! What do you want?!
To eliminate you!
--Looks like he wants to fight!
--Fine by me!
What's going on?!
H-Hey! What's with you three?!
He's gonna shoot us!
Sky island scary, sky island scary...
That is far enough!
What?! Who's this now?!
I am the Sky Knight.
He's gone...
What the heck's going on?! Who was that?!
And what's with you guys?! You're
pathetic, losing three against one!
Thank you for saving us!
I have no choice. This one is on the house.
Man... Talk about being worthless...
I can't move well... for some reason...
--It must be because of the thin air.
--Yeah, now that you mention it...
Are you Blue Sea people?
Blue Sea people? What's that?
Oh, yeah! Who are you?!
I am the Sky Knight.
"Blue Sea people" is the term for
those who live beneath the clouds.
The Sky Knight...
In other words, did you come
up here from the blue seas?
Yeah! That's right!
Then that explains it. This is the
White Sea, 7,000 meters in the air.
The White-White Sea even further
above reaches 10,000 meters high.
Ordinary Blue Sea people
can't possibly endure it here.
Alright! I've gotten used to it!
Yeah. I feel much better now.
No, no, no! That is not possible!
Anyway, why was that guy
speeding on top of the clouds?!
Now, now. Hold on.
I'm sure you have many questions,
but let's talk business first.
Business?
I am a freelance soldier-for-hire.
These seas are fraught with danger.
If you don't know how to fight
in the sky, guerrillas like that one
will come after you and turn
you into food for the skyfish.
For a 5,000,000 Extol One Whistle,
I will help you.
What're you talking about, old guy?
What?! That is quite cheap!
I won't lower it a single Extol more!
I need to earn a living too, you know!
What in the world is "Extol"?
And what's this "whistle" or whatever?
You came here via the summit
of High-West, did you not?
Then you must've passed an island or two.
Again, what're you talking about, old guy?
Wait! You mean there are other
ways of coming to this sky ocean?!
And "an island or two"? Does that
mean there are lots of sky islands?!
Don't tell me you came here via the...
We rode the Knock-Up Stream.
My word! That monstrous current?!
So there still are people
gutsy enough for that...
It wasn't a normal route, after all...!
We could've died, you know!
We could've done it more safely if
we had gathered more information!
What does it matter now? We're already here.
Sky islands scary, sky islands scary...
Did you lose any of your crew?
No, we're all here.
That wouldn't have been
the case with any other route.
100 people head into the sky,
a few arrive, and someone survives.
That is the gamble.
But with the Knock-Up Stream,
everyone dies or everyone arrives.
That's it.
Not many can make that all-or-nothing bet,
especially these days.
I now see that you are capable
navigators with courage and skill.
Yes, I must admit it was
only because I was here!
While these guys were on their
knees crying and giving up on life,
--I told them, "I will navigate us--"
--Hold on!
One blow of this One Whistle...
...and I shall come to your aid!
Normally, I would charge five million Extol,
but I will give you the
One Whistle as a present!
Wait! We still don't know your name!
I am Gan Fall, the Sky Knight!
And this is my partner, Pierre!
I forgot to mention it, but my partner Pierre...
...is a bird that ate a Horse-Horse
Fruit and gained its powers.
A bird?!
In short, he becomes a horse with wings!
Namely...
No way! Wow! A Pegasus?!
Yes! A Pegasus!
How... unexciting.
May luck be with you, warriors!
That was a weird thing it turned into...
Was there even a reason for it to transform?
Good question...
In the end, he didn't tell us anything.
You're right! Nothing at all!
Now we're back to square one.
How do we get up there?!
I know! Let's call that old guy and ask!
H-H-Hold on, Luffy! This is only
supposed to be used in emergencies!
What if that weird masked
guy shows up again?!
For now, let's take our ship somewhere.
Hey, look over there!
--What could that be?
--Isn't that a weird cloud?
It also looks like a waterfall...
Alright! It's decided! Let's check it out!
Wait! Stop! Stop!
There are huge clouds in the way...
What do we do?
They're floating in the sky ocean,
so they can't be ocean, too...
Then what kind of clouds are they?
If they were ordinary clouds,
they'd keep moving forward...
Let's touch one and find out!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
It bounced off!
Look! I'm on it! I'm not sinking!
It's all fluffy, like cotton!
What is this?! What is this?! It's too fun!
Wow!
--Now how does this work?!
--It's mysterious...
Me too! I'm coming, too!
Me too!
This feels great! It's warm and
makes me wanna sleep right here!
It's even better than a freshly-aired futon!
But this means the ship can't go
through places filled with these...
Hey! Find a route that the ship can take!
Right! Okay!
Hey, Luffy! There's something over here!
--What is it?! What is it?!
--Hey! Where are you going?!
Quit playing around!
--What is that?
--A gate?
Yeah! There's a big gate
under that waterfall thingy!
There are manmade objects
in a place like this?
There could be anything in this ocean
and it wouldn't be surprising...
We'll find out what it is
after we get through here!
--Left next!
--No, right!
--It's to our left!
--No, our right!
Let's call the old armor guy!
Stop that!
Alright! Looks like we're through!
It's a gate, all right...
And look, that waterfall-like
cloud really was a waterfall!
It's flowing over those
different clouds from earlier!
What's this now? "Heaven's Gate"...?!
That's unlucky! It sounds
like we're on our way to die!
Y'know, maybe we already are dead.
Ah! That would explain this weird world...
Eep! We're dead?!
Heaven, huh? This is gonna be great!
I finally get to go there!
Get real!
What was that for?!
Your jokes aren't funny!
Why did I get hit, too...?
Look! Over there! Someone's coming out!
Look! She has wings on her back!
It's an angel! Is that what angels are like?!
She's like a pickled plum!
U-Umm...
I am Amazon, the Heaven's Gate inspector.
Sightseeing? Or perhaps war?
I-I guess it's kind of like sightseeing...
We wanna go to the sky islands!
They're past this gate, right?
What do you mean by "war"?
It doesn't matter either way.
If you're going to the upper area,
pay the entrance fee of
one billion Extol per person.
That is the law.
O-One billion?!
There's that "Extol" stuff again...
How much is one billion Extol in Berries?
Whatever it is, one billion
sounds really expensive!
One billion per person...
Seven billion for seven people...
It's just to enter the country!
Do countries usually charge
that much just to enter?!
This old lady's trying to scam--
U-Umm, about the money...
What if we kinda don't have it...?
--You can pass.
--Are you serious?!
Or you don't have to pass.
I am neither a gatekeeper nor a guard.
I simply ask your intentions.
Then let's go! To the sky islands!
We don't got money,
but we're going through, old lady!
I see. The seven of you, then?
Yeah. But how do we get to the sky islands--
--Eh?!
--What the...?! Something's here!
The White Sea's famous Express Lobster...
It's moving!
It's a huge lobster!
Is it planning to go up the waterfall?!
--Hold on tight!
--What speed!
It's still a ways to the top!
This is Heaven's Gate Inspector Amazon!
Attention, almighty God and His priests...
Seven illegal entrants
into God's Land, Skypiea...
Give unto them Heaven's Judgment!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
Heaven is this terrifying of a place?!
It's not supposed to be like this!
This isn't Heaven!
Look! An angel's coming this way!
She's probably all wrinkly like the last one...
No... It's the real deal this time!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Godland, Skypiea!
Angels on a Beach of Clouds"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!