Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight
fierce battles against other tough
contenders from the New World.
Alright! Here we go!
The Gaon Cannon! Fire!
What is that?
Yes!
Head blow!
A long time ago...
It goes back 800 years, Law.
20 kings from 20 countries came together
at the center of the world
and formed one giant organization.
That's what we call
the World Government now.
The kings who created it...
...decided to move to the Holyland of
Marie Jois and live there
with their families.
The Nefeltari Family of Alabasta refused,
so there were 19 families to be exact.
The descendents of those
creators who still live there
and reign over the world are the Celestial Dragons.
In those countries, they elected
new kings out of necessity
and new royal families rose.
In the case of my country - Dressrosa,
the new royalty was the Riku Family.
And the old royalty who
moved to the Holyland
of Marie Jois
as the creators of the world were...
...the Don Quixote Family!
"Beautiful Sword!
Cavendish of the White Horse!"
OFF THE COAST OF DRESSROSA
Now, what should we do with this?
Bone-kichi, I gave her a single blow, too!
I know. You have a great suji (aptitude).
Y-Yeah? Do I?
I don't have any suji (muscle), though.
Because I'm a skeleton.
It'd be too cruel to dump her into the sea.
Yeah, she's a Devil Fruit eater.
I don't even wanna see her panties.
Wh-Who did you call Miss Universe?
Nobody said such a thing! No!
Should I hit her one more time?
Just leave her alone.
We gotta hurry and meet Tra-guy.
But why does he wanna leave Caesar with us?
Listen, I need you to...
....sail the ship to Green Bit now!
I wanna leave Caesar with you guys!
Yeah, it is strange.
Doflamingo resigned from the
Seven Warlords by our request
so we have to return Caesar to him.
Y-You idiots don't know anything, don't you?
Young Master-sama doesn't take negotiation
with brats like you seriously.
He didn't resign from the Seven Warlords.
What?
Hey, what do you mean by that?!
What do you mean?!
Ouch!
That hurt, you damn brat!
O-Nami!
You guys have been fooled!
Violet must've unearthed
all of your plans by now
and all of your friends
are probably captured!
What?!
All right! This stormy battle
royal is finally coming
to the final match - Block D!
All the competitors are
fighting for survival!
This battle is also going to
be bloody since there're so
many tough contenders.
First, I have to draw
your attention to this man!
He is a notorious class-A war criminal
from the Sea Battle of Dias!
SULEIMAN THE BEHEADER
A CLASS-A WAR CRIMINAL FROM THE SEA BATTLE OF DIAS
Suleiman the Beheader!
And...
An admiral of the Yonta Maria Grand Fleet!
"The Surmounter" Orlumbus!
"THE SURMOUNTER" ORLUMBUS - AN ADVENTURER/
AN ADMIRAL OF THE YONTA MARIA GRAND FLEET
A military captain of a southern country -
the Majiatsuka Kingdom!
Rolling Logan!
ROLLING LOGAN - A MILITARY CAPTAIN OF
A SOUTHERN COUNTRY - THE MAJIATSUKA KINGDOM
And there are more!
A FIGHTING LION - AGYO
A fighting lion - Agyo!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
AN ARSONIST - DAMASK
An arsonist - Damask!
A sorcerer - Mummy!
A SORCERER - MUMMY
A GLADIATOR - AGILIA
A gladiator - Agilia!
Any one of them can win this battle!
The match has just begun but
the one that stands out the most so far is...
...the man that we were expecting!
Cavendish of the White Horse!
Who are you?
Gardoa, the beautiful bounty hunter!
Gardoa-sama! You're so handsome!
What's with that spear?
This is like a medal to me.
I use bounties I get from catching pirates
to get shinier and shinier spears.
There are so many people with a
high prize in this competition.
It's nice to make money.
If I can get hold of the prize on you -
280 million berries,
I can even make a diamond spear!
Smells good!
Damn!
How would you like this, then?!
Where is he?!
I'm here!
A diamond spear?
You've got to be kidding!
What?!
People like you who try to best me,
I'll never forgive them!
We were wrong!
Cavendish-sama, you're so cool!
He's really strong!
Yes!
You hear that, Straw Hat Luffy?!
People cheer for me!
I'm more popular than you!
Move, Cabbage!
I can't see Rebecca because of you!
--He's right!
--We don't wanna see you!
Just go away!
Rebecca!
I'm gonna take her down!
Just as we expected,
contenders who are looking to gain fame are
targeting the despised Rebecca!
It may be just a matter of time
before she gets defeated!
Rebecca, behind you!
Take this!
Kill her!
Chop her up and let her fall into the water!
GREEN BIT
So you're the Celestial Dragon.
Doflamingo!
I was, to be exact.
But not anymore.
What is "bloodline"? What is "destiny"?
I don't think there are that
many people who've led such
a checkered life as mine.
Explain it to me so I can understand!
I'm sorry, Law.
I wish I could tell the story of my life
before I met you, over drinks.
But I don't have time for that.
I've got to do something about
the Straw Hats in Dressrosa.
I know there are quite a few people
who underestimated them and got hurt.
What's the matter, Fujitora?
Well...
I heard a clap of thunder
from the direction of the sea.
How does the sky look?
Thunder?
I may be blind,
but I always thought I could tell the weather.
Maybe I'm getting too old.
I believe Nami-ya can manipulate the weather.
The ship is here!
Hey, Joker!
If you got it back, give it to me already!
My heart! My heart! Hey!
Give it to me now!
I never said that was Caesar's heart!
What?! You've been lording that
over me all along!
In fact, my heart is missing from my body!
Yeah, I can't hear my heartbeat!
Joker! What are you doing?!
You're killing me! I'm gonna die!
I didn't feel anything.
What?!
Hey, what's wrong?! Stay with me! Hey!
What?! Was it a Navy soldier's?!
Then, where's mine?!
I heard my man screaming!
What are you doing, Heavenly Demon?!
Room!
Keep pinning me down with gravity, Fujitora.
Or I'll run!
Shambles!
What? What?!
Joker! Help me!
You still have that much energy, Law?
He just doesn't know when to give up.
You bastard! Let go of me, Law!
Where's my heart?!
Don't give me trouble, you squirt!
You know there's no place to run!
You see Tra-guy?
I can't see clearly because of the fog.
I see a weird forest.
I don't wanna believe
what that old bat said but...
...what if, what if Tra-guy's
plan didn't work out well
and if we take Caesar with us,
what's gonna happen, then?
Doflamingo will come after us.
--What?!
--Huh?
I'm scared!
Ow, ow, ow...
What? What? What just happened?!
Wh-What's going on?
There is something in the water!
I-I-It's a school of the Fighting Fish!
You got too close to the island!
The Fighting Fish?
What are they?
They're killer fish that can sink a warship!
--What?!
--O-Nami!
Come after me, Doflamingo!
If he goes for the ship,
it's all over for us!
I'm gonna draw him to the bridge
and get Caesar on board the ship
and fight Doflamingo on the bridge
so I can buy enough time
for the ship to get away!
What?
Is he gonna go across the bridge?
I don't get it.
Why does he want to get to Dressrosa?
It's more favorable for me.
No! Idiots!
I get it.
Wait, Doflamingo!
They have nothing to do with this!
It's over, Law!
The ship is gonna break up!
Stop! Or I'm gonna grill you!
Where did those Fighting Fish go?
Bone-kichi, where did they go?
The Fighting Fish... The Fighting Fish...
The Fighting Fish...
What?!
What is it this time?!
--Doflamingo is flying towards us!
--What?!
Young Master-sama!
What is this?! A nightmare?!
Are we gonna get killed?!
No!
Watch this, Law!
I'll viciously slay your allies
right before your eyes!
Don't!
Tra-guy, help...
Hey!
My friends are crying in fear!
Leave them alone!
Sanji!
Here comes quite a tough one.