Edited at https://subtitletools.com
You're no match for our martial arts skills.
Now, hand it over already...
...or else it'll get dirty with your blood.
Dammit...
I thought... I could defeat you.
To tell you the truth...
...Iceberg-san told me to run right away.
He told me to drop it quickly and run...
...since...
...it's a complete fake.
What?
I got stuck! Dammit! I got stuck again!
--Why does this always happen?!
--Straw Hat...!
Tempest Kick.
His kicks cut the wall!
Wh-What the hell are these?
We've got an emergency situation.
We don't have time for you.
--I can't move!
--Hey, restrain that guy, too.
Go home!
I've got nothing I could give you people!
If you don't, that puts us in quite a bind.
What should I tell you first...
...when you're about to die?
You disappointed me.
Lucci!
It's your own fault.
You should've given it to the
Government when they asked nicely.
Kaku!
If possible, I wanted to make this town
part of my memory without hurting you.
Kalifa...
So you also inherited your
master's obstinacy, huh?
Blueno, from the bar...
You guys... work for... the Government?
That's right. Going undercover
was a pretty easy mission for us.
In any case, your prudence
leaves me at a loss for words.
Now, Iceberg-san...
Where're the blueprints of
the ancient weapon Pluton?
Please tell us, before many people get hurt.
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Secret Bond! Iceberg and Franky"
I'd better hurry up. The waves
and wind are getting rough.
What's he doing?!
G-Give it back to me!
We have to... have our ship repaired...
That money is crucial to us!
With that money...
...we can finally repair the Merry's scars!
I can't let you jerks have it!
Come to think of it, he said
that 200 million Berries
was going to be used for
the repair of their ship.
It appears that he doesn't know
Aqua Laguna is coming tonight.
Hmph! What a waste of effort.
Okay! If I keep it airtight like this
and reinforce the ship with lumber,
it'll probably do fine.
That's not necessary.
Wh... Who's there?
"Who's there"?
Hey, hey... You've already
forgotten me... long-nosed lad?
Th-That voice... That guy's...
Wh-Wh-What'd you come
here for, you bastard?!
Now, now, don't lose your cool like that.
Fighting in a place like this
won't get us anywhere.
This area will soon sink due to a storm surge.
I guess we'll make this ship that you
love so much our hostage, too, huh?
Wh-What're you talking about?
Well... I have some business with Straw Hat...
...so I came here to kidnap you.
Don't worry. I used the back of my swords.
Why'd you have to knock
down all the shipwrights?!
Wow, Zoro is strong!
Oh, well... Let's go already!
Zoro! This way!
Yeah!
No, I said, this way!
How could you go in the wrong direction
when we're leading the way for you?!
A miracle?!
Oh, that way.
Nami! Zoro has disappeared!
This is a miracle!
He got lost again?!
See?! My head came out...
since it's made of rubber.
Okay, good job! Get every body
part out by doing what you just did!
Yep! No problem!
All right! I'm out... since I'm a rubber man!
Good job! Okay! Take off my cuffs!
Okay!
Just wait and see... damn bull and skull...!
We were undercover for five years.
Please don't worry. We didn't
cut corners with our work.
I do understand how dispirited you are.
However, since we can't spend
any more time on this matter,
we're going to try our best to achieve our goal.
If you're thinking of putting up an
unwise resistance, I suggest you don't.
You know the name "Cipher Pol," don't you?
It's the Government's
supreme intelligence agency,
with eight bases around the world,
called CP1 through CP8 by people.
When the Government orders it, they dig
up any kind of information in any place.
I know about them...
...but only up to CP8.
Right...
However, we are CP9, the 9th Cipher Pol,
a supposedly non-existent unit.
Since we possess a certain privilege,
we can't reveal ourselves to the public.
Privilege?
That's right...
This is in the name of justice to the end,
but when there're citizens who are
uncooperative toward the Government...
...we have permission to kill them.
How selfish...! Justice cannot
be a reason for killing!
The World Government has
partially changed their thinking.
Rather than remaining in fear
of the weapon's restoration,
they decided to awaken it
to make it into a force of justice
that can end this Great Pirate Era.
However, you don't want to help them.
You're saying that you don't want to "save"
those people who keep being victimized
by pirates around the world.
Nonsense... If the weapon is restored,
the world will only fight over its power.
The damage only keeps growing!
It seems that you don't trust
the Government, Iceberg-san.
I just know the nature of humans, that's all, lad.
Restrain yourself. Just how long are
you going to keep acting like my boss?
Kaku, check his pulse.
Pardon me.
Iceberg-san...
To tell you the truth, we came up
with a hypothesis a bit ago.
Please don't worry. It's not that
we're going to torture you now.
All you have to do is listen to our
hypothesis without saying a word.
I'm sure your blood will tell us the truth.
Be careful when you walk. Or you'll get hurt.
Get off of me!
Grandma, Grandma! Aren't we going back yet?
Well... we've got a nice wind blowing.
Why don't we take the long way?
It's just perfect for sobering up.
What? When you're still drinking right now?
Say, can you sober up
while you're still drinking?
Sure I can. I haven't been drinking
for several decades for nothing.
Er... Several decades?! That's weird!
That's weird!
That's weird! That's weird!
Ah... it hasn't been several decades.
It's been eight years...
Well then, I'll explain the thought
process leading to our hypothesis.
First, we have doubts about your
action of passing off the fake to us.
You guessed that the culprits
who came after the blueprints
were from the Government, so you
indicated where the fake was.
However, if it happened to be
someone who had a grudge against you
and they just came to kill you,
the real blueprints would lose their owner
and they'd no longer be passed down.
You're not stupid enough not
to think about that possibility.
Even though you knew that,
you still didn't try to give the
real blueprints to anyone tonight.
That means you've already
entrusted them with someone.
At the very least,
you don't have them with you.
So we think.
It's no use. Don't act up.
This is still only a possibility.
Of course, no convincing proof
can be found anywhere.
The past five years of our
surveillance and investigation
found no proof in your actions, either.
In addition, the person who is
entrusted with the blueprints
has to have proper shipbuilding skills.
Well, let me continue with our hypothesis.
Now things are getting more interesting.
These are the fake blueprints
that you passed off on us earlier.
When I look at it carefully,
there're signatures by the architects.
"Tom," "Iceberg," and "Cutty Flam."
At the end, there's a
company name: "Tom's Workers."
You might've thought that you outwitted
your enemy by using these fakes.
But you never even dreamed that
your enemy was hiding this close.
That was your miscalculation.
To an overnight intruder
who came after the blueprints,
these would probably just be trash.
But to us, who lived in this
town for the past five years,
these architects' names are very interesting.
Iceberg-san, you have a guest.
Tom's Workers, led by the
legendary shipwright Tom,
was a shipbuilding company
that was full of mysteries.
I think it used to be on this island,
but there's no list of workers
or company registration.
Just finding out the fact that you
were Tom's disciple was quite hard.
According to the report by the Government,
Tom had only two disciples.
And a Government official
verified that one of them died
in an accident that happened eight years ago.
Did you know... that Tom's
violent disciple Cutty Flam died?
However, I remember hearing
this name Cutty Flam before.
Iceberg-san, you have a guest. He said
you'd know who if I told you "Cutty Flam."
It was about four years ago, a little while
after we started going undercover here.
There was a man who came through the
Galley-La Company's gate to see you.
He used that name just once.
I remember it, too.
Me, too.
Shall I show him in?
No... turn him away.
In other words...
...Tom's other disciple Cutty Flam is still alive...
...and lives in this town...
...after changing his name to Franky!
What a roundabout way of meeting.
What're these?
Hey, they're the blueprints
for the ancient weapon.
Don't use the name Cutty Flam from now on.
Huh?
It's only a matter of time before I get targeted.
Leave the island with them... Franky.
Seems like there's no mistake about it.
I never thought that you and that
guy were connected like that.
It's true that no matter
how much we investigated,
we couldn't figure out his real identity.
But because he was a ship demolition worker
and because of his behavior,
we paid no attention to him.
I see... Involving a dead person
was indeed a perfect way to exploit
our blind spot, since our speculation
was generated only from the facts.
The Franky Family would come
to the shipyard to sell lumber.
So there were many chances
for you to make an arrangement
to give him the blueprints.
Now, come to think of it,
you could say that he was a
neighbor who kept a safe distance.
If you don't have the blueprints with you,
it makes sense that you held firm.
If it was your only fellow disciple
whom you entrusted them with,
it's also understandable that you didn't entrust
them with any of the foremen at Galley-La.
Now, our speculations
are connected as one line.
In addition...
...your pounding blood proved it to be true!
--Hurry!
--Hey!
Are you really sure this is the right way?
Don't you say that!
They've been hurt quite badly.
Over there! That door is the one!
There's no mistake!
Many people are down over there, too!
Hm?
Now, you go ahead! Ahead of us!
Cut down the door and make a dash!
--Go ahead!
--What the hell?! Don't order me around!
Hey, Straw Hat!
You idiot! Wrong room! It's the next room!
Oh, the next room?
Well, it's not your fault.
So many things are happening tonight.
You're only human. It's just natural that
you couldn't hide your consternation.
I appreciate what you've done for us.
We're done with you.
Let's hurry and find Franky.
You bastards...!
Hm?
Where's Robin?!
--Luffy!
How bothersome...!
Robin! I've finally found you!
Hey, Luffy! Where the hell have you been?!
Robin! I'm glad that I could see you again!
Hold on a sec... What's going on here?
Well, well, well...
Straw Hat...
Paulie...
Iceberg-san... What the hell...
...is going on?!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Hey, Robin! Why are you with jerks like them?!
That's right. They work for the
Government, right?! So why?!
Goodbye.
Wait! I won't accept it! We're not done talking!
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Come Back, Robin! Showdown with CP9!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!