Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago
to go on to the next stage the New World.
Let's go to the Fish-Man Island!
There's something at 6
o'clock! Is it a creature? No...
Are you guys all ready?!
--Yes, brother!
--Yes, yes!
The target is right there!
Hey, guys! There is a ship kind
of thing coming from behind!
Charge!
It's a pirate ship!
"Deadly Combat under the Sea!
The Demon of the Ocean Strikes!"
Run!
Hard to port!
Go, Sea Cow!
--They're coming after us!
--That sounds so familiar...
They're so persistent!
What do they want from us?
Stop!
The bubble is gonna pop!
--You're doing great, Sea Cow!
--Yes!
--Are they gonna come aboard?
--Sea Cow?
Wait a minute! That's...
The bubbles are joined!
Brother, now is the chance!
--Alright, should we do it?!
--Yes!
Hey, Momoo! You're Momoo of the
Arlong Pirates, aren't you?
Do you remember me?
I'm Nami! I was there at the Arlong Park!
Hm? Hey, Luffy, doesn't he look familiar?
Yeah?
Die, you damn thing!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
--Let's board their ship!
--Yes!
Whoa! He's coming through the bubble!
No, somebody's coming!
We gotta fight!
--Guys! Are you ready?!
--Yes!
While they're dumbfounded,
kill them all!
Let's go!
Yes!
Guys, follow my lead!
What?!
--What's the matter, Sea Cow?
--Why, Sea Cow?
--Oh no, we left Captain Caribou on that ship!
--Brother!
Alright, by way of greeting,
fire the gatling gun!
Kill all the Straw Hats and...
Huh?
No! Don't throw me out into the water!
That's something...
...you shouldn't do!
You have to value people's life!
The gods... the gods are watching
over you! Don't you think so?!
You're being inconsistent!
Weren't you gonna fire a
gatling gun and kill us all!
No, that was just... That
was just a play on words.
That wasn't playing.
Who are you? You must be
the captain of the ship.
Oh, Roronoa Zoro!
No way! I'm not a captain! I'm just...
I was forced to be a slave for them!
Oh, I'm sick of being on that ship!
He's making ridiculous excuses.
Oh yeah! This is great!
Can I stay on this ship for a little while?
Please?
Well, he is kind of pathetic...
No way! He just made it up!
What?! He just made it up?!
Hey, where did you find the Sea
Cow who was drawing your ship?
Oh...
Here is... mmm... Cutie-san!
You're the cat burglar.
Stop looking at our navigator like that!
Nami-san! You're safe...
...now!
That's getting to be a pain!
I just caught that sea monster somewhere...
Experienced people have
those animals pull their ship.
What?!
Is that so?
--Stop! Stop, Sea Cow!
--What happened?
Brother! I'll save you!
I wanna find a sea monster.
Hey, Luffy! What are you up to?
Oh, it's just a turtle... It's too small.
Come on!
Let's start his rehabilitation
with some less stimulating pics.
Hey, Nami.
The direction we're heading is slightly off
from where Log Pose is pointing.
Yeah, that's fine.
The right course should be south
west of where it's pointing.
It's faster to go straight.
Why should we do that?
If you go straight, you'd be
taken away by the sea current
and get stuck by an undersea
mountain or volcano.
What?! Volcano! It's
scary to be in the water!
But I thought the sea currents
in the Grand Line were volatile.
Is there any stable current?
Yes, just one.
This is good. Stay calm.
Everyone! It's gonna get
colder from here on out
so wear a coat or something.
Yes, it's getting chilly
- I can feel it on my skin.
Oh, but I don't...
You're a skeleton--you don't have skin.
Chopper-san, you can't do that...
You can't steal my line...
Are we going somewhere
cold? Not the deep sea?
Don't you know that the
water in the deep sea is cold?
Like in a bath tub, hot water
goes up and cold water goes down.
Oh yeah? I'm not a big fan of
baths so I wouldn't know.
I see.
If the sea is the same as a bath tub,
it's gonna get colder as you go deeper.
The temperature isn't the only difference.
You're still depressed?!
In the deep layer of the sea,
there are giant currents
called deep currents
that you don't get to see very often.
Those currents flow totally
independently from surface currents.
There are currents under currents?!
You know many things!
Because I'm really old!
All currents are connected.
One current flows eastward and
the other one flows westward.
They could also flow upward or
downward. It's like a giant dragon.
Deep currents flow really slowly.
Once they flow to the deep
sea, it takes 2000 years...
...until they flow upward to the surface.
2000 years?!
Yes, that's why there
are a number of myths...
about the dark and
undiscovered deep currents.
Monsters! Curses! Spirits of the dead!
What?! There are ghosts in the deep sea?!
--Huh? Really? I'm scared!
--It's exciting!
Ghosts... I don't know about that.
But we're gonna get on a downward flow.
That's how we get to the deep sea.
Deep layer...
Surface...
Downward flow...
Submerge...
Twang-twang!
So there are wonderful currents...
You guys didn't understand a bit, did you?!
You wanna sing, Nami-san?
Shut up!
What is that sound?
This is it!
Nami, I see it!
Yeah?
The wonderful current?!
Where is it?
That's cool!
--Oh!
--What is that?
So that's the downward current!
The downward flow--plume!
How... cool!
It's like a massive...
...waterfall in the sea!
Interesting!
The sea is "falling" far below!
At an extraordinary speed!
Nature's great!
What a spectacular stream!
I wonder how deep it is.
It's far greater than I had heard.
I can't see the bottom! It's completely dark!
We're dead!
With that speed,
we're gonna be slammed
into the bottom and die!
Is it really okay to go with the flow?
Don't worry about the ship.
Sunny is the strongest ship built
from the treasure tree Adam.
Alright!
Advance!
No way!
I didn't know that it lives here...!
It's a demon that rules the realm of water!
And the enemy of the human race!
Straw Hats! You should turn back now!
It's dangerous!
I had forgotten about you.
--There is a monster!
--What?!
What are you talking about? Cut that crap!
Those myths are just made up by someone.
It... It's right there...
Cut it out, guys!
B-Behind you...
What are you saying...
Be... Behind me?
Uh-huh.
Behind me...
It's the Kraken!
How huge!  The monster octopus!
Looks like he broke a lot of ships!
Ships that had left for the
New World have been attacked!
Please! I don't wanna die! Go back!
If you just wait for a few days, it would...
Shut up!
I have a good idea!
Let's tame him!
Huh?
What did you say, Luffy?!
Let's tame the octopus
and make him pull our ship!
No way!
Take a good look!
No, you don't have to take
a good look since it's huge!
Oh, it's big!
We're dead!
It must've been around for
several hundred years!
The Kraken appears in many
myths in the world -
it's like a visionary creature!
It has no bones and I'm a
skeleton without any flesh...
It's the polar opposite of me.
I don't care!
You're quite good.
You can't see this kind of thing often, so...
Sketching? How relaxed?!
I'll help you but do you
have any plan, Luffy?
The problem is that we're in the sea.
No. No. No.
The problem is the size of it.
It would be dangerous
even if we were on land.
What's wrong with them?
This is the kind of situation
when everybody agrees to
run away at full speed!
Shift the helm to the south!
Hey, Nami, go straight towards the octopus!
Don't be a fool!
--The octopus will...
--Whoa, whoa, Nami-san. I'm here for...
...here for...
...for you!
You held it! Good job!
Thanks to the rehabilitation
and to Nami for wearing a coat.
It's dangerous to be on this ship!
I've got to protect myself!
Something's coming from behind!
Brother!
They came back!
Coribou! Guys!
--We're gonna save my brother!
--Yes!
You came back to save me, huh?!
Don't do it!
--The coating popped!
--That ship is even bigger than Sunny!
Oh... Guys!
--They look like a school of jellyfish.
--Shut up, Roronoa! Cut it out!
It's coming!
--It's too big!
--How can we fight against it?!
Third Gear...
No!
You'll break the bubble!
Chicken Voyage!
Can we... get away somehow?!
Don't do anything! I'll beat it!
No! You're gonna break the bubble!
Listen! If you wanna fight against
it that much, here is an idea!
What is it? Tell me.
Okay, that's good!
That's the extra-vehicular
Flutter Kick Coating!
An extra-vehicular diving suit!
As long as you're in it, you can
fight as you want even in water!
If I let these fools do whatever
they want, I'll be in danger too!
You shouldn't have done that, stranger!
We wanted to run away!
Now, they're gonna fight!
I told you guys to run from the beginning
but that Captain-san won't listen!
Would you rather they fought on this ship?
Okay, good luck! Go far away!
This rope is annoying.
Stay away from this ship!
Alright.
--Okay, let's go!
--Yeah!
Huh?
Wait! You have to attach the safety rope!
You'll be separated!
Nami-san's worrying about me!
You guys! Draw his attention for me!
I'm gonna beat him with one strong blow!
I could beat him right away!
You can't cut him!
I want the octopus as a pet!
Are they okay?
Stay as far away as you
can! Even a millimeter...
But it's attacking us!
Move aside, guys!
Franky...
...Rocket Launcher!
--Got it!
--How powerful!
No, another arm!
Why does he keep attacking us?!
It's gonna hit us!
Guard Boost!
They got a hard hit!
Are you guys okay?
H-He did it!
--Well done!
--Yeah, Chopper!
We're gonna hit the mountain!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
What big hands!
--Yes!
--Nice, Robin! You saved us!
Good. Although I'm in water,
I was okay because it
was just a brief moment.
They did great.
Alright, it's my turn!
Here is the new technique!
Third Gear!
Facing the Demon of the ocean floor, Kraken,
Luffy, Zoro and Sanji use the techniques
acquired during their two-year training.
But then, the Straw Hats are
scattered in the Deep Sea
by the massive current caused by the battle.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Lost in the Deep Sea!
The Straw Hats Get Separated!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!