Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Let's get this underway!
Be still, Straw Hat Luffy's shadow!
I am your new master.
I'm about to provide you with a voice and body
so that you may live as a zombie.
Forget all of your past relations
and become my obedient soldier!
It's time! Awaken!
Arise from 500 years of slumber!
Magnificent!
How truly overawing!
He's a piece of art! A real devil!
Meat!
I'm hungry!
Wh-What?! Ow!
Hey, let go of me!
This freak... is really strong!
Care to say your last farewells?
This woman is going to marry me today!
Huh? I'm disappearing too?
Why?!
Nami vanished with him!
Nami!
"A Belief Worth Begging to Live For!!
Brook Defends His Afro!"
♪ Yo ho ho ho, yo ho ho ho ♪
♪ Yo ho ho ho... ♪
You refuse to quit even
after I flung you outside?
Of course! I will continue to
come back until you return to me!
Do you not know my name?
All cower at the mere mention
of the swordsman Ryuma!
Silence! You are my shadow!
Our bodies are worlds apart!
You will come back to me!
You belong under my feet!
What a disaster!
The Humming Swordsman isn't the
only one here who knows our secret!
This is rottin' bad!
"I can't die" is like our secret code.
I don't wanna live in fear of death!
I heard that after a person loses his shadow,
he gets taken down this long staircase.
Right! Luffy got carried this way.
We were chasing after him when Nami...
Do you think Nami is okay?
It's not like he wants to kill her.
We'll save her when we come back!
That's all the more reason to hurry to Sunny!
We'll wake up Straw Hat and the
guys and recover their shadows!
But the island is infested
with zombies. That won't be easy!
Speaking of zombies,
how did you take them out?
That skeleton taught us how. We used this!
Here, guys, take this.
--What is it?
--The zombies' weakness!
You saw how effective it was in my
battle against this spider monkey!
This is their weakness? What exactly is it?
It's salt.
Zombies have a weakness?
So we can purify them if we
stuff salt into their mouths, huh?
You saw what happened!
By the way, what exactly was that
monstrous roar that came from upstairs?
Seriously! We followed that sound here.
That was Luffy's voice.
Say what?!
I'll tell you all about what we saw.
Long story short, we're in big trouble!
Keep it coming! He still wants more!
How much does a Special Zombie eat?
He's going to consume
everything on the island!
He really stuffs his face...
Kumacy, why were you
harboring the pirates? Well?!
B-But I--
Don't talk! You're so not cute!
Sorry, Mini-Shallot!
You've been feeding me and I
don't even know who you are.
'Course, the quantity bites and the food's nasty.
Watch it, Special Zombie!
Don't step out of bounds!
Who do you think gifted us
with the ability to move?!
I wouldn't be so rude to the ruler
of Thriller Bark if I were you!
Someday the master is going
to become the King of the--
Eh?
I'm terribly sorry! He told me to say all of that.
Dude! Don't sell a friend out!
I'm hungry! I want more!
Bring him more food.
But he's gobbled up nearly
all of the food on the island.
What?
We're storing food in the
treasure room in the basement.
Feel free to serve that.
That's my Cindry-chan!
Always prepared for anything!
--Great!
--I'm impressed that you set
aside emergency rations.
Huh? But if you give that to Oars,
it defeats the point of the emergency rations!
I hope we completely run out of food.
That's not nice, Cindry-chan!
Gyoro, Nin, Bao! Run over to
Hogback's mansion and get the food!
We're on it, Master!
We'll lend a helping hand!
Don't let those pirates find you!
Same goes for the Humming Swordsman.
If these guys could remove
the spider monkey's shadow,
they're super bad news!
Gaaah!
Is it the pirates?! The Humming Swordsman?!
I thought I dropped this,
but here it is! It's the basement key.
Don't scare us!
This leads to the basement!
Haul the stuff back up--all of it!
Yeah! Hurry! Hurry!
Master!
Feed him already!
Yes, sir!
This batch is actually pretty good.
A salted fish is somewhere in that pile.
I hope he eats it.
What?!
I-It's salted?!
If the Special Zombie eats that, its shadow will--
If that happens, the master
is going to let us have it!
We have to find it before he does!
Fish... Where is the fish?
P-P-Perona-sama...
Shut it! Don't say anything, Kumacy!
Fish! Fish! Fish! Fish!
What are you doing?
Help me!
Oh, it's a fish.
Is this salt?
Stupid!
This is it! I just know it!
Hide the thing!
That fish looks mighty yummy.
I-I don't think you'll find it to
your liking, Special Zombie-sama!
R-Right!
That's the sort of thing I
have to find out for myself.
What are you doing? Do you want
to get eaten along with the fish?
Shut up!
No matter what, don't let him eat this!
Hey! Why are you guys getting
between me and my fish?!
Ummm...
W-W-We thought this might taste better.
Right, right!
Yeah?
Dried meat! Yeah, it's really good!
I'm starving after all that hard work.
I think I'll help myself to some fish.
Shhh! Hush!
Listen, Oars! Five hundred years ago,
you left behind countless legends
as an infamous villain!
And just now, I resurrected you in
modern times to serve as my subordinate.
"Subordinate"? Forget it! I have a dream.
I've never heard of a zombie like this before!
This room is cramped and boring.
I'm gonna head on outside.
Maybe I'll set sail and travel
once around the world.
A voyage around the world?!
Moron! That's impossible!
This special freezer is encased in
a super thick wall made of steel!
You couldn't put a dent in--
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
He's amazing!
That's awesome!
W-W-Wait, dude!
This is rottin' bad! Oars has gone outside!
That's strange. I could have
sworn my arm could stretch.
Oh, well.
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!
You are going to disgrace yourself by crying,
"Anything but my afro! Anything but my afro!"
as you beg me to spare
your life, just like last time.
No, that's not how it will go down!
I'm getting nowhere!
I mustered the courage to strike
down those scary-looking zombies,
but they got right back up!
They must have some sort of weakness!
At this rate, I won't get my shadow back
even if I find my zombie!
And to top it off, zombies have
horrendously scary faces!
One of the guys got purified.
What happened?!
This picky eater just had
to grill the fish with salt!
--Huh?
--The idiot! He must have been new.
He grilled the fish with salt...?
Could this be the zombies' weakness?!
B-Bastard! We stole your shadow
the other day, Skeleton!
How did you get back?
Answer my question!
Which zombie did you stuff my shadow into?!
If you don't answer, I'll scatter
fish all across the island!
"Fish"?
So what if you scatter them around?
Huh? Uh, that's strange...
But it couldn't possibly be salt...
Eh? "Salt"?
S-S-So what if you s-s-scatter that around?
It's salt!
Zombies really are insanely scary!
I hate nighttime!
J-Jeez... It was just a grasshopper.
It gave me a fright.
But it's dangerous for me to
be out during daylight hours.
Plus it's easy for enemies to find me then.
I've got it! I'll sing!
When I'm scared, singing can
serve as a good distraction.
I'll be careful not to look at the
zombies' faces as I swiftly purify them.
I'm bound to run into my shadow eventually!
Where is that song coming from?
Who's humming?
Who're you?!
No!
What's the deal? What is
happening on this island?!
He appears out of the darkness while humming.
This scary-looking swordsman
is searching for his shadow!
He's wiped out practically
all of the Soldier Zombies!
Please do something!
Perona-sama, we have a problem.
Shut it! Don't wake me up, Kumacy!
Get up!
At last we meet!
Why is he so strong? Isn't this
zombie supposed to be me?
I can't keep up!
And here we use the same style!
Surrender!
It will end the same no matter
how many times you come after me.
If you would like to increase
your speed somewhat,
I shall cut that troublesome afro.
D-Don't! At the very least,
please leave my afro alone!
Anything but my hair!
Why don't you understand?!
If you're my shadow, why don't you
understand how important this afro is?
Time has stopped for my body,
so it would never grow back!
What of it? I have forgotten
all about the days I served you.
My current masters are
Moria-sama and Absalom-sama!
A skeleton that treasures its afro
is nothing short of ridiculous!
P-Please stop! Anything but my afro!
Anything but my afro!
Not my afro! Not the 'fro!
That was a dirty move!
Are you not ashamed of yourself?!
Say what you will! There is a reason
why I cannot afford to lose!
You are most pathetic, former master.
I am sorry. I admit defeat...
Please let me go...
I will leave this island...
Then leave at once!
If you were to die, it would affect me as well.
That was the epitome of disgrace.
Say what you will!
While waiting for my chance to return,
I have spent these past five years...
...growing stronger!
Absalom-sama!
You better be ready to hold the wedding.
Yes, yes. We can start whenever you like.
My, what a lovely bride!
We're going to start right away!
Get her dressed and bring
her to the ceremony hall.
All right! I'm on it.
That right? So that skeleton
helped you out, huh?
And that's not all!
That punk said he's endured these past
fifty years to keep a promise with a friend.
A whale friend...
A-A whale...?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Man's Promise Never Dies!!
To the Friend Waiting Under the Distant Sky!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!