Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,--
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
After forming an alliance with Trafalgar Law,
Luffy finally encountered Caesar Clown
but was beaten by his mysterious power.
Meanwhile, Law, too, got taken down by
the Navy G-5 base commander - Vergo.
R...
Run!!
Straw Hat-ya...
We can't miss a beat here.
Let's fight back.
"Launching the Counter Attack!
Luffy and Law's Great Escape!"
A member of the Seven
Warlords - Trafalgar Law.
A pirate who was on the news recently
for making a stunning comeback -
Straw Hat Luffy.
And his comrade--the
Devil Child - Nico Robin.
The Wild Dog of the Navy--"White
Chase" - Smoker.
How did these big-timers end up
VARIOUS PLACES IN THE NEW WORLD
being captured by Caesar?
What?!
It's them! So that's where they are!
What should we do?
Let's see how things go for a while-bon.
Hey, they are...
He finally got off his ass! Straw Hat!
EUSTASS "CAPTAIN" KID
THE CAPTAIN OF THE KID PIRATES BOUNTY:
470 MILLION BERRIES
It's no use watching it.
And you're not the kind of guy...
...who wants to play an arms trader, are you?
KILLER
Killer.
A CREW MEMBER OF THE KID PIRATES BOUNTY:
200 MILLION BERRIES
You're right.
But I can't believe those
three are there together.
Yeah, that asshole - Trafalgar!
I thought he had lost his mind when
he became the Government's dog
but to nobody's surprise,
he was up to something.
Is he gonna start something?
We don't wanna fall behind! Let's move!
Kid, I beg you. Settle it peacefully.
I know! So shut up, already!
SCRATCHMEN APOO
Hey, Captain Kid!
BASIL HAWKINS
You look annoying as always!
Scratchmen! What are you doing?!
You made a big mess out of our lair!
Sorry, Captain! We couldn't stop him!
I was making sure that
you didn't have any snipers.
THE CAPTAIN OF THE ON AIR PIRATES BOUNTY:
350 MILLION BERRIES
Anyone would do so
when he gets summoned by his enemy.
See, Killer?!
This is why I told you not to call him!
Calm down. He's a powerful man.
THE CAPTAIN OF THE HAWKINS PIRATES BOUNTY:
320 MILLION BERRIES
How thoughtless of you to
keep a guest you invited waiting.
You assholes...
I'm gonna kill you both now!
Oh, I knew that's what you wanted!
I'm ready for it!
Bring it on! Check it out!
This is so stupid. I'm leaving.
Wait, Hawkins! Not so soon!
Everyone! Enough already!
We wanted to discuss...
...forming an alliance
with both of your groups!
Don't you guys even know how to talk?!
Fighting back?
Yeah, it's no use wasting our time here.
Let's get it over with.
Can anybody here burn things?
If nobody can, that's fine, too.
Franky can set fires.
He can even shoot a laser beam!
Oh yeah!
Why don't you burn this chain with the beam?
I need to use both hands
to shoot the Radical Beam.
The only thing I can shoot is...
...Coup de Boo from my ass!
Whatever.
Can you set fire to the Navy
ship down there on the right?
Huh? That one?
That's as easy as pie, young man!
You can count on me!
Franky...
...Fireball!
--The ship is on fire!
--Run!
Put out the fire!
What is he doing? Is he just desperate?
That Pacifista-esque guy!
It's no use.
After the experiment,
I'll chop up their bodies
and put them to good use.
--I can't see the cage because of the smoke!
--Captain-chan, you okay?!
--Smo-yan, is it smoky there?!
--Fool! He's a smoke man in the first place!
Hey, Trafalgar! It's getting so smoky here!
You're the one who did it.
You made me do it!
What are you doing?
Well then...
What?!
Now that we are not being picked up
on Caesar's Video Transponder Snail.
They're not gonna find out for a while.
You're unbelievable!
How did you free yourself
from Sea Prism Stone chain?
Well, mine was just an ordinary
chain from the beginning.
What?
So I untied myself easily with my power.
Room!
Do you know how many months I've been here?
Just in case of an emergency,
I put a number of regular chains
everywhere in the laboratory.
So I could avoid Sea Prism Stone
even if I got caught by accident.
I'm free!
Quit cheering, fool.
Yeah, yeah, I'm free!
--Yeah, yeah, I'm free!
--Now...
...what should I do with you two?
You've learned a little too much.
I have your destiny in my hands.
You know what you wanna
do with it, don't you?
Just do it already!
Smoker-san?!
We're back to ourselves!
Don't scream like a woman, young girl!
J-Just untie us!
I'd do anything you say!
Stop it, Tashigi!
Wouldn't you rather die than
grovel before a pirate?!
Right now, we have to beg for our lives,
throwing ourselves at his
feet if that's what it takes!
Because if we die here,
we can't save our people
and Vice Admiral Vergo...
I mean, Vergo will act as
he pleases in the Navy.
And the children...
We can't die here!
She's a little smarter than you.
White Chase-ya, I have
no obligation to save you
but if letting you go back to the base safely
makes Vergo lose his footing,
it works out well for me.
However, you need to forget everything
that you heard about me and Joker.
I'm not asking you a favor. It's a condition.
For sparing your life.
I can't see anything!
What's going on out there?
Yeah, I finally got out!
--Aha!
--What are you...
Yeehaw!
Hey, wait!
How dare he do whatever the pleases!
It's not like the cage is
made of Sea Prism Stone.
Our captain does that sort of thing
as soon as your back is turned.
That fool!
Hey, Tra-guy!
Aha!
How should I get in?!
Hey, young man.
I'd rather take care of the Sunny.
Do as you like.
Alright then, see you later!
Coup de...
...Boo!
I'm coming for you, Sunny!
I'm counting on you, Franky!
Oh, it stinks!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Hey! What are you waiting for, Tra-guy?!
Hey, Smo-yan!
Captain-chan! Are you okay?!
What should we do?!
Hey, look. It's already...
The poison gas will get here any minute!
If nothing is done, just like
people in that video, we...
I-It's no good! We need to
get inside the building now!
--Open the shutter!
--Damn it! Open up!
Run!
We can run faster like this
but it's catching up to us!
The dragon is so far ahead!
Let's catch it and fly already!
--I can't...
--Sanji-san, stay with us!
I can't run anymore!
Nami-san's cardiopulmonary
functions can't take it anymore!
The chest feels tight!
Her chest... Breasts...
Breasts!
I caught it!
What kind of stupid power was that?!
--The smoke is closing in!
--That creepy color...
It must be very poisonous!
Sorry, Brownbeard-chi!
You're badly wounded but
you have to carry us!
No problem. It's just like carrying dwarves.
I have to save my men anyway!
We have to save those kids!
I hope they haven't eaten those candies!
Hey, look! What is that?!
There! Somebody's running from the gas!
A dragon?
Don't tell me that's...
Can't you run more quietly?!
I mean, why doesn't it fly?!
I don't need a dragon's help!
Cut it out, guys!
We caught it thanks to Nami-san's sexy body!
Just by thinking about it, I...
This is no time for a nosebleed, you pervert!
The poison gas is catching up to us!
My arm muscles can't take it...
Oh, I don't have muscles!
Brook!
--Brook!
--That was close!
--Usopp!
--N-Nami-san?!
Let's keep running!
Why are you here?!
We have tons of questions,
too, but they can wait!
Let's get to the lab!
Yeah!
Hey, he's getting tired!
The gas will get us if nothing is done!
You all have to jump on my back!
Thank you!
Ouch!
Oh, this is good!
Good! Just go like that!
--That's nice!
--We're counting on you, Brownbeard!
You people are horrible!
--Hey! Hurry up!
--We're gonna die!
Damn! Damn! Damn! Shit! Shit! Shit!
Just open!
Th-The poison gas is...
...coming over the mountain!
Dammit!
This is it... We're gonna die...
The poison gas will reach here soon!
Smo-yan and Captain-chan can't even escape!
We're all gonna die!!
The shutter's opening!
--We have a problem!
--The shutter's opening!
Who touched the lever?!
Damn it! G-5 soldiers are
entering one after another!
--What's going on?!
--Hey, look!
N-No way!
The Navy G-5 Vice Admiral Smoker!
The Warlord - Trafalgar Law!
The pirate - Straw Hat Luffy!
I thought they were held
captive by the Master!
Good! Everyone's inside!
Now, what should I do with my heart?
I'm getting excited!
Why am I doing this with these guys...
Smo-yan! Captain-chan! You're alive!
Now, nobody's left outside!
We're safe from the poison gas!
What's that?
Ouch!
We arrived at the lab!
Whoa, whoa, whoa! Wait, wait!
Don't close the shutter!
Damn! We're so close!
Open it! Let us get inside!
Oh no! They're cutting us off!
We're gonna be killed by the gas!
We can't make it. We're
going to kingdom come.
Hey, Kin'emon!
Can you cut iron?
That's not so hard to cut!
Brownbeard, keep charging like this!
That's ridiculous!
I'm gonna crash into the wall!
Then do you wanna be
killed by the poison gas?
No way!
Who cares!
I'm gonna charge!
We don't have any other option now, do we?
Yeah, it's hit-or-miss!
Let's take a chance!
Are you ready?
Of course!
It's Zoro and the others!
That's a bizarre entrance!
What?!
They cut the shutter!
Hey! Everybody's here, huh?
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
We're all back together!
Alright! Let's let loose!
The Straw Hats manage to escape the clutches of Shinokuni and reunite.
However, their only remaining escape route is through the door to Building R.
Facing extreme circumstances...
...they finally signal the counterattack!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Get to Building R!
The Pirate Alliance's Great Advance!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!