Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Those're cannonballs!
Hmm?
Huh? That was way off!
What are you guys doing?
Cannon practice!
Awesome! You hit it on your first try!
Whadya think?! I'm awesome when
it comes to aiming! Impressed?!
It's settled! You're our sniper!
Come out, you damn pirates!
Hmm? That voice...
What the... What the... Who are you?!
"Sea"
Are you nameless pirate
wannabes trying to kill my partner?!
I dunno what's going on,
but stop breaking our ship!
L-Lost by a hair...
"Famous Cook!
Sanji of the Sea Restaurant"
Say, where're you taking me to today?
To the most wonderful
restaurant in the world.
Don't tell me... there's one
in the middle of the ocean?
Here's to your beauty...
Well, just wait until you see it...
Hey, if it isn't Johnny!
What?
B-Big Bro Zoro!
Wh-Why are you on
a pirate ship like this?!
Is something wrong?
Yosaku isn't with you?
Well...
What? Does Zoro know that guy?
What's going on?
Y-Yosaku is...
He's sick?
Although he was full of life
up until a few days ago,
now he keeps getting pale
suddenly and then fainting!
I have no idea what's causing it...
In the end, his teeth fell out
and his old wound opened up
and started bleeding.
I didn't know what to do any more...
so we were on a rocky island
letting him rest quietly. But then...
...a cannonball came
flying from this ship...
--W-We're sorry!
Sorry doesn't cut it...
Isn't that right, partner?
Big Bro... Is he going to die?
Are you all stupid?
What'd you say?!
--Wh-What're you doing?!
--Ouch!
If you mock my partner's
death, you'll pay for it--
Luffy! Usopp! Remember we
have limes in the storage?
Are you listening?!
Bring them here. Now!
--Y-Yes ma'am!
--Out of my way!
It's scurvy.
Scurvy?
If we weren't too late,
he'll be fine in just a few days.
R-Really, Big Sis?!
Big Sis, is he really...
Stop... calling me that.
In the past, it was a hopeless disease
that accompanied sea journeys.
--Here, drink it. Drink a lot.
--Here... drink more. Drink more.
But the cause was simply a
deficiency of plant-derived nutrients.
Ships in the past
didn't carry fresh fruits
and vegetables since
they weren't storable, so...
Okay, now. Put them all in his mouth.
Now he'll be fine.
You're amazing!
You're like a doctor!
Well, I always thought you were good.
Yeah, you're right. She is.
You should know at least that much!
You could die if you don't!
Wha...
--Yaay! Yaay! Yaay!
All those nutrients revived me!
All right, partner!
There's no way you can
recover this quickly!
Sorry for not
introducing ourselves first.
My name is Johnny.
I'm Yosaku.
The pirate bounty hunter duo!
We used to be
colleagues of Big Bro Zoro.
Glad to make your acquaintance.
I never thought that
I'd see you guys here...
But again, we're surprised...
We never imagined that the pirate
hunter Zoro became a pirate...
Yeah, I know...
Big Bro...
H-Hey, partner?!
This is a lesson.
Yeah. There're pitfalls like this
when you travel on
the sea for a long time...
Which means on the ship,
we have to consider
the distribution of nutrients
using limited kinds of food...
When we think about it carefully,
it's a necessary ability...
A necessary ability, huh?
Okay, then! A seafaring cook!
--What?
Let's go find a seafaring cook!
Aha! Then we'll be able to eat
yummy food even on the ship!
Exactly!
If you're looking for a cook like that,
there's a perfect place for that.
All right! Where's it?
But this place is close
to the Grand Line, and...
you hear rumors there about the hawk-
eyed man you've been looking for...
We'll head...
north-northeast!
Yes!
All right!
Our destination is...
...the Sea Restaurant...
...Baratie!
--Whoa!
What do you think, everyone?!
Whoa! It's a huge fish!
How lovely!
That's pretty funky!
Right?! Just like I told you, right?!
Wh-What the...
At a place like this...
A Navy ship...
S-Surely they're not gonna
shoot at us, are they?
Hmph! What an unpleasant
bunch we've run into...
Wh-When did they...
I've never seen that pirate flag.
Darn it!
We're not pirates!
I'm Iron Fist Fullbody,
Lieutenant at Navy Headquarters!
Hey, who's your captain?!
Come out and state your name!
I'm Luffy!
I'm Usopp!
We just made our pirate flag
the day before yesterday!
And I'm the one who drew it!
Hmph! Oh, you're just...
Hmm?
You two over there,
I remember seeing you before.
If I remember correctly, you're a bounty
hunter duo going after small fish.
Wh-What?!
So you finally got caught by pirates...
W-We are...
That's a laugh.
C'mon, let's get going.
Okay.
You think small-time bounty hunters
would go after these guys?!
Hmm?
Now, let's go to the restaurant.
They're an eyesore. Sink them.
--Yes, sir!
He ignored us.
Next time we see him,
we'll have to shut him up!
What is this...
They're wanted pirates, Big Sis Nami--
In other words, if we defeat them,
we'll get the reward money.
A very profitable business,
don't you think, Big Sis?
W-We're in trouble.
They're aiming at us!
Leave it to me!
Gum-Gum...
Slingshot!
Ow...
Owner!
Are you all right, Head Chef Zeff?!
Owner, are you all right?!
Hmm? What happened?
Is our reservation okay?
Head Chef Zeff, are you really okay?
I'm saying it's not okay!
Never mind, just get back to the
restaurant already! Get to work!
B-But Owner, you're...
You idiots! Do you
want me to get angry?!
Feeding customers is a cook's job!
Are you fools trying to put
my restaurant out of business?!
We brought him in.
He's the one responsible.
I-I-I-I'm very sorry!
Ahhh! Your leg...
Idiot!!
This didn't happen just now.
O-Oh, then it was like
that from the beginning...
But you gave me
bruises all over my body.
The medical fees and the repair
charges for the ship will cost you a lot!
I won't ask you to reduce the charges.
Oh?
But...
I don't have money!
You talk very candidly.
Well, if you don't have money, you
have no other choice but to work here.
Yeah, I'll make proper amends.
You'll do chores unpaid for a year.
Okay! Chores unpaid for a year!
I'll let you off the hook with that.
A-A year?! A-A year...
You mean a year?!
What's taking Luffy so long...?
Yeah...
Maybe they'll make him do
chores for a month or so...
He should've made it the Navy's
fault instead of being foolishly honest.
Hey, look.
Just as I thought, the man
sitting there is Lieutenant Fullbody.
He's a lieutenant at Navy Headquarters.
Huh?
He's gorgeous. How elegant...
It's amazing. Everyone's looking at you.
Well, they're admiring you.
This is good!
Th-This flavor...
Hmm... This scent...
This may be the scent of the soil
of Micquo of the North Land...
Bitter with plenty of body, a tad sour...
This wine is...
Iturutz Burger Stein!
Aren't I right, waiter?!
That's...
damn wrong, sir.
Your soup is getting cold.
Please eat it while it's hot.
By the way, I'm Sanji, the Sous Chef.
All the waiters ran off as of yesterday.
You really shouldn't laugh.
But he looked so confident...
Do you know a lot...
...about wine?
Well, yeah...
...although it seems my sense of
taste isn't working well today...
Hey, what's going on?
I'm sure I requested the owner to serve
us that wine when I made a reservation.
What do you mean by that?
Please reduce it to a week.
You talk very candidly.
Two weeks!
Hey! You wrecked my restaurant and
injured me, the Head Chef, seriously.
You can't settle that with just
one or two weeks of unpaid work.
I've decided! Three weeks!
Don't talk so...
...candidly!
No!
Hmm?
I've patiently waited
ten years to become a pirate.
I definitely don't want to
be stuck here for a year!
Hmm?
Okay, I've decided.
I'll get you to let me off the
hook in a week. So I've decided.
Oh? If you value time so much,
I'll tell you what you can
do to settle it quickly.
Ow!
Leave one of your legs here.
No!
Ha! You sure talk very candidly!
Tap, tap... tap...
Yaay! Yaay! Yaaaaay!
Waiter!
Hmm?
Didn't I tell you that I'm not a waiter?
But my, how beautiful you are!
Say, Miss, would you like to have
some wine with me over there?
Hmm?
Hey! Do you serve soup
with bugs in it to customers?!
Bugs?
What the hell is this bug?!
Hmph! This will make this
restaurant's reputation drop sharply.
I'm sorry, sir, but I don't know...
...since I don't know much about insects.
Don't mess with me!!
You could've eaten it if you
took that bug out, couldn't you?
It took three full days to
cook it, skimming the scum...
Aren't you acting a bit
too big for your britches?
I'm a customer! I'm paying you!
Please stop, Fullbody-san!
Shut up!
F-Fullbody-san...
Can money...
satisfy your hunger?
What'd you say?
I'm asking, "Can it...
satisfy your hunger?!"
No!
No! No!
Don't think that you can survive in
this world by repeating "No," kid.
No!
So candid...
F-Fullbody-san...
Sanji...
Sous Chef!
Hmm?
A fight?
Don't... waste food.
At sea, provoking a cook is
the same as committing suicide.
Remember that.
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
I wonder if Luffy's working hard.
I bet he's causing trouble.
Yeah, he doesn't seem a helpful hand.
What'd you say?! That's not nice!
Hey, have you found a
cook who might join us?
Yeah, I found him! It has to be him!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Unwelcome Customer!
Sanji's Food and Ghin's Debt"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!