Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
I'm sorry...
I wanted to carry you to further places.
I wanted to continue the
adventure together forever.
Merry!
But I--
It's us who have to apologize, Merry!
I'm not good at steering...
...so I ran you into icebergs at times...
There was a time I tore the sails, too.
Zoro and Sanji are stupid,
so they broke all sorts of things!
Usopp would fix them each time,
but he isn't good at it!
So it's us who have to...
But I've been happy.
Thank you very much...
for taking good care of me.
I really have been happy...
...because I had you.
Merry!
"Two days later"
"Peace Interrupted! A Navy
Vice Admiral with a Fist of Love!"
--Yaay!
--Blue Station...
--Hurry! Hurry!
--Blue Station, Water Seven.
All passengers, please make sure not to
forget your belongings when you get off.
Forget the money. Just take it.
I wish you good luck!
This bites...
How're things over there?
No good, it's a total mess!
At any rate, this year's Aqua Laguna
was terribly destructive.
This is far beyond our
ability to repair on our own.
Hm? That's...
Paulie from Dock #1! What's he
doing in a backstreet like this?
Paulie-san!
Out of our way! You guys
stay away! You're in our way!
Guys from Dock #3! I'll leave this block to you!
Okay!
Guys from Dock #5! Take the block next to the
scrap heap island! Start with private houses!
Okay!
You've got your regular work, too!
So work on the backstreets
during your breaks! I want it
all restored within a month!
Got it!
Get on it!
Yeah!
Whoa! They're too dependable!
That's our Galley-La Company!
"Remains of Franky House, north shore"
This sure takes a lot of time to build.
Well, our specialty is demolition.
So we'll be camping out tonight again, huh?
There, there.
Sodom... and Gomorrah.
You two get a good rest, okay?
That reindeer guy said that Gomorrah's
eyes will get better if he keeps resting.
Is that right? That's good news!
Hey, guys. Give me a hand, will you?
I need to go pick up a shipment at the station.
A shipment?
Could it be...?
Yep. It seems like that stuff has arrived.
"Dock #1, shipbuilding island"
Let us see the pirates
and let us apologize to them
for calling them assassins!
You can't! The pirates won't see anyone!
We owe them for saving Iceberg-san's life.
Let us at least thank them!
I'm from the Water Seven Newspaper!
Let me have some comments from the
heroes who saved our mayor! Please!
Just give up! You can't see them now!
Let us at least take their pictures, then!
--I said no! Are you all deaf?!
--I'll work as a secretary in place of Kalifa-san!
Let me do something to help!
Let us see the pirates!
No means no means no!
Amazing! They've got
unbelievable superhuman strength!
Is this how you want it?
Thank you! That's giants for you!
If we can do something like this
to help, just let us know any time!
You guys really are great!
Say, king of snipers...
Hm?
Is it okay for you to stay here?
What?
We were thinking...
If our bosses are still fighting,
we can't set foot on that island.
So we decided to help out
the guys on this island a bit
and then take our time going back to Elbaf.
If you like Elbaf, we can take you with us.
I...
Where I'm going is my own business.
I'm... leaving the gang!
Fight a duel with me!
I...
"Remains of Galley-La Company headquarters--
Iceberg's residence"
"Temporary headquarters building"
I see... So you burned the blueprints...
That's for the best.
You made an enemy of
the government too, huh?
Guess I did.
So... what are those plans
you've been drawing up?
Seeing the scale of this past Aqua Laguna
must have made the citizens worry
that this island itself might be
swallowed by the sea some time soon.
Well, if something like that keeps attacking,
the island might sink, too.
So what're you gonna do?
I'll have the entire island float on the sea.
What?!
Turn Water Seven into a ship?!
But i-is something like that possible?!
Did you forget...?
We witnessed a great man who
made the impossible possible
for quite some time, didn't we?
If you're a man... do it resolutely!
"If you're a man, do it resolutely," huh?
Now I remember.
You're right.
Hm?
--Click.
--Hello?!
Oh, is this Bro?
Oh, hey, Zambai! What's up?
Please rejoice, Bro! It's finally here!
It's just arrived by sea train!
The item that you purchased
for 200 million Berries!
So it's finally arrived...
"Special pirate room with kitchen and bathroom,
temporary headquarters building"
I'm coming in, guys!
Granny Kokoro!
Hey! I'm coming in!
And you kids...
Ribbit! Ribbit?!
Ribbit!
You stay outside.
Ribbit, ribbit.
Looks like everyone's finally woken up, huh?
You guys slept for two days.
You must've been quite exhausted...
of course, it's only natural after everything.
Oh? The King of the Pirates
is doing pretty good, too, huh?
Oh... It's not like that.
What do you mean?
Because he doesn't want to collapse
and miss any meals after fights...
Huh?
...he said he acquired the skill
of eating while sleeping.
He's actually sleeping?!
Amazing! Pirate guy!
What a skillful man!
Ribbit...
By the way, the Log for the Log Pose
should be ready in 2-3 days, right?
Hey, what's going on over here?!
Even if the Log is ready,
we can't move forward for a while.
The whole 100 million Berries
we saved to buy a new ship,
our clothes, furniture, and Bellemere-san's
tangerine trees... Everything...
...was swept away by the Aqua Laguna.
We can no longer go anywhere.
How gloomy...
We entrusted them all
with a backstreet inn, so...
Then I wonder if the visitors outside
have something to do with that...
Visitors?
--Excuse me...
--Hm?
Actually, we came to deliver these.
Hm?
Tangerine trees! I thought
I'd never get them back!
I'm so glad!
Well, when we were chasing you guys
around as Iceberg-san's assassins,
we confiscated everything as
pirates' belongings. Sorry about that.
Not at all! Thank you!
I'm happy for you.
Hey! We're back!
--We're back.
--Hey, Chopper! And Robin-chan!
It must've been heavy. Now, give me your hand.
Thank you.
I went to check on the
Franky Family guys' injuries.
Also, I didn't take my eyes off of Robin!
Okay! Well done!
Yep!
I told you, I'm not going anywhere.
It's a promise, okay?!
Yes, it's a promise.
Both of you! Look at this!
The tangerine trees were okay!
We got everything back,
including our money and belongings!
Yeah!
We can now continue our journey!
All right! I'm so glad!
Hm?
Yow! Are you guys super?! Everyone...
...isn't here, but that's okay.
What is it, Franky, all of a sudden?!
Listen!
I've got something important
to discuss with you.
On an island where wars
happen one after another...
What is it all of a sudden?
You just barged in here. If it's a
stupid story, we're not gonna listen.
Shut up! Just listen to my story!
No matter if the islanders start a war
where cannonballs fall incessantly,
or if everyone dies and the town
also dies and turns to ruins...
...this huge tree would continue to stand.
No matter what happens, this tree will not fall.
People once again nestle close to that
tree and create a town... A country.
Only a few trees like this exist in the world.
The name given to the strongest of all trees is...
..."Adam," the treasure tree.
A tree?
What about the tree?
Its wood appears on the
black market on rare occasions.
I wanted it... but it cost almost 200 million.
So it was impossible for me to buy it.
And then, there appeared pirates with
a lot of money--in other words, you guys.
You jerk! You'd better not have bought
something like that with our money!
Just keep listening!
A long time ago, I made the decision
that I'd never again build a ship.
But I wanted to catch up to the
person who was my goal after all.
The next thing I knew, I was
drawing blueprints for a ship.
My dream is... to use that treasure tree...
...to build one last ship...
A dream ship that crosses any sea!
I've already obtained this treasure tree.
I've already got blueprints, too.
I'm going to build this ship now.
So... when it's completed...
...will you set sail on the ship I've built?!
What?
What? What? Th-Then...
Then... a-are you going to give that ship to us?!
That's right. Nothing would make me happier
than for people I like to travel on my ship.
Well, that, and it's kinda like you
gave me the money for it, so...
The Oro Jackson, the ship of Gold Roger,
the only man who completed
the round-the-world journey,
was also built using this treasure tree.
I swear... I'll build an incredible ship!
I guess it can't be helped, huh?
Tom-san and you are both craftsmen after all.
Yeah... Now...
Now... I can understand the feelings
of Tom-san, who died with pride.
All right!
--You're a nice guy! We'll take it!
Thank you, Franky!
--Ribbit, ribbit! Ribbit, ribbit...
All right! We can travel to the next island!
Oh, I'm so happy! Luffy!
We're gonna get a ship!
Ribbit!
This is bad. To think that they figured
out our whereabouts this soon...
And Luffy's still sleeping!
I have to let them know immediately!
What?!
Sea...?
Crap! I went the opposite way!
What?! Sea again?! Dammit!
Give me a break! Is this island a maze?!
This is terrible. They came
to capture the pirates.
They saved Iceberg-san's life!
Hey, take a good look at that!
That battleship belongs to
Vice Admiral Garp from headquarters!
Garp, you said?!
That's the legendary marine who
cornered Gold Roger many times!
Why did such a high-level marine come?
Aren't the pirates in big trouble?!
Enough already...
Why the heck am I here again?
Dammit! Why's this gotta happen when
I have to let them know right away?!
Hey, there's an idiot over there.
Let's do it.
Hey, pops! We haven't
seen your face around here.
We want to have a word with you.
Oh, yeah?
P-Please hold on a second, marines!
--Our president is the only one back there.
--Shut up! There've got to be pirates!
N-No, there aren't!
Hey, don't enter without permission!
Stop! The Straw Hats are--!
Idiot!
You two, wait here!
Yes, sir!
What the hell?!
Who's there?!
So you guys are the Straw Hats?!
I've got some guys who I want
to have meet Monkey D. Luffy.
Navy!
Geez... He's as hopeless as ever.
What?!
Dammit!
Wake up!
Luffy!
O-Ouch! That hurt!
That hurt?! What're you saying?!
That was a punch! There's no
way that'd work on rubber!
There's no means to ward off a fist of love!
Looks like you've gone on
quite the rampage, huh, Luffy?
Ack! G-G-G...
Grandpa!
What?
What?!
A-A Navy Vice Admiral is...
His grandpa?!
Hold on a sec!
Luffy's grandpa is a Navy hero?!
Nooo! Sanji! Luffy's in danger!
What the hell is with his family?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Strongest Family?
Luffy's Father Revealed!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!