Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
That's it!
I never thought of that!
The final round of the
Davy Back Fight is underway.
The epic battle between the two captains...
...has finally reached a climax!
Luffy...!
I won't... let you have...
a single member of my crew...
...even if it costs me my life!
"Epic, Heated Combat!
The Fateful Final Conclusion"
With great drive, Straw Hat Luffy
gets back on his feet yet again!
--Even after countless knockdowns...
--Luffy...!
...he just gets right back up!
Just what are you?!
Luffy!
He's unsteady on his feet!
And he's out of breath!
This guy is incredible!
And yet...
...he still stands tall with a glimmer in his eye!
All for his friends!
Yes! Now this is a Davy Back Fight!
I'm so teary-eyed I... I can't see straight!
Luffy!
Luffy!!
--I'm moved to tears!
--Afro dude!
Luffy! Luffy! Luffy!...
A Luffy chant comes up from the crowd!
Has there ever been any other foe
who's given our boss so much trouble?!
What do you idiots think you're doing,
cheering the enemy on?!
--Boss...!
--Boss!
Boss! Boss! Boss! Boss!...
Just you watch. I'll end this now!
Slow-Slow Beam Sword!
You'll have to do better than that!
Damn! He hasn't got
enough strength left to run?!
I can't stand to watch Luffy like this!
Okay! It's time to finish this!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Our boss makes the first move!
He starts by slowing down a cannonball!
Foxy Fighter!
A Megaton Punch with
the speed of a cannonball!
It'll knock you out for good!
There it is! Our boss's cannonball stunt flying!
He's going for the finishing blow
aboard the Foxy Fighter!
Luffy! He used a beam
on you just before the ball!
Dodge as soon as you can move!
Oh! I can move!
The beam wears off on Straw Hat
just a moment sooner!
It's no use!
There's no escape!
Luffy! Look out!
Here's a present for you!
He got him! All of his attacks nail Straw Hat!
Luffy!
Boss! Boss! Boss!...
What's with him?!
He didn't have to go that far!
H-H-He's...
He's back up!
How...?!
I... win.
What?! You're barely
even able to stand upright!
But if that's how you want it...
...I'll pound you until you stay down!
Megaton Nine-Tails...!
Gum-Gum...
...Rush!
...Gatling!
Such intensity!
The combatants now exchange an
even more ferocious flurry of punches!
Slaughter 'im, Luffy!
Beat him!
Their barrages don't stop!
They just keep going!
Slow-Slow Beam!
Oh...?!
--What the...?
--He stopped moving...
S-Straw Hat has been knocked down!
No! Strike that!
Straw Hat is the one who's moving!
Just what has transpired?!
Curse... you...
How?!
Boss?!
A mirror! A mirror fragment
has fallen from Straw Hat's hand!
It was stuck... in my afro...
It's from the mirror in your room!
You little...!
Gum-Gum...
...Flail!
Oh, no...!
--Eight seconds to go.
--Huh?
Huh?!
Could this be what I think it is...?!
Seven.
What?
Six.
Boss!
Five!
What are you guys doing?!
Start counting too! Four!
--What?
--Dunno! But it seems fun!
Three!
Two!
One!
Three!
Two!
One!
Zero!
Hurray!
Luffy!
Boss!
Our boss is sent soaring!
Hurray! Hurray! Hurray!
And he lands...
...outside the battlefield!
The final combat round of the Davy Back Fight
has ended after a heated, epic
battle between the two captains!
Our boss's legendary record of 920
wins and 0 losses has been snapped!
Unbelievably, victory goes...
I won't... let you have...
a single member of my crew...
...even if it costs me my life!
...to Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy! You did it!
Luffy!
Our boss... lost...
Foxy Pirates versus...
Hey! Don't just sit there!
The boss needs our help!
All right! I'll go!
...the Straw Hats!
--I'm going! Move!
--I'm going too!
This orthodox-rules, three-coin game
Davy Back Fight is now over!
Boss!
Geez, could you have been any more reckless?!
Take this! And this!
Quit poking him so much!
He's seriously hurt, you jerk!
--And this!
--Afro power, my butt.
He had us worried the entire time...
Afros really are powerful, Nami-san!
Oh! He's conscious!
H-Huh?!
The game! How'd the game end?!
I thought I won... Was it just a dream?!
Don't worry. You won.
That's a relief...
I was never worried in the least!
Liar.
Now that I think about it, I got no reason
to be a pirate for any other ship.
--Boss!
--You should really stay still!
Hey, Straw Hat!
How dare you tarnish my
legendary undefeated streak?!
Boss!
Put 'er there, brother!
--Boss!
All right, Boss!
Spiteful Shoulder Throw!
Boss!
Are you that stupid?
Have you forgotten the rules?
Choose your 500 people already!
Yes! The final exchange awaits!
Chopper and Robin!
Thank you! I'm so happy!
You can have this back.
He starts off with two obvious choices!
Now who'll be next?! Hurry and decide!
Give us your pirate flag!
What?!
You can't be serious! You'd strip
us of our pride just like that?!
I don't need your sail.
You need it to go places, after all.
--Wow! He's so merciful!
--But our symbol's on there!
How do you expect us to use the sail?!
We don't need your pity! Just take what's yours!
All right.
Since your mark is all we need,
I'll draw a new one over it for you.
That way you can keep your sail.
Straw Hat... You're such a...!
"Fox"
There!
This sucks...!
--Wow, they're really grateful!
--No, we ain't!
H-Hold on just a minute!
You still have 497 more people to pick!
We don't need any more.
Rules are rules! You have to
choose 497 people, like it or not!
Aww. Do I have to?
Of course you do, idiot!
Luffy! A captain's orders are absolute... Right?
Yes. In which case...
Oh! Good thinking!
Huh? Huh?!
What? What?!
Oh! Okay!
I'll choose, then!
You!
--Me?
--Yeah. Everyone from you...
--...to you.
--Me?
How many people is that?
Well, we have 500 in our crew,
so excluding our boss, Hamburg-san,
and Porche-chan, that makes...
Oh, 497 exactly! It's 497 people...
...Captain Luffy!
Okay! It's decided!
The Straw Hats are victorious!
This concludes the Davy Back Fights!
It's the birth of the New Straw Hat Pirates!
But the Merry can't hold this many people...
We'll just have to follow along
in the Sexy Foxy for a while.
I guess so!
D-Don't be stupid!
The Sexy Foxy is my ship!
Your ship?
I'd love to see the three of you run
this huge ship all by yourselves!
Never gonna happen!
Never gonna happen...
Fine, then! Jerks!
--So long, Former Boss!
--Don't catch a cold!
--Brush your teeth!
--Take a bath!
Hey! Straw Hat!
I'll get you for this!
Do they ever stop being comedians?
All right, men!
Here's your first job as members
of the New Straw Hat Pirates!
Listen well!
--You can count on us!
--Rubber Boss!
You're all off the crew!
--You're kicking us out?
--Yep.
A captain's orders are absolute, remember?
You can go back to your old crews,
or even to Split-Head if you want!
You're free to go now!
That's all!
Former Boss! Wait up!
We belong with the Foxy Pirates after all!
How cunning.
Looks like it's all over.
Don't worry. They won.
There, there. I won't ride on stilts ever again.
We can follow the village together now,
however many years it takes.
You folks...!
I went and kicked their butts!
You're really hurt...
This is nothing new.
Thank you...
Ah, so that's why you accepted their challenge.
Not like you wouldn't have otherwise, though.
Man, you're rude!
Wh-What is this?!
Yikes!
Who are you?!
No, who are you?!
Th-The thing can talk!
I'm not a thing! I'm a mooole!
"Mooole"? Like a mole?
I'm the champion! Yo!
Not another weirdo...
Champion of what?!
I'm glad you asked!
I'm the world champion of hole-digging!
I'm challenging my own record as we speak!
What kind of challenge has you
wrecking the old stilts guy's house?!
"Old stilts guy"...?
Take a look. This is a "mooole."
Littonto. I'm about to go for
the stilt-standing world record.
Huh?!
Competing with the world is a long, hard road.
I'll be gone a few days. The mooole
will keep you company, though, right?
Can you manage while I'm gone?
Sure. But make sure you
come back as a champion!
But of course I will!
I promise!
Could it be? Are you...?!
It's me!
--Grandpa!
--Littonto!
I missed you! I missed you so much!
You went and grew so much
since I last saw you...!
I'm sorry for worrying you...
He's your grandson?
I missed my grandpa so much,
and that devotion led me to hole-digging!
And before I knew it, becoming
the greatest digger in the world
had become my greatest goal in life...
So you became the champion?
Yep! "Shoot for the other side of the world!"
I like that! You sound
just like the old stilts guy!
--Oh, you're too kind!
--That's not praise!
Say, couldn't you follow your
holes to reach your village?
Oh...
Isn't this great, old guy?!
Yes. I don't know how to begin thanking you...
Don't worry about it!
You too, Miss! I achieved my true goal,
all thanks to your insight!
I'll never forget what you've done for us!
Thank you!
Take care on your way home!
You too! I pray for your safe journey!
All right! Time for us to leave!
Nami! Is the Log ready?
Yep! We're good to go!
Let's get movin', then.
Yeah.
Let's hurry and snag us a shipwright!
Yeah!
All right, men!
Let's go find a shipwright!
Yeah!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
--Umm... What am I doing again?
--Who are these guys?
Why am I with a bunch of pirates?!
Who what where am I?
--Don't tell me all your memories are...!
--Oh, my head! My head!
--Are you okay, Long-nose?
--Oh, it's so itchy...!
Shut up, all of ya!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Was It Lost? Stolen? Who Are You?"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!