Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
saa yukou
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
However, Ace protected Luffy from Akainu's
attack  and lost his life in the process!
And then, Blackbeard turned up
and brought further turmoil!
This is...!
That pose is...!
"The Insatiable Akainu!
Lava Fists Pummel Luffy!"
The HQ building is gonna fall!
Leave your post!
We're dead!
Is this for real?
Somebody please tell me I'm dreaming!
Over the centuries we've kept
watch  over the seas from there!
I can't believe the fort of
justice the Navy's citadel...
...is crumbling before my eyes!
Blackbeard is the one who caught
Ace and triggered the war
and now he has Whitebeard's power!
Look, all you people of the world!
Behold me and my power!
What's gonna happen to this world?!
I can feel the power
coursing through my body!
Dammit!
What power! It feels like I could control
everything in the world at my whim!
Bastard!
Hey, what's wrong?!
What are you waiting for?
Doesn't anyone wanna fight?
I'm willing to fight you to your
hearts' content now! What a shame!
I have no choice.
Then, let's start with...
...sinking Marineford into water!
What did he say?!
Shock Wave!
A building can easily be rebuilt!
But the island of Marineford is located
virtually in the center of the world!
Fleet Admiral!
To protect the people of the world who
are threatened by rampaging villains,
it is important to them that we are here!
Justice that comes from
humanity will never perish!
Don't claim to be able to
sink this place so lightly,
you little punk!
Such noble beliefs! Huh? Fleet Admiral-san!
Well, then:
defend this place--if you can!
Damn!
Hurry up and bring the ship to the
island! We can't leave anyone behind!
Wait for us! We're coming now!
We gotta get out of here alive!
Hurry up, everybody!
The Navy's victory must be unquestionable!
We gotta survive and leave
here as Pops told us to!
Let the pirates know the power
of justice through fear!
--Justice...
--...Through fear...
We're almost there!
That's right! Now is the chance to
let villains all over the world know!
Our power that will...!
...save the world!
We're safe now!
The power of justice!
K-Kizaru!
Now is the chance!
Take Straw boy!
Thank you!
Inazuma!
You better stop, Jimbei!
You pest!
Let's finish this up!
I won't let you go any further!
New Kama Kempo: 44 - Aesthetic Technique!
Laser Surgery Fist!
My nails have melted!
Emporio Ivankov of the Revolutionaries army!
You use strange techniques as they say!
New Kama Kempo: 44 - Aesthetic Technique!
Fat Suctioning Fist!
I like it hot!
I have no time to play with you guys!
Ouch!
I burned my lips, my lips, my lips...
...or not! Because of
my over-applied make-up!
Ouch!
I-Ivan-sama!
You bastards!
Don't let them get away! Shoot!
Isn't this too one-sided?
We already know who won...
Is this really necessary?
Defeat them decisively!
Don't ever let them even
think about challenging us!
What's going on?
We'll let them know...!
...The power of justice that we own!
Destroy them!
Destroy them!!
What's this?!
Akainu!
Jimbei! Hand Dragon's son over to me!
I'll have an advantage once we
get to the sea! I can outrun him!
Oh no! It's frozen!
Aokiji!
He's coming!
Looks like you've got nowhere to run!
It's no good!
Straw Hat Luffy!
I got you!
Jimbei!
It went right through Jimbei
and got to Ace's brother!
Are they alive?!
Can't let him hurt anymore!
You're in my way, Jimbei!
Luffy-kun, I'm sorry! I couldn't save you!
You fool! You have to worry
about yourself right now!
I missed a little because you were in my way.
If it hit his heart, it
would've been easier for him.
Don't you think so, Jimbei?
Are you gonna keep protecting
him with a hole in his chest?
He's gonna die soon!
Jimbei, if I don't escape death...
I'm sorry but could you
look after my brother?
I'm not helping him because
he is your brother!
I have a high regard for Luffy-kun!
I've already made up my mind to save
his life even if it means death!
I won't let him die!
Even if I die,
I won't let Luffy-kun die!
That's nonsense!
Crocodile!
Sables!
Somebody, catch them and
put them on the ship!
Okay!
Crocodile!
You gotta protect the one you wanna protect!
Don't let them have their way!
Catch them!
It's over!
I'm sorry that I got carried away, everyone.
This is the end of Captain Buggy's legend.
Thank you for your support all this time!
Jimbei!
They're not coming down...
What's going on?!
Captain Buggy!
He helped Straw Hat and Jimbei!
That's exactly what I thought!
Huh?
Captain Buggy, you made us
believe that you were gonna run
but you helped your fellow escapee
Straw Hat when it counted!
How beautiful!
You're beautiful and shimmering!
They're being weird again!
Jimbei and Straw Hat!
What made you guys fly in the
sky with blood all over you?!
Anyway, why is it so hot here...?
M-Magma!
Thank you, red-nosed man! You helped us!
I don't know what's going
on and I'm not helping you!
But I allowed Luffy-kun to be injured!
He needs to be treated immediately!
Shut up! I'm the one who needs help, fool!
How could we get him treated here...
Did you call me "red-nosed man"?!
They keep getting in my way
when I'm about to get him!
Rose Rondo!
You're fools, one and all!
Do you wanna die to save that Straw Hat brat?
We've all seen his limitless tenacity
and power with our own eyes.
He's the one who Ace wanted
to save and Pops approved!
And we're bound to bring
him into the new era!
I thought that you all were better
than that! Not that it matters!
The Whitebeard Pirates!
Akainu!
The degree to which you see him as a
risk - that makes you wanna kill him.
The degree to which we have
high expectations of him -
that makes us wanna protect him.
They're the same, don't you agree?
You guys got me involved again!
Are you even listening?!
H-Hey, Jimbei?
Don't tell me that you're unconscious!
Where should I go now?!
Hey!
Whether he lives or dies,
it's as if he's in hell.
Then we can make him suffer
as we please while he lives!
We can't resolve this
through dialogue anymore.
So be it!
W-We're dead!
It's Sengoku vs. Blackbeard over there.
And it's Akainu vs. the commanders over here!
The fighting hasn't stopped!
Captain Buggy! Do something!
Damn it all, fools!
Give me a break... Honestly!
Captain, we reached the
point where it's not frozen.
Surface.
What is that?! The ship came out of water!
That's a submarine!
Is that another enemy?
Whose ship is that?
Put Straw Hat-ya on my ship!
"Straw Hat-ya"? That's really
a strange way to call somebody!
Who the hell are you, brat?!
Straw Hat-ya will become
my enemy at some stage
but a desirable relationship
is still a relationship.
There's no point in letting him die here.
THE HEART PIRATES--CAPTAIN TRAFALGAR LAW
I'm gonna help him get out of here.
Let me take care of him for now!
W-What?!
I'm a doctor!
The Navy's relentless pursuit continues.
As the meaningless battle rages on endlessly,
one young man stands lost
in grief on the battlefield.
That sadness gives birth to
a great power called courage,
setting the very world in motion!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Desperate Scream! Courageous
Moments that Will Change the Future"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!