Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where they instigated an all-out war
against the New Fish-Man Pirates,
who were holding a grudge against humans
and looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom.
Luffy finally defeated Hordy, the captain of
the New Fish-Man Pirates, in a fierce fight
and thwarted his plot. However...
Have it your way, instead
of the Fish-Man Island,
I'll have my vengeance against you all!
Monkey D. Luffy. I know your name now.
Come to the New World!
Sure, wait for me there.
There's some business I want
to settle with you, too.
I can't leave it in your
hands - that's too dangerous!
I'll kick your ass all over the New World...
...and make the Fish-Man Island my territory!
You insolent brat!
"Many Problems Lie Ahead! A Trap
Awaiting in the New World!"
--Here you go.
--Oh, thank you!
It's kelp tea - a special
product of the Fish-Man Island.
It aids in digestion so do
your stomach a favor with it.
It's good! How thoughtful of
you, Minister of the Right!
You are treating us most graciously
- I hope we're not imposing!
No, no!
There are no words to express
my thanks to you all, so...
We have to say goodbye to this island soon.
Do not mention saying goodbye, "Nose"pp-sama!
No, don't cry! I'm sorry!
And my name is Usopp.
Oh, where did Franky go?
He left to learn how to operate the ship.
Seems like  he needs to learn
a little trick to ascend.
So... this is the list of treasures
that were stolen from the chamber.
There are so many! The Tamate Box, again...
Tamate Box?
IN THE VICINITY OF THE CANDY FACTORY TOWN
Damn Straw Hat!
I can't believe he kicked me out!
But,
I have so much treasure in my belly.
I'm gonna buy, like, 100 pirate ships and
kill the Straw Hats in the New World...
T-T-The treasure!
It's all gone!
I can't even buy a hard candy now!
Oh my treasure-chan!
Where is it?!
How is everything-jamon, Jimbei?
Are the members of the
Sun Pirates doing well?
Yes. In fact, they have too much energy
and they are a bit out of control.
But I cannot believe they accepted it.
Even I was surprised when
I heard about it-jamon.
I had never expected the Sun
Pirates becomes Big Mam's allies.
Is it going well?
I have to say that while she is not a
reasonable person she lets us
do what we like.
Well, I was worried because it must be hard
for a man like you to work under somebody...
...other than Fisher Tiger.
You don't have to worry.
I don't mind working for someone.
Plus, in the New World,
the best you can do to protect your crew is
ally yourself with one of the Four Emperors.
Oh yeah? It seems to me like you
are doing it for the benefit
of the Fish-Man Island.
Even after Whitebeard's death,
this island remained safe under
Big Mam's name because you
connected us to her.
No, it's just a coincidence.
We are supposed to protect the island
but we are wanted pirates so...
However, Your Majesty!
I am thinking about breaking
away from Big Mam.
Oh, are you going to accept
Luffy-kun's invitation?
Hey, Jimbei.
Join...
...my crew!
Yes. I've made up my mind.
But the pirates' world is all
about obligation and honor.
Our contracts are made by exchanging cups of
sake and a verbal agreement - no documents.
So we have to be really determined
when we terminate a contract.
My concern is that there is a chance
that Big Mam will turn her
anger toward this island.
Boy... You do not have to feel responsible
for everything-jamon, Jimbei.
If that is going to happen,
so be it. I have a plan-jamon.
We just welcomed 70 thousand rowdy
fellows as new soldiers from
the Fish-Man District today.
So do not worry about us-jamon.
And if we lose Big Mam's
Jolly Roger as protection,
there is another one that I want to use!
A skull with a straw hat on-jamon.
I see! I like that Jolly Roger too!
King-sama!
W-W-We have a problem!
What is it, Minister of the Right?
Why are you in such a rush?
I just remembered something serious!
Relating to giving all the treasures
to Luffy-kun and the others.
If they find them, could you to
tell them to return the Tamate Box!
What are you saying?!
I will not tell them to return
something I already gave them!
But...
What?! It will explode if someone opens it?!
Why did you rig it with explosives?
Well...
After the contents of the Tamate
Box were stolen 10 years ago,
I thought, in case another thief
comes, we have to teach him a lesson.
So we set up a box-full of explosives
to explode when someone opens it.
Since I am in charge of the treasure
chamber and the Tamate Box...
All right. All right.
If Luffy-kun and the others
come back with the treasures,
give them the reason and ask
them to return it to us.
I am sorry.
But what if they open it
before they get here...
That is my concern, too.
King-sama, Minister of the Right!
Luffy-sama and the others just came back.
Oh, so they are okay?!
I am so relieved. I guess I
was just worrying too much.
What?!
All the treasures?!
To Big Mam?!
You gave them away?!
She said she was gonna destroy the
island if she couldn't get her sweets!
Can you believe how crazy she is?! I mean
- if it were meat, I could understand!
But don't worry!
I really stood up to her!
You stood up to one of the Four Emperors?!
You talked back to Big Mam?!
Wow! You are so tough, Luffy-sama!
That's not the point!
"Nose"pp-sama is scary!
My name is Usopp!
Okay, I'm sorry!
Boy, that's not good.
I have to break away from Big
Mam before it gets complicated.
You guys should not do anything
to make Big Mam angrier!
We won't! We're all gonna get killed
since she's one of the Four Emperors!
Hey, this is pretty bad,
Minister of the Right!
I can't believe it!
If they gave the Tamate Box to Big
Mam and if she opens it herself,
she will take it as Luffy-kun's
challenge to her!
That is a big problem-jamon!
Well, he had no choice though.
What's done is done.
I guess it was a tit-for-tat situation
so you couldn't help fighting with her.
You're right! No matter who she was, I'd...
Nami-san...
Why...
...did you give all the treasures away?!
That's what you're focused on?!
--I'll punch you!
--You already did!
All right! Leff's go thew the New World!
We have no future ahead of us!
This is it! We're doomed!
Meanwhile, near the Candy Factory...
Dammit! Somebody took all the
treasures before I knew it!
Who did this? I'm gonna
kill him at any price!
With a mountain of treasures
and the secret of the Mermaid
Princess as presents,
I know that person will like me!
Oh, a crowd!
Who are those two carrying heavy loads?
Straw Hat Luffy! How dare he challenge Mama!
Mama must be really mad-soir.
I wonder what's going to happen-vous plait.
The tea party is 4 days from now.
Let's stop by at some island and
get something really sweet. Grr!
We have to ease her anger
even if just a little bit.
I think that's the best we can do-soir.
Luckily, we have so many
treasures-vous plait.
Those are my treasures! I'm sure!
Who the hell are they?!
I will bury them alive!
I stole those treasures!
Give them back to me!
--That's...
--He looks familiar to me. Grr!
Oh, here he is!
His name is "Wet-Haired"
Caribou. A rising rookie.
Oh, he's got a 200 million berry bounty.
H-He's worth 200 million berries?
It's too late to beg for your life!
Swamp-Swamp...
...Gatling Gun!
I'll fill you with holes!
Mr. Pekoms!
What is that?!
A turtle?
You're a Devil Fruit eater!
Of course I am!
But you're just Zoan type, aren't you?
Drop dead!
Logia Devil Fruit eaters who think
they're invincible often die young.
Half-boiled challengers
always disappoint me-soir.
Let's go home-bon, Pekoms. Mama is waiting.
He beat a guy with a 200 million
bounty in a single blow!
As I recall, Mr. Pekoms has
a 330 million berry bounty.
Over 300 million?
That is how strong the pirate group led
by the one of the Four Emperors can be?
Will Luffy-san and the others be okay?
We are totally heroes now!
There's the Sunny!
Franky's there!
Looks like he's ready to go!
Hey, Franky!
Here we go finally!
Meanwhile, on the sea near the
Red Line in the New World...
An urgent report from the headquarters!
Several coated ships are emerging
from the seafloor at high speed!
Everyone, man your posts now!
I repeat!-- Everyone, man your posts now!
That's...!
A-A pirate ship!
Fire!
Hurry up! There's one more at two o'clock!
Pirate ships are emerging one after another!
What's going on?
Don't try to gain her favor like that!
Shut up! Go away!
I just got freed from hell at
last! I don't wanna die here!
Here comes a big one!
The captain is in danger!
I'm gonna embrace her to keep her safe!
Let me take that important task!
Hey!
Not again!
Nice! That's my Captain-chan!
What beautiful swordplay!
It's not just the swordplay that's beautiful!
You guys, be serious!
You all know how to ward off bombshells!
If you don't use that skill
now, when are you gonna...
Captain, you're talking to a mast!
I cleaned your glasses!
Thank you.
She's so cute! She's like
a flower in the filthy G-5!
I will die for you, Captain-chan!
Me too! Me too!
We're in a battle! Stop fooling around!
Otherwise, you'll get killed!
I'm sick of the G-5!
NAVY GRAND LINE 5TH BRANCH
"G-5" CAPTAIN--TASHIGI
I can't believe you guys are Navy soldiers!
Don't take me lightly
just because I'm a woman!
We're not taking you lightly!
We're just falling for Captain
Tashigi's cuteness...
There! You're taking me lightly!
You have to realize that you're Navy...
Shut up, Tashigi!
I'm interrogating someone here.
I'm sorry, sir!
I see.
So you all were captured by Hordy
Jones, a pirate from the seafloor.
That explains why
there was no rookie passing by
the Fish-Man Island for a month.
Captured? No, he enslaved us!
But when Hordy and his clan started a civil
war, a group of pirates defeated them
and freed us!
A group of pirates?
Yeah, but I'm not gonna
tell you who they were!
Idiot! Just tell them!
They're not just Navy
soldiers - they're the G-5!
They'd fish for sharks using a pirate as bait
or make a bonfire using pirates as kindling!
They're the Navy's craziest outlaws
who won't even obey orders
from the headquarters!
You have no idea what they're gonna do to us!
And of all men, we were...
...caught by the infamous
"White Chase" Smoker!
NAVY GRAND LINE 5TH BRANCH "G-5" VICE ADMIRAL
"WHITE CHASE" SMOKER
Vice Admiral Smoker! Can I take them?
No, don't!
I'll tell you! So help me!
The group of pirates who beat
Hordy and his clan was...
...the Straw Hats!
I know.
Fool!
With both excitement and uncertainty...
...the journey to the New
World is finally underway.
The Straw Hats acquire a new Log Pose...
...and say their goodbyes
to Shirahoshi and Jimbei.
To fulfill his promise to Shanks...
...Luffy finally sets off...
...on a new voyage.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Finally Time to Go!
Goodbye, Fish-Man Island!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!