Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
He ran into Buggy and a former
Baroque Works agent - Mr. 3,
and together, they have reached level 3!
This is level 3 - the Starvation Hell!
We have to get away from here while
we still have sweat to spare.
Let's go to level 4 in hurry!
Seriously?!
Soup spaghetti!
The Sphinx is awake!
Deep-fried noodle!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Meanwhile, Hancock who helped
Luffy to sneak into the prison...
...is about to reach the floor
where Ace is being held.
Un, deux, come on!
--Un, deux, faint!
--Who's singing?
Un, deux, come on!
Un, deux, faint!
"The Unleashed Swan! A
reunion with Bon Clay!"
Oh Come My Way!
Oh, oh! Oh Come My Way!
Yeah, yeah! Oh Come My Way!
I can barely stand in this Starvation
Hell but that guy's singing so happily.
If he's a prisoner, he sure is something!
Spin, spin! Oh Come My Way!
It sounds familiar! This must be...
Hey, partner! I think this guy can help us!
H-Hey! W-Wait a minute!
Yeah, yeah! Oh Come My Way!
Spin, spin! Oh Come My Way!
You guys are doing great!
I spin and spin like I'm caught
up in the tide of the times!
This way!
Wait! Listen to me! That's...
Guys! You can't be that tired!
It's not that hot!
I can make more people suffocate!
Oh! What's up, Mr. 3!
Just as I thought. It's you...
What?! Mr. 3?!
Hey, wait a minute! Why're you here?!
You're behind bars, so you've been caught?!
No, no. It's me who has been caught!
I was so surprised I had to do a double take
with an "Oh Come My Way" Kenpo called...
...Looking Back on that Autumn Night's Dream!
Hey! What kind of animal is this?!
Let's be sure to not let him out.
What're you saying?! Let me out!
How much hotter can it get?!
But if I keep going down these stairs,
I think I can get to where Ace is!
He headed down?!
Is that true?! You're not
fooling with me, are you?!
--No!
--Certainly not!
Okay! Thank you for letting me out, Mr. 3!
I owe you!
--Ah?
--Alright then...
I'm on my way, my friend!
Oh Come My Way! It's the way to hell!
This is the best for all of us.
Yeah, for sure...
How did he slip through our tight security?!
There's just one invader.
But if we let him rescue Ace,
not only Impel Down but the World
Government will be humiliated!
We're gonna get into that prison
and in the name of Navy Headquarters,
we must catch Straw Hat Luffy!
Wait a minute!
W-Who are you?!
I'm Sadie-chan who loves torturing people!
After being breached by an
intruder, taking Navy help
would only further
disgrace Impel Down's name!
She can't be serious using
"chan" to refer to herself...
Shut up!
You better call me "Sadie-chan!"
I can't resist those screams!
You bitch!
Hold it! Are you saying that
you don't need our help?
Yes. This prison is a labyrinthine hell.
If you don't know it well, you can't help us!
We'd appreciate your help if
you just guard the outside.
We'll raise this drawbridge which is
the only entrance to the prison...
...and seal off Impel Down completely!
Don't worry. There is no way out...
...of this underwater prison!
Alright then, we'll guard the outside.
You're a good boy.
A koala?
You're kidding me!
A koala.
A koala?
We're completely sealed off!
Hannyabal?!
Magellan's here, too. What's going on?
You have a special visitor, Ace!
Guess who's here!
Jimbei! Even you have never met her before,
so there's no way that
Ace can guess who it is.
She's well-known but never shows herself!
She leads the Kuja - the tribe of warriors!
She's a Warlord of the Sea!
Strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
She is the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Yeah, yeah, Hancock! Hancock-sama!
Yo, goddess! When I become
warden, will you marry me?!
Please!
Ouch! I really wanna become the warden!
I mean, it really hurts
to be hit by the warden!
What are you doing?!
Wow! Is she it?! She is so beautiful!
So she's the Snake Princess
of the Kuja? Hey, turn around!
Hancock-chan!
Look how sexy she is!
Young lady! Come to our cell!
We will love you tenderly!
What a good smell! I wanna
visit the Maiden Island!
There's only women and
everybody's naked there, right?
What do you want from me?
Nothing. I just wanted to take a look at you.
Because you will become the cause
of the war that I will take part in.
So I'm worth a look, then?
Boa Hancock! Are you ignoring us?!
Come here!
You've always been an empress with a strong
will who never obeyed any summonses,
but you're taking part in this war?
Suddenly, you value your
title of Warlord of the Sea?!
So you're Jimbei. Don't snarl at me.
Yo, yo, young lady! Young lady!
They're talking! Shut your mouths!
Shut up, Magellan! Go have a shit as always!
Yeah, he's right!
Hey, Snake Princess!
I bet the girls on the Maiden
Island are hungry for us guys!
Hey you! Give me your post as warden!
Vice Warden!
Hey girl! I said "get your
ass over to our cell!"
You guys!
She turned!
You keep taunting me with
those coarse voices...
I'm scared!
Oh, god! I can't resist!
How cute she is! Let us have her, Shit Man!
This is the vilest place in
the world! It makes me sick!
The prisoners call you "Shit Man."
How can you stand it, Warden?
They must've crushed any
pride you take in your job...
Wow! She's irresistible!
Shame on you, Shit Man!
However...
Let me have her, Shit Man!
Shit Man! Let me have Hancock!
I'm infuriated at their rudeness!
Wow! Warden, w-w-wait!
That's gonna harm us, too! No!
You've gotten carried away!
Ugh! Oh man!
I have to show you...
...who is boss in this prison!
Oh man!
His Hydra appears!
--What're you doing?!
--Stop, Magellan!
You fool! We were just joking! Don't!
You bastard! You can't do this to me!
Oh no! You're gonna die!
I need... I need an antidote! Shit!
I have the authority and the ability...
...to execute any of you at
my whim! Don't forget it!
All right, Hancock-dono.
You can talk freely now.
I'm done.
Hey! Is what you just told me true?!
Why would I lie to you?
Oh yeah!
He was worried that you might get mad.
Are you done already?
What were they talking about?
I dunno. I was trying really
hard to get away from you.
Ace-san.
What did she just tell you?
She said that my brother's here!
What?! The one with a straw hat
that you always talk about?!
That's insane!
Ah? I didn't notice but I'm
climbing now! I wanna go down!
But I guess If I keep going, it's
gonna go downwards at some point!
I'm hungry!
We got an image! He's
about to enter district C!
Alright, I see him!
Sea Prism Stone nets, again!
That was close!
Oh no! The lion!
Damnit!
Wait a minute, you lion!
I'm here to help you!
Zoro!
I fooled you!
Swan Arabesque!
--Swan, swan!
--Oh?
Spin, spin! I'm spinning!
He's not Zoro but he sounds familiar...
It's been a long time!
Straw-chan, it's me!
So how was my secret talent?!
Cool!
Gimme a break!
--Running now wouldn't be like Bon Clay...
--Huh?!
If we abandon pals who would risk
their lives to pick up their pal,
will we... be able to
enjoy our food tomorrow?!
Miss Hina! The sheep ship
is heading to the east!
What?!
You were tricked, weren't you!
We’re experts at disguising
ourselves! And...
we’re the Straw Hats’ friends...!
Bring it on!
We'll never forget you!
Bon-chan!
I'm so disappointed that you're not
Zoro but at least you're alive!
It's our chance! Get Straw Hat!
Go away!
You assholes! What do you think
you're doing to my friend?!
Yeah, Sphinx! Fight back!
Okay! He's not gonna attack us
after getting busted up like this!
You gotta get rough to teach
a wild animal a lesson!
Fried noodle bun...
Hey, Bon-chan! I thought
that you were dead...
...after sacrificing yourself for us!
Gimme a break! Queers never die!
Oh, is that right?!
Let's see how Mr. 2 Bon Clay's power works!
He ate the Clone-Clone Fruit
and he can turn into anyone whose face
has been touched by his right hand.
He turned into Zoro because
he touched him before.
Here's another escapee!
He keeps gaining friends as
he descends deeper and deeper!
Blugoris! Don't let them get away!
By the way, Straw-chan, I heard
that you wanna get to level 5!
Yes, indeed! Can you show me the way?
Alright, I'll go with you!
Actually, there's someone
that I wanna see on level 5!
You sure?!
Okay then, let's do it together!
Uh-huh!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Luffy teams up with Mr. 2 Bon Clay again,
and they blast through level 3, taking
out armies of Blugoris along the way.
At last, they're close to level 4!
But before they get there, an
immensely powerful demon guard,
Minotaurus, stands before them.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Warden Magellan's Strategy!
Straw Hat Entrapment Completed!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!