Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Awesome! Nami! Check it out!
The pirate ship!
Hey! I see an island below that light!
We're going to land there!
Why've you not reported to me after
finding the Millennial Dragon?!
Our main forces will now
head for Warship Island!
All ships, move out!
Stupid Nami makes the
men do all the work...
Hey, you! Less complaining
and more pushing!
Don't start getting cocky, you!
Finally made it...
We're alive... right?
Yeah, it seems that way...
What's that?
What is this?
"Showdown in the Ruins!
Tense Zoro vs. Eric!"
Wow! What a huge picture!
What's it of?
It looks like some
sort of map... Oww...
But it's too worn out
to make any sense of.
But what is this place, anyways?!
Wasn't this supposed
to be the dragons' nest?
Dunno.
Well, Apis?
I don't know.
Grandpa Ryu says he doesn't
know what this place is, either...
Man! He's always just a useless old guy!
He's what?!
But it's the truth!
Then how exactly are you being useful?!
Me?!
Hey, guys! Look at this!
The ceiling picture's fallen down!
Yikes!
It's huge!
Whoa, talk about dangerous!
This whole building's ready to fall apart!
If we dilly-dally around here,
we'll be in danger, too!
Let's get the heck outta this place!
But this might be the dragons' nest!
I don't see any dragons
around here, do you?!
Hold on a second!
What is it, Nami-san?
This might not be Lost Island...
See!
You don't even know the reason why!
Quit making stuff up!
How can you tell that, Nami?
Look up.
Up?
At the ceiling picture?
Look closely.
It's a map that marks
the location of Lost Island.
That island with a
dome-shaped building on it...
That's this island.
That dome is this building.
It does look just like it...
And the people around the island
are the people who once lived here.
I'd wager they're probably Apis' ancestors.
Our ancestors?
Say, do you remember what
old man Bokuden told us?
Nope! I was asleep!
Come on, now! He said
the people of Warship Island
had traveled there from another island.
He did?
Come to think of it,
he did say something like that...
Then does that mean the dynasty
he kept blabbing on about
was on this island?
Probably.
So what had me wondering
were all the dragon statues
and paintings on the way here.
I think they might've been used
by the people living on this island
to worship the Millennial Dragon as a god.
I bet the Millennial Dragon used
to fly over this island long ago.
I see!
That would lower the chance of the
dragons' nest being on this island.
But...! If so, then where's the real one?!
Wouldn't it be that island
with the dragon drawn on it?
That's right!
There's an island ahead of where
this island's people are praying.
That's the real Lost Island!
The dragons' nest must be there, too!
But...
Wait a minute!
That island is shaped like...!
Yeah.
Assuming the map is correct,
the dragons' nest is on Warship Island.
But I thought there were no places
on Warship Island that fit the bill?!
But that's what the map says!
Or are you saying the people
long ago just drew random nonsense?!
Yeah, you guys!
Nami-san'd never say
anything that's wrong!
This means it's somewhere on that island!
We'll figure it out if we go check it out!
But... It could also have sunk
to the bottom of the ocean...
No, that's actually much more likely.
That would explain why
nobody's ever found it yet.
Apis?
Grandpa Ryu!
Think back, Grandpa Ryu!
Where is the dragons' nest?!
We thought it was this place,
but there's nothing here!
There's only a painting, Grandpa Ryu!
Does the painting bring
back any memories?!
Our only hope now is that you
remember something, Grandpa Ryu!
Come on! Please!
Remember, Grandpa Ryu!
Grandpa Ryu!
Alright! So the dragons' nest
really is on Warship Island, then?!
Eh?! How did you know
what he said, Luffy?!
I just did!
You're right.
Grandpa Ryu said he remembered!
He says the dragons' nest
is on an island east of a peak
that looks like a warship...
Man! Why does he say that
only after we went through
all that hardship to get here?!
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry for dragging
you all the way out here
for something that might've
already sunk into the ocean...
It was all for nothing...
Not necessarily!
Who knows? The dragons' nest
could be somewhere unexpected!
And there's no telling for sure
without checking it out, right?!
That's right!
Being discouraged this
easily isn't like you, Apis!
You'll never get anything done
if you're afraid of failure.
There's nothing wrong with
living a roundabout life...
Everyone...
So, let's go! Grandpa Ryu won't
get any better if we just stay here!
Right?!
Yeah!
Thank you!
Is something wrong, Zoro?!
Someone's here.
With bloodlust.
Thanks for the explanation.
Now I know where to find
Dragonite and the dragons' nest...
You again?!
But there's no point if it's
at the bottom of the ocean...
So it would seem my only option
is to take your Millennial Dragon.
No!
Besides, we don't know if their
nest is on the ocean bottom or not!
He said he had Sickle-Sickle
Fruit powers, if I recall...
That's one nasty guy we got here...
Sickle-Sickle Fruit?!
He has Devil Fruit powers?!
Hey...
Luffy.
You go on ahead and take
Grandpa Ryu to the ship!
I'll catch up with you later.
Got it!
W-W-Whoa, now! The ship?!
We don't even know
where the exit here is!
Then we can just... make one!
You're not seriously gonna--!
Huh? I thought that would
bust it open, but...
Oh, geez...
It's open! It's open!
It worked out! It worked out!
Let's go, Apis!
He's less than a caveman...
Oh, no, you don't!
Dammit, Luffy! Get going already!
Oh! My bad!
So fast! So fast!
W-We always make it out alive, don't we?!
It's not for certain that we'll
live through this! That idiot!
This makes going back a cinch!
Damn you! Get in my way
and you'll pay!
So let's see how you plan
on making me pay!
I'm pretty confident that right now
we're the fastest moving
things in this world!
What kind of thing is that to brag about?!
Luffy! Do something!
We're gonna wind up in pieces
before we get to the ship!
It's okay! It's okay!
How are we okay?!
Sickle-Sickle Wind Slash!
What was that?!
You can't run away from me!
I have no time to be playing with you.
My only goal is that Millennial Dragon!
Get back here!
Are they alright?!
Hey! Will Zoro really be alright?!
Yeah! He'll be fine!
But he's up against a guy
with Devil Fruit powers!
He doesn't stand a chance,
no matter how strong he is!
He'll still be alright!
Luffy! Ahead! Ahead!
This isn't good...
Don't give us that!
Do something!
Over there, eh?
Sorry. I can't let you pass here.
Whatever. It's up to me
whether I pass or not!
Out of the way!
Damn! That nimble bastard!
I told you I'm not letting you pass.
Just stay right there!
Luffy! There's another dead-end!
Wanna bust it down?
No!
I'm pretty sure that up ahead is
the cliff we followed on our way up!
If we do that, we'll fall over it
head-first and then we're goners!
Think we can fly?
No!
I told you not to get in my way!
Now die like a good little boy!
It looks like we somehow
managed to make it...
Man, we seriously have
incredible luck or something...
Alright! We made it, right?
Get ready to set sail! Let's go!
No more, please...
Damn bastard...
You're totally... gonna pay!
Luffy!
He says... He says Zoro's in trouble!
What do we do?! We gotta help him!
Die!
Zoro!
Bingo!
Awesome!
No, not this pattern...
Here we go!
I told you to stop doing this!
Oh. My bad.
I swear, someday
I will chop this guy up!
Damn!
I refuse to let you escape me!
We're out! We're out!
That's definitely weird...
What?! They did?!
Yes, sir! They're on their
way to Warship Island again,
with the Millennial Dragon in tow!
Then make chase the moment
we're ready! On the double!
Y-Yes, sir! A-And one other
thing, Lt. Commander!
While in pursuit of them,
Eric-sama also reappeared
and has just returned to ship!
What a bunch of useless clods.
We should just sink the lot of 'em...
Sir?
Nothing! Thank you for the report!
I'm glad to see you've
returned to the ship unharmed.
Did you get the Dragonite?
If you have time for sarcastic remarks,
then go after them already!
Look at 'em come! Look at 'em come!
They'll never catch up with us!
The Going Merry is faster and
more agile than bulky Navy warships,
but what are we going to do
when we get to Warship Island?!
--We'll be okay!
--How will we be okay?!
We just need to find
the dragons' nest first
so Grandpa Ryu can get better, right?!
Easier said than done!
Their nest could be
at the bottom of the ocean!
We just need to search the
bottom of the ocean then!
That's big talk for
someone who can't swim...
Anyways, we need to get back
as fast as we can!
We don't have time to be
messing with the navy!
Nami-san. It doesn't look like
that's going to be an option...
Wow! Cool!
It's like a gargoyle!
Hey, now!
The small fries have leapt forth...
Now is the time!
Open to the left and right!
Crane Wing Formation!
Is this for reals?!
Just how many ships
does the damn navy have?!
Listen, now!
Connect all ships by chain links
to create a complete wall
that won't allow even a
single small fry to escape!
What now?! They have us blocked off!
Jump onto a ship, kick the guys off,
and cut the links!
That's the only choice, obviously!
Wow! You can do that, Usopp?!
Go! Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
I thought as much.
Doesn't sound too bad to me, though!
Eh?! But, are you serious?!
There's no way you could
survive if you tried that!
It's okay, Apis. Things'll work out.
But make it quick, you guys!
You can count on me, Nami-san!
Alright! Let's go!
All ships, take aim!
The target is the pirate ship!
But do not hit the raft behind the ship!
It must not be damaged
in even the slightest!
Stop the ships.
All ships, full stop!
Nelson Royal...
I had you pegged as a fatty
who can do nothing but eat,
but when you're on the sea,
it's as if you've been reborn...
A mere commodore,
but a commodore nonetheless, huh?
This feels great!
Alright!
Let's go!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Ah! We're done for!
They're gonna take us down!
Who the hell thought
of this plan anyway?!
It was you!!
The ride's about to get rough!
Hang on to something!
Alright, Nami-san!
Oh, that round is gonna hit us.
Quit your blabbing and do something!
Yo, I'm on it!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy, Completely Surrounded!
Commodore Nelson's Secret Strategy"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!