Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards have invaded
the plaza to make it to the scaffold!
In the midst of the Navy's onslaught,
with the Whitebeards' assistance,
Luffy finally freed Ace! However...
Watch what I do.
Wait!
Luffy!
"Looking for the Answer! Fire Fist
Ace Dies on the Battlefield!"
Ace...
Ace!
Ace-san!
He's been beaten! Dammit!
Stop Akainu!
Can't believe it!
Hurry up! Do something about these handcuffs!
I'm trying but... Damn, I can't break them!
Oh yeah! He can do it!
--He?
--Yeah, the guy who uncuffed Ace!
I'll make the key! Uncuff him right away!
Yeah, you're right! Bring him here now!
Okay!
Fire!
How's this war going to end?
We made you pay for what you've done to
Ace! Have you learned a lesson, Akainu?
No way! Is he a monster?!
Looks like you're still alive!
"Fire Fist" Ace!
Don't do it...
Don't do it!
Ace!
I can't believe you let your
guard down, Whitebeard!
I won't let you interrupt!
Brat!
Jimbei!
You can't touch him anymore!
You're just delaying the inevitable,
Jimbei! Since you were once a Warlord,
I bet you know what I'm capable of!
I'd be happy to risk my
life if I can delay it!
I've been ready to die from the beginning!
Jimbei!
Marco! He's here!
Gee, thank you for helping
me! I almost got killed...
Cut the crap and uncuff me now!
V-Vice Admiral Garp!
What are you...?
Garp!
What are you doing?! Are
you losing your mind?!
You better keep holding me
down like that, Sengoku!
Because if you don't, I will kill Sakazuki!
You fool!
Looks like I need to execute a traitor, too!
Jimbei, get down!
How annoying!
So you guys are Haki users!
How could we let that happen?!
I couldn't have more regret about it!
Can't you see that it's too
late to save "Fire Fist?!"
Take a look!
Ace...
Hey, are you all right? Hey.
Ace, you need to get treated right away!
I'm sorry, Luffy...
Huh?
In order to save me,
you pushed yourself that far but...
...I couldn't make it all the way.
I'm sorry.
Wh-What are you saying?
Don't be ridiculous!
Somebody, treat him!
Please! Please help Ace!
Hey somebody! Help Ace! Please!
--Hurry! This way! Give him first aid now!
--Okay!
Straw boy...
Ace! Are you alright?!
Hurry up and treat him!
Okay, let me see the wound!
Please!
This is...!
Huh?
Hey.
What's the matter? Hurry up and help him!
I'm sorry.
What do you mean by that?
What's going on?! Just do something!
Hey, aren't you a doctor?! Hey!
It's no use.
My organs have been burned.
I can't hold out any longer.
I can tell that my life is ending.
That's not true!
Oh yeah, Ivan-chan!
Hey, I beg you!
Inject that stuff into Ace! Please!
Like you did to me, why can't you help Ace?!
Hey, I beg you! Please! Help! Help Ace!
Please inject that into Ace...
Straw boy!
Ace boy... can't make it!
Huh? No way.
You promised me!
You said...
...that you'd never die...
...no matter what!
Ace!!
Ace...
What did you say?
You can't hold out any longer?
You promised me...
...that you'd never die...
...no matter what, Ace!
Do I even deserve to have been born?
What if Gold Roger had a child?
Of course I know what'd happen to him!
He'd get his head cut off for sure!
No way! I'm not content if
we kill him that easily!
How about we prick him with a needle
once for every grudge that
someone holds against Roger?!
No way! Instead, we'll burn him alive first
and humiliate him prior to death
in front of the whole world!
That's nice!
Everybody will say "that serves him right!"
I want to hear from him as he dies:
"I'm sorry I was born! I'm
just a piece of trash!"
But I don't think that he ever had a child!
No one wanted me to be born.
Ace! You caused trouble in the city again!
They're making a fuss about
it! Don't give us a hard time!
Hey! Are you listening, Ace?!
--Shut up, Dadan!
--What'd you say?!
If I were stronger, I would
have killed all of them!
I wouldn't even have a will to live...
...if it weren't for Sabo and a
high-maintenance brother like you.
Oh yeah. If you see Dadan
someday, say hello for me.
When I face my own death, I
even miss a woman like her.
Like I said, don't say that you're gonna die!
There is one thing that makes me wanna stay.
That is my desire to see
you fulfill your dream.
But I'm sure that you can do it!
Because you're my brother!
That day...
Listen, Luffy.
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
Uh-huh.
We gotta go out to sea someday...
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
Like we promised that
day, I have no regret...
...in my life.
That's a lie! Don't tell a lie!
I'm not lying.
Something tells me that what
I truly wanted was not fame.
Did I deserve to be born?
What I wanted was the
answer for that question.
Become my son!
You better tell me that my
beloved son is all right.
I'm your brother!
You can say whatever you want!
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
Guys! Rescue Ace and...
...destroy the Navy!!
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
Finally...
I made it! Ace!
Just tell me one thing.
Are you happy to have me as your father?
I can't raise my voice to let
everybody hear me anymore.
Could you tell them...
...what I'm about to say now?
Pops!
Everybody!
And you Luffy.
Thank you...
...for loving someone like
me who is good for nothing...
...and who has such bad blood in his veins...
...up to today.
Thank you!
Old man.
Huh?
Do you think...
...that I deserved to be born?
That's something...
...you'll see as you live.
Ace...
It is a reality difficult to accept.
Ace's death cruelly unfolds
before Luffy's eyes.
But the battle does not pause.
As the pursuit intensifies,
Whitebeard's rage shakes all of Marineford!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Navy Headquarters Falls!
Whitebeard's Unspeakable Wrath!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!