Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"North Block"
"West Block" "South Block" "East Block"
The feelings of those who are in anguish
are crushed by a dry cloud of sand.
There are those who seek hope,
and those who cling to hope.
Their feelings cross each other,
uncertain what to do,
marking an era of history ending in sadness.
Vivi and her friends continue to fight in
order to save Alabasta from its crisis...
In addition to Usopp and Chopper's victory...
...Sanji crushed Mr. 2 Bon Clay.
Meanwhile, Nami was engaged in
mortal combat with Miss Doublefinger,
who has Spike Spike Fruit powers.
Take this!
Tornado Tempo!
--What?
--The doves tangled up on me...!
As a result, Usopp's invention,
the Clima Takt, led Nami to win the battle.
The only battle left was the one
between Mr. 1 and Zoro.
So basically, your body is hard as steel.
Unless I'm capable of cutting
even steel, I can't cut you down, huh?
That would be correct.
Smashing and cutting
attacks don't work on me.
I see. This bites.
Since I'm not yet capable of
cutting steel, I can't defeat you now.
Humph... Then what're you going to do?
Well, I'll sympathize with you.
What?
I've been waiting for a
difficult situation like this.
I've been thinking that it's about
time for me to go to the next level.
When I defeat you,
I'll be a man who can even cut steel.
"Secret of Powerful Swordplay! Ability to
Cut Steel and the Rhythm Things Have"
Humph... When you defeat me... huh?
This might throw cold water
on that enthusiasm of yours,
but ever since I gained Dice Dice powers,
I've never been given even a scratch by
those who call themselves swordsmen.
No swordsman can defeat me.
Ahh... I get the picture...
...but you can store all those
old tales away in an album.
I don't know how many swordsmen
you've fought in the past,
but we've never met before, so...
It seems that at least your tongue is sharp.
Thanks, baldy.
We'll see how long you'll last.
No, how long you'll last.
Oni...
...Giri!
Tiger... Trap!
I told you, didn't I...?
It's a little shocking that you
didn't even get a single bruise...
This is also the first time
my opponent is still standing
when I thought my attacks were solid.
Of course...
...since we've never met before...
That's right!
This guy's entire body is a blade.
So his blades don't have a front or back!
Sparkling Daisy!
Th-This is...
I'll blow you away.
When it comes to training,
I've done it more than anyone else.
I've also been in many difficult
situations that had me on the brink.
When I defeat you, I'll be a
man who can even cut steel.
I've never been given
even a scratch by anyone.
What is it that I lack...?!
Teacher...! Teacher!
Hm?
Is it true that there're men in this world
who can cut anything, even steel?
Yes, it's true.
Now, watch this paper carefully, Zoro.
Teacher, you didn't cut it.
Listen, Zoro.
There're swordsmen out there
who are capable of cutting nothing.
But they can also cut anything,
even steel... using the same sword...
The strongest swordsmen are able to
protect that which they want to protect
and cut that which they want to cut.
Swordplay that harms whatever it touches...
I don't consider it real swordsmanship.
Do you understand?
Teacher, I'll be a swordsman
who can cut anything!
Zoro, were you listening
to what I was saying?
Humph... Hurry up and try cutting me.
You can't cut my body down
if you just defend.
Unfortunately, I don't think I can show
you my valiant figure cutting steel...
...because when I cut steel,
that's when you die.
Makes sense...
I'll cut... everything up into pieces!
"Swordplay that cuts nothing"... huh?
How pointless...
I'll cut everything up into pieces!
Swordplay that cuts nothing...
Cut nothing... but cut steel... I don't
understand what it means at all!
Thrust and Thrust... This is the
secret of powerful swordplay!
Atomic Spar!
I'll just cut you up!
Crab... Grab!
What an odious bastard...
The feeling is mutual.
Let me tell you one thing.
Don't consider me a swordsman.
I have many weapons
that can tear your body up.
Spiral Hollow!
If you're not a swordsman...
then an excavator?!
I'm an assassin!
Sparks?! Just how fast is it spinning?!
They'll be repelled!
I can't do excavation... because
I'll drill and cut everything up.
Crap!
What a momentary misjudgment invites is...
...death!
You're still breathing...
I won't show my back to him...
How're you gonna struggle
with your bare hands?
You're not even a swordsman.
You won't understand even if I explain.
Humph... I'm not even interested.
Spar... Break!
Die in peace...
I have... bad luck with stones today...
You guys! Make sure you
deliver Vivi back to her home!
See you at the Alubarna Palace!
Are they... all okay...?
Why is he standing...?
After being cut so many times...
Did he dodge all those falling stones?
I dodged... these stones?
No...
I could tell... the place where
no stones would be falling...
Swords...
There's one underneath
that stone... I can tell...
What's he doing...?
I've experienced this feeling before...
It's awfully quiet around me...
I can hear my heartbeat very clearly...
Is this... precisely what it feels
like when close to death...?
I sensed a hint from the falling
stones as if they're living things...
No, it wasn't a hint...
It was clearer than that...
Rhythm...
Stones'... rhythm...
Trees have their own rhythm...
Soil has its own... Is that what it is...?
Listen. There're swordsmen out there
who are capable of cutting nothing.
Does "cutting nothing" mean...
know the rhythm...?
That's... the ability to cut even steel...
You... what the hell did you do?
After receiving such an enormous attack...
When you're bleeding that much...
There's no way you can be still alive...!
I can hear... the rhythm of his steel...
My will is flowing into the sword...
Fine... I'll completely finish
him off with the next attack.
The only question left is...
...whether or not I really
have the ability to cut steel...
It's hard to think that you can defend
my attack using only one sword...
That's all right. I won't defend any more.
So you're now prepared. Fine by me!
One-Sword Style... Lion Strike!
Atomic Spurt!
I give you my thanks...
I can become stronger still!
He's indeed... become stronger...
during this fight...
Are you... going to cut
diamond or something next...?
That would be a waste...
You win...
"Alubarna - North Block"
"Battle in front of the Mehdi Assembly Hall"
"Winner: Zoro"
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
Why're you crying?
Because that mole hag
said that Luffy's dead...
Is that true?!
You guys believe that?
Of course not!
Then stow your snot away.
There's no reason for you to fight any longer!
Surrender right now...! Royal Army!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battle is Over!
Koza Raises the White Flag"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!