Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome treasure
at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King of
the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
The horizons everyone dreamed
of were separate at first
but now they can be seen through
a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny is
leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve your
dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
Whadya think, old fortress
guy?!I rescued my crew!
♪ We are the Navarone Marines! ♪
♪ We'll show you our fiery spirit! ♪
The special capture operation at Dock 88 is ready!
We can now capture the Straw Hats!
Don't let your guard down.
What do we do, Nami? Do we go there?
Yeah! Let's rely on Dr.
Kobato to lead the way!
"Breaking Through the Siege!The
Going Merry Is Recovered"
Is this really the right way, Usopp?!
Don't worry! This is
definitely it! Keep moving!
Y-Yeah! Merry's dock was just
around the corner there!
But this seems too easy. I don't like it...
All right! Let's steal our ship back!
Now this is somethin'...
So we were being ambushed!
Sniper Team #7, to the front!
Take aim!
Just like that?!
Gum-Gum...
Fire!
...Balloon!
What are you doing?!
Cannon Team #12, to the front!
Bazookas?!
Fire!
Duds?
Damn, what is this?! My eyes!
I can't see! My eyes are all irritated!
Those were flash bombs!
Sword Team, to the front!
Charge!
Bastards!
I'm fine!
Oh, that's some nice equipment there.
You can borrow these!
Thanks.
Tatsu-Maki!
Blinders don't work on me,unlike
a certain lovesick moron!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
And...
...Whip!
What a cinch!
Huh? Where's Sanji and Zoro?
You took care of 'em!
Oh, sorry.
You dumbass!
Oww...
All right, you dimwitted moron!
What was that you said earlier?!
What the heck are you guys fighting for?!
Fire!
What the--? Crap! I can't get this off!
Luffy!
Stay right where you are!
Your wanted posters say "dead or alive,"
but here at G8, we prefer alive.
But if you resist any further,I
can't guarantee that.
H-Hey, Luffy! Can't you get that net off?!
I can't! It won't come off at all!
Plus I'm suddenly out of strength...
Sea Prism Stone?!
What?!
That's right! That was a Prison Bomb,
meant for use against those with
Devil Fruit powers!
What do you think, Straw Hat?!
I knew he'd come...
What're you doing?!
It's dangerous here! Return to your station!
Don't be such a stick in the mud!
Not good!
Dammit! There's still this many
left,even after all the ones we beat?!
Just give yourselves up.Escape
is absolutely impossible!
All hands, take aim!
Got no choice!
Attack!
What is this?!
Huh? Was that--?
I'm on the verge of death...
Usopp!
What terrible injuries! He's
badly wounded! The marines did this?!
Damn them!
No, no, no...
Kobato?!
U-Umm, Lt. Commander?
Who are you?!
What's the big idea?!
We've been taken hostage! Please save us!
We were forced here against our will!
Kobato-san?
This giant is one of the pirates!
Eh?!
W-Wait! When did I do that?!
What is this?!
Who's that other girl?
How should I know?!
"Justice"
Seriously! Huh?! What're you talking about?!
We can't act carelessly with
the hostages there!
Damn that coward! This is why I hate pirates!
That giant was the fake doctor, then?
He has to be! He's carrying his crewmate!
That's right! I'm a rough and
tough member of the Straw Hats!
Even crying babies shut up around me!
Better do as I say, or
these hostages are dead meat!
All right! Have your men
stand down and let us through!
Now I get it.
Interesting.
Hurry up, or I'll snap
these girls' necks like twigs!
He'll do it, too! He's so
crazy not even we can stop him!
Are you upholders of justice gonna
let two helpless ladies die?
"Justice"
Chopper! That's cowardly! I misjudged you!
You shut up!
He's gonna kill us!
Please, do what he says!
No! No, no!
How many times do I have to say
it?!We have 1,000 mouths to feed!
We have to be efficient to make
it in time! You're too slow!
Oww...
You didn't need to hit us...
What's that? You got a problem?
I'll tell you right now-- save your big talk
until after you've proven yourself to me.
Now come here and help prepare!
Doesn't Jessica-san seem a bit wound up?
I guess the fact that that
cook was a pirate hit her hard...
Not to mention that the real new guys
are losers who're all talk...
That's enough talking there!
Yes! We're sorry!
Here, Billy! Try out my special sauce!
Pretty good, huh?!
Or not...
No, it's good...
But it's our usual flavor, isn't it?
Yes! Exactly!
Ever since I tasted his cooking,I've
felt like we're lacking something.
It's not bad or anything. It's just...
He had flair, I'm sad to say...
Damn it! What did he do differently?!
Jessica-sama.
What?
Could this be of use somehow?
Seems he left some recipe notes
before he left...
That pirate did?!
Recipes for his cooking?!
Oh, come to think of it, he...
I'll write down my recipes for you, then.
What about it?
Eh? Oh, I was hoping--since
he did leave it and all--
that we could maybe use it...
Don't be stupid!
Can you really proudly
call yourselves cooks of Navarone
if you accept help from a pirate?!
Who do you think our marines are
fighting as we speak?!
Don't you have any sense of pride?!
Umm...
Sorry to interrupt, but...
What the hell is this?!
Can't you even peel potatoes right?!
Our men always did it...
And it was always like this...
Listen! This is a battlefield!Even
a single potato is a vital resource!
Even shreds of potato skins are--
U-Uhh...
You two need to start all over with
dishwashing for a while!
Y-Yes, ma'am!
L-Lt. Commander...
I'll pull my men back.
All hands, lower your weapons and withdraw!
Stand down! All sniper squads,
lower your guns!
Lt. Commander...
We have no choice.
Wow, that worked well.
I hope so...
Huh?
I owe you one, Zoro...
H-Hey! Was that Kobato-san's voice just now?!
Y-You think so too?!
Mechao-san! What's going on?!
Kobato's being held hostage.
Eh?! Isn't that bad?!
Nah, don't worry about it.
I can see whether my daughter's
crying for real or not!
But my main worry...
...is them!
As you can see, we've opened the
way! Now release them!
Yes! It worked!
Hey! Chopper!
No! I'm not letting them go
until we can escape!
Damn you!
I've contacted Squadron
#17,as you ordered, sir.
Good. Have them standby for my signal.
I give in to your demands!
Get onto your ship!
He's a good sport. But
is he telling the truth?
Hey, hold on, you!
Nami. Chopper. Love cook.
Huh?!
Run to the ship on my signal.
Luffy, stretch your arms and get everyone
on board. Can you do that?
No problem...
I see...
Lt. Commander...
It doesn't matter. If anything
happens, I'll take responsibility.
If we let them escape now,all
of G8 will be shamed!
Whoops. Silly me.
What the--?! Don't scare us like that!
N-No!
You fool! He's on your side!
Crap! Nami-san!
Get to the ship somehow!
Let's do it, Captain!
I have no choice! All hands! Attack at once!
I knew that dunderhead would do this!
We have no choice!
Go, long-nose!
Hey, guys! We're gettin' on!
Are they alive?
And now for you and me!
What?!
Damn them! Don't let them
escape!All squadrons, open fire!
B-But there's still a hostage!
Warning shots are fine!
We did it, Merry!
Why can't you ever rescue us normally?!
That takes its toll on regular people!
All right, everyone! Get up!
Is that the pirate ship?!
What's the deal? Why won't they
order us to attack?!
I hear they have a hostage. Some
nurse they captured.
Pirates sure are nasty!
Oh, is that her?
Whoa, the hostage is giving orders!
This is one hell of a fiasco!Are
the ships ready yet?!
I'm having them hurry!
Dad!
Oh, Kobato.
You've had quite the unusual day!
You released the ship, didn't you?
You've caused a real mess.You'll
be punished for this, you know!
What father can sit idly by when
his daughter is about to get hurt?!
Kobato-san had been rescued!The
plan was underway!
What about the other one?!You
completely ignored her!
Officers have to learn not to
view people too lightly!
You could learn a thing or
two from Commander Jonathan!
Lt. Commander! About that hostage!
All sections believe that
she's part of the Straw Hat crew!
What?!
Stop right there, Inspector.
Where are you going?
I don't believe I'm required to
report my actions.
We are.
I see. Then please tell the commander this.
"I had a lot of fun."
Screw you!
I guess there's no point
in disguising myself now.
Why're we going along
the edge of this cliff?!
We'd have cannons on both sides if
we went through the middle!
This way, we only have to
worry about one side!
Where am I?!
Oh, he's awake!
Huh? When did I get on Merry?
After a bunch of this and that.
I see! Nami as a hostage! Nice!
Isn't it, though?!
You are good at tricking people.
But why'd the ship start moving on its own?
Oh, I bet it was the old maintenance guy.
Why's that?
I just get that feeling.
Nami-san dressed as a nurse is really nice!
We managed to get out, but what do
we do without maps or charts?
This is why I wanted to look
around the place first, you morons!
Robin-chan!
So cool!
So Major Shepherd was a fake?
I'm sorry, sir. She got away.
You're not at fault.
I just have a bad habit of
being weak around pretty women.
Huh?
Anyway, that makes six. We're currently
searching for the last one!
Oh, there's no need for that
now. I just found her.
Sir?
I contacted the medical room.
They said they aren't missing any nurses.
A map of this fortress!
I thought we might need it to escape.
You know the score!
You're the only one who's on my side, Sis!
A-Am I?
They're shooting at us!
I thought we were okay
cause we had a hostage!
They were bound to realize
the truth eventually!
Warships are coming after us!
There is no hostage! Everyone
on board is a Straw Hat member!
I repeat, all cannons,commence
firing consecutively!
That's this fortress'
gateway: the "Sea Gate."
Usopp, prepare the bow cannon!
Chopper! Don't get my orders wrong!
Got it!
If that's the only exit, our only choice
is to break through by force.
But I don't like that there are
more shallows than this chart shows.
That's unsuitable for a
port, so why is it here?
Something doesn't seem right...
It's all-clear on your end?That's
fine, then. Keep watch.
Reporting, sir. The pirate ship appears
to have reached the Sea Gate.
That makes it checkmate...
But it's a real shame. You
weren't careful enough, Straw Hat-kun.
Say what?! We don't have a single cannonball?!
Nope! We don't even have a
box to hold explosives!
That does seem only natural,given
that the navy confiscated the ship.
What're we gonna do?! We can't bust
through that gate like this!
Just means we gotta fight our way through.
All we gotta do is gain control of the
device that raises and lowers it.
Don't talk like it's easy!
Don't worry! I have a nice idea!
Target the enemy pirate ship!
Fire!
Gum-Gum Balloon!
Yes!
I see! I hadn't thought of that!
Nice, Luffy!
Now let's get--
We have no cannonballs or explosives?
Nami?!
Hey, what's wrong?!
Nami?
We've been had...
The treasure is gone!
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,on
the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give
in,even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared
of,we can overcome it
Where'd you disappear to, you damn pirates?!
Don't tell me you managed to
sneak past the cannoneers
and vanish beyond the horizon
in that short period?!
They won't try to escape.
There's no point without the gold!
Pirates leaving treasure behind is
shameful! Right rudder, full!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Pirate Ship Disappears!Fortress
Battle, Round #2"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!