Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made a raid on the Navy HQ to rescue
his brother, Ace who was to be executed!
But his struggle ended in vain
and the historic War of the
Best in Marineford has ended.
"Landing at the Maiden Island! The
Harsh Reality Falls upon Luffy!"
WEST BLUE
A pirate ship is approaching
Lascamp, West Blue!
But bases in that area have no ships!
The nearest bases outside of that area are...
The 80th division will send back-up!
This is South Blue checking
the location of the site!
Dammit!
I thought pirates would be
afraid of us after killing
Whitebeard and gaining victory!
Instead of laying low, they
are going wild everywhere!
What's gotten into them?
Pirates have made a raid on Lascamp!
We lost touch with the site! Send back-up!
I repeat, send back-up to Lascamp!
Load supplies! Let's head for the Grand Line!
Two weeks after the War of the Best,
people start to seeing
effects around the world.
Y-You can't come any further!
Don't come into our town!
You heard the news, didn't you?
Then you know that this island is
no longer Whitebeard's territory.
This symbol is meaningless now!
That's right! Whitebeard is dead!
Listen, and engrave this in your mind!
The man who takes control of
this island from today is me -
the pirate Brownbeard!
The war ended with the death of
Whitebeard and the victory of the Navy.
But contrary to what the Navy thought,
the situation has grown
tense all over the world.
Meanwhile, a short time ago,
Hancock, Jimbei and others decided
to head to the Maiden Island
to harbor the unconscious Luffy
and joined up with the Kuja's ship.
--Big Sis!
Snake Princess-sama!
Sorry that I made you worry,
Sandersonia, Marigold, and everyone!
Thank you for your warm greeting!
We are all so grateful for
your great work as a Warlord!
Alright then, this is it for my
role in supporting Straw boy.
Heehaw!
Do you mind if I leave the
rest up to you, Jimbei?
Yes. I can't swim as I want yet.
The least I can do is stay
here until he gets well.
I don't know how I can help him, though.
It was a curious turn of fate to meet you.
I agree.
Although we were both locked up in
the greatest prison in the world - Impel Down,
if it weren't for Luffy-kun,
we would have never met each
other at all I suppose.
We both tried really hard to keep up
with Straw boy at Marineford, didn't we?
It's hard to say goodbye to you
but I have sweet candies waiting
for me to come back to the kingdom.
Please take good care of Straw boy!
Bye, Straw Hat! Thank you for letting us out!
My dream can come true because of you!
Say "hi" to him when he wakes up!
--See you again if we have a chance!
--Hang in there!
You can't die, Straw Hat!
Okay, let's go!
To the New Kamas' home and our mecca!
To the Kamabakka Kingdom! Heehaw...
We have to head for the Maiden Island, too.
And the pirate ship that Luffy is on arrived
at the Maiden Island - Amazon Lily,
the female-only empire
where men are prohibited
and Kuja, the tribe of
female fighters, lives.
--Snake Princess-sama!
--Welcome back!
I'm so glad that the princess is safe!
There are men on the
strange ship in the back!
--Look! There are only women!
--It's true that it's a female-only island!
--They snuck into the ship! Unforgivable!
--W-Wait!
--Smells nice!
--I feel lightheaded!
This must be heaven!
Hey, you guys.
You gotta go back in, otherwise you'll die.
People, stop! They're not our enemy!
Snake Princess-sama!
Luffy is in that ship!
He suffered greatly, mentally and
physically, during the battle at Marineford
and he is hanging between life and death now.
Luffy's here?!
Ladies, carry Luffy to the Kuja
Castle as soon as possible!
--I'm gonna look after Luffy...
--Wait a minute, Snake Princess!
Granny Nyon!
It's fine if it's just Luffy.
But we can't allow those
men on that strange ship
to step foot onto the Maiden Island.
It's against our country's policy!
Then, let's just allow the
doctor to come with him so...
No!
We can't allow any men to come onto
the island, even if he is a doctor!
We have so many good doctors on this island!
Well, I don't care either way but...
...do you have the same medical
equipment and technology as my ship?
If his wound opens up, he's going to die.
Take Straw Hat-ya if you don't care about it.
Luffy's gonna die?!
If that happens by any chance...
Oh, I'm gonna... I'm gonna...
It's obvious that we can't save
Luffy-kun without this man.
If he can't come in, we have no choice.
We must go somewhere else.
Impossible! We'd be
attacked by the Sea Kings!
Even if we get away from them, the
Navy could find us at anytime!
What should we do?!
Oh, well... We only do
it as an exception but...
...you can stay in the area of the bay.
The Sea Kings won't attack you there.
Then, I'll stay with them
to look after Luffy...
No!
Damn Granny Nyon! You just
keep saying "no" to me!
Luffy! I hope you'll get better soon!
Looking at Snake Princess-sama,
I can tell that Luffy is
in critical condition.
Luffy...
Two weeks have passed.
Law and others are staying in the bay...
...to provide Luffy with treatment.
How much longer do we have to
stay in such a small space...
Yeah, the only thing to look forward to is...
--Guys, sorry to keep you waiting!
--It's a meal time.
Finally!
Here it is.
--The only consolation is that the food is good!
--I agree!
--Here you go!
--Thank you...
Please don't push and wait for your turn.
Aphelandra!
Don't talk to men!
Luffy is the exception because
of the princess' orders.
Don't forget!
Okay!
Come on, it's no big deal!
Right, Aphelandra-chan?
I'm not gonna say it again!
We're sorry!
Excuse me.
Is Luffy awake?
I see.
It's up to Straw Hat-ya's spirit.
Whether he's willing to live or not.
--Margaret, let's go already!
--I'm coming!
I'm sorry! Take good care of Luffy!
Margaret, how many times do I have
to tell you not to talk to them?!
I'm sorry!
Big Sis...
Luffy...
You've always been like this, Luffy!
You've never even listened to me...
...and always done such crazy things!
Don't do it...
Don't do it!
--Stop it, Straw Hat!
--You wanna destroy the ship?!
Ace...
Luffy-kun!
Where's Ace?!
This is dangerous! Calm down, Straw Hat!
What is going to happen
if we leave him like that?
Well, it's simple. Like
I said when we got here,
if his wound opens up, he will die.
Yes, now is the chance!
--Let me go, dammit!
--Stay still, Straw Hat!
--Shut up! I'm looking for Ace!
--I told you that "Fire Fist" is...
I said "let me go"!
Where's Ace?!
--Ace!!
--Damn! He's out of control!
--It's Luffy!
--We got to tell Snake Princess-sama!
Snake Princess-sama! Snake Princess-sama!
Luffy woke up!
--Luffy-sama?!
--Really?!
I'm glad. I wanna see him right away!
You can't, Snake Princess!
Everybody wants to see him.
You can't discipline your people if
you allow yourself to go and see him.
Men are prohibited on this island.
We let strange men stay at the bay area
and that's enough of an exception for us!
I know, but...
Before that, Big Sis, you
need to eat something.
That's right, Big Sis! You've
barely eaten since you got back!
That's right! Luffy must be very hungry, too!
Fix a lot of great dishes
that will give him energy!
Yes, we'd be happy to!
I'm gonna help you! Ladies, let's do it now!
Yes, Snake Princess-sama!
I should just let her do that. She
just wants to fix some food...
Then I'm gonna take them to him!
So you're going?!
We promised that when he gets
well, we would invite Luffy alone.
Wait for that moment!
I can't! I am an empress!
Don't tell me what to do!
I said no!
The most important thing is
the hereditary policy of this country!
Honestly! You're infected
by such a strong virus!
I can't believe that the fearful
pirate empress has become love sick!
However, he must have been like a small ant
diving into a tempest at
Impel Down and the Navy HQ.
It must have been an act of God to let
him live and be brought back here.
I wonder what God expects from him.
--Hey, pass me the wrench.
--Okay, here you go.
Hey, do you think you can fix the ship?
Yeah, I'll manage.  That aside,
where did Straw Hat go?
Jimbei is gone, too.
I don't know.
Well, I heard that if a man enters the
Maiden Island, he's gonna be turned to stone
but maybe it's worth dying for.
According to Aphelandra-chan, not
all women were there at the port.
The female-only island that I dreamed
of! I wish I could take a look inside!
You're gonna die, you idiot.
I wonder if there are female bears...
It's Maiden Island!
I'm sorry.
Only humans! There are only humans!
I'm really sorry!
Where am I?
Maybe it was all a dream...
I'm sorry, Luffy...
I couldn't make it all the way.
Go away! Go away!
Luffy!
No!
Go away! Go away!
If I don't escape death...
I'm sorry but could you
look after my brother?
The war is over!
Ace-san is...
Don't say it! Don't say anything!
I already pinched myself
hard enough to rip my skin!
If it were a dream, I should've woken by now!
It's not a dream, is it?
Ace is really dead, isn't he?!
Yes, he is dead!
Hey grandpa, who is Ace?
Oh, he is...
...the guy who will become your brother!
Luffy! I'll see you at the
top of the pirates' world!
Come to the top!
Ace!!
Next week is a special
collaboration with Toriko!
Those Barbecue Pigs are scary!
Whew, I'm stuffed! That was tasty!
Apparently there are lots
more of these things!
Really?!
That's what Toriko said! I wanna go home!
Okay! We're going with Toriko!
What?!
Next week, the special Toriko x
One Piece collaboration episode!
"The Strongest Tag-Team! Luffy
and Toriko's Hard Struggle!"
Don't miss it!