Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight fierce battles
against other tough contenders from the New World.
Premier Hachis Hash!
Pentachromatic Strings!
Overheat!
Room!
Law, eh?
Everyone!
I want you to take him
and head for Zou!
The Navy ship is flying towards us!
Doflamingo is coming from that way!
Meteorites?!
Room!
Hey, Law!
I realize we have
to carry Caesar as far as possible.
It's clear we have to leave here now.
But I thought Dressrosa was just a waypoint.
Our main purpose was killing Kaido of the Four Emperors,
wasn't it?
Aren't you getting too hung up
on Doflamingo?
Get ready for Coup de Burst!
I'm afraid that I have to break up my alliance
with the Straw Hats now.
When I joined forces with them,
my only purpose was to use them
to stop the manufacture of SMILEs.
Even if I can't kill you right now,
Kaido will kill you sooner or later
once you lose all the SMILEs.
I see.
So you're gonna sacrifice
yourself to kill me.
I want to see how the world falls into a mess
after you die,
but more importantly,
I want to make you pay for what you did 13 years ago.
Joker!
"Rebecca's Special Attack!
Back-to-the-Water Dance!"
You want to make me pay?
For what I did 13 years ago?
You know what I'm talking about.
What are you gonna do with Giolla?
You know what kind of family we are.
He's right, Law!
I don't mind sacrificing myself for the Young Master!
You better run as far as you can.
I'm not gonna leave
the Young Master and run!
I don't need you.
I don't need you here. Just go.
Y-Yes, sir!
I saw Black Foot earlier.
Which means our plan is not going so well.
You lost your trump card, Caesar.
You will lose the SMILE factory
while you're fighting me here.
This will be your end.
It is unreasonable for you to hold a grudge against me,
Law!
It's not a grudge.
I've been living my life until today...
...to attain that man's
long-cherished ambition!
OFF THE COAST OF DRESSROSA
We barely got away
from Doflamingo but...
...will Tra-guy be okay?
Hey, guys!
Are you keeping a lookout?
This is Brook here! It looks all serene
from a 45-degree angle!
You gotta look in all directions!
All right, ma'am!
A 360-degree spin!
I see some clouds now.
I can't believe that guy can move through the air
by attaching strings to clouds!
Brook!
Don't miss even a slight movement.
Oh, I don't know
since my eyes are like...
...knotholes!
If he comes flying towards us again,
I'll generate strong wind and blow the clouds away!
Then he can't chase us.
That's a good idea.
Only Nami-san could've come up with it.
But I wonder if it's really okay for us to head to Zou
like Law told us.
We were under attack by the Navy and Doflamingo
at that moment so we needed to get away but...
In any case, you guys gotta protect Robin-chan
even if it costs your life! Okay?
Clank.
How were they?
My precious Robin-chan is
with Franky and Usopp.
Then, if Zoro and Kin'emon can meet Luffy,
everything's okay, right?
Yeah, but Zoro is bad at directions.
I don't know if he can make it to the Colosseum.
Well, Kin'emon's with him so he'll be fine.
I wonder if Tra-guy is okay.
His plan was not to kill Doflamingo
but let Kaido of the Four Emperors take care of him.
As long as he focuses on getting away,
he'll be fine.
Uh-huh.
What's the matter, Momo?
You turned into a dragon, again.
I-I thought back and I can't stop shaking.
That man who flies...
You mean Doflamingo.
I saw him
the last time I came to Dressrosa.
What?
Young Master, you're gonna kill him!
What's your problem?
Who are you?
You're a gladiator, aren't you?
Who wants to see
you guys running around?
If you can't chop anybody up,
at least get yourself sliced and show people your blood!
No matter how great
his or her personality is,
every human has a cruel side
and they all get excited when they see blood.
Blood and death.
That's entertainment!
Pull yourself together!
What a bunch of scum.
Don't let them fight like that again.
Y-Yes, Young Master!
Kin'emon! Momonosuke!
Oh, Kanjuro!
I found a harbor.
Let's steal a ship there.
This country is too dangerous!
I just realized Kanjuro is held captive
by that horrible man
and I can't stop worrying.
I hope you're all right, Kanjuro!
Why are you looking like that?!
Depends on what they want
from you guys
but often, hostages wouldn't be treated so badly
so he's gonna be alright.
You're not really concerned!
You're thinking about something else, aren't you?!
Oh, which reminds me,
Violet-chan said she'd be alright, too!
I'll be alright.
I talked to my friend
and the Government will protect me.
Really?
Yes. I guess they've arrived at the harbor
to pick me up by now.
Believe me.
Okay. It's too bad
that I can't come with you
but as long as you're safe...
Thank you.
I think I can go on thanks to you.
Well... But if you wanna thank me,
you can kiss me on my cheek...
Oh no!
Your ship is getting attacked by the Fighting Fish!
What is a Fighting Fish?
You better go help them!
Nami-san!
--Damn, Rebecca, that little bitch!
--She's so persistent as always!
Just go to hell already, you little tramp!
Horse-san!
Yes?
Take me to the palace!
Okay!
DRESSROSA - THE CORRIDA COROSSEUM
V-V-V...
Vice Captain!
What? Vice Captain?
What are you talking about?
Y-Y-You're Zoro-senpai, aren't you?
Luffy-senpai's right-hand man?
What? Well...
Looks like you're not
disguising yourself too well.
Let me just say this. I'm not Zoro!
Y-You don't have to hide it!
I also know Luffy-senpai is fighting in this Colosseum
under the name "Lucy"!
What?!
I-I-I'm talking
to Zoro-senpai like it's nothing!
I-I'm so thrilled!
Why are you crying?!
How do you know
about Luffy and my name?!
I'be albayz bween your ban!
Huh?
He can't even have a conversation.
I gotta say it!
I finally get to meet him!
A-A-Auto...
--Stop crying!
--Y-Yes!
I just got scolded by Zoro-senpai!
C-Can I have your autograph?!
--I said it!
--My autograph?
If I bring Luffy-senpai here,
can I have your autograph?
You can do that for me?
I'll be counting on you!
H-He just said
he'll be counting on me, didn't he?
Zoro-senpai said he'll be counting on me!
Why do you have to cry again?
What are you doing?! Just go!
Th-Th...
Th?
Then!
Wait for me there!
I'm gonna bring him at the risk of my life!
He doesn't have to risk his life for it...
Z-Zoro-senpai said
he'll be counting on me!
H-He's really trusting me!
It feels like...
...I became the right-hand man of
Luffy-senpai's right-hand man!
It's great!
It's amazing!
I've got to do this right!
The battle royal at the Corrida Colosseum!
The heated match of Block D!
Tough contenders are attacking fiercely
and the others are getting eliminated one after another!
The one that's standing out among them is...
...the military captain of the Scorchistan -
Rolling Logan!
ROLLING LOGAN - A MILITARY CAPTAIN OF
SOUTHERN KINGDOM OF SCORCHISTAN
Let's see what happens if I go all out!
Let's see what happens if I roll!
What you're seeing is
what Rolling Logan is famous for!
It's a special attack - Rolling Cradle!
With that high-speed rolling,
his enemy's equilibrium gets thrown off!
And his finishing move is...
Let's see!
The Leg Split!
The crowds are getting all excited!
Oh? On the other hand...
They're fighting quietly
in contrast to Logan's showy style!
This is the great example of
ill weeds growing apace!
The cursed princess - Rebecca!
The crowd is jeering loudly!
You can do better than that
as a human!
Bring out all your power!
Get up, Rebecca!
I don't wanna do it anymore!
I don't wanna hurt anybody!
Even if you don't want to do so,
you have to become stronger,
Rebecca!
Soldier-san!
Y-You tramp!
Dammit! She's so persistent!
That's Rebecca's favorite move -
the Back-to-the-Water Dance!
You have to become stronger,
Rebecca!
She takes advantage of her
opponents' advancing momentum
and draws them to the edge of the ring.
Then she holds her sword in front of her
with her back against the water.
Finally, she moves unbelievably fast
utilizing her opponents' moves
and lets them fall into the water!
That's it!
That is her Back-to-the-Water Dance!
Yes! Remarkably, Rebecca has never hurt anybody
in all the battles that she took part in!
I didn't know
she used the Observation Haki!
Haki?
She has also never been
wounded by anybody
and she won it all by letting opponents fall out of the ring!
She has never been defeated!
She's quite a fighter!
Go, Rebecca!
Her fighting style is not unbeautiful
and I don't dislike it to be honest!
But would it work in this competition?!
Tough contenders from various countries
all have different fighting style!
They're not your ordinary gladiator!
Let's see what happens
if I break your bones!
Ill Weed-chan!