Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
Princess Vivi, in her attempt
to prevent any fighting,
arrived at the Yuba oasis, but the
rebel army was nowhere to be seen.
And, at long last, Baroque Works'
Officer Agents sprung into action.
The clash between the royal and
rebel armies is close at hand!
"Luffy vs. Vivi! The Tearful Vow
to Put Friends on the Line"
Excellent work today, my fellows!
So let's hit the hay for now and
regain our strength for tomorrow!
Nighty-night!
You've been sleeping this whole time!
Why, you...
Don't compare me with you monsters!
Now you've done it!
Besides, you win today's
laziness award, Blue-Nose!
It's not my fault I can't stand the heat!
Sanji-san. That's my--
Yes. I thought you might have a
hard time sleeping alone tonight...
And what do you think you're doing there?
Oh, that took some nerve.
Which one of you is spoiling for a fight?!
Do you guys not understand
the point of a nap?!
Alright! You're in trouble now!
Hey, old guy. There's still no
water. My throat's bone-dry...
How can you live in a place
like this? This is bad...
There'll be water.
The Yuba oasis is still alive.
Yuba, you see, can't be
beaten by some lousy sand!
I'll dig it back up
as many times as it takes!
This is very important land
that the king left in my hands.
Oh! Okay! Then let's dig!
Oh! Wait! Stop!
Don't re-fill the hole I just dug!
Are you trying to fill holes?!
No, I'm digging.
No, the sand you're digging out
is going into the hole I dug,
so I'm trying to say that all my
hard work will be for nothing!
Oh.
Oh! So it's a mystery hole!
No, it's not!
Come to think of it, the sand
has stopped flying this way.
All this, in such a short time?!
Even though he must be
exhausted from his long trek...
May you have a nice rest tonight.
Meat...
Pleasant dreams.
Gimme a break!
Just how long are you
going to make us wait?!
At least offer me an Octopar!
Don't make me dance! I'm a swan!
Don't make me spin around!
Mr. 2. Just wait quietly.
Seriously! You imbecile! Imb!
You too, Miss Merry Christmas.
You make my back hurt!
I guess there's no chance
of you all getting along.
Though that won't be necessary anyway.
Miss All-Sunday...
Thank you for coming all
the way to this gathering
in the town of Rainbase, where the
people dream of winning it big.
Welcome to Raindinners,
the largest casino of all!
Could you skip the formalities and
cut to the chase, Miss All-Sunday?
Yes. I'll get right to the point.
Yeah! Get started! Started! Start!
But first, I'll need to introduce
you to our company's boss,
whose face you still don't know.
As his secret proxy, I've been the
one who's had you work until now,
but there is no longer any need for that.
I take it you understand...
At last, the time has come...
...for Operation Utopia.
Crocodile?!
This will be Baroque Works' final operation.
It would seem you know who he is...
at least on the outside, anyway.
Of course we do! But why one of
the Seven Warlords of the Sea?!
Talk about a real big shot!
We've actually been the
underlings of a pirate?!
You're our boss?
Dissatisfied?
Not exactly dissatisfied,
but the Seven Warlords are pirates
with government permission to plunder.
Why would you need to
own a company like this?
What I want is neither money nor status.
Military might.
Military might?
Allow me to explain in good order...
...my true objective
and the whole picture of
Baroque Works' final operation.
Something like that really
exists in this country?
And we're going to steal the
entire country along with it?
This is giving me such chills!
In short, these assignments of ours
are the final pieces of this enormous plan?
That's right.
Every job you've performed
since Baroque Works was founded
has been a part of this operation.
And those letters are your final orders.
At last the time has come for the
Alabasta Kingdom to disappear.
Once each of you has
fulfilled your mission,
this kingdom of Alabasta will wreck itself...
...and, with nowhere to go,
the rebel and royal armies
will tragically fall into
Baroque Works' hands.
In a single night, this land
will truly become our utopia.
Operation Utopia is Baroque Works'
last and greatest operation.
Failure is not an option.
We begin at noon tomorrow.
Understood!
I wish you luck.
I must ask that you hold off with
this Operation Utopia of yours.
Mr. 3. How did you get into
this secret underground room?
Mr. 3! Where the heck did
you come crawling out of?!
I'll get rid of you,
just like I was ordered to!
Wait, Mr. 2.
Crawling out of? How rude.
I merely stuck by your side
since the Spiders Café...
...as I took a ride on Bunchi's car.
Nice to meet you, Boss.
I've humbly come here
to ask for another chance.
It was only natural that you
be sent to take my life, Mr. 2,
after I failed to accomplish
the task given to me.
That is why I changed course slightly
and headed for the Spiders Café,
where we agents are stationed.
Failed to accomplish your task?
What are you talking about?
You know. H-How I let the Straw
Hats and Princess Vivi escape...
Escape, you say?!
Are you saying they're still alive?!
What did you say on the Transponder Snail?!
Did you not say you took care
of the pirates and Vivi?!
Transponder Snail?
What are you talking about?
I never used a Transponder Snail
while on Little Garden.
What?!
Heya. You've called the Damn Restaurant.
You want reservations?
This isn't good.
So that's why the Unluckies
haven't returned from the island.
So, I assume you at least
got rid of one or two?
N-No, actually...
B-But there was an
inaccuracy with the information!
She actually had four pirate escorts,
and there-- and there was a
long-nosed man with them and--
Damn you!
Zero-chan! Come on,
explain what's going on!
None of it makes any sense!
I... I met them!
I ran into these guys on my way here!
What?!
Him! Him!
Her!
Him!
And him, right?!
And...
...this is Miss Wednesday,
who is this kingdom's Princess Vivi!
Meaning they were actually our enemy?!
Yes. They know my identity.
They will interfere with
the operation if left alone.
And Mr. 3.
It seems they have gained one person
and one animal, just as you say.
Setting the pet aside,
it seems we can safely assume
that Vivi and the other four
are already here in Alabasta.
Mr. 2. Make photographs of
the faces you just displayed.
B-But, Boss!
I swear that I will take care of that
crew and Vivi with my own two--!
Quiet, you damn fool!
Mr. 3...
Mr. 3!
Do you know why I gave you your rank?!
In terms of fighting skill alone,
even Mr. 4 outclasses you, Mr. 3!
It was because of the underhanded,
contemptible tenacity you have
for accomplishing your duties!
You've really let me down!
W-What is that?!
H-He's drying up!
W-Water...
Water...
Have all the water you want.
It's feeding time.
What is this place? Underwater?
I-It's almost like an aquarium...
A b-bananagator!
That runt's caused me much trouble...
He just doesn't know how to stay dead!
Listen, now! Take a good look at these five!
They're bent on stopping the rebellion.
If we leave them alone,
eventually they will come to us!
But, Zero-chan.
Even if she is the princess,
do you really think she can stop
the rebellion at this point?
Unfortunately, the rebel leader
Koza and Princess Nefertari Vivi
are apparently close childhood friends.
It's a swell of 700,000.
Even if it can't be easily stopped,
she can bring confusion to the rebel army.
I've already had many
Billions join their ranks.
The fact that there's
been no word from them
must mean they still haven't
taken any direct action yet.
Whatever the cost,
Vivi and the rebel army must
not be allowed to make contact
before the operation.
Miss All-Sunday.
Yes?
Given the circumstances, I don't
mind using Transponder Snails.
Contact the Billions in Nanohana.
Tell them to kill them on sight!
Do not let Princess Vivi
and the pirates into Katorea!
Vivi and Koza must not be allowed to meet!
Yes. Right away.
Now you get going, too! You don't
want to be late for the party!
Our utopia is near at hand.
I don't want any further trouble.
Please leave it to us, Boss!
You can count on us!
Go enjoy yourselves!
I'm sorry for being so unseemly, Vivi-chan.
No, you're not unseemly at all!
Well, we should be off!
Oh, Luffy-kun. Take this with you.
Wow! Water!
Water!
You found some?!
Last night, just after you
fell asleep while digging,
I reached a moist layer of sand.
That water is the moisture
I managed to extract from it!
Oh! That sounds kind of
complicated, but thanks!
It's genuine Yuba water!
I'm sorry it's all I could get...
I'll drink it with care!
Luffy! What're you doing?!
Luffy?
What's wrong, Luffy-san?
I quit.
Huh?
You "quit"?
Luffy-san... What do you mean?
C'mon, Luffy!
We don't have time to put up with
your whims, you know! Get up!
Aren't we going back?
Yeah.
If we don't go back to Katorea the
way we came and stop the revolt,
a million citizens here are gonna
clash and things'll get ugly quick!
This is for Vivi-chan! Now let's go!
That's boring.
Say what?!
Vivi!
Yes?
I wanna kick Crocodile's ass!
If we stop the people rebelling,
will that stop Crocodile?
Besides, we won't be able to
do anything in Katorea anyway.
We're pirates, you see. Things
are better off without us around.
He can really get straight to the
point without thinking sometimes...
Despite being Luffy.
T-That's--!
You want it so nobody dies in this fight.
None of the citizens, and none of us!
Even when we're up against
a Warlord of the Sea
and a million people are going wild,
you hope everyone will stay safe and sound.
Don't you think that's too soft-hearted?
Hold on, Luffy! At least show
some sympathy for Vivi!
Wait, Nami-san.
But...
And what's wrong with thinking that?
What's wrong with not
wanting people to die?!
People die.
Stop talking like that!
Say that again and I'll make you pay!
That's exactly what
we're trying to stop here!
The rebel army, the royal army,
and the people of this kingdom
haven't done anything wrong!
So why do people have to die
when it's all Crocodile's fault?!
Then why are you putting
your life on the line?!
Whoa, Luffy! You're going too far!
Damn it, Luffy!
Just one look at this kingdom
and even I can tell...
Tell what?!
...what most needs to be done!
Yuba, you see, can't be
beaten by some lousy sand!
As if putting your single life
on the line is enough!
Then what should I be putting on the line?!
I can't let him get away with this!
I don't have--!
I don't have anything else
that I can put on the line...
At least try putting all of our
lives on the line together!
Aren't we friends?!
Aren't we friends?
Oh, you can cry those kinds of tears...
We will stop the rebellion!
I know you actually hate this
and want to beat him up the most!
Now tell me...
...where Crocodile is!
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I scoop up my hands, and the sand
and time that spills from them
show me that this is what
I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
no one knows about
Eh?! The Navy's chasing them!
So why are they running this way?!
Say! Tony-kun hasn't come back yet!
Leave him! He'll manage!
The Navy's here!
You're the one bringing them here!
This isn't good!
Baroque Works is gonna spot us!
I think it's too late for that.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battlefront of Alabasta!
Rainbase, the City of Dreams"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!