Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy
whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached
the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates
who are looking to destroy
the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find
themselves caught up in the
turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
Straw Hat! Please!
We don't need the past!
Reset our history to zero!
Wipe out those phantoms who shut
the island away from the sun!
Bring the Fish-Man Island back...
...to zero!
Brother-hoshi.
As long as you let me handle
it my way, don't worry.
Our minds were made up when
we arrived at the plaza that,
along with Jimbei, we wouldn't
let anyone harm the island!
Leave it all up to us, Brother-hoshi!
We're friends, right?
You can't get away from me!
Hordy-sama!
Yowahoshi!
Stay with me! I promise
I won't let you be hurt!
Okay!
"Luffy's All-out Attack! Red Hawk Blasts!"
Oh? Huh?
I lost him.
The guy in stripes.
Where did he go?
Fool! I'm here!
You're gonna be dead before you notice!
Take this!
Camouflage Carpet!
Huh?
I heard a voice around here!
Z-Zeo-san got...
...Stabbed!
How was that, Skeleton?
My weapon-destroying technique
called Body Sword Crush made...
...the tip of your sword crumble...
I stabbed you.
He still has too much pride!
Just think that way and get defatted...
Get defeated!
This time, he...
...Stumbled.
Shh! Don't say that.
You just fumbled your words.
Hey!
You dumbhead!
Oh? Oh?! I lost him again! Where did he go?!
Hidden Flail...
...66 Neck!
I learned something...
...in the last 2 years,
about the true power of
the Revive-Revive Fruit.
When people die,
their souls must go to the next world.
But my soul,
in order to keep its existence in this world,
radiates a strong energy almost
like other corporeal beings.
It enables me to rock a crowd
of people better than anybody
else when I play music.
I can draw them into my world and
even create illusions for them.
Even when my soul leaves my
body, people can see me clearly.
I certainly exist in this world.
I did it!
I took down one of the Straw Hats!
No, you didn't.
What keeps me alive in this world
is neither bodily organs...
...nor muscles.
It's my...
...soul!
What?!
Oh! I've got a lot of spunk! All right!
He's pretending he wasn't surprised!
Did you get it?
So, in other words, as long
as my bones don't get damaged,
your attack can't pierce me to the bone.
And,
this sword cane which the Longarm
Tribe sharpened for me -
it's called Soul Solid!
Its soulful slash will make you feel
the cold air from the land of the dead!
It's the "Freezing Sword"!
Have a good look!
That's awesome, Brook!
The Freezing Sword - how cool is that?!
That's my Soul King!
Oh, thank you very much.
Oh! Oh no! Dammit!
I lost him again!
I have to keep it up too!
Everybody's gained skills
to go on to the New World!
Concerning your friends?
Don't worry!
I'll make sure you all get
drowned in the deep sea!
Special Attack!
Fireball Cutter!
Green Star!
Whoa! Ouch, ouch, ouch!
You bastard!
Looks like you're a burden to the Straw Hats!
You didn't hit me at all!
Don't rush around, mole shark.
I'm a cookie-cutter shark!
I just...
...finished setting a trap!
Luffy-sama!
Hordy-sama is coming!
You wouldn't let anyone harm the island?
Give it your best shot!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
...Bazooka!
It's not working!
Luffy-sama!
It's no use, Straw Hat.
We were granted power from heaven!
Give it up! You can't stop the Noah now!
And you will lose everything!
No, I'm gonna finish the
whole thing with this one!
You can't finish anything!
Drop dead!
Second Gear - Armament!
I'll never...
...let anyone die again!
Gum-Gum...
I'm gonna bite your arm off!
...Red Hawk!
Luffy-sama!
Straw Hat!
He...
He did it!
Straw Hat Luffy-san defeated...
...Hordy, the captain of
the New Fish-Man Pirates,
finally!!
It's not over yet!
Yowahoshi, take me to the Noah!
Okay!
At your full speed!
What?! No way! Captain Hordy lost?!
What's gonna happen to the Noah?!
This is it! For the island and all of us!
Run!
Zeo-san, please! You know this island is...
Don't be fooled!
Captain Hordy was chosen by heaven!
Some loser human could never beat him!
B-But if the Noah destroys the island,
we're getting nothing anyway!
Death is another way to get revenge.
Hate humans even in death!
Tragedies will become our flesh and blood.
And our grudge will never go away.
Somebody will take it over
and get our revenge for us!
There he is.
Captain Hordy and all
you officers are insane!
Humans made us insane!
Stop running!
Direct all of your anger toward humans-bogon!
Humans are responsible for every single
disaster that Fish-Men meet-zugan!
Are humans that terrible?
That's ridiculous!
I mean, when you look at history,
humans did horrible things to Fish-Men...
Stop!
Madam Sharley!
See it with your own eyes!
In the plaza and up in the sky,
humans are fighting against the
pirates from the Fish-Man District!
Is he a human, too?
There are some strange ones but...
...you have to see it with your own eyes!
If you don't, you have no
right to say something!
No matter what happens,
you have to look at things
with an impartial eye.
Those of you who won't fight
to the death will get
killed by me in order to leave
your hatred toward humans behind!
You can't do that to your own people!
Oh, that was close! Thank you, Skeleton Mask!
It's you again.
You've never died before so don't
talk like you know all about it!
Get killed and leave hatred
behind? How ridiculous!
Nothing is left behind when you die!
All you can leave behind is your bones!
Very persuasive!
Thank you!
I don't like people who
devalue the lives of others!
I can't even stand their smell!
Even though I don't have a nose!
It's you guys who are devaluing lives.
It's so impressive that none
of you is trying to escape
but you humans will die once
the Noah hits the island!
Although I can't tell if
you're a human or not!
Our captain - Luffy will become
the King of the Pirates someday.
And he said it clearly.
That he wouldn't let anyone
harm the island and
we can leave it all up to him!
I believe in him so there
is nothing to worry about.
Now, I'll do my part.
I won't let you disappear
in front of my eyes again!
Although I don't have eyes!
How's this? Surprised?
Yeah, that's enough. Oh, I'm so surprised!
Oh yeah?
Now, shall we finish this up, Jimbei?
Yes, let's do it.
Hey, wait! I've lost my swords.
How can I fight now?
Don't ask me.
How annoying!
I'm gonna end this fight by
using a daring technique!
One, two...
On the third step, you will get
shot by me and that'll be it!
Don't talk nonsense!
Stop dreaming your stupid dream!
You weakling! Are you crying sour grapes?!
Oh boy, I'm losing my edge.
I used to bluff better in the past.
But now, I can actually do these things.
What the hell is that monster?!
Was it here before?!
Oh, that's...
Chopper!
Th-That little guy got bigger suddenly!
Hey! Whoa, whoa!
You didn't have to go out of control!
I'm okay, Usopp.
What's wrong?
L-Look at that!
H-Hordy is...
I can't believe it!
Luffy-sama!
Let's go!
There is air!
The Straw Hat crew finally
demonstrates its true power...
...and attempts to overpower
the New Fish-Man Pirates.
Meanwhile, Hordy, having derived
immeasurable power from the Energy Steroids...
...and the severely wounded Luffy...
...grapple in a final battle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Coming to an End! The Final
Decisive Battle against Hordy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!