Edited at https://subtitletools.com
We're not gonna let even
an ant pass through this gate!
Gatekeeper giants Oimo and Kashii
showed up at the main island front gate
and stood in the way of the
Franky Family. However...
Timber Hitch Tug!
Ow...! Ow, ow, ow, ow...!
...the situation was reversed
by Paulie and Zambai,
and the gate was about to be broken open.
Meanwhile, Luffy, who had already
passed the main island front gate,
was being slowed down by an
overwhelming number of soldiers.
Five are down?! So it was
actually just five guards?!
Geez... You can't even make a report properly?
Five... hundred guards...
"Tower of Law"
Lucci and the others,
with Franky and Robin in tow,
headed to the Tower of Law,
where Spandam was waiting for them.
Welcome back! Lucci, Kaku, Blueno, and Kalifa!
That's sexual harassment.
Just calling your name is?!
Anyway, you've done a great
job over the past five years.
Oh, that's right... This isn't really a
reward for your efforts or anything,
but I do have something I wanna give you.
Well, I'll do that later.
So, in any case, let me meet...
the "hope" of the entire world!
And the Straw Hats on Rocketman
were getting ready to charge in.
Now, guys! It's time!
Let's go, shall we?
Samurai-man! Take care of the iron fence!
Leave it to me.
Go in already!
You too!
Coo coo?
Chapapa... Chapa!
I feel on top of the world!
I'm surprised to see you survived that
accident eight years ago, Cutty Flam.
And also... the woman whom
the world considers dangerous
and has been trying to capture, Nico Robin...
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Find a Way Out!
Rocketman Takes Flight!"
I'm feeling great! However...
...unfortunately, the public doesn't know
how truly valuable and great
what we've achieved today is.
It'll be several years...
...before it actually comes to be known.
In my opinion, the justice those old geezers
in the current Government dole out
is too lenient!
Goals can't be achieved without sacrifice.
We're working in order to
ensure peace for all of humanity.
It's fine if we have to sacrifice some
fools in our way to maintain peace...
...including that fishman who didn't
hand over what we told him to...
He deserved to be killed...
as a rebel against justice.
He deserved it. He did!
You're crazy!
Tom-san put his life on the line
to protect the blueprints
because idiots like you exist!
Wh-What're you guys doing?! Help me! Hey!
Ow, ow, ow, ow! Ow!
Kumadori!
Yoyoi!
Roger!
Hurry up and help me, hey! Hey!
Now... now... now...!
Yoi!
Yo...!
Ow!
Oh? Where did Chief Spandam go?
I... I'm here. I'm right here. H-H-Hey...
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
Gum-Gum... Whip!
Giant Scythe!
Bell!
Mallet!
Bazooka!
Gum-Gum... Stamp!
This is the main island, reporting to Chief!
Chief Spandam! Please come in!
It's no good! I can't get through!
Does he have the receiver off again?
Not again, at a critical time like this, seriously!
Hey, where did Straw Hat go?
He's right underneath you!
What?! Right underneath us?!
Attack him at once!
There he is! He's down there!
Dammit! I've been boxed in!
Gum-Gum... Volcano!
Th-The wall is... The wall is falling!
Get out of here!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Ah! Watch out!
Chief Spandam! Please come in!
Please advise us on countermeasures!
We can't stop Straw Hat Luffy!
Straw Hat Luffy is headed to the courthouse!
Strengthen defenses! Hurry up!
Be quiet!
What's this ruckus?!
You guys woke me up!
Ch-Chief Justice!
"'Three-Headed Baskerville'
Chief Justice, Enies Lobby"
That's right! As a matter of fact,
I am the Chief Justice of Enies Lobby!
On the left, I am Left Baskerville!
On the right, I am Right Baskerville!
And in the center, I am "Central Freeway"!
Say what?!
Ch-Chief Justice! A pirate is going
on a rampage on the main island,
but they said that they can't
get in touch with Chief Spandam.
Please give us instructions on his behalf!
A pirate! Pirates are guilty!
Hmm...
Oh, come on. Why don't
we make him not guilty?
Hmm... Then, let's split the
difference and give him...
...the death penalty!
Say what?!
There's trouble, Chief Justice!
We got a report that Kashii was taken out
at the main island front gate
by the Straw Hat's comrades
and that Oimo is losing, too!
What?! Don't let them past the gate!
Send 100 Watchdogs immediately!
Yes, sir!
Dammit! The promised five minutes is up!
This is bad! Hurry up and open
up the path for Rocketman!
I'm not gonna let you through this gate!
We unlocked the gate!
Now we can push the doors open!
What?! Shoot!
All right! Good going!
Go!
Don't touch this gate!
Rope Action!
Top Knot! Take this!
Whoa! Just what you'd expect
from a Galley-La foreman!
What?! This is just a rope!
Franky Family! Pull it!
Yeah!
Just leave it to us! Let's go, Sodom!
Gomorrah! Grab the rope!
Charge into the gate!
H-Hey! Hold on a sec! I'm feeling dizzy!
Push the doors!
Look! The doors are...!
The doors are opening!
What's Oimo doing?!
A little bit more!
The gate has been opened!
"Main Gate"
H-Hey...! Hey!
Hey...
That's... a sea train?
What's going on?
What?! It's rushing straight towards us!
Don't tell me they're trying
to jump onto the main island...!
Can't be! There's no way they
can jump over that iron fence!
Hurry up! Don't let them charge in!
Close the gate!
Hey, granny!
Hm? What is it?
Change of plans! Have the
train go as fast as it can!
Roger!
Guys, looks like we're changing our plan.
The samurai-man says that everyone
should hold on tight to the car.
He said that!
Hold on tight?!
Why?
Hey, idiot swordsman! Did something happen?!
They closed the main gate.
What?!
What?! This is terrible!
We're gonna crash into the gate!
What're we gonna do?! What're we gonna do?!
--Dodge it, Kokoro-san!
--What're we gonna do?!
Don't worry. There's a way.
That's our Zoro!
Hit the fence with a thrust, frog!
What?!
Ribbit!
Ribbit, ribbit, ribbit!
Don't tell me...!
If we keep on going like this,
we're gonna run ashore on the iron fence!
No way!
The sea train is...
...flying!
Noo! We're gonna die!
What?! Are we gonna die?!
Ahhh!
Nami-san! Quickly, into my arms!
There's a huge hole where
we're gonna land, you idiot!
Zoro! You'd better have
thought about the landing!
Just leave it to...
Whoa...
--...luck.
--Ribbit!
So it's up to luck?!
Ahh! Oimo is down!
A-Are you... the Straw Hats?!
--That's right!
--We are?!
That's not important.
Let's hurry and move ahead!
All right! Guys! Now move
ahead as far as you can!
Yeah!
Paulie!
Dammit!
Who are you, bastards?!
We're the first-class guards of Enies Lobby,
the Watchdogs of the Law,
Watchdogs for short!
"'Watchdogs of the Law'
First-Class Guards, Enies Lobby"
On the orders of Chief Justice Baskerville,
we'll cast judgment on you
and bring you down at this gate!
Dammit! They send one guard
after another to block us!
Oimo! What're you doing?!
How could you let pirates
like them open the gate?!
Ow!
I passed out!
Oh, shoot! He came around!
I won't forgive you!
You're not gonna get away with this!
What?!
Wh-Why the hell...
did Rocketman come from the sky?!
There was no point in us opening the gate!
Wh-What just happened?!
Are they okay after charging in here like that?!
Th-They aren't coming out...
Hey, what happened?!
Wh-Who are those two?!
Huh? Should we have
introduced ourselves first?
That's stupid. Why should we?
Roronoa and the others are here!
We've been waiting!
It was just as I instructed.
Really?!
Gum-Gum... Storm!
He went that way!
Dammit!
Don't let him get away!
Hold it!
We've finally cornered him!
Y-You have nowhere else to run!
You guys...!
Don't get in my way!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Seriously, that idiot! He rushed out by himself!
What else is new?
But what're we gonna do?!
We're surrounded by a ton of enemies!
That's fine. I've been waiting for this.
Why don't we have some fun, too?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Catch Up with Luffy!
The Straw Hats' All-Out Battle"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!