Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
and involved in an all-out war!
If I am the only one who you want to kill,
please do not harm the other people...
...of the Ryugu Kingdom!
Come and get me!
Damn Yowahoshi! I told her to stick with me!
Don't mess with me, Vander Decken!
But I like this idea!
I'll be counting on you to save
my beloved Shirahoshi-chan!
You ready, Luffy?!
Go ahead!
"Hurry up, Luffy! Shirahoshi's
Life in Jeopardy!"
Th-The Noah is...
The Noah is turning away. It's
not gonna crash into the island!
Princess-sama saved us
by drawing the ship away!
--Princess Shirahoshi!
--Please escape!
Where are you going, Shirahoshi?
There's no way for you to run!
Shirahoshi!
I have to go out to the sea in order
to keep the Noah away from the bubble!
The bubble can't take any more damage!
But the main entrance is too far from here.
If I am correct, Luffy-sama's friends were
the last ones who left the Ryugu Palace.
Then maybe the gateway is still open.
Damn! Isn't there anything that we can do!
Our princess is risking
her life to save us all!
It's not her fault that Decken is after her!
Not only is Decken on that ship but now
Hordy is climbing aboard one of the chains!
Princess Shirahoshi's life is in danger!
He betrayed me, that lunatic - Decken!
But he can still be useful.
Be careful for Hordy, Luffy!
Fish-Men are way stronger
than humans in the water!
Got it!
I can't let him pierce the
bubble and go out to sea.
I have to do it carefully -
not too strong, not too weak.
Sanji!
Armee de L'Air Assault...
...Gum Shoot!
What a big chain!
Am I in between the bubbles?
Hordy! He's still under the bubble.
Pull! Pull!
We don't have stop it! We only have
to slow it down a little bit...
...before it catches up with Princess-sama!
--Pull!
--Don't let the Noah go any farther!
Princess-sama! Get somewhere safe
while we're slowing it down!
Damn! Stop!
Those fools!
Everybody!
They must be out of their minds!
They can't move it even a millimeter!
How senseless is that?!
What?
Hey, quit it!
Shark Arrows!
Worthless scum!
Because of cowards like you guys, humans
think they can make fools of Fish-Men!
Your lives mean nothing to me!
People like you just keep bringing
shame to Fish-Men. Drop dead already!
Everybody...
That bastard!
Princess-sama, escape! H-Hurry...
I have to keep going!
I was right! The entrance
to the palace was left open!
Hey, stay with me! Damn Hordy!
Princess Shirahoshi is going...
...out to sea through the gateway!
--The Noah is going after her!
--Princess-sama, go farther!
Oh, it's going up!
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Oh no, the chain!
How inconvenient it must be to be a human!
You all act so tough on the ground
but you couldn't even win a fight
with a Fish-Man child in the sea!
That's how weak you are!
I'll make you regret standing against me!
Hordy!
Where do you think you are?!
You're not on the ground!
Humans become powerless in the water
but for a Fish-Man like me, this is where I
can use my true ability to the full extent!
It was very fortunate for me
that Shirahoshi went out to sea!
Shark Arrows!
Devil Fruit eaters fare no better than
ordinary people in the water.
Maybe worse.
Isn't it ironic, Straw Hat?
Pathetic and powerless!
That's how you truly are!
No matter how big you talk!
You humans can't even breathe in the water...
Straw Hat, a piece of trash like you
will never become the ruler of the sea!
You ought to regret what
you did and beg for mercy!
You can't even do that now, can
you? You pathetic, lowly creature!
Rot in hell, Straw Hat!
Damn you!
Are you okay, Straw Hat?
B-Brother-hoshi!
That stupid hanger-on -
what a useless gesture.
You can't get away from me, Straw Hat!
Pull! Pull!
We don't have stop it! We only have
to slow it down a little bit...
...before it catches up with Princess-sama!
--Pull!
--Don't let the Noah go any further!
Princess-sama! Get somewhere safe
while we're slowing it down!
I-In order to save the people
of the Ryugu Kingdom,
I have to draw the Noah
away from the island...
...as far as possible!
Shirahoshi!
How do you like your freedom?
You no longer have those
walls of the Hard Shell
Tower that were protecting
you for last 10 years!
You have a choice of bleeding to death
or being crushed by the giant ship - Noah!
I'll give you one last chance, Shirahoshi!
If you say "Yes," I'll spare your life!
Have mercy, Decken-sama!
Marry me!
You're not my type!
Gee...
All right...
Then go to hell!
Drop dead and live in my heart forever!
As my beloved wife!
Now!
We're not gonna let her marry a guy like you!
She's our only baby sister! We're
not gonna let you hurt her, Decken!
Brother Mamboshi-sama! Brother
Ryuboshi-sama! Hoe-sama!
Brothers-sama!
We're not your brothers!
Brothers-sama! Some people at the
plaza tried to save me and...
Shirahoshi! Don't cry now!
No! Brother-sama got mad...
I'm not mad!
According to Father, we can't even
let the ship get damaged-la-ti-do!
So we have to return it to the seafloor
without letting it hit anything!
Here it comes!
Oh no! In any case, you shouldn't swim
near undersea mountains or trenches!
The Noah will get damaged!
Then where should I go,
Brother Mamboshi-sama?!
Go up! There are too many
obstacles down here!
Okay!
We'll go beat Decken!
You will never get away from the Noah
and my unending love, Shirahoshi!
Thank you for saving me!
You got hurt before - are you okay?
Members of the royal family, soldiers,
citizens... all of them got hurt or died.
And even Shirahoshi is trying so hard
to save the Ryugu Kingdom while injured!
So this is not the time for me to
suffer from such minor injuries!
I need to ask you a favor.
Maybe not now.
The Merfolk are the greatest
swimmers in the world!
But to me, they look like stop motion!
That bastard!
Shark Slicer!
We're dead once it hits us!
Should I chop both of you up and
feed you to the little fishes?
The pirate with a 400 million bounty
and the prince of the Ryugu Kingdom.
What exquisite food for them!
He's coming!
Although his power is phony, he's fast!
Hang on tight!
He's pretty strong in the
sea! Almost like Zoro!
You're not supposed to be
impressed at a time like this!
No matter where you go, you can't get
away from the Shark Slicer's blade!
Is he trying to escape in the cloud of dust?
The Noah is...
Shirahoshi!
--Shirahoshi!
--Hey, go to the deck of the ship!
Damn Decken!
Is that what you wanted to
ask me before? But why there?
Because of what Jimbei told me.
Do you think the ship is
filled with water, Jimbei?
I don't know but I know Decken
is a Devil Fruit eater.
Which means there must be air for him!
It'll be easier for me to fight there.
I wanna kick the crap out of Hordy
and the guy who throws things!
I promised Yowahoshi when we left the
tower, that I was gonna protect her!
Speaking of promises...
We three will become great
warriors like our father...
...and protect Shirahoshi with
our lives as we promised!
I have a promise to keep too!
We were defeated by that cheap
hoodlum who relies on some
fake power from the Energy Steroid!
What a shame!
I'm sorry that we suspected you...
Don't mention it. Take me to the deck!
You wanna go to the deck?
Hordy!
I can take care of Straw Hat anytime.
But there is something that
needs to be done right now.
--Go after him already!
--No, wait, Straw Hat!
Why?!
I'm sure you know it by now.
Hordy has an advantage in the
water since he is a Fish-Man.
--If nothing is done...
--What should we do?
I have an idea!
Go up! Go up!
Like I said, it's no use, Shirahoshi!
As long as my Mark-Mark Curse is in effect,
there is no way for you
to get away from the Noah!
Oh, Hordy Jones!
What happened to Neptune? Did you kill him?
I'm tormenting Shirahoshi with the Noah now.
Don't you think it's a good idea?
Huh, Bro?!
I have a good idea too!
What is it? Let me hear it.
If you die now...
What'll happen to this ship?
Decken!
Hordy suddenly attacks Decken.
His terrifying plan was to
destroy Fish-Man Island!
Hordy then attacks Shirahoshi
to complete his ambition!
But then, Luffy's new attack
is unleashed on Hordy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Fierce Fight Begins! Luffy vs. Hordy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!