Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
O-Oars is back on his feet!
I don't know what happened to Luffy,
but he dealt plenty of damage.
Pierna Fleurs!
The weather forecast is rain!
Cool Ball!
Rain Tempo!
Crank it like mad!
I'm cranking it!
Here it comes! It's the Super Cold Cannon
connected to the extra-large freezer!
Fire!
Now it's my turn!
Darn it!
Go!
Not a chain!
Be careful.
Third Gear!
Bone Balloon!
Zoro, push in Oars' stomach.
Three-Sword Style...
...Secret Technique!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Here goes nothing.
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Bazooka!
He did it!
Now go smack Moria awake
and make him return our shadows.
The sun is almost up!
I don't need... a wakeup call.
Moria!
Straw Hat, how dare you
trash my Thriller Bark?!
I lost my crew because they were alive!
But with undead zombies,
I have nothing to lose!
Come to me, all of the
shadows on Thriller Bark!
Serve as my power!
Shadows Asgard!
Bro!
He's collecting all of the shadows
on the island and absorbing them.
Straw Hat, I'd say you absorbed
around 100 shadows.
In that case, I'm absorbing 100...
200!
300!
400!
500!
600!
700!
800!
900!
1,000 shadows!
"Our Bodies Vanish! The Morning Sun
Shines on the Nightmarish Island!"
A thousand...
...shadows...
...are inside of Moria!
We're in a load of...
This can't be real.
We're doomed. What the heck is that?
I'm back to normal.
It's as good as dawn!
We're out of time!
Oars was a pushover for Straw Hat
when he had 100 shadows.
And he has ten times that!
Where is he storing all of that power?
Since it's his power, he must have
way better control of the ability!
Th-This is hopeless!
We've come too far for
crap like this! It's not fair!
He even has Straw Hat's shadow.
Yeah.
I imagine he has ours as well.
They're all inside...
...of his stomach.
Right.
Run! This is a lost cause!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa!
He put a crack in the island!
The mansion attached to
the mast is collapsing!
Run for it! Head for the forest!
It's over for real this time!
No! I'm gonna vanish!
My body is gonna vanish!
Please save me!
Stupid! Hurry into the shadows.
The morning sun is coming through!
Make your way to the forest
through the shadows!
Don't leave the buildings' shadows!
Captain Lola!
Captain Lola, what's keeping you? Hurry up!
Guys, please run for it.
H-How could you say that?
You're in the same boat!
But I'm responsible...
...for this gamble!
Just look at them.
Those guys...
They aren't the least bit fazed.
And here they've lost their shadows as well.
Do they still intend to win?
But all it took was one hit for him
to put a crack in the island!
Right now, Moria is way more
powerful than Oars ever was!
As long as they intend to fight,
I'm not leaving this spot!
If we selfishly place our faith
in him as the "Star of Hope"
and then split as soon
as the going gets tough,
we're no better than lowly insects!
But this situation is hopeless!
I want you to escape.
As the captain, our obligation
will be met if I stay behind.
Guys... Treasure your lives.
Captain Lola!
The sun is shining over there!
Hurry into the shade!
I'm fine!
This is what it means to
place your hope in someone!
Captain Lola!
No...! Do you want to die?!
I'm either going to live or die!
I don't care which way the coin flips.
I will never go back to
hiding in the shadows!
Captain!
He's practically going berserk.
He doesn't have full control of the shadows.
It looks like anger and foolish pride
made him overestimate himself.
Hey, guys. We're out of time.
I'm gonna push myself a bit.
Please take care of things after that!
Okay, you can count on us!
Send him flying!
Hey, you guys! What makes
you think you stand a chance?
There is no way you'll win!
You're up against a monster
that's a thousand strong!
Right! Stop and think for a second.
He even has your shadows!
He has your monstrous power!
And we're running out of time!
If you're here to watch, shut your trap.
We've already won the fight with Moria.
But it all comes down to finishing
things before the sun rises.
Moria plans to use his insane power
to buy that brief period of time.
Second Gear!
Will we get obliterated first?
Or will Moria self-destruct first?
Go, Luffy!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Rocket!
Look! The shadows are coming out.
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
Jet Bazooka! Jet Bazooka!
Gobs of shadows are being released!
Why are the shadows leaving
if they're under his control?
Moria is losing control over them
as he starts to black out.
Even Moria can't fully control
a thousand shadows at once!
--Gum-Gum...
--Brick Bat!
Black Box!
I'm trapped!
I'm going to crush you!
That was a direct hit!
It was just like the punch
that put a crack in the island!
Straw Hat!
Stop it!
This is your baptism!
This is what happens when a whippersnapper
tries to act like a big shot on these waters!
This is what you get for defying
one of the Seven Warlords!
H-He's cruel!
Know your place! The world is devised
to crush anyone who stands out!
Luffy-san!
Luffy!
He got back up!
It doesn't matter if I'm
a "whippersnapper"...
...or if I stand out!
No one...
...can...
...crush me!
No one can crush you?
Your ability to say that
without any justification
proves just how green you are!
It's because I'm rubber.
In just a sec, I'm gonna make you
spew out all of the shadows!
What's with him? Is he immortal?
He's incredible!
The morning light!
Crap!
Stupid! Get in the shadows or you're toast!
Help me! My hand is vanishing.
Hurry into the shadows!
The courtyard isn't safe anymore.
Third Gear!
Bone Balloon!
Hey, is it wise to use that
attack more than once?
Of course not!
Don't you remember what using
Second Gear did to you that one time?
Use your Gum-Gum to shoot yourself over here!
Once you're here, I'll carry you!
We're surrounded by the sea
and a bunch of battleships!
If we stay here, we're gonna be killed!
I-I can't...
What?
My body... isn't moving at all.
Don't be ridiculous! You defeated the enemy!
We got Robin back, too!
All that's left is for us to go back!
Please! Try hard!
This really is nuts, Luffy!
Your body can't take this!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Jet Shell!
It's so powerful!
More shadows are coming out!
I won't let them escape! They're my minions!
Shadows, I am your sovereign!
That bastard! He doesn't
plan on giving up our shadows.
My shadow!
Come back to me!
--Captain Lola!
Captain! Captain!
My shadow, can't you hear me?
We were always together,
clear from the time I was born!
We came into this world together!
Come back to me!
I spent the past three years searching
for the zombie that contained you!
Now you're in there, aren't you?
If you can hear me, come back! Come back!
Captain Lola!
Please hide in the shadows!
You're gonna turn to ash!
But... But it's killing me!
It's right there!
You're right! Supposedly all of our
shadows are currently inside of Moria.
They're right in front of us!
We'll never get another chance like this!
But we're up against one
of the Seven Warlords...
She's right... Come back!
Shadows, come back!
Come back!
Come back!!
Come back! Come back! Come back!
I'd like to say something to my shadow, too.
If you want to become the
King of the Pirates...
...you had better...
...stick with me!
Straw Hat, curse you...!
I dare you to go to the New World!
The real nightmare awaits
you in the New World!
Our shadows are coming back!
We made it in time!
Here come our shadows!
H-Hey, guys!
Whoa!
Shadow, please hurry!
What the heck?!
No way!
Come on, guys!
W-Wait! What is going on?!
Didn't we take down Moria?!
Luffy!
It sounds like my fears were justified.
So it would seem.
Do not leave witnesses to testify
that Straw Hat defeated Moria.
I am assigning you to a special mission.
Annihilate the entire Straw Hat Crew!
That will be easy.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Not Out of Danger Yet!
Orders to Annihilate the Straw Hat Crew!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!