Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Protect Iceberg-san!
Yeah!
You're acting like I'm a stranger.
Please leave it to me.
Well... You have my gratitude.
There're tons of people there.
If we carelessly plunge in,
we'll be in big trouble.
Look who's talking!
This is where we find out what we're made of.
Yeah...!
An explosion!
Things have gotten kinda crazy!
Hm? Where's Luffy?
Whaaat?!
Give it to us...
...and... we'd like you to die.
This is no longer something as
simple as an assassination, is it?
We're a group that carries out justice.
We are Cipher Pol No. 9,
an undercover intelligence agency.
I see. So thanks to Luffy,
this is our chance to infiltrate, huh?
Are you guys ready?!
What part of this is light?!
I'm stuck and can't move!
I have to hurry...
Just wait... Robin!
Dammit! Where'd they go?!
One person, and one animal with
two people. That's all we've confirmed.
Shall we go guard the bedroom?
But our foremen are there.
There's no such thing as too
many guards. Let's go back them up.
What the hell is going on?!
Someone! Third floor!
Come to the front of the
president's room and the bedroom!
The guards were annihilated!
Someone! Come upstairs!
What are you saying?!
--Tilestone-san!
--Kaku and Lucci should be there!
But they're...
What?!
Kaku! Lucci!
Good grief, there's no
end to this. No word yet?
You bastard!
How dare you...?!
What a noisy man.
Iceberg-san had better be okay!
Check it yourself.
Iron Body.
His giant hammer was...!
N... No way...!
You son of a...
Let go, you bastard!
Is that Herculean strength of yours your pride?
I can't move my arm!
There's no way my power can be beat...
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"CP9 Takes Off Their Masks!
Their Shocking True Faces"
His giant hammer was...!
N... No way...!
You son of a...
Let go, you bastard!
Is that Herculean strength of yours your pride?
I can't move my arm!
There's no way my power can be beat...
Three of the foremen have been...!
Get some reinforcements from downstairs!
Shave!
--We found them!
--It's Roronoa Zoro!
They showed up at last!
Don't let them get away!
I saw that woman this afternoon, too!
After them!
Hey! Why isn't Luffy here?!
How should I know?! I wanna ask that question!
What do we do?!
Now that it's come to this, it's like
we've been caught in the act anyway.
If we go on the offensive,
there's a way to get in.
What?! Hey, Zoro! What're you gonna do?!
Running around the building
won't get us anywhere.
We'll openly plunge in from
the front and look for Robin.
What?!
But they're shipwrights!
They're not our enemy, you know!
Don't worry. I'll use the back of my swords!
Out of our way!
But you're inflicting fatal wounds on them!
Well... I'm shocked.
To be honest, I never thought
I'd see you here... Nico Robin.
Have we met before?
No.
We met for the first time last night.
But I've wanted to see you all this time.
I even put your wanted poster up
in my room to ensure I never forgot.
Shall I give you my autograph or something?
That would be... nice!
So you wanted to kill me?
That's right.
Before you destroy the world!
Why do you go searching for the Poneglyphs?!
Since ancient times,
the Government has declared
globally that it's a serious crime
to seek and decipher the Poneglyphs.
I'm sure you know that much.
You too know of the
existence of the Poneglyphs.
Just knowing about it wouldn't be a crime.
But the only one in the whole world
who can decipher those texts...
...is you.
That's exactly why the Government
put a bounty on your head,
even though you were only eight years old.
It's because you're the only one in the world
who can restore the ancient weapon!
I see... So you even know about the weapon...
All things considered...
...I never thought CP9 was an
organization that really existed.
If it does, it means that you've
already left the Straw Hat Pirates
and have been helping the Government.
It's bizarre for a woman who's been
pursued for 20 years to act like that,
but, well, that's not my concern.
If the weapon gets restored through
deciphering the Poneglyphs,
whether its owner is righteous or evil,
the result will be the same.
The weapon can never bring
forth "peace" to this world.
The world will go under for sure.
We mustn't call forth a relic of the past!
You're right. I do agree with you.
But it's none of your business.
Whatever I do to research history,
you, a stranger, have no
right to say anything to me.
Well... not quite...
...since you and I are in
the same boat, in a sense.
I...
I have the blueprints of
the ancient weapon Pluton.
The blueprints of the weapon?!
Pluton is the name of a battleship
built on this island a long time ago.
The shipbuilding engineer who created
this overwhelmingly powerful weapon
had the blueprints passed
down for generations.
He felt that if by some chance
Pluton started running out of control,
there would need to be a force to counter it.
In order to get them...
...the Government has finally
resorted to using force.
To think that you're helping
them without knowing that...
I'm too shocked to speak.
The man named Tom,
who entrusted the blueprints with me,
had been concerned about a girl
who alone was able to escape from
the Ohara incident 20 years ago.
He said that although she was small,
she was dangerous, since she had the
same ideology as the Ohara devils.
I inherited the creator's will, so I have
the responsibility of stopping you!
Now that the Government has come to
know of the existence of the blueprints,
essentially, it'd be better if I burned them.
But I can't do that, because you're alive,
and so there's still a possibility
that the weapon can be restored!
Is that all you want to say before you die?
With all due respect, even if you
killed me and stopped its restoration,
if the blueprints get stolen from you,
wouldn't it be the same thing?
Well...
...let me tell you one more thing.
You're the ones who got taken in by a plan.
Oh, that's it!
I was finally able to get out! That was terrible.
Okay, I'll swoop in this time for sure.
I'll go capture Robin. Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
You're no match for our martial arts skills.
Now, hand it over already...
...or else it'll get dirty with your blood.
Dammit...
I thought... I could defeat you.
To tell you the truth...
...Iceberg-san told me to run right away.
He told me to drop it quickly and run...
...since...
...it's a complete fake.
What?
A fake, you said?
How foolish...
I don't know who you are, but this
means your plan failed, doesn't it?
How pathetic. Sorry, pal.
I don't even know what you're looking for.
How cocky... You think that you outwitted CP9?
In any case, even though you're only a decoy,
we can't keep you alive now
that you've become involved.
I got stuck! Dammit! I got stuck again!
Why does this always happen?!
Straw Hat...!
Huh?
Ah! The rope guy!
What happened to you? Are you okay?
You're covered in blood.
You sure are full of surprises!
That'd be you! This is the third floor!
Straw Hat Luffy...
So you took the trouble to come
to take the crime upon yourself?
Ahh! Masks! Are they masks?!
Then you people must be the ones
who're making Robin do stuff!
Give Robin back to us, you damn bastards!
Dammit! Hey! Say something!
Tempest Kick.
Whoa!
His kicks cut the wall!
Straw Hat!
What the hell are these?
We've got an emergency situation.
We don't have time for you.
I can't move!
Hey, restrain that guy, too.
This is no time for fighting.
Right...
Click.
It's me. A problem occurred in our plan.
Everyone, come to the bedroom right away.
Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
Got that? Don't shoot Iceberg yet.
I wouldn't have minded playing
with you a little longer, but...
...something came up. So, excuse me.
What?! Are you trying to run?!
No.
Since something came up,
I gave him a finishing blow.
Ahhh! Lulu-san is...!
--No way...!
--By just one hit?!
--Hold it!
He flew again!
Are you... okay?
This is... nothing!
I see. Straw Hat, why did you come here?
Everyone thinks that you guys are the culprits.
I'm sorry... It was all because
of our wrong assumption.
Don't worry about it.
We're used to being pursued.
More importantly, a member of our
crew was taken by masked men.
So I came to take her back.
You're talking about Nico Robin, right?
You're strong when you fight, right?
Yeah, I am!
Can you beat them?
Yes, I can!
Then, fight with me! I wanna beat them, too!
--You do...
--Of course I do!
Why... Why does Iceberg-san have to be
killed by some totally strange idiots?!
Give me a break!
Who the hell are those people?!
The hell with the undercover
intelligence agency, bastards!
He was... my teacher.
He helped me to become
an established shipwright!
Why would someone like him be...
But you're too injured to...
I said I want to beat the
crap out of those idiots!
Who cares what happens to my body later on?!
I'm gonna fight to the
very last bone in my body!
Dammit! Take these off!
Okay! Take them off! Dammit!
Go home!
I've got nothing I could give you people!
If you don't, that puts us in quite a bind.
What should I tell you first...
...when you're about to die?
You disappointed me.
Lucci!
It's your own fault.
You should've given it to the
Government when they asked nicely.
Kaku!
If possible, I wanted to make this town
part of my memory without hurting you.
Kalifa...
So you also inherited your
master's obstinacy, huh?
Blueno, from the bar...
You guys... work for... the Government?
That's right. Going undercover
was a pretty easy mission for us.
In any case, your prudence
leaves me at a loss for words.
Now, Iceberg-san...
Where're the blueprints of
the ancient weapon Pluton?
Please tell us, before many people get hurt.
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Don't tell me-- you guys are CP9?
Now, tell us where the blueprints are.
Nonsense. If the ancient weapon is restored,
the world will only fight over its power.
It seems that you don't trust
the power of the Government.
I just know how humans are, that's all, lad.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Secret Bond! Iceberg and Franky"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!