Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
This is...
...one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
He's the "Tyrant" Bartholomew Kuma!
If you were to go on a trip,
where would you like to go?
Of all the stupid...! I nearly let
the weight of your title crush me.
What a dreadful man!
Negative Ghost!
And Special Hollow!
I can't ask Moria's whereabouts
when you're being belligerent.
Where'd she go?
Aren't you the Cat Burglar?
You're part of the Straw Hat Crew!
What gives?! He got up there
in the blink of an eye!
Did he warp...?
Is he after Luffy? I've got to let him know!
I've got ya, Moria!
The shadow? I've been chasing after the...
Sh-Shoot! He pulled a fast one on me!
"Oars + Moria! The Most Heinous
Combination of Brains and Brawn!"
Darn it! When did he swap out with his shadow?
Why, you--!
Hey! Wait, Moria's Shadow!
Don't leave me here!
Where am I?!
Hey!
Shoot! This bites.
I said that I would recover everyone's shadows.
It'll be bad if I don't get our shadows back.
Uh... What happens if we don't have shadows?
Now I remember! As we are now,
I'm pretty sure the guys and I will melt in the sunlight.
We'll be in a jam when the sun rises, huh?
Shoot! I have to finish this up before dawn!
I never dreamed this would happen!
For now, all I can do is follow Moria's shadow!
Zoro, I really think we should
buy time until Luffy defeats Moria!
I just obtained the black blade, Shusui.
Can you blame me for wanting to test it out
on the monster standing before me?
Come on, man!
Oars!
Huh?
Have at me! I will be your opponent!
All right.
You're going to fight him alone?!
Whoa, Zoro! There is no way
you can fight him by yourself!
Come back here so we can regroup!
Comparing the two swords,
the black blade, Shusui, is considerably
heavier than my old Yubashiri.
Hey, Zoro! Dodge!
Going by its weight...!
Amazing! He used brute strength
alone to divert that punch!
Three-Sword Style...
...108-Pound Phoenix!
It's huge!
Drat! It didn't hit him!
I can't believe he dodged that!
Shusui's slash absorbed the ones
from the other two swords
and became one big slash!
But there is excess damage
around where it cut the stone.
It's proof that I haven't
mastered this sword yet.
It is several levels more
powerful than my old one,
but it doesn't seem like
the most compliant of swords.
You gave me a great blade, swordsman Ryuma!
You're good! I bet that
woulda hurt bad if it hit,
you bastard!
I'm gonna trample you!
Lemme step on you!
--Zoro!
--Will he be okay?
Jerk!
Unless I make a bigger opening,
all I can do is dodge!
Now!
Three-Sword Style! 108--
Now I'm going to crush you!
Zoro!
Tsk!
I bet he's as flat as a pancake.
Huh?
He isn't there!
Where did he go?
Darn! I can't see him through the dust.
Three-Sword Style...
...108-Pound Phoenix!
Yikes! That was close.
Damn! That stupid monster dodged again!
Shrimp, quit sneaking around!
Zoro! S-Seriously, don't do anything crazy!
Even if by some miracle
you managed to defeat him,
all you'd get out of it is Luffy's shadow!
We don't even know where
your and Sanji's shadows are.
But if Luffy defeats Moria, everyone will
instantly get their shadows back!
You don't need to get hurt
fighting an immortal giant zombie!
Let's believe in Luffy and work on
keeping this behemoth busy!
I fully believe in him...
...but even Luffy has a weakness.
Huh?
Trickery!
The invisible man, the ghost girl,
and the master of shadows...
This island is a nesting grounds for
deceptive Devil Fruit power holders.
I doubt the enemy will
fight Luffy fair and square.
That's a good point.
Yeah.
If he gives Luffy the slip and morning comes...
Luffy, the cook, and I won't be able
to put up a decent fight anymore!
So at the very least, if we can get
Luffy back to normal before dawn,
he'll take over from there.
I'd say we have less than
thirty minutes until sunrise.
But these are foggy waters.
The morning sun won't hit everywhere.
So morning is on the horizon...
This fog is the only thing in our favor.
Honestly, the fear of annihilation is
just now setting in with sunrise so close.
Ah, I found the runts!
Wh-What's that?!
Why is the ship shaking?!
What's going on?!
The ship must have gotten caught
in another weird current like earlier!
Huh?! Hey, look!
It's the sky!
It's the pre-dawn sky!
The fog is dissipating before our very eyes!
What's going on?!
Does this mean we've left the Florian Triangle?!
It's because Oars was fooling
around with the rudder earlier!
That bastard! Look at what he's done!
This is stinkin' bad!
Thriller Bark has pulled out of the fog!
We're doomed!
Sunrise is just around the corner!
Is this the end of the line?
It's too soon to give up!
The Star of Hope's crew is
fighting even as we speak.
H-Hey, check that out!
It's Moria's shadow!
It's flying back to the mansion.
So what?
Stupid! Don't you see?
Straw Hat has been chasing it.
It should lead him right to us.
In other words, if we set up an ambush...
Oh, I get it!
Great! Let's inform the captain and the others.
We have to stop Straw Hat!
Yeah, got it!
Moria-sama, something horrible has happened!
After all this time, Thriller Bark
has left the foggy waters!
All because of Oars!
Moria-sama!
Don't make a scene. So what if we left the fog?
We're pirates! I don't care where
we are as long as we're on the ocean!
Uh, but...
More importantly, zip your lips, because I
am entertaining the most unusual of guests!
Isn't that right, Tyrant Kuma,
the only Warlord who does the Government's bidding?
I'm sure the Government finds you useful,
but what are you plotting?
People like you are the most unsettling!
If you were to go on a trip,
where would you like to go?
Whoa, whoa! Don't go there!
I know what your powers are.
Did you come to fight me?
State your business! What brought you here?
I came to make a report.
A report...?
It has been decided who will
fill the empty Warlord seat
created by Crocodile's dismissal.
You should have said so sooner!
Who was it and what ocean was he from?
There are a bazillion pirates out there!
The name of his successor is Marshall D. Teach.
The man also goes by Blackbeard.
Blackbeard? I've never heard of him.
He ran away from Whitebeard's crew.
People are already starting to talk about him.
Vortex!
St. Elmo's Fire!
Damn it!
Die in darkness!
Flame Commandment...
Flame Emperor!
News hasn't reached your foggy waters,
but he joined after proving his strength.
And what was his original bounty?
Zero.
I see. So his capability is still unknown.
I'm amazed the Government approved.
But at least that seat has been filled!
Won't this help stabilize
the world's power balance?
No, I imagine this will do the exact opposite,
but that is irrelevant.
To cut to the chase, the Government
is rather concerned about something.
Since the incident at Enies Lobby,
they are constantly keeping
tabs on the Straw Hat Crew.
They knew if the Straw Hats followed a
Log from Water Seven to Fishman Island,
the chances of you stopping
them here would be high.
Do you see what the Government fears?
The Government
is afraid that Straw Hat
will defeat yet another of the Seven Warlords.
Don't give me that! You're worried about me?!
Me, the person who took this seat
to suppress the weak pirates?!
If necessary, I would be willing
to offer you my assistance.
Who do you think you're talking to, bastard?!
Are you saying I might lose to a
small band of inexperienced pirates?!
You cannot 100% guarantee victory in battle.
Who would have predicted
the defeat of Rob Lucci
during the incident at Enies Lobby?
Jet...
...Gatling!
Even so, are you telling me
that the Government is so scared
that they want to throw
two Warlords at them?! Well?!
I thought I'd help after delivering the report.
It is not as though I was ordered to assist you.
Then feast your eyes on what I do
to those pirates while you're here!
And then tell those pampered
idiots what you witnessed!
Tell them about how Gecko Moria effortlessly turned the
Straw Hat Crew that outwitted them into zombie soldiers!
The fog...!
This sucks!
That thick fog... was our one ray of hope!
Who planned for the fog to
clear up now of all times?!
The morning sun is going
to shine straight onto us!
Damn it! We've got enough problems on
our hands without having to deal with Oars!
The sky is unexpectedly clear tonight.
M-Moria! It's Moria!
Where?! Where is he?!
Hey, don't mess with us!
The sun will be rising soon.
Should you really be farting around?
Why is he here? What happened to Luffy?
Huh? I can hear Master's voice!
Hey! Hold up, Usopp!
Where the heck is Moria?
Can't you see him? Look up there!
In the gut! He's in the middle of Oars' gut!
Inside his stomach?
I see him!
Hogback! This was his doing!
What is Moria doing there?
So where's Luffy? Did Moria
seriously give him the slip?
Or did he...?
No one can take Luffy down!
Yeah!
That's strange. I could have
sworn I heard Master's voice.
There he is! Is that a cockpit?
I'll be! Is my tummy a cockpit?
Hey!
This is pretty well made!
I wanna ride in the cockpit!
Hey, stupid! Don't stick
your fingers in the cockpit!
Okay, Master!
This is so cool! I'm like a robot.
Roar! I'm a giant robot!
Creak, creak, creak, creak!
Screech! Screech!
Whoa, that was close!
I'm the giant robot, uh, Oarsbomber!
Nice to meet you!
Why Oarsbomber?
Oarsbomber?
How could you be a robot
when you're a zombie?!
Robots are like, "Ka-ching!" and "Ka-ling!"
I'm psyched that I get to be a giant robot!
Oars, give it a rest! Don't get so hyped up.
Okay, Master.
Okay, punks! I am going to
offer you the chance to fight me.
If you are victorious, you can
set all of the shadows free.
All of you can attack at once!
But if you don't defeat Oars,
you'll never pull me out of him.
That creep...
That's low!
We can't purify Oars if we don't defeat Moria,
but Moria went inside of Oars!
But doesn't that simplify things?
Our target is right there.
We have to take them down!
Usopp! If a little wouldn't cut it,
go find a boatload of salt!
That is the only way to purify Oars.
We'll weaken him as much
as possible in the meantime.
Yep! Leave that to us!
--Let's do this.
--Okay! You got it! I'll go get some!
I'm pretty sure there was a kitchen
in the first mansion we went to!
There should be a bunch of salt there!
I thought they looked pumped,
but they're after salt.
Hey, Oars! Crush the path to the mansion,
along with that long-nosed guy!
Make it impossible for them
to reach the kitchen!
Okay, Master.
Usopp!
Huh? What?!
Crap!
Usopp!
Shit! Oars is acting intelligently
now that Moria is with him!
Usopp!
Where are you?! Answer me!
He's okay!
I thought that you might need salt,
so I gathered it in bulk!
Brook!
You're a lifesaver!
I am your Brook!
Who are you guys?
We're the Risky Brothers!
We'll give you incredible powers!
Say what?
S-Stop it!
What do you think?
I'm bursting with power! Nothing can stop me!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Secret Plan to Turn the Tables!
Nightmare Luffy Makes His Appearance!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!