Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
Hm...? What's that?
Hey! There's a flock of birds to starboard!
Alrighty!
Gum-Gum...
...Grab!
Hold on a sec... Hey!
Hey, look.
It's a girl!
Ugh!
A wind is coming.
A strong wind is...
I feel like this ship hasn't
been moving at all for a while...
Ah!
Dammit...!
We've entered the Calm Belt!!
Charm Belt?
What the heck is that?
Calm Belt! It's an area of sea
where nothing moves a muscle!
"Nami grew her muscles"?
Idiot!
What was that? An earthquake?
Earthquake? On the sea?
You guys, enough chit chat!
Fold the sails and start paddling now!
Put the ship back on its earlier path!
Okay, Nami-san!
What're you panicking about?
Paddling? This is a sailboat.
He's right. Why're we taking
the trouble to go back
to where the Navy is waiting for us?
Just do what I say!
We're in big trouble!
Well, the sea is quiet.
Yeah.
All right, fine! Then I'll
explain it for you! Listen up!
Since we rushed and ran away,
we came further south than we planned!
Then did we enter the Grand Line?
All right!
If it was that easy, anyone could enter!
Look. The Grand Line is
running between two sea areas!
Do you get it?
The area on both sides of
it is called the Calm Belt.
The reason is unknown but in these areas,
there's no wind and no current.
They're an area of sea with complete calm.
Sailboats run by catching winds,
so it's an extremely dangerous area,
indeed, a fatal area, for them!
Luffy, did you get it?
Yeah. At least that we're in trouble.
I see. Good, you got more than I thought.
So this is what the geezer meant
when he said it was dangerous...
No wonder there hasn't been any wind.
We can't do anything
if the ship doesn't move.
We can just wait until
the wind starts blowing.
Like I said, once you're in
this area, wind never blows
no matter how long you wait!
And, that's not all!
There's another reason that
people call this area dangerous!
In this area...
Ah! Another one!
What's going on?
Something is coming this way.
Here they are!!
Huh...? What's that?
They're huge!!
The Calm Belt is the
nest of the Sea Kings.
Moreover, the ones here are super huge!
They're another reason why
people can't cross the Calm Belt.
"Miraculous Creature! Apis's Secret
and the Legendary Island"
What're we gonna do now?
F-For the time being, no one move.
They'll probably go back
into the sea eventually.
Then we'll paddle hard using our oars.
Are you serious?!
Idiot!
Sorry.
A frog is coming!!
What?! What?! What?!
Oh, no!
Y-Your arm is stretching!!
Luffy! Do you have
the power of a devil fruit?!
Yeah, that's right.
Luffy!
Stretch your arm downwards again!
Hey, Luffy!
What're you doing?!
I don't know.
Apis!
Watch out!!
One, two...
What did she just do?!
She pulled his nose hair.
Hold on a sec...!
If you do that...
He's gonna sneeze!
Ahh...
That's a huge nose hair!
All right! We're going back!
What?!
Do it some other way!!
Amazing! I feel like we're flying!
Idiot!!
We are flying!!
Looks like we're back
in the area we came from.
I don't see any sign of the Navy, either.
Ahhh... I thought I was a goner.
Good job!
Yep!
Okay! Unfurl the sails!
Our destination is...
Of course...!
Warship Island!!
We can't see anything.
Well, we can see the fog.
Apis, is it really around here?
Not sure.
"Not sure"? You...
It should be close by.
That's our Nami-san!
You sure know your stuff.
Ah...! Look!
Huh?
Oh! It's a sailboat! It's huge!
Now listen here...
The word "huge" doesn't
begin to describe it.
Then, a super humongous sailboat?
No!
That's Warship Island.
It's shaped like a warship,
so it's called Warship Island.
I see! Interesting!
Ah! That flag is...!
Pirates!
Pirates!! Pirates have come!!
Pirates?
Stay inside!
Hi! I'm home!
Apis...!
Why are you coming out
from the pirate ship?
What's going on?
Say, you guys...
Wh-What?!
Is there a BBQ restaurant on this island?!
Huh?
Wh-What's this guy?
Listen! They're pirates,
but they're good ones.
Are there really good pirates?
Yes!
Weren't you taken away by
the Navy in the first place?
That's right. But I escaped.
And these guys, Luffy and
the others, saved me. Right?
Yeah.
What'd you do, Apis?
We don't know why, but the
Navy was looking for you.
You should stay away from your home.
They're still around.
What am I gonna do?
We'd like to help, but...
...they're pirates, right?
Ahh, what should we do?
Like she said, we're good pirates.
Apis!
Come to my house!
Who's that?
Don't know.
Grandpa Bokuden!
I'm glad you're safe.
Thank you for saving Apis.
How about this? I'd like to throw
a small welcome party for you.
Is your place a BBQ restaurant?
It's not a BBQ restaurant,
but Grandpa Bokuden's pork buns
are the best on the island!
All right! Let's go!
Well then, we'll go.
Hm?!
There she is!
Eric!
I've been here all along...
I thought that that girl
got lost in the Calm Belt
and wasn't going to come back alive!
Can't be... That girl...?
She's...
...back on Warship Island!
Capture that girl, you bum!
Then they escaped from the Calm Belt...!
There,
the preparations are finished.
Wait a little while.
Cool!
Whoa! Smells good!
I see... This is the real deal.
Old man, how long do we have to wait?
Hm? Well...
maybe about 4-5 hours...
What?!
Ah, I'm starving.
Bokuden-san,
why is the Navy after Apis?
Do you have any idea?
Apis! Do you have any idea?
Not at all!
You said there was a reason
but you didn't want to tell.
Oh that! I lied.
What?
Then none at all.
None at all?!
Really, there's nothing on this island.
Nothing but an old legend.
Legend?
The residents of this island are said
to be descendants of Lost Island people
who prospered but sank into the sea
tens of thousands of years ago.
On Lost Island, there lived
dragons called Millennial Dragons.
The bones of those dragons
are called Dragonite...
...and it's said to be
an elixir of immortality.
I see...
But a legend like that is no reason
for the Navy to get involved.
Yeah. Why is the Navy doing
this in the first place?
That's the thing I don't get.
Doesn't this legend hold some
sort of clue or something?
To begin with, the first king
of Lost Island was Iscardunk.
Here we go again...
Now, King PokePortes had three children.
The oldest son was BokeHontas,
the second son was BokeBonboko, and
the third son was BokeBokepon.
Shhh!
One day, the king said to these three,
"Listen. Go find the tree that grows stars,
which is said to be in dragon's valley.
So BokeHontas,
BokeBonboko and BokeBokepon
journeyed out, one to the sea,
Once Grandpa starts that story,
one to the mountain and one to the forest.
it'll take forever.
I'm not gonna listen to all that.
Now, the 317th King IngriMongri III's son
Hey, how long is this gonna go on?
IngriGrimori was quite a wise ruler.
Who knows.
He had 18 children. His 18 children...
...He was a king who
carried out major reforms.
This King Ikemenes had so many children.
Ahhh, I'm starving...
We won't be able to eat
until this story is over, will we?
He had many princes. 65 of them!
the pork buns until then?
Pork buns?
I hear it was like, "If you throw a stone,
Luffy?
it'll hit one of the princes."
I gotta take a leak.
Pork buns...
Hold on, Grandpa Ryu.
Oh, no!
He's coming this way!
What am I gonna do?
Please! Don't come here!
Pork buns smell yummy.
No way!
I didn't hit him yet, right?
Ahhh, pork buns...
And, the 1,111th... no,
the 1,121st King was HokeHontas.
So, NemeNememitas
Hey, where're you going?
thought about what he could do
I'm worried about Luffy.
since he's gone for a long time.
to protect this kingdom.
So I'll go check.
Then, he made preparation
That's not fair.
before large countries attacked them.
Nami-san's lovely
even when she sneaks out.
Phew! Good grief!
Luffy!
Ahhh! Not even one bun is left!
Yeah, this is yummy.
Yummy?! How do you intend to make
up for eating everyone's share?!
What're you talking about?
Geez... Hm?
What's this?
What made this trail?
Hm? Dead end?
What's the deal?
Hm?
Hey, Luffy, what're you doing?
A hole.
What?
Looks like they went across here.
Luffy!
Yep! Gum-Gum...
Suspension Bridge...
Grandpa Ryu!
This is the other side of the mountain.
How far did they go?
Ah, that's...
Yes, I was fine.
These weird pirates saved me.
No, they're not that scary.
You must be hungry. I brought
Grandpa Bokuden's pork buns.
Here you go. No! Slow down!
Oh, I'm sorry. I still don't know yet.
Although I'm searching very hard,
I still haven't found a clue yet.
I wonder who on earth Apis is talking to.
Hey, Apis! Who're you talking to?
Don't just jump out and say "hey"!
No! Don't come here!
Whoa!!
Luffy, what's the matter?
Ahh!!
Stop it! I said stop it!
Amazing! Amazing! Amazing!
Hey, Luffy...
This is the real thing! Is he alive?
Stop it! Leave him alone!
I can't believe... that it really exists...
I thought that dragons were just legends!
This is incredible!
Where did you come from?
I see... You want to go home, huh?
Okay...
Grandpa Ryu says that you
can be his friend, Luffy.
He says he can tell
you're a good person.
Luffy, how could you
read Grandpa Ryu's mind?
I somehow did.
Somehow...?
How did you know?
Oh, well, I...
Could it be... a devil fruit...?
You have the power of
a devil fruit, don't you?
Yes. I ate one called
Whisper-Whisper Fruit or something.
Since then, I've become
able to read animals' minds.
That's why you knew
a wind was coming that time.
Yep. The seabirds told me that.
I met Grandpa Ryu thanks to
the Whisper-Whisper Fruit, too.
Who is it?
I've never heard such
a sad voice before...
Hold on! I'm coming to help you now!
Was it you who called me?
He had lost his energy.
He said that he got separated
from his friends and
that since then he had
been looking for Lost Island,
where the dragons' nest is.
Didn't Lost Island sink
a long long time ago?
Grandpa Ryu says that the
island will surface again.
He says it's about time,
but he no longer clearly
remembers where it is.
He's gotten very old
and lost the energy to fly.
But he keeps telling me
that he wants to go back.
I wanna help, but I can't figure out
where such an island exists at all...
The legend by itself
doesn't really give me a clue...
So I asked the Navy who happened
to stop by this island about it.
That was a mistake.
They were looking for Dragonite.
Dragonite... you mean
the one for immortality?
They took you away
because of such a thing?
Yes. They told me to tell them
everything I knew and took me away.
The pendant that I made with a claw
Grandpa Ryu gave me may
have been another reason, though...
That's why you escaped in that storm...
--You are too reckless!
--I know.
That's why I keep this a secret to
the villagers and even to Bokuden-san.
I don't want to cause troubles for them.
But I want to take Grandpa Ryu back
to his home no matter what it takes.
He always tells me that he'll
get his energy back for sure
once he goes back to the dragons' nest.
I'll find it for him no matter
how many years it takes.
For sure... No matter what it takes,
I'll find it for him.
Okay then! I'll take him there!
Luffy! Were you listening?!
Lost Island sank into the sea!
But since the legendary
Millennial Dragon actually exists,
I'm sure Lost Island
also exists somewhere!
An island that's not even on a map?
Yeah, that's why we're going!
An island that's not even on a map, huh?
Oh, what the heck? Let's go!
All right!
Really?! Really?!
Yeah.
Thank you!
Now that that's been decided, eat more!
Oh, Luffy, I forgot to tell you...
Grandpa Ryu is a little senile.
That girl had a pendant with
a Millennial Dragon's claw.
She must know about Lost Island.
That darn girl who knows
the secret of the Dragonite...
I'll definitely capture her this time!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Taking the Millennial Dragon
back to his home?
Why'd you promise such
a thing without asking us?
Hey, let's go to Lost Island!
Hey, the Navy is following us!
Everyone, please help us!
Let's go, Nami-san!
A runaway journey of love
beyond the ocean! Mellorine love.
Are you stupid?
What'd you say?!
On the next episode on One Piece!
"Eric Attacks! Great Escape
from Warship Island!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!