Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Terrible news, everyone!
Pirates are attacking!
Pirates! Pirates!
Run for your lives!
Pirates! Run for your lives!
"Liar of Justice? Captain Usopp"
It'd be reckless to go straight
into the Grand Line now!
Yeah, some meat would
be nice to have first.
Eating nothing but fruit
everyday is no good...
Need some booze, too!
What're you talking about?!
That's not what I mean!
The Grand Line is the most
dangerous place in the world!
On top of that, it's crawling with
strong pirates after the One Piece!
And they're all on
powerful ships, of course!
We need more people, too.
The number of crew members,
the lack of equipment on this ship...
There's no way we
could survive like this!
Yeah, we need a cook. And a musician.
A musician?!
You're so stupid...
A little to the south of here is
an island with people living on it.
It'd be best if we can get
ahold of a real ship there...
Alright! Time to eat some meat!
Don't forget the booze!
You guys!
Pirates are here!
Pirates!
Everyone run away!
Pirates are here!
Pirates!
Terrible news!
Pi... rates...
The pirates...
...are just a lie!
Oww...
You exaggeration-spewing kid!
I'm gonna get you today for sure!
Stay right where you are!
I'll show you a thing or two!
Here they come!
Here they come! Here they come!
Get back here, you damn kid!
Just try and catch me!
Come and get me!
Dammit! He got away again!
He's one hell of a troublemaker!
He's in trouble if I find him!
Where the hell'd he go?!
Another job well done today!
I sent the wind of excitement
into this boring village!
There he is!
Oh, it's you guys!
Good morning, Captain Usopp!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
Pepper! Carrot!
Is it just you two? Where's Onion?
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Oww!
Terrible news!
Onion...
What's he freaking out about?
Terrible news! Terrible news!
Terrible news! Pirates are here!
There's a boat with a skull
mark at the north shore!
Yeah, right!
It's the truth!
T-The truth?
It's true! This is bad!
Oops! It's time for my snack!
Don't run away!
Actually, I have "I'll Die if
I Don't Eat My Snacks-iosis"!
Liar!
Don't you want to be
a real pirate, Captain?!
What good is a pirate
who's afraid of pirates?!
If I recall correctly,
it was Buggy the Clown's mark!
B-B-Buggy the Clown?!
I think I'll just...
But it was two small boats!
And three people or so...
Alright! Let's go, Usopp Pirates!
To protect this village's peace!
Alright, let's go! Follow me!
R-Right!
Finally on dry land again...
There's a village past here?!
Yeah. It looks like it's
a small one, though...
Oh! In that case, meat, meat!
Meat, meat, meat!
There's a place to eat
in this village, right?!
Forget about meat
for a minute, will you?!
Huh?!
Careful!
I sense people!
Where?! Where?! Where?!
Look out!
So cool!
Is this the time to be impressed?!
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
People praise me--
and then praise me more--
as "Captain Usopp"!
Huh?
If you're thinking of attacking
this village, then forget it!
My 80 million subordinates
won't sit by quietly!
Awesome!
You're lying, aren't you?
Yikes! She saw through it!
See, you admitted it.
I admitted it to her!
What?! He was lying?!
Curse you, you crafty tactician!
80 million may have
been an exaggeration,
but I do have great men
under my command!
Like maybe three people?
She saw through it!
R-Run!
H-Hey, you guys! Don't run away!
I've never heard of pirates
using slingshots before!
You're neat!
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
I'm a very proud man!
Because of my great
pride, people call me...
"Proud Usopp"!
You saw it yourself just now!
My slingshot skills are far
greater than your average pistol!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
Huh?!
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
What you're looking at
now are real pirates!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
Huh?!
I'm saying those aren't
for threatening people.
R-Real pirates definitely have way
more punch behind their words...
Awesome...
We stole those lines!
Eh?
From Shanks, a pirate I respect!
S-Shanks?!
You know Red-Haired Shanks,
the great pirate?!
Yeah.
Your dad's Yasopp, right?
Eh?
Yeah, Yasopp is my old man...
But how do you know that?
"Food"
Good, huh?!
I met him when I was a kid!
So my old man's on Shanks' ship?
Yep! You guys look the same,
so when I first saw you, I wondered...
Really?!
My old man's on such
an awesome ship?!
I dunno about now,
but I bet he's still with him.
After all, your dad was
a good sharpshooter!
Awesome!
That's nothing. I could even shoot
an ant right between the eyes!
Y'know, Luffy,
I got a kid named Usopp,
just about your age!
You've already told me
lots of times! I'm sick of it!
What?!
Well, I'm gonna keep on
tellin' you more about him!
It was sad to say goodbye,
but there was no other choice!
There was but one reason:
the pirate flag was calling me!
Stuck! Stuck!
Usopp. I heard enough about
you to make my ears sore.
Yasopp was a great pirate!
Yeah, huh?!
I'm proud of my old man, who leapt
onto these possibly endless seas...
...to live with his life on the line!
Then that makes this easier!
Do you have any friends in this
village who know how to sail...
...and anyone who
can supply a big ship?!
As you can see, it's just a tiny village...
Sorry, but we can't
live up to your hopes.
On the top of the hill...
There was a huge mansion.
Say! Do you know them, Usopp?!
Think you could ask them
to help pay for one?
You can't go there!
I-I just remembered
something I hafta do!
I have lots of influence here!
Eat and drink as much as you want!
Alright! Later!
Why was he in such a rush?
You wish to see Usopp?
Not this again...
May I? I want to talk to him.
That will not do.
That man is the village's
biggest exaggerator!
For someone in your weakened state,
Usopp's exaggerations
would be too much to handle!
But...
Your late parents firmly
instructed me to protect you...
...to the fullest of
my abilities, Miss Kaya.
Now then, I'll leave
your medicine here.
Please be sure to take it.
Cheapskate.
"Cheapskate" will do just fine.
What's bad is bad.
Pardon the intrusion--
Usopp-san!
Heya! You seem as down as ever!
I'm sorry!
I'd really like to invite
you in as a real guest...
...but Klahadore refuses to allow it...
He's not a bad person, though.
Don't sweat it!
After all, I am a brave
warrior of the sea!
I'd only feel cramped inside a house!
So what adventure are you
going to tell me today?
Hmm, let's see...
Alright!
The story of when I fought the
giant goldfish at the South Pole...
...when I was five!
Goldfish?
Yeah! What first shocked me...
...was the immense size of its poop!
It was so big that I landed on it,
thinking it was solid ground!
Is this really the place?!
Yeah, the pirates dragged him inside!
We gotta save him!
But they're real pirates!
They might've grilled and eaten him!
You idiot!
It's old hags who eat people!
Alright! Get ready, you guys!
This will be the most epic battle
since the Usopp Pirates' formation!
Yeah!
The Usopp Pirates have arrived!
What're they?
The captain is gone!
You don't think he...
H-Hey, pirates!
What'd you do with
our Captain Usopp?!
--What'd you do with him?!
That meat was yummy!
Meat?!
Don't tell me the captain...
W-What?! What did you do?!
If you're lookin' for your captain...
...we ate him.
Old hag!
What're you looking at me for?!
You just had to say something stupid!
Whew, it was just a joke?
Huge!
If our captain ran off at
this hour, he'd be here.
Oh? What's he come here for?
To lie!
That's a bad thing!
He's not bad! He's great! Right?!
Yeah! He's great!
How does that work?
Kaya, the girl who lives here,
is weak, and she's had depression...
There was a ship
stopped near the goldfish,
and on it was a pirate
bigger than even a mountain!
ever since her parents died
from an illness a year ago.
His face was hilarious!
Even though she has lots
of money, she's so sad.
So our captain tells his special
made-up stories to make her laugh!
'Cause our captain's
the best at telling lies!
Never heard of a pirate with
a face like that, have you?
Oh, so he's great!
Yeah!
I like the captain's meddling side!
I like his bossy side!
I like his exaggerating side!
So that's helped her
feel a little better?
Yeah, a lot better!
Great! Let's ask her for a ship after all!
It's thanks to Usopp
that she's gotten better.
Just getting in is impossible!
There are way strong
guards at the gate!
--Huh?
--Where'd Luffy go?
I'll go ask!
Wait, you're not gonna--?!
Gum-Gum...
H-His arms stretched!
He's a monster!
...Pardon...
--Hey!
--Wait, Luffy!
...the Intrusion!
...And so we escaped into the sky
atop a gigantic slingshot ball!
Huh?
Yahoo!
That worked great!
Did not!
A-Are you all right?!
Yeah! It's okay, it's okay!
They're new recruits who heard
all about me and came from afar...
...to join the Usopp Pirates!
No, not me!
I'm here to ask a favor!
A favor? Of me?
Yeah!
--We want a big ship...
--You, there!
What are you doing?!
Klahadore...
I don't appreciate you breaking
in here without permission!
Who's he?
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Who does that butler think he is,
treating people like thieves?!
Yeah! We only came
inside to get a ship!
That has "thief" written all over it.
That weird guy's way more suspicious!
What's that ring?
Hey, look! That butler is
with him! What's going on?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Weirdest Guy Ever!
Jango the Hypnotist"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!