Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After being ejected from the Sabaody
Archipelago by Bartholomew Kuma,
Luffy was separated from
his friends and arrived alone
at the female-only empire of Amazon Lily.
Big Sis!
Big Sis! What happened?!
What in the world happened?!
Oh, I, uhh...
He saw my back.
After seeing the secret hidden on the
back of Pirate Empress Boa Hancock,
Luffy was caught by the Kuja Pirates
and taken to a fighting arena.
Love-Love Beam!
Hey...!
Hey, you! What did you do to them?!
They saved my life, you know!
This is the warrior nation of Amazon Lily.
The strong are beautiful.
Fight your hardest and perish.
We will watch and see you off.
You guys are screwed up.
That woman...
She turned your comrades into stone,
so how can you all sit
there and laugh like that?!
Th-The savage is yelling at us!
Unbelievable! What a vicious creature!
I feel bad about those three,
but the Snake Princess was
right to do what she did!
They're the ones to blame! They
broke the rules of our land!
Whatever I do,
I will be forgiven.
The reason for that is,
yes...
...because I'm beautiful!
You piss me off!
These guys have powers?
"A Difficult Fight for Luffy!
The Snake Sisters' Haki Power!!"
Execution! Execution!
Execution! Execution!...
The younger sisters'
Snake Pit Dance is about to start!
I can't wait to see Marigold-sama's
"Salamander" with my own eyes!
"Youngest Sister, Marigold Snake-Snake
Fruit, Model King Cobra"
And Sandersonia-sama's
"Eight-Headed Serpent"!
"Middle Sister, Sandersonia
Snake-Snake Fruit, Model Anaconda"
How magnificent she looks!
She was a strong warrior
to beat the Gorgon monster,
and this is proof of it!
The cursed younger sisters are lovely too!
Cursed? What're they talking about?
They look like they've
eaten Devil Fruits to me.
He's finished for sure now!
I can't wait anymore! Hurry and start!
Execution! Execution!
Execution!...
Perhaps I should swallow him whole...
Or squeeze him to death...
Don't tell me he's scared stiff!
Just stand there and die!
Hold on! Time out!
What? Going to beg for your life?
Apologizing now won't
make your crimes go away!
No, it's not that.
What's going on?
Look!
There!
You're not cracked, are you?
Wait here, you guys!
Sorry you got turned
into stone because of me!
If Chopper were here,
he could've examined you right away,
but maybe you'll go back to normal again
like when Aokiji turned
me and Robin into ice!
Are you sure you shouldn't be
more concerned about yourself?
Shut up! I can do whatever I want!
That man...
Is he trying to save Margaret and the others?
That can't be!
He's already been sentenced to death!
Alright, then...
So I just gotta kick your asses now, right?!
What a joke!
What did he just say?!
He intends to beat the younger sisters!
Hilarious! Making people laugh
after being sentenced to death!
Men really are hilarious!
Is that okay, beating you up?
Yes, that's fine!
If you haven't given up on your life yet,
then I'll warn you in advance:
I wouldn't fall into the pit between
the seats and the ring if I were you!
You can fall if you'd like,
but the bottom is filled with blades, so...
Are you ready to go now?
Yeah! All set!
Good.
Then let's begin!
Kill him, Sandersonia! Marigold!
Through combat,
give him the ultimate punishment
for the great crime of sneaking onto
our maiden island and offending me!
I've been waiting for this!
I guess he has some skill...
Get him, Marigold-sama!
What the...?!
Poison?! That was close!
Wrong! It's powerful poison!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
It bounced off!
That hurts!
How...?! I'm made of rubber!
See! He really is all bark and no bite!
But it's true that men stretch! How neat!
Huh?! Am I not rubber anymore?!
No, that's not it!
Then why do impact blows hurt?!
That's not fair, Mari!
You're hogging him all to yourself!
I want to have some fun with him too!
Why does that hurt?! I'm made of rubber!
Come to think of it, that axe guy also...!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Hoisa!
Wh-What the...?!
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
It's exactly the same!
But he didn't have powers!
Does that mean it's not a Devil Fruit power?
I take it you have powers, too.
A Paramythia type, from the looks of it?
I knew it!
Why are you lying and saying you're cursed?!
That's a secret we can't tell anyone,
not even an opponent about to die.
Damn!
But I take it you can't use Haki?
Most outsiders can't.
That's why you're weak.
Left kick...
Over here!
She read what I was going to do!
Snake Slam!
Yes!
That one didn't hurt.
Same as usual.
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Snake Dance.
What amazing moves!
With Sonia-sama's Haki,
there's no attack she can't dodge!
You're very straightforward.
I can read you like a book.
What's going on?!
She's guessing my every move!
Focusing entirely on offense
is nice and all, but...
Snake Stick!
Ouch!
Don't forget that there are two of us!
Not good!
He's falling into the pit!
Something seemed unnatural
about that just now...
That man...!
Th-That was close!
So close!
He should've just kept falling!
However tenacious he is,
he still doesn't stand a chance
against the younger sisters!
They're at the very top of the Kuja Pirates!
The Snake Princess put
her hair behind her ear!
Her loveliness knows no bounds!
This man is the very definition
of "nothing but talk."
I can't help but laugh.
Shut up, you dumbass!
Oh, my!
He spoke abusively to
the Snake Princess again!
Unforgivable! Hurry and kill him!
Sonia! Mari!
End that man's life at once!
To ensure there are no further outbursts...
...from his filthy mouth!
I was hoping to have
a little more fun with you,
but you heard our big sister!
It looks like playtime is over now.
Let's give the criminal despair and death!
Margaret!
Hey! What're you doing?! Don't touch them!
What if she breaks?!
She saved my life, you know!
We are going to break her.
You said she saved your life.
Then that's all the more reason to.
I feel bad for her,
but this is your punishment.
Don't be stupid!
This duel is between me and you!
Stop it!
Above.
Hey, you!
Damn! Let go!
You're the only one who
thinks this is a duel.
This is a public execution!
Just sit there and watch!
The emotional trauma you gave our
sister goes much further than this!
Everyone here looks up to the Snake Princess!
She's strong, noble, and the most
beautiful woman in the world!
The Pirate Empress, Boa Hancock!
Hey! Stop it!
She looked up to you guys, you know!
Everyone in this land does.
So I think this is what she would want!
The hell it is!
What are you, stupid?!
Oh, my. What crude language.
After her, we'll break the other two as well.
Nice and slowly, too.
That'd make it more painful
for you too, right?
Here goes!
Three...
Hey! Stop!
Two...
Stop it! Do you hear me?!
It's no use.
One...
Margaret!
I said stop!
The warriors are fainting!
Could this be...?!
What a relief!
She isn't hurt anywhere!
Oh, I guess you guys are sensible after all!
That was the Conqueror's Spirit just now...!
This can't be real!
Only one out of a million
people can master that Haki!
Only a chosen few can use it!
I've never seen any person who
can use it other than our big sister!
This boy has the "qualities of a conqueror"
to stand above others!
He has the Conqueror's Spirit, just as I do?!
How can this be?!
Is he no mere boy after all?!
Just who is that guy?!
What's everyone blabbing about?
What's the big deal?
He doesn't realize he used Haki?!
I guess he hasn't figured
out how to control it.
Alright!
You showed me you're strong!
Now let's get on with the duel!
Luffy activates Second Gear,
and the sisters respond by unleashing
their true Snake-Snake powers.
Sandersonia's hair turns into giant serpents
while Marigold cloaks her body in flames,
and the sisters continue their attack.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"All-Out Special Power Battle!!
Gum-Gum vs. Snake-Snake"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!