Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Hit him with the light!
What the heck are you doing?!
Jerk, I'll get you for this!
What is that?! My shadow?
Hey, don't do it!
I've obtained 300 million
Berries' worth of might!
Now I can complete the greatest
Special Zombie in history!
"The Warrior Known as the 'Devil'!!
The Moment of Oars' Revival!"
Now Straw Hat Luffy belongs to me!
At last! I've finally obtained
the ultimate subordinate!
L-Luffy...!
What just happened? Did you see that?
That's his shadow! He cut off Luffy's shadow...
His shadow...? Didn't that skeleton,
Brook, mention something like that?
He stole Luffy's shadow?
Is he the one who took Brook's?
I can't believe it... How did he do that?
Hey, Kumacy! You were mumbling
something again, weren't you?
Didn't I tell you to zip it?
Get it through your head!
I'm tired of repeating myself!
You're not cute when you talk, so don't talk!!
You're too harsh on Kumacy.
You're beary harsh.
Why are you goofing off, punk?
"Shut up" means "be quiet"!
This shadow will bring me one step closer
to becoming the King of the Pirates, Hogback!
It's been a decade since we first met.
I put all of my prowess into creating
No. 900 for a day such as this!
With that shadow in it,
I'm certain it'll become the
most powerful zombie in history!
It will be a great asset!
The day I become the world's
"King of the Grave" is close at hand!
I can practically see the day I turn
the cute critters of the world
into zombies and make them
serve me in my dream kingdom.
Right! You can command absolute loyalty
from the shadow of the nastiest bastard!
The world will transform into a
land filled with obedient zombies.
If I'd had a subordinate as powerful as this,
that idiot Kaido never would have
defeated me in the New World.
Let's wake him up!
Gyoro! Nin! Bao!
Yes, Master!
Open the door to the special freezer!
Right away, Master!
Wait for me, No. 900.
I'm bringing the ultimate shadow down to you,
so be quick about making
me King of the Pirates!
Spider Mouse!
Sir!
Toss Straw Hat Luffy's body onto the ship.
Don't forget to remove the spider silk.
We can't have him dying on us.
--Roger!
--One moment! I need to make a report!
What is it?
Captain Tararan, the spider monkey,
was just defeated!
He was defeated?
It's not as though the foe removed his shadow.
But that's exactly what happened!
He lost his shadow?!
R-Right!
Absalom, there is only one
man who could do that...!
The Humming Swordsman!
It sounds like Hildon's report
was accurate after all.
What a disaster!
It looks like the Humming Swordsman
is removing shadows wherever he goes.
We've already suffered heavy losses
before anyone realized he was here.
At this rate, we're going to relive
the nightmare of five years ago!
What?! We have to go back to the ship?
You mean Sunny?
Right. The worst they'll do
to your captured crewmates
is steal their shadows!
But it's not as though that's fatal.
Just look at me! I'm a prime example.
Oh, I actually did die!
But that's a different story!
When ya get down to it, it's not
like losing your shadow'll kill you.
Precisely! But the thing is,
everyone falls unconscious
when their shadow is snatched away.
They won't awaken for two days.
The stronger the person,
the sooner he is put on a ship
and kicked out of Thriller Bark.
Why do you think they'd do that?
To prevent the victims from returning
to the island to recover their shadows?
Bingo!
Then why don't they kill us
when we're out cold?
They can't.
This is important, so pay attention!
For starters, even if you separate
a person from his shadow,
they are still of one mind and body.
If the human dies, the shadow will disappear.
That means the zombie will die then as well.
That wouldn't serve the enemy's needs!
Hence they always keep the human body alive.
So even if your friends lose their shadows,
I promise they will get sent
back to your ship alive!
The worst case scenario would be for
the two of you to fall victim as well!
It would mean that all of you are doomed
to wander the ocean without your shadows!
Awaken your friends while
there is still time to act!
This is the only chance you get to look
for a way to recover their shadows.
Did you understand all of that?
I see. Everything sounds logical enough.
Here, guys, take this.
What is it?
The zombies' weakness!
You saw how effective it was in my
battle against this spider monkey!
What's that?!
It's the zombie's "soul."
His soul?! But I can see it leaving his body!
C-Captain!
It's high time you returned...
...to your rightful master!
This is their weakness? What exactly is it?
It's salt.
Salt?! If we gotta purify
the things to take 'em out,
are they some kinda curse?
Well, I suppose they are in a way.
The zombies were originally
animated thanks to a Devil Fruit.
Salt holds the power of the ocean.
So just as a power holder
grows limp in the ocean,
the salt breaks the fusion
between a fake soul and a body.
Makes sense! So that monkey spewed out
the shadow that was inside of him, right?
That never would have occurred to me.
To reiterate, please stuff salt into
a zombie's mouth to defeat it!
That's the trick! Even for this
bag of bones, that's a snap!
--Snap! Snap! Snap!
--But Brook...
Why are you so knowledgeable
about the zombies and this island?
That has to do with when I lost
my shadow five years ago...
Naturally, they sent me back out to drift at sea.
Fortunately, I was able to
turn back by the time I awoke.
And thus I returned to the island and fought.
I faced the zombie who holds my shadow!
But in the end, I lost miserably.
I fled for fear of my life.
No matter what...
No matter what, I did not want to die!
I am the sole survivor from my ship!
Someday I must pull out of the Devil's Sea
and carry out the promise I made to my friends!
So I ran for my life!
But ultimately, extending my
life did not resolve anything.
So I am done running!
Until I defeat that man and recover my--
Well, you'll have to pardon me.
I'm in a hurry. Take care!
Stop right there!
On top of everything you've told us,
answer this one question before you go.
The Humming...!
Grah, the Humming Swordsman!
Damn it! He's the only person to have
figured out my zombies' weakness!
Huh? Huh? How did he figure
it out in the first place?
What is she doing?
And how did he come back--
Hey, Cindry-chan! Why do you
keep standing in front of me?!
Humming Swordsman...
I've heard about him, but what is he like?
Perona! Don't you know what he looks like?
That would explain how he
slipped through your recon.
So it would seem.
Master, the seed of trouble
has returned to our island.
That's none of my concern, simpleton!
You can deal with him!
H-Hey!
Sorry for the wait!
Now then, let's go to the freezer!
It's freezing!
Sir...! The present condition is such...
Stupid! You should have mentioned that first!
If that's the case, he should
buy us plenty of time.
Sir!
Come report to me if there
are any other problems.
Now go toss Straw Hat out!
Roger!
Ready, go! Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
Heave, ho! Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
Heave, ho! Heave, ho!
--Luffy!
--Stupid! Don't pop out!
He won't die just because they took his shadow!
Remember Brook!
Uh huh...
Kumacy, hurry it up!
Coming!
We can't leave now! Let's bide our time.
They're going to do something
with Luffy's shadow.
We gotta find out what!
We can worry about recovering it later!
That duo is long gone.
Where did they go?
I never expected them to defeat Tararan!
Whoa, there!
Oh, here's the spot!
Jeez! Did you get lost, Jigoro?
Off my back! Now where are my foes?!
Let me face them now! Give me enemies!
Franky...
What is it, punk? I'm not crying, you dummy!
Don't look at me!
What compelled you... to ask him that?
Shut up! I can ask whatever I want!
Gosh darn it! I freaking love that skeleton!
You'll never find a better guy!
Darn it all!
You sure won't.
They really are scary!
Th-The Humming Swordsman... is terrifying!
I was so scared...
But I won't give up!
I will never, ever give up!
Never!
I will recover my shadow!
I can't wait!
When I saw his corpse in the Land of Ice,
my body wouldn't stop trembling.
It's breathtaking when you
think that this terrifying beast
used to terrorize the seas 500 years ago!
--Cold!
--When he conquered a nation, he'd carry
the entire island back to his domain.
It's said he created a kingdom of thugs.
I was so close to the famous giant
known as the legendary "Continent Puller."
I-I'm freezing!
Where the heck are they going?
Beats me, but I think they said
something about a special freezer...
That explains it!
The Land of Ice? A corpse?
I never dreamed I'd get to see
that legend with my own two eyes!
This is a zombie creator's--
Hey, Cindry-chan! Why are
you walking in front of me?
Yet another legend shall come back to life!
Long time no see, No. 900.
Now, it's time for him to awaken!
He is the only berserker to have
gone down in history as a "Devil."
Oars!
What's going on? They put
Luffy's shadow in that giant!
We've finally uncovered the
secret behind the zombies.
Ouch! Let go! What's your problem?
Nami, what's wrong?
It's that invisible man again!
Nami, you're... vanishing!
Wh-Why...?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Awakening After 500 Years!!
Oars Opens His Eyes!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!