Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After the Straw Hat crew
rescued the mermaid Camie,
they met Rayleigh, the craftsman they
were looking for, at the auction house.
Roger turned himself in.
I'm not going to die, partner...
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Do you think you can do it?
The Grand Line still far surpasses
anything you can imagine!
Your foes will be powerful, too.
Can you rule this mighty sea?!
I'm not gonna rule anything!
It's the freest person in this sea
who's the King of the Pirates!
I see...
"No Escape!?
Admiral Kizaru's Light Speed Kick!!"
Take care!
Don't do anything crazy!
Yeah! Same to you guys!
Say bye to Hachi for us, too!
How over-the-top. We're going to
see them again in three days...
It's always sad to say goodbye.
See you later!
Well, then. I should be off, too.
Okay! We're counting on you!
Still, it was a real shock
to run into a member
of the Pirate King's crew
in a place like this.
He's a real intimidating guy,
for an old geezer.
Well, he is the most
renowned man in Roger's crew!
So that's what crewmen on
the Oro Jackson were like...
I am boomingly proud of the fact
that I helped the man named Roger!
I'm glad to have met him!
I didn't know you were the type
to respect your superiors...!
W-Well, sometimes I do!
Hey.
Wanna go to the amusement park?!
Shut up, you!
Do you even understand the situation?!
You still haven't learned your lesson?!
I want to go...!
Not you guys, too!
It's Admiral Kizaru!
The only thing to do now is run!
Get the pirates!
Hello?
There are wanted men everywhere!
Watch out for the ones
worth over 100 million!
--Run!
Hello? This is Kizaru. Hmm? How odd...
"Navy Headquarters Admiral --
Kizaru (Real Name: Borsalino)"
Hello?
That's odd...
Th-This is really bad!
Th-There's still a slight chance!
If by some luck I can take him down,
I'll suddenly become famous!
Huh?! Don't be an idiot!
This is the navy's greatest
military force we're talking about!
Hello? Do you read me?
--Now! Take this!
--S-Stop...!
Hello?
--H-Hey!
--Damn! I'll get you this time!
Huh?! What the...?!
I definitely hit him that time!
It went right through his head, right?!
How odd...
He's obviously got some kind of powers!
Guns ain't gonna work on him! Let's run!
Say, I was wondering if you could help me...
I'm looking for a man named Sentomaru...
He's a subordinate of mine, you see...
Sheesh. All I did was ask a question...
Uhh, I think Kizaru-san is
going a bit overboard...
He knows better than to break
the Hustle Muscle Mangroves!
I think I might've overdone things a tad...
Talk about crazy...
So that's Admiral Kizaru, huh?
Apoo-san! We're in danger, too!
We should really get out of here!
You're such a fool.
Where's the fun in slinking away?
Nothing beats running away
after making an enemy mad...
What are you planning to do?!
Come on! Pick up the pace!
A lot got away...
Yeah.
Requesting backup at the harbor!
What's happening?!
I don't know!
I don't know why,
but all the soldiers have
turned into kids or old people!
What's going on?!
Oh... My aching back...!
A masterpiece!
It was her doing!
It was Jewelry Bonney!
She has a bounty of 140 million!
Which one do you prefer?
What happened?!
Hello?! Respond!
Watch out for the rookies
worth over 100 million!
I repeat, watch out for the
rookies worth over 100 million!
You're Capone Gang Bege,
worth 138 million, aren't you?!
You can just forget about setting sail!
Where's your crew?! Gone off on their own?!
You're one unlucky bastard! Give yourself up!
In terms of troop strength, you lose!
What's this commotion?!
Captain Hawkins!
There is no need to hurry.
Fate has already been decided.
Say, I was wondering if you could help me...
K-Kizaru?!
--W-We'll keep him busy here!
--Please escape, Captain!
Don't panic. I will not die today.
How do you like that?! You're charred black!
Get back, Kid Pirates!
Oww! So hard!
Room.
Shambles!
I got you now!
Oww! Huh?
How irritating!
How about this, then?!
Troublesome bastard...
It's not over yet, Eustass-ya!
Looks like you still
haven't had enough of me!
I'm telling you, we should
hide in the amusement park!
Liar.
You just wanna go and have fun!
It can't be!
Who're you?!
Enemy attack!
Hurry it up!
Commence attack! Cannons, ready!
Open the gunports!
Commence bombardment!
What?!
Fire!
What the...?!
There's stuff inside his body!
It turned big--!
What's going on?!
He didn't do anything himself!
Cavalry! Charge!
Something else is coming
out of his stomach now!
Troops keep coming out!
I-It's horses this time!
Capone Gang Bege!
What the hell power does that guy have?!
Firing squad! Aim!
What's this smoke?!
Father! There's too much smoke!
I told you you don't have
enough troop strength!
Get outta here! Hurry!
I still haven't eaten enough...
I'm sure there'll be good food
on the next island, too!
Hey! Did you hear?!
A Warlord of the Sea has joined the attack!
Are you serious?! Who is it?!
A Warlord?!
I was fully expecting an admiral...!
I guess quietly passing by Navy
Headquarters is out of the question.
But...
...I have my pride to think of, too!
Please, just escape, Captain Hawkins!
Captain Hawkins!
Combat: Chance of Defeat: 100%.
Say, can you help me?
Escape: Chance of Success: 12%.
I'm looking for a man named Sentomaru...
Defense: Chance of Evasion: 76%.
Hey...
I know no such man.
Ask someone else.
Well, actually, if I can't find him,
then that leaves me with spare time...
And if I'm not busy,
I obviously can't let a wanted man go...
Especially one like you,
with a 249 million bounty...
..."Magician" Basil Hawkins!
Speed is weight!
Have you ever been
kicked at the speed of light?
Captain!
We're ready to set sail!
Alright! Let's scram!
Wh-What happened?!
H-Hey! What happened?!
I don't know! He suddenly went flying!
This guy's strong, all right...
Whoa! He's still going!
H-Hey! What happened?! He just suddenly--!
Where'd the attack come from?!
Captain!
Impressive. You far surpass what I imagined.
That's odd...
To think two would be destroyed already...
Against an admiral,
ten isn't enough to feel secure.
That's "Mad Monk" Urouge!
That's not all!
That's Bartholomew Kuma,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea!
I'm at a loss! What strength!
There's an even stronger foe to worry about.
You can't be serious! That's Kizaru!
What tragic fate!
A navy admiral ahead, and a Warlord behind!
Is this the end of the line?!
Not necessarily. I do not yet see
the shadow of death upon you.
You don't say...
Hawkins, of North Blue, huh?
Thank you for the joke, foe as you may be!
What the...?!
Someone else has joined the fight!
That's...
"Red Flag" X. Drake!
Why is he here?!
Is that the extent of your power, Mad Monk?!
You, again?!
Rear Admiral Drake.
Crap! I hadn't planned
on running into Kizaru!
I've taken quite a beating,
but let's find out now if
I really have any hope left or not!
I think I'll start with
a small counterattack.
Look! Things are really crazy now!
This is great stuff!
This is really dangerous!
They're all going to die!
This is our chance to escape!
Are you crazy?
The real fun is just about to begin!
Who're you?!
--Get back, Luffy!
--He's one of the Warlords of the Sea!
A Warlord?! How come you guys know that?!
Don't let that attack hit you!
It's a shockwave!
What is this?!
He can do this, too?!
Hey! You lied about it being a shockwave!
That was...
...a beam!
This is no time to be excited, you morons!
Bartholomew Kuma! Why are you back?!
That bastard...!
Wait, is he the guy you said
showed up on Thriller Bark afterward?!
Yeah, that's him!
Things got real bad when he hit us with
shockwaves from the paws on his palms!
He had planned to wipe us out there...
...so he must've come back
when he found out we survived!
You gave us plenty of trouble back then!
Coup de Vent!
Did that work?!
No, the guy's still right as rain...!
Luffy-san!
Second Gear!
We know he's strong,
so let's go all-out at the very start!
Guess we have no choice!
Something's off here...
He seems different from last time.
Is it just my imagination?!
Let's go!
What's taking so long?!
The warship should have arrived already!
How odd...
Why hasn't Uncle Kizaru contacted me yet?!
He better hurry.
They're going to...
...get rid of all the rookies!
Is he that different from the Warlord
of the Sea that we met before?
Yeah. The real one would've
teleported and dodged our attacks.
So he's a fake?
But that's the real problem.
That'd mean there are two
guys who're this strong.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Overwhelming!
The Navy's Fighting Weapons, the Pacifistas"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!