Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
However, 10 years ago, in the East Blue...
What did you do?!
Ace!
Don't do it!!
"Where can freedom be found?
A Sad Departure of a Boy!"
Dadan!
Stop it, you sea cretin!
Let go of Ace!
What are you guys doing here?
Finally we found you!
These are pretty serious
wounds, Luffy! Are you okay?
Dogra...
I don't see Sabo anywhere!
Sabo went home. He's not here.
Ace!
You're the boss monkey from Mt. Corvo!
I'm the mountain bandit - Dadan!
I don't know why but I'm registered
as their foster parent.
I won't stand by and watch someone
try to take my boys' lives...
...even if I'm not their real parent!
I'll just let you go if you back away.
If you don't, I'll have
to resort to violence!
Try it!
Oh yeah? Alright then...
Run!
Yes, boss!
Hey, what're you doing?!
Ace, hurry up!
Ace!
I...
...won't run!
What're you saying, Ace?!
Don't try to fight him!
Bluejam is a real villain!
He's not a guy that a kid like you can beat!
--L-Let me fight, too!
--No, Luffy!
You all, why don't you
take Luffy and go ahead!
B-Boss!
I'll take responsibility
for bringing Ace home!
Boss!
Go!
--Y-Yes, ma'am!
--Ace!
Boss! Come home safely!
A woman and a child.
If you overestimate your
ability, you'll only get hurt!
Only the strong and the
cowardly survive in wars!
The brave always die.
Is that so?
What a fool!
Damn!
I'm a dead man! The fire
is all over the place!
How could this happen all of the sudden?!
--It's hot! It's hot!
--There's no way out!
We have to give up!
What just happened?
There's a path!
The explosion left a path!
I don't know what's going
on but this is great!
Hey look, there is a ship!
I see a ship!
This path leads up to the shore!
We can get away by following it!
Let's go before the fire returns!
How awful they are to burn the
area and the residents there!
By the way,
how did you know the situation in such
an outlying country in the East Blue?
Is there something special
about this country?
This country is an example of how
the world will be in the future.
There can be no happiness in a world
where the undesirables are thrown away.
Someday, I will change the world!
If I stay here... I'll never be free!
Even in a country like
this, there are children.
Those of you who are willing to
fight for freedom, come aboard!
GOA KINGDOM "ROYAL PALACE"
HIGH TOWN
Did they find Sabo?
I just called in the military.
They'll find him soon.
I see. Sabo is giving us
a hard time, isn't he?
Yeah...
Is this town really safe?
It looks like the fire will
engulf the town any minute!
Isn't there any way to enter High Town?
No, there isn't.
They don't even allow a bug
to enter - nobles only!
--Boss!
Ace!
Boss!
Ace and Dadan didn't return
from the burning Gray Terminal.
Easy, easy, wait, Luffy. You're not
recovered - where're you going?
I gotta go and look for Ace and Dadan!
You can't do that!
Ouch!
See? That's what I told you.
You're seriously wounded. You
have to rest nice and easy.
There are a lot of troops
in the Gray Terminal now
to take care of the mess after the fire.
It's not just burned junk
that they're throing out,
but survivors, too.
They're gonna kill you if you go there.
But...!
I wanna see Ace!
I know that Sabo is worrying about us, too!
THE FORMER SITE OF THE GRAY TERMINAL
What a great view!
How can you be so happy?
It's a pain in the butt
to clean up this mess!
If we find a survivor, we're
to shoot them on sight.
There aren't any.
But there aren't as many dead
bodies as I thought there'd be.
It was a big fire. It could've
burned out the bones.
I was nervous yesterday,
thinking that the
fire might get to this side of the wall.
They say that Bluejam's
ship was on fire, too.
It's nice to know that
those villains got burned!
It's morning!
Hi! it's a nice day, isn't it?
Yes, it is a lovely morning!
There are still so many of them!
Enough with this game of tag, okay boy?
No matter how many times you
run, you can't get away, Sabo!
All the police and troops
have a picture of you now!
You will never get out of High Town...
or even out of this house!
You two, change your uniforms and
start working here as guards.
But we have our duties...
There is nothing that a nobleman can't do.
I'll get the approval of your superiors.
Sabo, you must barricade
yourself in your room
and educate yourself in your role as a noble!
No!
As you know, I can make things
happen just by giving the word.
So I can take care of
you or those two easily.
Am I understood?
Dad...
Ace... Luffy...
So why don't you mend your ways
and study hard like Stelly.
And...
...study so that you can make your parents,
who brought you into the world, happy!
Because that will make you happy, too!
Don't you think so?
Father!
Don't worry! I'm here for you!
You're so dependable, Stelly!
Okay, Let me buy you some luxurious clothes
for the ceremony the day after tomorrow.
There, we'll see the
Celestial Dragon in person!
I'm... helpless!
Okay, that's it for today.
I'll check your homework tomorrow.
Okay, have a nice day!
Ace... Luffy...
I don't think that you died in the fire.
You guys are okay, aren't you?
I wish I could see you.
But I know I'll put you guys in
danger if I try to see you now.
This place is like a birdcage!
I don't think I can stand living in
this country filled with stale air.
What is freedom?
Where can I find it?
Your shift is over.
Is it the time already?
You shouldn't be sleeping on the job.
Sorry. By the way, how
are things in the town?
The ceremony is just a day away, right?
It's crazy. People are going
wild getting ready for it.
What bad luck!
It's a once-in-a-lifetime
thing but I got to be here.
This boy and I will be the only
two in this house tomorrow.
I wanted to see the Celestial Dragon.
It depends on your attitude.
All the citizens will be
at the harbor tomorrow.
It'll be such a pain to stand guard there,
compared with this baby-sitting gig!
Then, why don't you take my place?
No way!
Alright, we're leaving now.
Take good care of Sabo.
Yes, sir.
The day of the World Noble
from the Grand Line's visit
to the Goa Kingdom has arrived.
A lavish ceremony is prepared
for the arrival of the ship.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
Hello, this is A-team on the coast.
The Celestial Dragon's ship
will arrive in a few minutes.
Roger that. It's all quiet here.
We'll continue to stand guard.
Clank!
Hey, look! There is a ship leaving port!
--What?
--Is it a fishing boat?
Hey! Come back here! Don't get
in the way of the ceremony!
It's a child! There's a child on the ship!
A child? I wonder which family he's from.
A child?
Honey, could it be...?!
No, that's impossible! The
guard is looking after him!
What a nice day! It's
perfect for setting sail!
Oh no! That's mine! Somebody
stole my fish boat!
Look! He has a black flag on it!
Does he think that he's a pirate?!
No way! A kid can't just become a pirate!
--Where is he heading?
--He's disrupting the ceremony.
The Government's ship will arrive soon!
Hurry up and do something!
Y-Yes, sir!
Hey!
Kid, come back here now!
The scariest fate for me is to
lose myself in this country and...
turn into someone else!
I'm not gonna go back!
Is it Sabo on that ship?
The Government's ship is here!
The ship is huge!
I'll die if I crash into it.
Let's avoid that.
Good. He's turning away.
It seems like the commoners are welcoming us.
Yes.
They're so blessed that
it's rare to even see them!
I can't believe that a real
Celestial Dragon is on that ship!
By the way, what is that?
That looks like a fish boat.
It'd be nice to be captain
of a ship like that someday!
Commoner!
How rude is that!
The fishing boat has been hit!
Ace and Dadan return to their hideout.
As everyone is rejoicing
over their safe return,
they learn of the tragedy
that struck Sabo at the port.
Realizing with sympathy
what Sabo had tried to do,
Luffy and Ace are befallen
by regret and grief.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Take Good Care of Him! A
Letter from the Brother!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!