Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome treasure
at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King of
the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
The horizons everyone dreamed
of were separate at first
but now they can be seen through
a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny is
leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve your
dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
In order to prevent Luffy
and Nami from reaching the ark,
Eneru released Mamaragan. However...
It's useless, Eneru.
The land won't be beaten!
Luffy was approaching the ark.
Hand over... the golden bell!!
"God"
Disappear with the land!
Raigo!
Gum-Gum...
...Fi... re... works!!
Gold Peony!!
Clear up!!
Straw Hat! Ring the "fire of Shandora"!!
Luffy finally reached the ark, and at the
end of the fierce fight with Eneru...
Well then, I'll ring you as well!!
"God"
Gum-Gum...
...Gold Rifle!!
Reach!!
"The Battle Ends! Proud Fantasia Echoes Far"
Can you hear it?!Old diamond-head! Monkeys!!
The city of gold... was right here!!
That bonehead did it!!
How beautiful...
What a pretty sound! What is this?! What?!
I believed that this
moment would come one day.
So this was the ring that Noland heard.
Suu... I wonder if Vearth is singing...
So God really... exists?
What a miracle!
I had half given up on the bell
ringing again after its 400-year silence.
Great Warrior Calgara... Can you hear...
...the echo of the fire of Shandora...?
What happened to this land?
What is this tone? Could it be...?
Is this the legendary...?
Are you hearing this... Montblanc Noland?
Sorry to have kept you waiting so long.
I hope...
...this reaches your descendants!
You like this bell's sound, too?
Old-timer! Th-This is...
Yeah! There's no doubt about it.
There's only one bell in this
world that echoes this far!
This is romanticism.
From the sky...
I'm getting worked up.
About the monsters that appear with
the cumuloregalis clouds,
there used to be a story like this.
When there is a human far up in the
sky and strong sunlight shines on him,
his figure is reflected in the
deep mist of the far sky.
The shadow looks as if it's a huge monster.
So the true form of those monsters are the
shadows of the humans in the sky?!
Then does that mean that we've
already confirmed that people live in the sky?
Yeah.
I thought the story was a meaningless fantasy
and I'd forgotten about it,
but it seems that it was true.
I can hear the loud ring of the golden bell.
The city of gold really exists in the sky!
"Noland The Liar"
Noland wasn't... My ancestor wasn't a liar!
You rang it to tell me that from the sky...
...right, kid? I appreciate it!
"Monkey"
Old-timer?!
What's the matter?! Are you sick?!
Those kids... I'm glad they were safe!
I was... so worried...
Look!! That's...
God's ship...
It's God!!
They're sinking...
God Eneru and his ship are...
...sinking...
The bell's ring is the fire of Shandora,
a long-gone city that took
pride in its prosperity.
The island's singing voice that proclaims
the end of the battle...
The promised ring was delivered
after 400 years...
Although the journey of the
restless island was long,
it's hard to forget the distant memory.
Long ago, people entrusted their words
in the sound of the bell.
They placed proud words in the
song sent to the distant sea.
Comrades...!
It rang...
Yeah.
I wonder... if the old
guy and the others heard it.
Yeah, I'm sure.
We're... right here!!
Tie the ropes to strong-looking trees!
Aisa... Were you worried?
Here... your treasure!
I don't care about that!
Laki...
How's everyone else?
They're fine! Don't speak right now...
Someone's there!
Am I still alive?
No! You have to get treated right away!
My treatment can wait.
Before treating me, do something about
that guy, or he'll die.
You're right! His body's falling apart,right
down to the bones. This is terrible!
Hey, that's one of the guerrillas.We
don't owe him anything.
Yeah. I don't really know why, but
it seemed like he was going all out, so...
Huh? What the heck?Are you
feeling sorry for him?
Who knows...?
Um...
Is he gonna be okay, Raccoon-Doggy?
I'm a reindeer! Look, I have antlers!
Don't worry. He'll survive.
Thank you!
Pierre, go and rest with
those Blue Sea people.
Pierre, hurry up and go bring the families!
So, in the end, both the golden bell
and Eneru's golden ship...
I think they fell.
So now it's a city of gold in name only, huh?
Which means our journey in poverty continues.
I'd want those dials rather than gold,
since we won't be able to get them once
we get back to the Blue Sea.
In any case, I wonder
if Nami-san's all right.
I wonder where Conis-chan is...
Is it okay to leave Wyper with
the Blue Sea people?
Don't worry. It seems that Aisa
made friends with them.
At any rate, we have to hurry.It's
pointless if our enemy wakes up.
Gather those who can move.We'll
banish the priests to the clouds.
Yeah!
Are you done with him?
Yeah. All he needs now is rest.
Yoo-hoo!!
Luffy!
Nami-san!! Conis-chan!!
Luffy!!
Everyone! I'm glad you are okay!!
I was so worried, but I couldn't do anything.
Conis-chan, so you were worried
about me that much!
I don't think so.
Is that food, you guys? Where'd you get it?
We found the priests' food storage on
our way back through the forest.
There were more.
But how did you get down from that height?
We used my Gum-Gum Balloon.
By the way, Conis, where's your old man?
Hm?
Well... um... he protected me...
...and then Eneru...
Don't tell me...
Conis-chan...
Conis-san...
Conis...
Hey, we're talking about you!!
I'm sorry I'm still alive!
Father!!
In the White Sea on the lower level?
Yes. I found myself thereafter
being knocked off.
Those who came down to the lower level
heading towards Cloud End
are also coming back to the White-White
Sea via restored Milky Roads right now.
However, since there's no
Angel Island anymore,
they're heading towards Upper Yard.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much, God!
I'm no longer known by that name.
You were all forced to work in a place like
this for six long years. I'm sorry.
We lost Angel Island, the home we
were supposed to return to.
The Shandians, too, lost their
home,Village Hidden in the Clouds.
Is the battle really over?
God's army is gone, but...
Chief, is the 400-year rift something
that can be filled so easily?
Boy, I stuffed myself!
It's totally night now.
Shall we go back to the ship now?
Nami, what're you saying?!
Huh?! If we go back to the ship,
we can have a long relaxed sleep
in a warm bed, right?!
Hey Usopp, you heard what she said?
Yeah, it's terrible. Not
thinking anything after seeing that,
you're unqualified to Be a
pirate-- no, to be a human!
"That"? What're you talking about?!
What the heck are you talking about?!
I'm returning... to where God should be...
Things that obstruct my field of
vision cannot exist in the sky.
You all were in my way.
I won't let anyone have
it. It's fit just for me.
It's a boundless land, just like a dream.
Now, let's set off, Maxim...
To God's world that floats
brightly in the night...
To the land without end, the Endless Vearth!!
Where am I?
Inside the ruins of Shandora.
Gan Fall!
Oh, you shouldn't move yet.
You... are a Skypiean!
Rest.
Chief! Were we captured by the Skypieans?
There's no distinction
among those injured in battle.
The golden belfry... We still have the
duty to protect it to the end!
This is...
...the sound of drums announcing a battle!
There's fire on the ruins, too?!
Don't rush, Wyper. Wait a little and
see how things turn out.
No matter what kind of heroic reason for the
fight there was in the distant past,
to us who live in the present
time,this sky is our home.
The land, at least, is not refusing anyone.
But at this very moment, there's actually...
Right... Go ahead and check
it with your own eyes.
Right now, no one wants to fight.
It's party time!!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens as you wander about
Just like the moon,you
keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection
wanes as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who
spend countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
Hold our true motive in
your hearts and speak not of it.
Where did you learn those words?!
So these are the words
engraved on the belfry...
The ancient weapon Poseidon?
Why was Gold Roger...?Could
the Rio Poneglyph be...?!
We're pirates, you know.Now,
let's snatch the gold and run!!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"I Made It Here! The Yarn
the Poneglyphs Spin"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!