Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
What do you think you're doing?!
Stop that!
What are you doing to my sea charts?!
"Fishmen" and "sea charts" this,
"circumstances" that...
I don't know about any of that...
...but I'm gonna destroy everything!
Gum-Gum...
...Battle-Axe!
Nami!
You're my friend!
Yeah!
"Setting Out with a Smile!
Farewell, Hometown Cocoyashi Village"
Arlong Park has fallen!
We're free!
Free!
Everyone! Celebrate! Dance!
Arlong Park has fallen!
We've lived these
past eight years for this!
We've lived so we can smile today!
We're gonna party 'til we drop,
even into tomorrow and the day after!
Lady!
Chabo...
I just saw Arlong Park for myself!
It's awesome! It's in pieces!
Pretty awesome, huh?
Yeah! The guy who did
that must be really cool!
Who was it?! The guy who
beat Arlong is here, right?!
Yeah. Right over there.
Which one?! Which one?!
The guy with the straw hat.
Are you sure he saved the island?
Unbelievable as it may seem.
Meat! Is there any more meat?!
He's still at it.
Sounds like ol' Zoro's really hurtin'.
Well, yeah.
A normal person with those wounds
would take two years to fully heal!
You fool!
Trying to take care of such
a big injury on your own...!
Oww!
Honestly! Are you folks really pirates?!
Don't you even have... a ship doctor?!
A doctor? That sounds good, too!
Luffy?
-But a musician comes first. Right, Zoro?
Why's that?!
Pirates sing, you know?
So why does that come first?!
Hey, Doctor. Where's Nami?
She doesn't seem to be here...
Nami, huh?
If you can't find her around,
then she's probably "there."
What?! You're still here, Nami?
Your friends've been
looking for you, you know.
Say, Nojiko, Gen-san.
If Bellemere-san were alive,
do you think she would
stop me from being a pirate?
A pirate?!
Give me a break!
Of course she'd never let her
precious daughter be a pirate!
She wouldn't stop you!
Nojiko!
Even if she did...
...would you really listen to her?
Absolutely not!
I see...
What's with you, Gen-san?
You two are definitely
Bellemere's kids, all right.
Gen-san?
Nami. You've already
made up your mind, right?
Then live how you want!
Just as your mother did!
I'm sure that's what
Bellemere wants, too.
Whew, I'm stuffed!
Sometimes it's nice to only eat!
Are your wounds all better now, Zoro?
This's nothin'! Some food
and drink'll fix it right up!
Yeah?
But how long is this
dumb party gonna last?
This is the third day now!
What's wrong with that?
When you wanna celebrate,
you should go all out.
Hey, Sanji! That melon you just had!
Was there something on it?!
What's with the meat in your hands?!
Sure was. It's "raw ham melon,"
so there was raw ham on it.
Raw ham melon?! That sounds yum!
W-Where did you get it?!
Dunno...
The whole village is a buffet party,
so I dunno where I got it...
He's long gone.
He's been eating non-stop
for three days straight!
Now, then. I'm done eating.
Now I think I'll...
...pick up some girls!
I am Captain Usopp...
Way to go, kiddo!
...hero of love and courage...
Can I have your autograph?!
...who finished off the
strongest fishman boss!
Here's an Usopp Support Song!
Who was it? Who was it?
Who beat the fishman?
Hmph. How boring.
What is?
I thought you'd be
more down in the dumps.
Like, "Why didn't this happen
before my dad died?!"
That's how I felt at first.
But now I'm thinking about the future.
The future?
We've been saved by that
straw hat guy and his friends.
But starting tomorrow, we have
to start from scratch on our own.
There's no way we can forget
what's happened in the past,
and I don't think we need to.
But, I think what's most important
is what happens from now on!
What we do now.
What things we need to do.
We're the ones who're gonna
support the villages now,
so I decided to think that way instead!
Cheeky kid!
Oww!
Why're you pinching me?!
I don't understand! Why?!
And here I was hoping to harass
you some more for good measure!
You've harassed me plenty,
you dumb tattoo punk girl!
"Punk" will do just fine!
Will it come off?
I'd like to say, "No problem,"
but there's no way to remove it fully.
There'll be some scarring.
That's how tattoos are.
Yeah. I know it's stupid of me.
They stay on for life.
I don't want anyone to see this!
This... this tattoo...
I'm not even really Arlong's friend...
...but it's like I've
been branded a pirate!
Nami...
Nojiko! What is that?!
Oh? You mean this?
It's no big deal! It's just a decoration!
Now me and you are the same!
Say, Doctor.
There's a tattoo I'd like to have...
Here.
Those two can dance!
Here's Usopp Support Song #185!
Bellemere.
Your daughters have grown up
to be truly strong and respectable!
It's almost as if I'm
seeing you in life again!
What?! You're going to be a marine?!
There's no use trying
to stop me! I'm going!
My mind's set!
We're going to live life
to its fullest from now on.
We've lost and sacrificed far too much.
Which is why we're going to smile
as insanely much as possible now.
Raw ham melon!
Huh? There's no food around here.
That's no good. Time to go back.
Hold it, boy!
A grave? Did someone die?
Yeah. A long time ago.
Oh, my deepest conveniences.
Huh? Deepest concussions.
Huh? Deepest compli--
Deepest condolences.
That.
Hey, boy.
Nami is going to ride your ship.
She's going to be a pirate.
It'll be a dangerous journey.
That's fine. There's no way around that.
But, if you guys ever do anything
to take away Nami's smile...
...I will come kill you!
Yeah. I'm not gonna
take it away, though.
Got it?!
I got it!
Usopp Support Song #368!
Who is he? Who is he?
He's the coolest guy in the world!
His name is Great Captain Usopp!
"I'm leaving this behind.
This belongs to all the villagers. --Nami."
Wow! Today's a big feast!
Do you two know what today is?
Today is the day I first met you two!
It's the day you two
became my daughters!
Wow!
C'mon, stop crying!
A storm destroyed
the orchard. So what?
You need to be strong girls who
can smile even during hard times!
Do that, and then nice
things will come to you!
It'll come, I promise!
Nami! Could you get me the salt?
First you learned how to draw
sea charts, and now land maps!
I'm studying navigation too now!
Navigation, too?!
It is Nami's dream!
I'm gonna use my navigation skills
to travel to all the world's oceans!
And then I'm gonna make a
world map of everything I see!
So your map of this island is your
first step toward your dream, then?
Yeah!
It's all over, Bellemere-san.
It took eight years,
but we're finally free!
Me, and all the others...
It's exactly like you said.
"If you live through it,
nice things will come."
You were right!
All the villagers are smiling so happily
from the bottom of their hearts!
And me! I'm thinking
of leaving this island!
It's all right! Don't worry!
They're really pleasant people,
and pretty strong, too!
For eight years, I drew
lots of charts and maps...
...but this is the only one that's left.
But that's exactly it! This time,
I'm going to draw charts for me!
I'm going to travel the world
with them-- my friends!
That was my dream, so... so...
...I'm not sure when I'll
come back to this island...
I'm... going now.
This the last of it?
Yeah!
Alright!
Are you finished loading it all?
Yeah!
Now, then. We got lots of
provisions now. We're good to go.
We were only here a few days,
but this island's full of memories, huh?
Yeah!
We owe you a lot for
everything you've done.
We're gonna get back to our
profession of bounty-hunting again!
This is goodbye for now,
but we look forward to the day
we meet again somewhere!
Take care!
You guys, too!
Well, we should get going, too!
Hey! Hold on! What about Nami-san?!
Maybe she's not coming?
W-Why not?!
You! You made another pass
at Nami-san again, didn't you?!
Why would I do that?
No, you definitely did!
Oh, yeah. She achieved her goal,
and she has no reason to be a pirate,
You can't stand that me and
Nami-san are all lovey-dovey!
so she might be happier here.
Are you an idiot?
What'd you call me?!
What about my happiness?!
If Nami-san isn't on the boat,
then 98.72% of my reason
for being on the boat is gone!
Hey, you! I couldn't find
the raw ham melon anywhere!
Hey! Where's Nacchan?
That's the thing! Nobody's
seen her since this morning!
What?! She's leaving
all the money behind?!
The 100 million Berries?!
She left it in our house,
along with a letter.
She's planning to journey
without her money?!
But she's the one who
risked her life to earn it!
She says it's okay, because
she'll just steal some more.
Once that girl says something,
there's no changing her mind.
That fool! We're the ones who
still haven't thanked her enough!
Nami-san!
Nami!
Nacchan!
Get the ship moving!
Huh? She's started sprinting!
She says to get the ship moving.
But...!
Don't tell me she's planning to leave
without letting us
thank her or say goodbye?!
You can't be serious!
Set the sails!
H-Hey!
They're setting sail!
Wait! We still haven't thanked you!
Stop, Nacchan!
At least let us thank you!
Hold it! I won't allow
you to leave like this!
Hey. Is it okay to let her leave like this?
Why not? It's her decision.
Nami!
Why?!
She didn't!
Huh? My wallet's gone!
Mine, too!
Same here!
Take care, everyone!
How dare you?!
You damn brat!
Hey. She hasn't changed a bit.
Who knows when she'll betray us again?
Nami-san! Good!
You lousy sneak thief!
Get back here!
Give back our wallets!
You punk!
Come back anytime!
Take care of yourself!
We're grateful to you guys!
Boy!
Don't forget our promise!
Bye, everyone! I'll be back!
She got us good!
My own little sister got me!
Have fun!
Here, Genzo.
What's this scrap of paper, Doctor?
That fool. She never learns.
She got another tattoo before she left.
What mark is this?
It's a tangerine and a
pinwheel, apparently.
Huh? Gen-san!
What happened to your pinwheel?
I doubt there's any need for it now.
I'll be back!
Hold on, Gen-san!
Stay away from Nami!
No, but, I want to see her smile, too!
She starts crying because
you have such a scary face!
But what am I supposed
to do about that?
I know!
This'll make you laugh, right?!
If I always keep it here like this?!
What do you say, Nami-chan?
Look. I really don't think a dumb
pinwheel is going to make Nami...
Oh. She laughed.
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Oh, no!
What's the matter?!
The newspaper's gone up in price!
What kind of problem is that?!
Then don't buy it!
What're you saying? We hafta
know what's going on in the world!
Plus we can use the backs
of the flyers as notepads!
Oh! Good thinking!
See, like so!
Huh?! This is...!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Bounty! Straw Hat Luffy
Becomes Known to the World"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!