Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome
treasure at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King
of the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
The horizons everyone
dreamed of were separate at first
but now they can be seen
through a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny
is leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve
your dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of
the tail end to the future
"Farewell, Navy Fortress!
The Last Battle for Escape"
Not good! Not good!
Not good! Not good! Not good!
My subjugation squad!
They got you good, Inspector Shepherd.
I-I've driven them this far!
I leave the rest to you!
If they escape now, it will be
entirely your responsibility!
Entirely mine? Very well.
But you'd best report to headquarters
about a certain someone else
who kept getting in the way.
The Straw Hat pirates...
They're exactly as
Admiral Akainu described them.
As strange as it sounds, it's thanks
to them that we can now prove
the importance of Navarone Fortress
to the faultfinders at HQ.
They entered our impregnable fortress,
broke through many traps and pursuits,
and are now attempting to escape again.
But, however great they may be as pirates...
General? Oh, good.
Stand by until I give orders.
Yes, sir! Remain on standby!
Yes, sir!
Commander! Are you just going
to sit there idly and watch?!
Now, now. Just watch patiently.
The time for checkmate is nearing.
But...!
As I said, they're as good as captured.
The 9:00 pm net has
already sprung into action.
What do you mean? What is this
"9:00 pm" stuff you keep mentioning?
You'll just have to wait and see!
All right! Full speed ahead!
Our navigator doesn't seem
interested in going forward, though.
Nami-san! What's wrong?
Is there something behind us?!
Look! Navarone warships!
Whew! They don't seem to be chasing us!
They dropped their anchors?!
They must've given up.
I wonder.
They gave in to our brilliant skills!
Even when they could at least fire at us?
Don't tell me there's some other reason?!
That's what's bugging me-- I don't know!
Bugged Nami-san is lovely, too!
Commander! It's finally begun!
Good. Do as I instructed.
Was that Drake?! Then order him
to pursue them this instant!
Why are they lowering their
anchors and sitting there?!
The reason they've dropped their
anchors... is because it's 9:00 pm.
"9:00 pm" again?!
If they don't drop their anchors,
the fangs of Navarone's
waters will eat them up.
The fangs of Navarone's waters?
What's that sound?!
It sounds like a flowing river!
There's a river on this island?
I must not have noticed it this afternoon.
Can you see now?
Nami-san! What's happening?!
T-The rudder isn't working!
The tide! A huge outward tide
happens at this time at this fortress!
No!
Eaten by the waters' fangs?
However skilled a navigator
those Straw Hats may have,
the fact that they're on a ship
means they can't escape from this net.
No one escapes from my clutches.
So that's what the deal was...
What are you acting satisfied for?!
When we first tried to escape,
I was puzzled as to why they'd use
a bay so full of shore reefs as a port.
So?
It was the other way around.
Shallows are bad for ports,
so they normally use the Sea Gate
to regulate the water level inside.
But they can use the low tide in an emergency
to make this great fortress
of Mother Nature inescapable!
So that's why ships could only
come and go at specific times.
You're so smart, Nami-san!
Your logic is spot-on!
So, what do we do?
All right! Let's head for the Sea Gate!
We can't!
Full speed ahead!
Pay attention!
Luffy!
W-What the--?!
We've run onto a reef!
The hull!
It's been ripped open!
Someone come help!
O-Oh, no!
It's damn huge!
Can't we plug it up?!
A plug! Something to plug it up! A plug!
Huh?
The water stopped...
I'm drowning! I'm drowning!
The ship's completely run aground!
Does that mean--?
We can't move forward or escape.
Looks like the enemy was counting on this.
I'm drowning! I'm drowning! I'm gonna drown!
It's one thing after the
other with these guys!
What now? Ditch the ship again and run?
And go through the same stuff again?!
It's not the same! The ship's gonna
sink when the tide comes back!
The gold, too?!
I refuse to let that happen!
Save me! I'm hungry!
This is the Impact Dial!
Can we use this?!
Given how much the tide has
gone out, we won't have to worry
about the ship sinking
until the next high tide.
But we can't move, either.
Okay! Let's have some food!
How can you be so carefree?! Look at that!
Attention, Straw Hat Luffy and his crewmates!
"Full of Power!"
"Carbohydrates!"
"Navy Dining Hall"
Seems the Straw Hat pirates
got caught in the 9:00 pm net!
Not even they can escape from
the fangs of Navarone's waters!
What's gonna happen to him?!
Well... Pirates have always been
subjected to capital punishment...
You can't, not in your
condition! You're sick, Dad!
Quiet! That stupid sickness is long gone!
He better not have ruined
that wonderful ship!
If he has, I'll kick his ass!
Mr. Raccoon Dog...
You've fought most valiantly
against the Navy's great G8 Fortress!
I'm impressed, enemy as you are.
You've done admirably, but this
is checkmate, Straw Hat Pirates!
Listen! Don't you even dare
think about trying to escape!
I can anticipate everything
you might think up!
Yes! Atta boy!
As commander of Navarone Fortress,
I will greet the Straw Hat
Pirates with utmost respect!
Give yourselves up quietly!
Luffy!
Straw Hat!
You and Roronoa Zoro both
have bounties on your heads,
so I will have to hand
you over to headquarters.
But I will guarantee the safety
of the rest of your crew.
But if you even think of
escaping... I'll get mad!
Too lenient!
I'm the commander here. You're the
inspector. Be quiet and inspect.
A-At this rate, I'll wind up having done
nothing but get in the way of a badger!
I came to crush this fortress, but now
my own relevance is in question!
If you'll excuse me, please!
We still have a chance!
An Impact Dial!
When we escaped from the fortress,
I gathered a ton of impacts!
We might be able to make the
ship float in the air using this!
Oh!
Ah!
We just need to use it to go
somewhere where there's ocean!
But one shot won't be enough.
With that huge hole,
the ship'll sink right away!
If we could just make the
octopus balloon fly again...
Yeah, good thinking!
Couldn't we re-inflate it
with Flame and Breath Dials?
Yes! Yes, that's great!
The octopus isn't here...
The octopus...
The octopus.
Damn octopus...
The octopus...
The octopus?!
I have it.
He says he has it.
He has it?
He has it.
He damn has it.
So he has it.
He has it?
Yep. I have it.
Eh?!
See?
What do you have that thing for?!
It saved our lives on
our way back from the sky.
Maybe so, but didn't it feel gross?!
Gross how?
Let's have the octopus work
for us again. Okay, Long-nose?
Y-Yeah.
But hold on. I can't find my Flame Dial--
It was neat, so I was playing
with it in the kitchen!
Oww! You moron!
Now, then! That just leaves us
with who'll fire this Impact Dial...
What's with those looks?!
Whose Impact Dial is that?
Usopp's.
Right, Long-nose?
It's only natural that the suggester does it.
You're so wonderful, Usopp!
I really respect you!
Oh, come on. We'll help you out.
Y-You can't be serious...
Then it's decided!
No!
General! Prepare to open fire!
Yes, sir!
Prepare to fire!
Preparations complete!
Good work, dear.
Work is important, but you need
to eat at the proper times, too!
But broccoli and carrots
and green peppers aren't--
No, I haven't finished work yet!
The Straw Hats are sealed off so completely--
surely they can't do anything now.
Now you just need to capture them alive.
Yes... But they could still
defy all our expectations.
How can they possibly escape,
trapped between land and sea?!
Where did they appear from?
Eh?!
They still have the sky.
All set here!
Roger that!
Things are ready up here!
Take care of things down there!
No! I don't wanna!
This's gonna hurt like crazy!
Three!
Two!
One!
Damn you, Straw Hats!
You've embarrassed me to no end!
I will crush you all myself!
Impact!
They are flying!
Those guys...
What?!
How do I put this...?
We're falling! We're falling! We're falling!
Robin! You're up!
Cien Fleurs!
We're still falling!
Luffy! The Flame Dial!
All right!
Inflate, you!
Usopp-sama! You got another order up!
D-Don't be stupid! I'm not a tofu seller!
I'll make you some damn
tres bien tofu sometime! Okay?!
You can't be serious!
Fly!
Please, please, please fly!
I said fly, so fly!
You can do it, Mr. Octopus!
Whoa! What now?!
Water's getting in!
Urgh! All right! Usopp-sama's
going for another one!
Support my shoulders and arms again...
Well said!
That's how you do it!
This pain is the Going Merry's pain!
Three!
Two!
One!
Fly!
Fly!!
Impact!
A giant octopus?!
You gotta be kidding me!
It worked!
A hot-air balloon, huh?
Hmph, so you refuse to listen to me?
Shoot it down when it's within firing range!
But do not shoot the ship itself!
They must be caught alive!
Those are some tall orders...
Fire a warning shot!
If they don't stop, aim the
second shot for the balloon!
Understood!
I refuse to let you escape, Straw Hat!
Not yet... The first one's
just a warning shot!
It's all over!
You've done it again, Major Shepherd...
He's gone...
Mr. Raccoon Dog and the others are flying!
Just like I told ya! They fell from the sky!
Awesome! It really is a hedgehog!
What an impressive-looking fortress!
This is goodbye, old man!
Adieu, Jessica-san!
Are we gonna be okay?!
Won't we get shot down at this speed?!
This fortress is for
protecting the peace at sea.
They don't have cannons
that aim into the sky.
Dear...
They finally got away.
Oh, General! Are you all right?
Yes, Commander! The battery has
been ruined, but no one is injured!
Glad to hear it! Good work!
Commander! Let's go after them!
Order a search-and-destroy!
They escaped into the sky. Give it up.
But--!
Lt. Commander Drake. You did well!
Thank you for your hard work!
Commander...
Oh! Major Shepherd!
Commander!
Are you going to blame this on me?!
This was all your fault!
I'm going to contact headquarters
and make sure your heads
roll and roll and roll and roll!
Even if you are Admiral Akainu's lapdogs,
my report will bring this
outdated hedgehog down!
I'm going to make it so none
of your men remain in the navy!
I don't kiss!
You dumbass!
"Justice"
Are you sure about this?
You let the Straw Hats escape...
Yes. I didn't invite them here,
plus we achieved our primary goal.
Eh?
Don't you get the feeling that
everyone here has started to unify?
I have noticed it, actually.
That's good enough. They gave
a good jolt to this fortress.
I'm aware that headquarters
thinks we're unnecessary.
That we're "too big,"
that we're "peace addicts"...
But that's fine with me!
What's most important is that
we soldiers and you support staff
work hard to protect
the peace, don't you think?
There are still pirates out
there like the Straw Hats.
Headquarters will probably be
reminded of the need for this fortress.
I won't let you all get
thrown out into the street.
Have you fallen for me again?
You dummy...
But do you think he'll give a
good report to headquarters?
I got carried away and slugged him...
It doesn't matter! Besides,
I was going to hit him, too!
Well, then, Straw Hat. How far will you go?
There are people at headquarters
who express interest in you.
Your road ahead won't be an easy one.
Flying feels so nice!
How far are we gonna fly?
How should I know? Ask the octopus.
It's nice to enjoy a leisurely trip
through the sky sometimes.
But no more navy bases!
As long as I'm with Nami-san and Robin-chan,
everywhere is heaven!
Moron.
Huh?!
I said, "Moron."
Well, then! Guess I'll
get to fixing the hull!
But I sure am hungry!
Sanji! Food!
I'm hungry!
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,
on the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give in,
even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared of,
we can overcome it
That fortress was so fun!
But where are we gonna land
this time? I feel so uneasy...
An island's been visible for a while.
Why couldn't you say so sooner?!
Man, how dull!
Are you referring to me?
No, I'm sorry.
It's the island that's dull.
What's with this island? What is this?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Great Adventure at Long Ring Long Land!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!