Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
After a great adventure,
Luffy and his crew finally
reached the sky island of Skypiea.
However, Nami's group was taken
away by "Heaven's Judgment,"
and Luffy's group, on their way
to God's Island to get them,
encountered trap after trap...
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Meanwhile, Nami's group,
which was taken to a sacrificial altar...
He has priests on this island too, you know!
Anyway, we can't make God angry!
It's common sense, you know!
Sorry, but...
...I've never once prayed to God.
And so, Zoro's group left Chopper
behind and entered the forest...
I'm the one in the most danger!
"10% Survival Rate! Satori, the Mantra Master!"
Where is this God, anyway?
If he's a god, he might have already
foreseen our actions long ago.
Things'd be a lot faster if he came to us...
I'd rather he not show up!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
The god on this island is horrible!
Oh, Lord... Please stay nice and peaceful...!
Oh! And please let us find some treasure...
Is that what you care about?!
Anyway, walking along the
river won't get us anywhere...
We should cross and check out the other side.
Yes.
But how?
Use a vine to swing across like before?
Or do we climb a--
Damn! They're here, too?!
F-Forget it! I am not crossing this river!
We'd pretty much be feeding
ourselves to the skysharks!
But there's no guarantee we can get across
even if we keep walking along the river!
I said forget it!
If you're gonna go,
then you can go alone, Zoro!
If you're that scared, you shouldn't
have come in the first place!
Say... This ground...
What about it?
It's dirt.
Of course it is. It's ground.
This is a sky island.
You're right.
It isn't all fluffy...
Eh? Oh, right!
Sky islands are made out of island cloud...
It feels like such a long time
since I've touched dirt like this...!
Why is this island different?
In any case, it's certain that
this is an unusual sky island...
Looks like checking into
it might be worth a lot...
A Level 2 Crime, huh?
Who do you take God for?!
Choose an ordeal...
We shall present it with our own hands...
Sin is living in ignorance.
The means to attaining peace
do not lead into Heaven...
"Swamp Ordeal"
Swamp!
"Iron Ordeal"
Iron!
"String Ordeal"
String!
"Ball Ordeal"
Ball!
Choose an ordeal!
So, what do we do?
Alright! Let's go with "Ball"!
Why's that, Luffy?!
It sounds fun!
That's your reason?!
These are ordeals!
They're not gonna be fun!
No, but I agree with "Ball."
It's the only one that
doesn't sound too violent...
I mean, "swamp" makes me think of...
I'm sinking! Someone!
I get the feeling that once you sink,
there's no coming back up...
Then what about "Iron"?
They're gonna hit us!
Denied! That sounds totally bad!
Then what about "String"?
It sounds easy, and not too bad at all, but...
High up!
N-No!
Its easy sound makes it seem suspicious!
"Ball Ordeal"
A huge ball!
Squish!
It sounds round and soft,
but it's the most likely to be a trick!
We really need to think this over!
There's no time to be wishy-washy!
We're already there, anyway!
Let's go with "Ball"!
A-Alright! Guess I'll go with
Luffy's hunch on this one!
Then it's decided.
But don't let your guard down.
We're on God's Island,
10,000 meters up in the air!
Anything could happen here!
Let's go! Ball!
Hey, now! Don't shut your eyes, driver!
Even when they're open, it's pitch black!
Say, there's other stuff like this, right?
Like what?
You know how there were four entrances?
Maybe one of them was the right one,
and the others were wrong?!
Eh?! What?! Don't say that now!
What happens if we chose the wrong one?!
If it's the wrong one... Hmm...
Maybe we'll fall off the sky island?
Don't be stupid! We can't fall off!
It's 10,000 meters to the Blue Sea, you know!
You could reflect on your life
multiple times on your way down!
Even falling has it limits!
Quit bein' idiots!
That's obviously not gonna happen--
No! You gotta be kidding me!
We're alive...
I seriously thought we were
gonna fall 10,000 meters...
It's all because you said
misleading stuff, Luffy!
That was scary! I thought I was gonna die!
Still, what is this place?
They're balls...
They're small "island cloud" balls...
Awesome! It's like big snow!
What a weird place! It's so neat!
The Milky Road leads above the trees...
But what part of this is an ordeal?
Who knows?
It'd be great if there's nothing at all,
but I doubt that's the case...
Maybe we got the right entrance?!
I bet if we chose the wrong one,
we'd be in trouble right about now!
Y-Yeah! You might be right!
Right?!
Idiots, don't let your guard down!
Would you really let criminals get off free?!
Give things some thought!
There might be traps like earlier...
Stay sharp!
Let's just keep moving...
I'm thirsty! Let's have some tea!
Huh? Yes, let's! Open up
the rice crackers in your bag!
Ooh, good idea!
You guys!
C'mon, just one rice cracker!
Yeah! Let's eat, let's eat!
No! Listen! I'm gonna keep steering.
You guys keep watch on both sides!
It took us really high up at some point...!
But it's strange...
There are four priests,
so I assumed each entrance led to one...
...but I guess not.
Hey! Usopp! Pass!
Okay! I got it! Pass!
I told you to keep watch!
A snake!
You jerk! Get outta here!
That was a shock! Why...?!
Sanji! Look out! A cloud!
Kick it far away!
Dammit! Are all these
floating things snake eggs?!
This isn't good...
What's the deal with these balls?!
There's no telling what will come out!
These clouds are called "surprise clouds"!
Surprise clouds?!
Heso!
Who're you?!
Thank you for choosing my "Ball Ordeal"!
"Skypiea Priest
Satori of the Forest"
Who is this dumpling freak?
Don't tell me he's a priest?!
You're the ball ordeal?! A ball?!
Quit dancin'! Who the hell are you?!
Wow, he seems dumber than I expected...
Didn't Nami and the old guy
say they were really strong?
Hey! Dumpling!
Nami-san and the others are safe, I hope?!
Do you mean the sacrifices?
If so, I wouldn't know.
Even if they're left alone, they're going to die!
Even if they manage to escape,
they're still going to die!
Say what?!
You should worry about yourselves.
Just so you know, you'll of course
need to beat me to continue ahead!
Okay! Here he comes, Luffy! Get 'im!
Alright! I'll shoot him down!
Gum-Gum...
Oh, you're going to stretch?
...Pistol!
No way!
Luffy!
Luffy?! Hey! You're alright, right?!
Regular hits don't work on you!
Hit?
It is a bit different from a hit!
I'll show you different!
An upper kick with the right foot...
Collier--! What?!
Only the well-trained are
given the power of "Mantra"!
Impossible! He predicted my movements?!
Sanji!
It is different from a hit!
Impact!
The shock destroys the body from the inside!
D-Dammit! Sanji! Usopp!
Yeah, I'm alright...
But what the hell was that?!
No idea at all...! He's mysterious!
My name is Satori!
I am one of the priests of
the almighty God Eneru!
I own the Vearth in this Illusion Forest!
Illusion Forest?
Yes!
This forest!
And...
...your boat will be lost in its illusions!
The boat is taking off!
Your boat will now speed along
this forest's Milky Road at random
and eventually leave through
this forest's only exit!
I'm sure you realize it, but losing a dial boat
is the same as losing your
way to the sacrificial altar.
So you must find and board
the boat before that happens.
Of course, these countless surprise
clouds and I will not allow that.
Welcome to the sacred ground of Upper Yard!
This is the Illusion Forest Ball Ordeal,
with a 10% survival rate!
10% survival rate?!
Zoro! Nami! Robin!
Don't leave me all alone!
Please come back!
Who'll save me if I'm suddenly attacked now?!
This is all because Luffy wanted
to go to the sky island...
I'm sure Luffy and the others
are headed here in search of us.
Oh, yeah! Luffy and the others are coming!
Oh! Then I just need to endure it until then!
I just need to play it safe and
wait for Luffy and the others!
In the meantime, I'll fix the ship!
Zoro did ask me to!
Alright!
When Luffy and the others find out
I'm handling the ship fine alone...
The hammer!
I-I have to go get it...
But...
You'd better hurry before the boat
goes deeper into the Illusion Forest!
Hey! We gotta go after the boat
before we lose sight of it!
If we lose it in this forest,
finding it again'll be tough!
Wait, Usopp! The same is
true if we get separated!
Luffy! What about you?!
You guys stop the boat!
I'm gonna take care of the ball guy!
In your dreams! I'm filled
with good fortune and pride!
I guess we do need someone
to stop that potbelly freak!
Don't do anything reckless!
He's got some weird powers!
We'll come back once we stop the boat!
Right!
Hold it right there, Ball!
Grabs a branch...
Gum-Gum...
The same as before.
...Pistol!
What's wrong? I thought you
were going to take care of me?
I said I will... and I will!
I won't miss this time! Gum-Gum...
A fake punch, followed by a kick...
...Whip!
Again!
Gum-Gum...
Where is it?! Where'd the Crow go?!
We gotta catch the boat, quick!
Dammit! Can't see from down here!
Alright!
Watch yourself, Luffy!
These priests are no ordinary people!
Let's find the boat ASAP
and get the hell outta here!
U-Urgh... I-I'm stuck...!
How stubborn.
Even if we're far apart
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
You have a friend here to share the pain
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
I won't let it just be a dream
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Crap! At this rate, we're gonna lose the boat!
What are these surprise
clouds and this ball guy?!
Sky fights are strange!
This is no time for crappy ordeals!
We gotta save Nami-san and Robin-chan!
Zoro! Nami! Robin!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ordeal of Spheres!
Desperate Struggle in the Lost Forest"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!