Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesome treasure
at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be King of
the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
The horizons everyone dreamed
of were separate at first
but now they can be seen through
a single telescope
A bitter compass of destiny is
leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieve your
dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse of the
tail end to the future
How's it look?! Have we lost them?!
Looks like they've given
up. I can't see them.
Really? Good!
Anyway, that monstrous cannon sure scared me!
Where the heck were they hiding that thing?!
A cannon?!
Yeah, you know, that huge thing that
the warriors were carrying.
Oh, that...
"Oh, that"?! Hey, it's no
laughing matter! It was really scary!
He's right! Don't laugh!
Ah! There they are! It's Nami and Conis!
What?! Nami-san!! Conis-chan!!
Ow!
Are you all right?!
Of course!!
"Off to the Blue Sea!!
Finale Woven by Feelings"
What? They rushed off of the island?
Yes. We couldn't even give them our gift.
How disappointing...
I wonder if they even realize how much
we appreciate what they did.
Exactly. They have no idea how I feel.
It's not fair, Aisa... that you
alone got to say goodbye to them.
Everyone's in an uproar that we
let our saviors run away.
But Luffy and the others told
me not to tell anyone.
Did you say anything to them?
Yeah! I said, "Thank you."
Hey Laki, did you know?Luffy's
body stretches!
He'd be like, "Gum-Gum Pistol!!"
Hey, Aisa, don't move!
I didn't know there was a strong warrior
like him in the Blue Sea, too.
I wanna be like him, like "Gum-Gum...!"
Aisa...
Let's just trim your hair for
today. Let your hair grow.
What?
I'm sure it'll look good on you.You're
a girl, so you should look cute.
Cute?! Me?!
That's right... since there won't be any
need for you kids to carry arms...
...and since you can now live
freely,like people in the sky should.
You're ladylike today.
Now, don't move, Aisa!
Ladylike Laki!
Aisa!
Great Warrior Calgara...
We were told that the Shandians' role
had been fulfilled.
And I'm sure your wish was delivered to
your best friend as well.
We no longer have to make future
generations shed blood.
The battle is over...but
we won't lose our pride!
So please continue to watch over us.
We swear that we will not let the fire
of Shandora go out ever again!
I am the Sky Knight,a
freelance soldier-for-hire.
This land won't need such a thing anymore.
What this land needs now is
someone to govern it.
I'm saying that I'd like
you to be that person.
You're the best suited for it. This
city belonged to your people from the start.
What's this all of a sudden?That's
not a good reason.
With this battle, I think everyone
must have realized...
...that no one can own Vearth.
"God" is our support.
The name of the land is Skypiea.The
name of the city is Shandora.
The only person who can unify them is you,
who continued to be anguished by
the battle in this land.
Sky Knight Gan Fall... I would like you
to take the seat of God again,
and support this land
whose scar is still deep.
We'd like you to, as well!
Gan Fall-sama!
If it's you, we'll accept it, too!
Yeah!
Gan Fall!
God!
Please come back!
Honestly...
Just when I thought I could finally really
enjoy growing pumpkins...
Everyone! We can see it now!
Please look to the front! It's Cloud End!
Ah! Let's see!
I see... So we can go back down from there?
We got here sooner than I thought.
So we're going back down, huh?
Yeah, now that we're about to go
back, I admit I hate to leave.
It's time to say goodbye to
this pure white sea.
The sky island was fun...
though it was scary.
So once we go through that gate,we'll
be heading straight down
to the Blue Sea via a Milky Road, huh?
I wonder if we can visit
the sky island again...
Hard to tell with this place.
Well then, everyone! I'm
sorry!We'll say goodbye here!
Please take care, everyone!
Thanks for seeing us off!
Conis-chan! Take care of yourself!
Say hello to the others!
See you!!
Thanks for everything!
No, we should be thanking you!
I'll never forget you all!
Conis, old guy and little white
one! You all take care!!
Yes!
Now, furl the sails immediately and
hold on tight to the ship!
Alright! Do as the old guy said!Sounds
like it's gonna go pretty fast!
Yeah, we're sliding from
a 7,000-meter height! Hurry up!!
Okay!
Wh-What?! What?!
He says, "Don't forget about me."
Oh... That's the South Bird we
brought to the sky with us.
Now, Captain! We got the
log for the next island!
Yeah! Once we get off from here,we'll
start on a new adventure again!
Guys! You ready?!
We're gonna go back to the Blue Sea!
Yeah!!
Everyone! Be careful while dropping!
While dropping?
Heso!
Here we go! The sky island's famous
Octopus Balloon!
It's an octopus!!
You son of a...!
Ow-ow...
Wh-What?! What the...?!
Hey, look! This is so cool!!
What the hell is this?!
It's a balloon!
This is fun!
We've slowed down!
I... I thought that I was finally gonna
go to the netherworld.
Ring it! See off the saviors
of this land by ringing the bell!
Heso!
Luffy! See you again!!
Come visit us again!!
Thank you!!
Go back to the Blue Sea safely!!
When you look up, you see the sky.
Is this God's Land on the clouds
a dream or reality?
10,000 meters far up in the sky...
If you listen carefully, you
can hear the sound of the bell.
It rings today, and it
will ring again tomorrow.
The sound of the bell that echoes in the sky
glorifies and sings about
the wandering land...
This is cool!
Yeah! This feels so good!
You're calling off the search?!
It's just natural, right?!The
city of gold was in the sky.
We won't find anything at
the bottom of the sea.
This is the end.
There's no point in staying here.
Old-timer...
I really thank you all... for joining me
to pursue my dream for years.
What're you saying...?
Don't treat us like strangers...
Say, you guys!
What kind of romanticism shall
we go after next?!
"Noland the Liar"
We'll follow you to the ends of
the earth, old-timer!!
Gold! Gold! Gold! Gold! Gold!
We've finally become super
rich!!What shall we buy?!
How about buying a huge bronze statue?!
You moron! What's the point
of exchanging gold with bronze?!
We should increase the number of cannons!
Let's buy ten of them! Ten!
Nami-san! I want a lockable refrigerator!
Don't be stupid! What're we gonna do
when we get hungry?! I object!
I... I... I want you to buy me some books!
I want to read medical books
from other countries!!
That's just why we should
buy it, you dumb ass!
Hey, hold on a second, you guys!
We'll split the treasure
once we get back down, okay?
Please buy books for me!
If we buy whatever you guys like, I have a
feeling that it won't do us any good.
Navigator...
I wonder where this ship is heading.
Where? The next island...
What?! What?!
What's the matter?
What's the matter, Nami-san?
Darn! We started riding an air current at
some point and now we're drifting!
Air current?!
Come to think of it, there is a wind...
Is that a problem?
Of course it is! As it stands, we
don't know where on the sea we'll land!
What're we gonna do? In this state,I
can't set the sails and control the ship.
Well, don't worry. We'll just head back to
the next island once we reach the sea.
You just blurt things out
casually, as always...
But...
What is it, Sanji-kun?
Well... I guess it was my imagination.
Hm? What're you talking about?
No, nothing...
There's a problem! Hey!
Oh, it was just a dream.
What's with you?!
I'm gonna cut you into
fillets,you damn Moss Head!
You scared me!
Now, now, Zoro's tired, too,after
the battle in the sky, so...
The sun's completely set now.
But it's a nice view.
Yeah, you're right.
Hm? Is it morning?
I just said that the sun set!
It's taking quite a long
time to get to the Blue Sea.
I'm so worried about how
far the ship will drift.
Then shall I sing a love song
or something to take your mind off it?
Shut up!
It'd be quick and easy if we drifted
to Raftel, wouldn't it?
Usopp! That'd be cool!
That's not possible.
To get to Raftel, we still have to go
more than halfway around the Grand Line.
Uh, well, yeah... I know that.
In any case, I'm so bored.
When are we gonna reach the sea?
Oh, just go to sleep.
If you're bored, come
here,too, Zoro! This is fun!
Oh? Luffy?
Where did his voice come from?
It sounded sorta far off.
Luffy! Where are you?!
I'm over here! Everyone, come up here, too!!
This is fun!!
Ugh! So he is up there!
Awesome! This is awesome!!
Hey! Don't be reckless!Our
lives depend on that balloon!!
Don't worry! Don't worry!
No, Luffy! Come back down!
Hey Luffy, stop it!
What's the matter all of a sudden, Sanji-kun?
This octopus is shrinking!If we
don't do anything, we'll fall!
What?!
Hey, Luffy!
What's going on?
He said this octopus is shrinking!
What?!
Now that you mention it,it
looks smaller than before.
What're we gonna do?!We're
still pretty high up!
I wonder if it'll last
until we reach the sea...
Hey Luffy! Something is
strange,so come back down!!
That was quite a scare, since it
stopped bouncing suddenly.
Like I said, the octopus is shrinking!
O-Oh? I didn't do anything,but
we came back to the ship!
Ahhh! We're falling! We're falling!!
This is bad! At this rate,we'll
be swallowed by the sea!
There's no guarantee that
we'll fall into the sea!
Ugh! That's right! Dammit!
What're you doing, Usopp?!
What else?! Protecting the ship!
What're you gonna do?!
Don't be reckless, Usopp!
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
Okay, it worked!
Alright!
I'm gonna use all the Breath Dials I have...
There! Float!!
It's slowed down.
Sweet!
Were we saved?
Looks like it.
Did you see my wonderful work?!
Usopp, you're so cool!
I wondered what was gonna happen
for a moment there!
Yeah, seriously, I thought that was it.
Why?!
Usopp!!
Everyone, grab onto something and hold tight!
It's cold...!
Nami-san! Robin-chan! Are you okay?
That startled me! The octopus suddenly
shrunk all the way!
I wonder if the air leaked out.
What the heck happened?!
But we somehow made it down... without dying.
You! Thanks!
Still...
...we really went to an incredible
place, didn't we?
Now that we've fallen, it's so far up.
It's as if we were dreaming.
It's a dream land. I wonder if we
can go visit again some day.
You might be able to get closer if you die.
Zoro, so you think you can go to heaven?
You jerk!
Well, things're calm now at any
rate.I'll make coffee or something.
I'd rather have dinner, Sanji!
I'm saying I'll get on it right
away,so have some coffee and wait!
Okay...
By the way...
Where the heck... are we?!
If you're feeling lonely, talk to me
You gaze at the heavens as you wander about
Just like the moon,you
keep your gaze constant
And your deep reflection
wanes as you slowly disappear
Stay as you are, let those words guide you
Dream, you travelers who
spend countless nights drifting
Even if you may not be able to go back
you will surely start moving forward again
Ugh! Where are we?!
What are these spotlights?!
A stage?! Is it my one-man show?!
Idiot!
This is the siren for a state
of emergency! Could this place be...?!
If that's the case, it looks like
we've fallen to a damn troublesome place!
Looks like we'd better first
get away from the ship.
What?! What about dinner?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A State of Emergency Is Issued!A
Notorious Pirate Ship Has Infiltrated!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!