Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Thanks!
I flashily thought I was a goner there!
There's no need to thank me.
You're Buggy the Clown, right?
How do you know that?!
Who are you?
I'm looking for a certain man.
What do you say?
Will you team up with me?
"The Wait is Over!
The Return of Captain Buggy!"
To where are we headed, Buggy?
What?! I smell like I farted?!
No!
F-First, we need to find my crew...
I wonder where they are now,
and what they're up to...
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
Retreat for now, men!
Everyone! Run away on your own!
Wait for us!
Is everyone here?!
Are the people who got off
the ship with you all back?!
Yes!
--Yes.
Yep!
Captain Buggy isn't...
Captain Buggy isn't here!
Captain Buggy!
Who knows how long
it's been since then...
Or even where
Captain Buggy flew off to?
What's going to happen to us?
What's the future of the Buggy Pirates?
This was all because of that girl
thief named Nami or whatever!
Roronoa Zoro... I will take
your head by my own hand!
Zoro! Did you finally catch cold
after always sleeping on deck?
I've never gotten sick
before, only injured.
Come to think of it,
I've never had a headache myself...
Is someone out there talkin'
about me being a master swordsman?
Ah, I see. Wait!
Someone's talking about me!
Honestly!
Being a hottie is punishment!
Someone's always talking about you...
Whoa!
Captain Buggy!
I always felt he was a cold-hearted,
horrible captain when he was well,
but now I realize he was a bold
and open-hearted pirate-like pirate!
When I look back, we were allowed
to ravage to our hearts' content
only because we had
Captain Buggy's backing!
Today, let's give the greatest and
flashiest funeral for Captain Buggy!
Captain... Rest in peace!
Please leave the rest
to me, Acrobat Cabaji,
the Buggy Pirates' Number Two
and Chief of Staff!
I promise to rebuild the Buggy Pirates!
Hold it!
Cabaji!
W-What?!
It's only natural for Captain
Buggy's successor to be me,
Beast Tamer Mohji-sama,
the vice-captain!
I'm the captain!
You can stay vice-captain
for the rest of your life!
Hey, guys!
We're gonna decide who gets to
be captain by seeing who's stronger!
Fine by me!
Mohji! Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji! Cabaji!
Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji!
Acrobat Technique: Monkey Showman!
Secret Technique:
Candid Camera Police Trio!
Murder at the Open-Air Steam Bath!
Die...
Mohji!
That's what you think!
Looks like I'll just have to fight
you until your body falls apart!
Yeah. A man-to-man fight.
I'll take you down with these two fists!
Mohji! Mohji!
Cabaji! Cabaji!
Yeah! You got 'im!
Ooh! So close!
Damn you... J-Just give up already...
N-No, you give up already...
I'm going to be captain!
Shut up!
Yes! Our Captain Richie!
Captain Richie!
Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
Our great captain!
With Captain Buggy now gone,
the most worthy of us to be captain
is Captain Richie!
Captain Richie! Our great captain!
Captain Richie! Captain Richie!
Our great captain!
Our great captain!...
Who are you people?!
Who gave you permission
to come onto this island?!
You do realize this island belongs
to us, the Bear Claw Tribe, right?!
Captain!
Oh? So you're these guys' captain, huh?
Amusing! Are you picking a fight?!
W-We surrender...
Hey! Hey!
What is it?
You don't need to shout so loud;
I can hear you just fine.
Did you find something good?
Yeah! That's my...
...super flashy
Buggy Pirates pirate ship!
What's with this big grave?!
W-What?! I have a big nose?!
Who're you calling Big Nose?!
Eh?! Eh?! Are you talking about me?!
I said grave! Grave!
Red?! Red, you say?!
You're saying I have a big, red nose?!
What? My grave?!
Took you long enough.
But who did this?! This is morbid!
Not to mention this is
an old wanted poster...
Oh? There's someone
on the ground there...
Wha?!
Mohji! Cabaji!
What happened to you guys?!
C-Captain Buggy...
I-It's so good to see you...
I'm so glad you're all right!
I thought we'd never see you again!
I'm so happy, too!
But what on earth happened here?
Who did this to you?!
Eh? We suddenly got
punched out of the blue, so...
Embarrassingly enough,
we can't remember a thing...
The Bear Claw Tribe did this.
Bear Claw Tribe?!
Yeah. If you're going to
save them, you'd better hurry.
Bear Claw tribesmen are famous
for being food connoisseurs.
The captain says that lions taste bad!
We taste bad, too!
I won't be very tasty at all!
This guy tastes way better than me!
Lies! Lies! He tastes much better!
I'm too boney! I got nothing to eat!
Don't worry!
We're the Bear Claw Tribe!
We're iron chefs!
Some wine and spices
will take your smell away!
What do we do with this food?
What are they?
I've never seen such
strange ingredients before.
Do we boil it with them?
I just hope it doesn't
give me stomach trouble...
Chop-Chop-Chop...
...Chop-Chop-Chop-Chop...
Is that...?!
Chop-Chop-Chop-Chop
Chop-Chop-Chop...
Flashily reassemble!
I'm back!
--Captain Buggy!
--What?!
Sorry I took so long, men!
Liven things up with
a super flashy Buggy Ball!
Richie!
Acrobat Technique:
Murder at the Steam Bath!
Let the beast-taming show begin!
Do you really think you can
hit me, Buggy the Clown-sama?!
I hafta thank you all for
everything you did to my men!
Here I flashily come!
Chop-Chop Kick!
Chop-Chop Punch!
Die flashily!
Chop-Chop Rice Cracker!
Chop-Chop Festival!
Chop-Chop Punch!
Chop-Chop Carnival!
H-He's doing this all for us!
That's our captain!
Captain Buggy!
I'm so glad you're all right!
I've greatly pained you all,
my adorable underlings!
Our pain is nothing at all!
Who're you calling a weird creature?!
All the hardships you had were
because of that damn Straw Hat!
Incidentally, who might this
pretty young woman be?
Don't forget "really cute"!
Y-Yes. I had been
wondering about that myself...
This nice woman saved
my life! Her name is...
U-Uhh...
Umm, I'm sorry.
What was your name again?
Everyone! The Buggy
Pirates are back in action!
Captain! What is our first goal now?!
The head of Monkey D. Luffy!
Hey. I think I see an island.
Eh? Really?!
What island is that?!
I just told you the other day!
Huh?
So that's the island where Loguetown is!
It's a pretty big town, right?
Yeah, that's what I hear!
Then it sounds like there might
be a market with fresh ingredients.
I'm hittin' up the weapon stores.
Being stuck with one sword doesn't
suit a Three Sword-Style user.
In that case, I guess I'll
check out some equipment shops!
That island is where Gold Roger
was born and then executed, right?
Wow, you actually remember!
The town where the
King of the Pirates died...
Also known as the city of
the beginning and end...
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
So this is the city where Gold Roger,
King of the Pirates, died!
This place is filled with great
ingredients and beautiful girls!
Think they got any bargain sales?!
What are you, a housewife?
Climbing the execution platform
and seeing the scenery comes first!
I want some swords, but...
Do you have money?
I can lend you some at 300% interest!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Town of the Beginning and End;
Landfall at Loguetown"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!