Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and returned to Sabaody Archipelago to
go on to the next stage - the New World.
Oh, what is this?
It got tense all of the sudden.
But, Rayleigh, Luffy is not here!
Don't worry!
Captain!
Huh?
Isn't he the guy you're looking for?
Oh!
Luffy is here already!
I gave Sanji a Baby Transponder
Snail when he came here.
He's with Zoro.
Alright, I'll fight you!
I trained my legs in hell for 2 years!
Bring it on! I'll cut you in half!
Oh, that's good because
you guys have to hurry
- the Navy will be here soon.
So it's only Monkey-chan that we can't reach.
But take this Vivre Card.
It will lead him to you.
Grove #42 will be perfect - it's on the sea.
Take the ship there and rendezvous!
It's a little busy but you
all got through these 2 years
and it's time for the new journey!
"The Battle is on! Show Them
What You Got From Training!"
As for the rest, read
this before you set out.
You can learn how to operate
a coated ship in detail.
Okay, thank you!
I wonder how Luffy has
changed in these 2 years.
I can't wait to see him!
Me too!
Okay, let's go to Grove #42!
Oops, I have to call Zoro and Sanji.
But Luffy...
I hope he doesn't get
caught up in some trouble.
Oh, that's right, it's Luffy.
We never set out peacefully because of him.
Leave it to me!
I'm gonna go pick him up! I have an idea.
Hey, you fools! We're gonna
arrest all of you in our way!
What are you doing, Navy?!
Don't bother Soul King!
Hey, what's going on there?
It's out of control!
The Navy who came here to
arrest Soul King has been
blocked by his fans
and he got away somehow!
Damn! That traitor!
Yes, I have some big news!
The musician, Brook, is a
friend of Straw Hat Luffy
and he is a pirate himself!
Thank you! The timing was perfect!
Sister Shakky asked me to do this!
Your friends will be waiting at Grove #42!
It's been a while! My heart
is filled with anticipation!
Oh, I don't have a heart to be filled.
What's wrong with them?!
They're both extremely strong!
You've improved a bit, you
third-class swordsman.
You've learned some idiotic
kicking skills, yourself!
I hope your cooking skills have
worsened, you shitty cook!
--what did you say?!
--Ring, ring, ring...
--Huh?
Ow! That's right!
The Navy has set out and Luffy
should be here somewhere!
We're gonna take Sunny to Grove
#42 so come meet us there!
Roger.
Clank.
--What did he want?
--Weren't you listening?
Well...
Navy. Come. We. Ship. Run.
Get that?
No, I don't! Why are you talking like that?!
Say it in a proper sentence!
I thought a musclehead like you
couldn't understand sentences.
Okay. You. Later. Slashed.
Yeah, yeah.
By the way, do you hear that uproar?
You're right. There. Noisy.
Huh? What's going on here?
Shut up, you guys!
We already found one of the
perpetrators who have insulted me!
It's this guy!
I'll teach him a lesson first!
About how formidable I am!
And what I'm about to do to him
is a warning to you all, my men!
If you mess with me, this
is how you're gonna end up!
Do you understand?!
A guy with a 400 million
berry bounty sure is scary!
What's the matter with this guy?
Zoro, Sanji, do you know him?
Huh?
Well you see, a little while ago...
That's it, you pirates!
Straw Hat Luffy and his
following! Just surrender!
The Navy...?
We're blocking off every exit of Grove #46!
You can't get away now!
Huh? How did the Navy find out about me?
What are you talking about?
Captain! We're under siege!
You fool! Don't panic!
This is why we recruited the new members!
We have guys with bounties over 100 million!
But there are a lot of them...
Stupid! Watch this!
Hey, Caribou!
Use the Navy soldier as a
shield and make a way out!
Navy soldier?
They caught our scout!
Damn, that's not good!
Huh?
What did you say, Big Boss?!
I said "use the Navy soldier
as a shield," you fool!
I see. Use this Navy soldier as a shield...
What are you doing, Caribou?!
We got to use him to get away from here!
I can't do that, Big Boss!
What?
Because this soldier lied to me saying
he hadn't called the Navy yet!
No, stupid!
That crazy ass! He ignored my order!
Uh-oh, he did it...
There is an unspoken rule that you
can just tell a lie to bad guys
but we should put a stop to that!
Looks like you guys have
no intention to surrender!
Let's get the pirates!
Fools! Our boss is a man with a 400
million bounty - Straw Hat Luffy!
Let's fight!
This is no good, Captain, let's run!
You fools! You have to listen to me!
Huh? What are they calling me "boss"?
Again, what are you talking about?
Don't be scared! Go!
You're...
The 88 million berry bounty
- Lip "Service" Doughty!
I liked the way you fight.
Don't be scared! Get ready to shoot!
He's got a 92 million berry bounty...
"Gashed" Albion!
Don't back down! Fight for justice!
Yeah!
It stinks! Hypocrites' blood!
A 210 million bounty - "Wet-Haired" Caribou!
Just surrender!
What?! You're a Devil Fruit eater?!
You should not do that!
It's not healthy to push yourself too hard!
My sword...!
We can beat them, Captain!
Those pirates are strong!
Yeah, you're right.
Hey, guys!
The one who kills the most Navy Soldiers
will become my right-hand man!
So go for it!
Yeah!
Your right-hand man?
What about us?
You guys better do something too
because, with this much power,
I'm gonna launch out into the world!
Whoa! What is it now?!
Pacifistas!
What?!
Why are the Navy's human weapons here?!
They're the bear-like men!
But Hancock told me not to cause trouble...
Again, what the hell are you talking about?!
A pirate--Straw Hat Luffy. Verified.
Are those real Pacifistas?
They're aiming at me?!
Pacifistas, huh? It's exciting!
88 million berry bounty. Lip
"Service" Doughty. Subdued.
Captain Doughty!
Follow the Pacifistas! Catch the pirates!
Yeah!
A single blow?!
He had an 88 million bounty
and he was no match...
This is bad news... Oh,
Captain, where are you going?
--Wait for me!
--Hey, hey!
Fools! I don't wanna fight
him - he beat Doughty!
We better run!
Straw Hat Boss, do something!
If nothing is done, those human
weapons will kill us all!
Big Boss!
Huh?
Big Boss is gone!
Big Boss?
That's how they call Straw Hat?
Wait! My side hurts!
Fool! Run! They're gonna kill you!
Stupid! You're in my way!
Huh? Who are you?
That's...
Big Boss!
That's interesting!
--Look at that, Coribou!
--Yes, brother!
--Not that way, fool!
--I'm sorry!
Big Boss Luffy, beat them up!
Show them Straw Hats' power!
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?
Get out of my way or I'll kill
you and pull out your bowels!
This may surprise you! I'm the
Revolutionary Dragon's son!
And the grandson of the hero--Garp!
I wreaked havoc during the War of the Best!
I'm a big-time pirate with a
400 million bounty--Straw...
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
Why are they calling you Straw Hat?
Hey, you! Don't you know who I am?
Get out of my way or I'll kill
you and pull out your bowels!
This may surprise you!
I'm the Revolutionary Dragon's son!
And the grandson of the hero--Garp!
I wreaked havoc during the War of the Best!
I'm a big-time pirate with a
400 million bounty--Straw...
Straw Hat is not scum like you!
Huh?
What?!
Straw Hat Boss!
I see.
They all got fooled and became his crew.
PX-5, who is he for real?
"Triple-Tongued" Demalo Black.
A 26 million berry bounty.
--What?!
--26 million? That means he is...
...An imposter?!
They found out! Let's run!
What's up with that shit?!
So he posed as Straw Hat
Luffy and tricked us!
Because the real one is dead!
Damn! I almost got ripped
off by a jerk with a
measly 26 million berry bounty!
What?
So He was posing as me?
That Sanji and Zoro, too?
They looked just like the real ones!
I better leave here before it's too late.
The one who fooled you is an idiot
but you guys are just unlucky.
You all have to come with us.
And I don't know why but the
real Straw Hat is here too.
What?
When we entered this area, PX-5 detected him.
Shoot at him, PX-5!
That was close!
What are you doing?!
This bag is holding all my precious lunches!
H-Here's his poster...
Looks exactly the same!
So that guy is the real Straw Hat!
Brace up!
We came here to catch the real one anyway!
Straw Hat!
Oh, it's you! Are you gonna
get in my way again?!
I've been told not to cause
trouble in order to set sail!
Don't worry! You don't need to set sail!
Unlike 2 years ago, I'm officially
a member of the Navy now!
So I'm gonna catch you here!
PX-5!
That's slow...
What?!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
Straw Hat...
He is using Haki!
He beat the Pacifista with a single blow!
See ya!
I think I'll see you somewhere again!
Wait, Straw Hat!
Don't let Straw Hat get away!
Yeah!
Hey, Luffy!
Oh?
Luffy! I knew it was you!
Why are you always in trouble?!
Oh!
It's no mistake this time!
It's been a while, guys!
Roronoa! "Black Foot"!
I knew they were alive!
PX-7!
Outta my way!
I cut him!
No, I broke his neck!
The Straw Hats! The real ones!
They're nothing like the imposters!
Hey, Luffy, you're the 9th.
Shut up! Cut it out!
Luffy, hurry up!  Everybody's
waiting at the ship!
Okay!
Don't let them get away!
Catch them at any cost!
It's really been a long time!
I wonder how everybody is!
I'm so happy!
Hey, what's wrong?
Oh!
Rayleigh!
What?!
No way!
D-Dark King Rayleigh?!
I came here to check but you seem alright.
Your power sure has improved.
Uh-huh!
Now go to your friends!
Uh-huh! Rayleigh, thank you for
everything these past 2 years!
You're out of character. Just go!
Rayleigh!
I'll do it!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After two long years
the Straw Hats finally assemble on the Sunny.
But there is no time to rejoice.
As they are about to depart for
the sea floor paradise, Fish-Man Island,
the pursuing Marines arrive on the scene.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everyone Together! Luffy,
Setting Out for the New World!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!