Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World, Luffy and
his crew reached the Fish-Man Island,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates
who are looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Friends or foes? That's something...
...you'll have to decide on your own!
"A Big Clash! The Straw Hats vs.
A Hundred Thousand Enemies!"
S-So he's the Straw Hat Luffy who
invaded the Navy HQ twice, 2 years ago!
A pirate ship is here, too!
So are all the Straw Hats!
Silly Straw Hat! I can't believe
he was hiding in the shark's mouth!
I thought that skeleton and the others
were captive in the Ryugu Palace.
--We've been waiting for you, Straw Hat!
--H-He really came!
Madam Sharley! The pirate
with a hat just showed up!
He saved the King and the Princes!
Straw Hat boy...
Did I do okay, Jimbei?
It wasn't so disastrous,
considering it was Luffy.
Mm-hm. Although it did not
go exactly as we had planned...
A FEW HOURS AGO--SEA FOREST
Outta my way!
No, I won't let you go!
Luffy-chin... Boss Jimbei...
Hey, that's enough already!
E-Excuse me, but they are
going to kill Father-sama!
I said "Outta my way"!
I'm gonna go kick those guys' asses!
How many times do I have to tell you?
I said "Wait"! Let me finish!
How would you describe our relationship?
We're friends!
That's right.
It's such a simple relationship but the
Fish-Men and humans couldn't establish it
and have been struggling to do so for years.
When I left you the message
"Don't fight against Hordy,"
I meant "Don't fight him recklessly."
Don't rush!
If you just go and beat Hordy up,
people on the island will think that you
are just another violent human bully.
Instead,
I want you to become the hero who
will save the Fish-Man Island!
Hero?
No!
What?!
We're pirates!
I love heroes but I don't wanna be one!
Do you know what heroes are?
Say there is a chunk of meat.
Pirates will have a banquet and eat it
but heroes will share it with other people.
I want all the meat!
Is that how he defines a hero?
So it all comes back to meat again.
I will let you have your meat
just as long as you do as I tell you!
Okay.
What?! That easy?!
In the simplest terms, I will call for
your help so I want you to respond.
Help you?
Yes, first, Megalo and I will get caught
voluntarily and enter the plaza.
While they are paying attention to us,
one of you sneak out of
Megalo's stomach and...
Out of his stomach?
They will have the letter
from the Celestial Dragons.
What letter?
Oh yeah.
Luffy was sleeping so he
missed most of Jimbei's story.
It is...
...something Queen Otohime acquired
10 years ago, at the risk of her life
and it will define the future of this island!
And they will also have
the key to free the King.
We need to get our hands on those 2 things.
Who is up to it?
I'm good at stealing! I can do it with Robin.
Yeah.
All right. Once you free the King,
I will call for Luffy-kun's help.
And once Luffy-kun emerges gallantly,
out of Megalo's body,
people will notice that Luffy-kun
and I are working together.
Princess-sama, you wait somewhere
completely safe outside of the plaza.
And after we pass you the letter,
flee with the freed King and the Princes.
Meanwhile, the rest of you, get to the
Ryugu Place now and save your friends.
And then, hurry to the plaza with them.
Now--about how to rescue your
friends in the Ryugu Palace...
Figure it out yourself!
You don't care about us, do you?!
Okay! Super count on it!
We have the Sunny!
We'll figure it out!
Mm-hm.
Once this is all set into motion, how do
you think the citizens will respond?
Both the citizens of the Fish-Man Island
and the outlaws of the Fish-Man
District respect Jimbei-san.
Uh-huh. So if they find out that Boss trusts
Luffy-chin with his life, to save the King,
they'll root for you, Luffy-chin!
Straw Hat.
Luffy-sama.
I am only doing this because
you asked me to, Jimbei!
It's uncomfortable having
everybody cheer me on.
Yeah, we're not used to that treatment.
I'd fight the king of the devils himself
if the Mermaids-chan cheered for me!
Thank you!
That settles it.
Okay, let's do it!
Is there something else?
Should we pick a codename
for this operation?
Who cares!
Alright, let's hurry up!
So you saved your friends at the
Ryugu Palace successfully.
Straw!
Pappagu! I'm happy to see you again!
But, but, I've had quite a few brushes
with death because of them!
Straw Hat Luffy is a human and a pirate
THE OUTSKIRTS OF CONCHCORDE PLAZA
but he's on our side, right?
Princess Shirahoshi called for his help!
It looks like he came to save
this country with Boss Jimbei!
Straw Hat!
They love you so much.
But you only saved the King
temporarily so don't push your luck!
You're just a human pirate!
Mermaid Princess-san, you're so beautiful!
Excuse me, could I look at your panties?
Don't ask the Princess that!
Then, show me yours.
Why should I?!
We're all together again finally!
They're ignoring you!
Well, that's because I
said it in a small voice!
Nami-san! I rescued those idiots!
--Do you love me now?
--Yeah, yeah.
You fool! We got to the exit on our own.
Uh-huh.
And you couldn't have
done it without my help!
Pappagu helped them?!
No, before that, Brook became a ghost and...
Ghost?
That's right.
My newfound ability helped us!
I don't have much time!
I need the key... I mean, the sword!
I don't have time...
Stay away, Ghost!
Pappagu-san!
Huh?
How did the ghost know my name?
It's me!
I don't have any ghost friends!
You're the Bone, aren't you?
The water is here finally!
What are you doing, Brook?! It's too late!
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Oh, welcome back.
Here, your sword!
Good job, Zoro-san!
Alright, Zoro, let's get out of here!
--Three-Sword Style!
--What?!
You cut too much!
Oh yeah?
I can't swim anymore!
I-I need to breathe!
Damn!
I-I'm gonna die!
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
Super we're here to pick you up!
We made it.
That's how it went.
Brook's new ability sounds awesome! Anyway...
Those guys got their
captain beaten by Luffy.
How come they don't seem worried?
You're right. That's odd.
Here you go.
It's the letter from the Celestial Dragons.
Thank you all!
This is the hope of the Fish-Man Island,
that Mother-sama left behind.
But I think it's not safe for Yowahoshi.
Mm-hm, her capture was
not a part of our plan.
Neither was asking her to escape on her own.
Luffy-sama, what did you just call me?
You were calling me
"Coward (Yowamushi)" before.
Yeah, it's not like I know everything but
you're not as timid as I thought you were.
So I'll call you Yowahoshi from now on!
It's understandable why someone would
hate those who they think wronged them.
That man who insulted you...
That's exactly what he's doing.
But a coward couldn't have been so strong
and borne such hardship
on her own for this long.
She is right.
Princess Shirahoshi, it must have
been hard for you through the years.
I'm sorry.
I caused you trouble
because I kept it secret.
It's okay. I like you
just the way you are now.
No passing on hatred to the next generation.
That's what those brave
heroes were trying to teach us.
Don't tell the people
on the island anything!
Don't let resentment or hatred
get the better of you for my sake.
There is a small "sprout"
that bloomed in your heart.
If all people on the island share it
and think the same way as you do one day,
there will be no more
fighting and the conflict
between Fish-Men
and humans will be over.
I don't think the years you
suffered through were meaningless.
You must have been trying
so hard to protect...
...that small "sprout"
single-handedly, day after day.
But let us protect it for you this time.
Y-Yes!
Thank you very much!
She may not be a coward
but she sure is a crybaby!
Straw Hat! Kick the crap out of them!
Vander Decken was so useless!
I needed him to get rid of Shirahoshi.
Captain Hordy!
The Energy Steroid is
still working as I thought.
No wonder. He took a lot of them.
Captain's back!
She's the legendary Mermaid
Princess with that troublesome power.
So I needed to take out Shirahoshi
as soon as possible, but...
...you people duped me completely.
Jimbei.
I should have noticed when you
gave in without resistance.
You're quite taken with
these humans, aren't you?!
I despise your kind the most!
Fisher Tiger who you grew up together
with in the Fish-Man District
and Arlong who was like a brother to you,
were both beaten or killed by humans!
But instead of seeking revenge for them,
you joined hands with humans!
You are as gutless as Neptune!
When I become king of the island,
I'll change everything!
This year's World Summit
is a perfect opportunity!
I'm gonna kill the human kings from
all over the world at Marie Jois
and the legend of a terrifying
underwater kingdom will begin!
We'll drag all humans in the world
into the water and enslave them!
Eventually, no one will be able
to stand against Fish-Men.
Even in the world of pirates!
All pirates will fall down on their knees
before us--the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Look at these human pirates with
confidence in their ability to fight!
You will all be like them, Straw Hat!
I'll be the one who becomes
King of the Pirates!
The King of the Pirates?
You're just a band of 10 half-assed
pirates. You can't do anything!
We have 100,000 on our side!
Th-There are so many of them.
Straw Hat and Boss Jimbei have only
10 people. Are they gonna be okay?
If they lose, Hordy will take
over the Fish-Man Island!
And we will be kicked out of our home!
Beat them up! Straw Hat! Boss Jimbei!
Straw Hat!
Kill them all, New Fish-Man Pirates!
Here come 100,000 enemies!
How can we fight them?!
It's impossible!
This is why I don't wanna
get involved with you guys!
Before we fight, we could get squashed.
Squash?! No!
100,000 enemies?! I'm so
stunned - my eyes will pop out!
But I don't have eyes to pop out!
100,000 is nothing! Let's do this!
Don't hide behind us while you say that!
Here I go! My time has come!
Super Armored Me!
All right! Bring it on!
There are 10 of us.
So we each have to beat 10,000 of them.
They outnumber us but it
doesn't mean they're stronger.
It's not like they're elite Navy soldiers.
So don't shit yourself.
What did you say, you stupid Moss Head?!
Bring it on, you Bloody-nosed, Two-bit Chef!
Hey, Luffy!
L-Luffy-kun!
Luffy-sama?
That 400 million berry prize is mine!
No, mine!
No way!
Kill him!
What's going on here?!
He didn't do anything but
so many of us got knocked out!
Hey, stand up, guys!
Damn! He beat half of us in a single moment!
That means 50,000 people
in an instant? What did he do?!
What's going on?
Wh-What? What just happened?
He's so strong. That Straw Hat boy...
The Straw Hat pirate did it?!
Cool, Straw Hat!
That was Haki!
He's gotten much stronger in just 2 years.
That was Conqueror's Haki?
So he was capable of that, as I thought.
That's what I needed from my captain.
Otherwise, he needs to step down.
That was amazing! Luffy-sama!
You're Hordy, right?
I guess I have to kick your ass.
You can become king of whatever
you want in any country.
But there can only be
one King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats have begun their all-out
battle against the New Fish-Man Pirates.
Surrounded by Hordy's superior numbers,
they must protect Shirahoshi
from the relentless assault.
And the new attacks developed over two years
by Zoro and Sanji will erupt!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Deadly Attacks One After Another!
Zoro and Sanji Join the Battle!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!