Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Sogeking.
Hm?
Shoot through that flag.
Roger.
Huh?
This is my new weapon,
a huge slingshot... named Kabuto!
Have a good look at its power!
Special Attack... Firebird Star!
Oh, no...!
Mission accomplished.
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
after making the entire world your enemy!
Bring it on!
Robin!
We still haven't heard you say it!
Say you want to live!
Robin...
Robin!
To live...
I thought it was something I dared not wish for.
No one ever let me wish for it.
The sea is vast, so someday, definitely...
...you'll come across friends who'll protect you!
If... it's really okay for me
to utter my wish for once...
I...
I want to live!
Take me to the sea with you!
You guys...! I love you guys, dammit!
Let's go!
The drawbridge is coming down!
Looks like they pulled through. Good timing.
Robin!
We're gonna rescue you for sure!
The drawbridge is coming down! Go! Straw Hat!
How dare those damn pirates?!
We're not gonna let it happen!
Get the trench mortar ready!
Stop the drawbridge! Break it if you have to!
Yes, sir!
The drawbridge stopped coming down?!
How dare they get in our way?! Damn bastards!
Who's doing this?!
Hey, pirates!
What?! Kokoro-san?!
I heard everything!
What're you guys wasting time for?!
Wasting time? But the
bridge is only halfway down.
Jump with all your might towards the falls!
The sound of the sea train?
Huh? What's the meaning of that smile?
Here we go!
I knew it!
Nooo!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'll never be a pirate!
I will too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a
crew every bit as good as yours,
and I'm gonna find the
greatest treasure in the world,
and I'm gonna be King of
the Pirates! I'll show you!
When I was a kid, I swore that I'd
gather a crew and become a pirate...
...like the pirate who protected me.
You're already one of my crew.
Robin...
Just like the pirate who protected me,
I'll protect you, too!
"Jump Towards the Falls! Luffy's Feelings!!"
Then take me on your next voyage, Shanks!
I wanna be a pirate too!
As if you could ever be a pirate!
Why not?!
Luffy. Just bein' a good swimmer
doesn't mean you'd make a good pirate.
I'm good at fighting too!
My punches are like pistols!
Oh, really?
What's that mean?!
He means you're too much of a kid, Luffy!
Seriously, you're as old as my own kid!
I'm not a kid! I'm a grownup!
Now, now. Don't get so mad.
Here! Have some juice!
Wow! Thanks!
See, you are a kid! Ha!
That wasn't fair, Shanks!
Don't laugh!
Stupid cheapskate Shanks!
Pardon us.
Oh... So these are "pirates."
Look pretty damn dumb.
Welcome...
We're mountain bandits. But we
ain't here to tear up the place.
Sell us some booze. Ten barrels oughta do.
I'm sorry. I just ran out of alcohol.
That's odd.
These pirates seem to be drinking
something... What is it, water?
No, what they're drinking is the last of it.
My apologies. Looks like we
drank the whole place dry.
Sorry!
You can have this, if you'd like.
It hasn't been opened yet.
There's an eight-million-Berry
bounty on my head, you know.
One bottle ain't even enough for
a bedtime drink! Don't insult me!
Now the floor's all wet.
Sorry about that, Makino-san.
Do you have a rag?
Oh, I'll do that!
Seems you like to clean. Then maybe
you'll find this more fulfilling.
Not worth our time if they're
out of booze. Let's go!
Later, wimps!
Are you all right, Captain? Are you hurt?!
Oh, I'm fine. No problem at all.
He got you good, boss!
Talk about lame!
Why are you laughing?!
That was so uncool!
Why didn't you fight them?!
No matter how many there are
or how strong they seem,
you're not men--or pirates--if you
laugh after something like that!
I can understand how you feel,
but he only spilled some booze on me.
It's nothing worth getting mad over.
Whatever!
Eating out of frustration, Luffy?
Shut up!
Wait, what're you eating?!
That box! Did you eat what was in that box?!
Y-Yeah...
Spit it out! Right now! Every last bite!
W-What're you doing, Shanks?!
What... was that?
What you ate was the Gum-Gum Fruit!
The Gum-Gum Fruit is known as a Devil Fruit!
Eating it turns your body to rubber,
and makes you lose the ability
to swim for the rest of your life!
Eh?! No way!
You dumbass!
What's the idea, boy? People were
drinkin' and havin' a nice time.
Dammit! Apologize! How dare you
make fun of Shanks and his crew?!
Did I say something to offend you?
You did! Now apologize!
Mayor!
You see the looks on those pirates' faces?!
He got covered in booze, but didn't
say a word! Talk about pathetic!
Pirates are just a bunch of wimps.
They're nothing but talk.
Stop it!
Stop making fun of Shanks and
the others! They are not wimps!
Stop, Luffy!
Stop making fun of Shanks and
the others! You stupid bandits!
You oughta watch your mouth, boy.
No one who's ever made me
mad has lived to tell the tale.
Wait!
Let the boy go! Please!
I don't know what Luffy has done,
nor do I intend to fight with you!
If you're not offended, I'll even pay you!
Just, please! Spare the boy's life!
Mayor!
Leave it to senior citizens
to know how the world works.
But no, it's too late for him now.
After all, he's made me angry...
You're the bad guys! You mountain apes!
You're a lost cause, kid. You can
regret all this in the next life!
--Luffy!
--Please! Let him go!
I was wondering why the bar was empty...
Looks like it's those
mountain bandits from before.
Captain!
Shanks!
So you pirates are still here, huh?
Have you been scrubbing the
village clean this whole time?
Luffy!
I thought your punches
were as strong as pistols?
S-Shut up!
I dunno why you're here, but you'd
best leave before you get hurt.
Any closer and he'll shoot your head off, wimp.
He said no closer!
Don't make me blow your head off!
Put your life on the line.
Huh?!
Now that you've drawn your pistol,
put your life on the line.
What the hell're you talkin' about?
I'm saying those aren't for threatening people.
N-Now you've done it!
These bastards fight dirty!
--Dirty?
--Cut the crap.
What, do you think you're
dealing with saints or something?
You're looking at pirates!
Shut up! You got nothin' to
do with this in the first place!
Listen, bandits.
Whether I'm splattered with
alcohol or food or even spit on,
most of the time I'd just
laugh and forget about it.
But...!
No matter what the reason,
anyone who hurts my friends has to pay!
Shanks...
Has to pay, huh?!
Lousy pirates! Kill 'em, men!
I'll handle this. Should be easy enough.
Don't get cocky, bandit.
If you wanna fight us, then go
drag a warship here or somethin'.
So strong!
H-Hold on! The kid attacked us!
You are a wanted man.
Damn it!
A smokescreen!
Luffy!
I made a clean getaway!
They'll never expect a mountain
bandit to escape onto the sea!
Dammit! Let me go,
you stupid ape! I hope you die!
You wish! You're the one who's gonna die!
After all, you've made me mad!
So long!
Dammit! Dammit!
Those guys are scum, but I couldn't
even hit them once! Dammit!
Sorry! I got no use for you anymore!
W-What the hell?!
Help...!
Shanks!
Get lost!
I'm in your debt, Luffy...
Makino-san told me everything.
You fought for us.
Hey, don't cry! You're a man!
But... Shanks...!
Your arm!
It's only an arm. It's no big deal.
I'm just glad you're alright...
You're leaving, then?
Yeah. It was a long stay, but now we part ways.
Bet you'll miss me, huh?
Well, yeah, but I won't
ask you to take me anymore.
I've decided to become
a pirate on my own now!
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'll never be a pirate!
I will too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a
crew every bit as good as yours,
and I'm gonna find the
greatest treasure in the world,
and I'm gonna be King of
the Pirates! I'll show you!
You're gonna surpass us, huh?
In that case...
...I'll leave this hat with you.
It's dear to me.
Take good care of it!
Ten years later,
I sailed out and became a pirate.
Just like Shanks protected me,
I'll protect my friends!
Nooo!
Just wait, Robin!
"Straw Hat Theater"
"Part 1"
That bastard...!
"Usodaba Gang's base of evil"
That detestable Chopper Man!
I'm not gonna let him thwart my plans
to take over the world anymore!
"Evil Incarnate, Usodaba"
This is Dr. Usodaba, evil incarnate!
He leads the evil Usodaba Gang
and schemes to take over the world!
He's an evil scientist who produces evil
phantoms, monsters, robots--anything!
Those are some of his underlings behind him.
I'll lure him out to my base and
wait for him here, ready to strike.
And then, I'll crush him with
my gang's full fighting power!
Swoosh!
His weakness is...
That's right, his assistant, Namifia!
"Pretty Assistant, Namifia"
This is Namifia, a pretty assistant!
She efficiently manages
Chopper Man's missions.
Now, men, go!
First, bring me a hostage!
Dabada!
We brought one!
--'Sup!
--Hey, you brought him?!
"Champion of Justice, Chopper Man"
This is Chopper Man, our hero
and champion of justice!
He flies around using his Chopper
cape and fights for world peace!
His weapon is his cuteness!
"Cute Spark!!"
With his killer "Cute Spark,"
he can make any enemy's heart melt.
If that doesn't work, he uses "Chopper
Violence" to beat the crap out of them!
I want tea.
Hey, what's the big deal, relaxing at my base?!
Hm?! What's that big thing in the garden?!
It's my secret weapon!
Stop checking it out, you jerk!
Can I try riding on you?
Sure, go ahead.
Hey! Why are you making
friends with him, Luffybomber?!
"Secret Weapon, Giant Robot,
Giant Luffybomber"
This is Giant Luffybomber, a giant
robot and their secret weapon.
It's a giant robot that's fifty meters tall.
When Usodaba comes on board,
it becomes your worst, strongest enemy.
Special traits: It can speak.
Personality: It does its own thing!
"Rice Ball Monster, Zorokiller"
This is the rice ball monster, Zorokiller!
When he demands rice balls,
if you don't have any,
he gets angry and says, "Make sure
you have some from now on!"
"Flower Monster, Robiflowern"
This is the flower monster,
Robiflowern. She's an evil woman
who's been defeated by Chopper Man's
killer "Cute Spark" time after time.
"Naughty Monster, Sanjiropus"
This is the naughty monster, Sanjiropus.
He insists that he isn't naughty, but he's
always thinking about naughty stuff.
He shows no mercy to guys.
"The Usodaba Gang's Evil Three"
They are the Usodaba Gang's Evil Three.
They have nothing to do
with this story, though...
Thus, the evil gang has been wiped out.
Whoa! Amazing!
You're cool, Luffybomber!
Darn straight I am!
Chopper Man! There's trouble
in one of the eastern towns!
Okay! I'll head there in Luffybomber,
the giant robot I obtained the other day!
--It's not here!
--I sold it.
--What?!
--Go! Go! Our Chopper Man!
Fight for world peace!
D-Don't worry, Robin-kun.
Y-You've got us on your side.
He says, while trembling in his boots.
I-I'm just trembling with anticipation!
Yeah? Well then, let's hurry up and take
care of these World Government guys!
Then we'll rescue Robin-kun without fail!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ways of Men!
Zoro's Techniques, Usopp's Dream"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!