Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
But they have yet to gather and are
stirring things up as a fragmented crew!
Luffy set out from the Ryugu Palace
with Mermaid Princess Shirahoshi.
Robin got information about a Poneglyph
that's hidden somewhere
on the Fish-Man Island.
I think this kingdom holds the
important key to the 100-Year Void!
Franky found the Sunny at the Sea Forest
- the resting place for sunken ships.
I'll do the coating. Count on me, completely!
Oh, thank you... Um... Can I ask your name?
I'm Den.
Oh, by the way, somebody has been
sitting there for quite a while.
Oh, that's Boss Jimbei!
He said he's expecting somebody.
Zoro, Usopp, Nami, and Brook who
have unintentionally taken over
the Ryugu Palace by accident...
...came face to face with
Hordy, Vander Decken
and his rebel forces who are
trying to destroy the kingdom!
My Shirahoshi disappeared?!
She's my... My daughter-jamon!
We've been in love for a decade!
Nothing will tear us apart...
...except for death!
Before you become somebody else's,
I'd rather see you dead with your blood
splattered all over! Shirahoshi!
"The Battle in the Ryugu Palace!
Zoro vs. Hordy!"
That's an octopus-san!
That's a blowfish-san!
Oh, there is a killifish-chan as well!
Coward, you only see fish!
Look, a rice ball and a doughnut!
Meat!
Luffy-sama, you're only seeing food!
Am I?
Jamon! Jamon!
Jamon!
What is it all of the sudden?
F-Father-sama! He must be
worrying about me at the palace now...
Boy, you're such a pain.
Here, Coward!
Luffy-sama!
Why are you laughing?! Swallow her now!
Vander Decken is going after Shirahoshi!
Neptune-sama!
I beg you-jamon, you people!
I'll give you anything you want!
Let me go after Decken!
You can take silver, gold and jewels...
...or my soldiers' lives or anything!
Huh?
No no, King!
He's gonna catch Shirahoshi!
My treasure--Shirahoshi!
How pathetic, Neptune.
I never thought that the hateful Straw Hats
would help us conquer the Ryugu Palace!
"Hateful"?
He's got Arlong's mark, too!
Jimbei told me there was something
going on in the Fish-Man District!
I can't believe you, a former proud soldier
of Neptune's army, are the ringleader!
Shame on you, Hordy!
Shame?
I'd feel shame if I had felt any
real pride to be in Neptune's army.
The only reason I joined the army was to
learn fighting skills in actual combat.
And that's all.
--You bastard!
--I became stronger thanks to you.
What do you mean?
You all have failed to notice
what's been going on on the island.
Since I was a child, I've seen Fish-Men
oppressed at the hands of irrational humans.
Help me-dosun!
We've gone through all the trouble
to get to the Fish-Man Island,
why don't we take a Fish-Man back with us?
L-Let me go-dosun!
Give us back our friend! You kidnappers!
Do you Fish-Man brats
wanna mess with us humans?
They're worth far less than Merfolk
but we can make some extra
money by selling them as a set.
I can't take it anymore!
They can't even breathe in the water...
...but no matter how much we kill them,
these damn humans never go away!
I admired Arlong's ambition to
take the arrogance out of them!
We're gonna restore his dream!
We're the New Fish-Man Pirates!
I was training myself to become
Arlong's right-hand man one day...
...when he set out to conquer the world
from the East Blue as he planned.
But...
...unfortunately he was
stopped by some humans.
So these Fish-Men are followers of Arlong?!
What?! Arlong?!
Just kidding! I've never had Arlong before...
Ouch! Hey, Usopp-san, why did you kick me?!
Just shut up for now!
Enough with chit-chatting
and let's get down to business.
Stay away!
Wh-What the...
Shark Grip!
What a strong grip! What
the hell is he doing?!
--No! I tell you this is no good!
--What should we do?!
Nami-chin?
Camie, do me a favor!
What?
Is that his own strength?
Yeah, he hasn't taken an Energy Steroid yet.
The walls are broken!
Oh damn! It's a flood!
--Oh this is no good! Especially for me!
--I'm gonna drown!
--No, water drops!
--Get down! He's gonna do it!
Shark Arrows!
Those water drops are becoming arrows!
You bastard! How dare you
shoot my soldiers at random!
Stop it!
You fool!
--King-sama!
--Don't do that!
No-jamon! You guys are my subjects-jamon!
Neptune-sama!
What an idiot! What kind of a king
becomes a shield for his men?!
You don't have what it takes to be king!
--King-sama!
--Damn Hordy!
It's awful! He's shooting at the unarmed!
And he's way stronger than Arlong!
One-Sword Style!
Bird Dance!
Hey wait, Boss Hordy! It's...
That bastard! He shielded
himself with his own man!
Hey guys, untie the soldiers!
What?
The negotiation with the
kingdom has broken down.
We couldn't keep our word to give
them back all the hostages unharmed.
He's so trustworthy.
Alright, I got it!
Oh, my foot is in the water!
I'm losing my strength!
Help me, Nami-san!
Oh? Where is Nami-san?
Huh? Nami is gone?
Where did she go? Camie is missing too!
Boy! First Luffy and now Nami?
But we have to untie them first!
Hang on for a minute, Brook!
He's driving my bones too hard...
Why don't you run now?
Please untie the others.
I have no energy left...
Untie the others and take up your arms!
Don't let them do a damn thing!
Destroy all of Neptune's
army and the Straw Hats!
Special Attack--Green Star "Rafflesia"!
--Whoa! A flower from earth opened up!
--I've never seen such a flower!
Take it!
Oh, it stinks!
Damn! How stupid!
--How's that?!
--I can't take it anymore...
Zoro! The water is rising!
I have a favor to ask!
Let those two get out of here!
What about you?
No one can get away with
that guy chasing after them!
Don't stand in my way of
conquering this country!
Okay! Nothing has been broken.
Sorry that I pushed you
so hard all of the sudden.
You can rest here for a while.
Do you want me to help you with the coating?
No, every man knows his own trade best.
Okay, thank you!
Oh, there you are, Sunny!
--Robin!
--Is she your friend?
Yeah. Did you finish your business?
Not yet. I really need to
check something. There it is.
Hey hey, outsiders should stay out of there!
Thank you for your suggestion.
She's odd, isn't she?
Look who's talking.
You were the only one who
could see my arrows earlier.
Is it because you've seen Arlong's?
If you've learned how to see them for
the second time, that's impressive.
But no matter how skillful you are,
no one can beat a Fish-Man in the sea!
You can't deflect them in the water!
Three-Sword Style! Dragon Twister!
Oh, seems like I can have some fun.
I don't have much time!
CORAL HILL--AT THE SHORE
Stay with me! It's gonna be okay!
Hurry up and get out of here!
Don't worry about us now!
Just think about yourself...
What do you guys want?
We want the Mermaids back!
You humans only see us as novelties!
Ah? What are you talking about?!
Don't play dumb, you pirates!
We heard that 3 more young Mermaids
disappeared at a beach in the south.
Where are those girls?
I don't know what you're talking about!
Why do you think that we
did it? It's true that...
...I love Mermaid-chans so much
that I wanna take them away!
But we didn't kidnap them.
See? You just said that
you wanna take them away!
Why are you guys arguing? Be quiet!
I knew humans did it!
Get out!
Ouch!
There's some left in it! Don't waste food!
Shut up, human!
Oh? Sanji! Chopper!
Hey, Sanji! Is your nosebleed stopped now?
Is that Luffy?! What's that blowfish?
A human gentleman and...
...a racoon! It looks exactly
the same as in the book!
A-Are they your friends, Luffy-sama?
They are my crewmembers!
They are?
Look! That's their captain!
That straw hat... He's the boss
of the Mermaid kidnappers!
I don't want them to see me! Megalo,
close your mouth a little more!
I'm gonna go down there for a bit!
What?
He came down!
Hachi! I thought that was you!
Straw Hat...
What happened to you?! Who did this?!
He's not saying!
Get off of this island!
That's all he's been saying!
But if I'm correct, the pirate--Straw Hat
is occupying the Ryugu Palace now!
They're kidnapping Mermaids! He came to
kidnap more leaving his men at the palace!
Maybe he's gonna kidnap
Princess Shirahoshi in the end!
Don't be ridiculous! That's impossible!
The Princess is a giant
smelt-whiting Mermaid
and the God of the Sea--
Neptune's beloved daughter!
Some people might dream about kidnapping
her, but no one could do it for real.
What is that blowfish?
No!
What?!
--Oh!
--Huh?!
Princess Shirahoshi-sama?!
Um... Well, uh...
You found me!
She's big! Don't tell me that that is...
...the Mermaid Princess?
What? Is there anybody behind me?
No, Sanji! Don't turn around at any cost!
Huh? What's going on?
If you do, you're gonna die, Sanji!
Oh, no.
They kidnapped the Mermaid Princess!
Angered by the kidnapping
of Princess Shirahoshi,
the terrifying Hammond of
Fish-Man Island captures Luffy.
And then, Vander Decken
finally reveals himself!
Can Luffy escape his bonds and safely
take Shirahoshi to the Sea Forest?
And, upon seeing an attractive mermaid,
Sanji is once again in danger!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Keep Shirahoshi Safe!
Decken Close Behind!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!