Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
So you finally found a tree to call home?
No one is born into this world to be alone!
Yeah, you're right, Saul.
Hey! Robin!
Maybe... I'll try it, too.
Yeah! Do it! Do it, Robin!
Please don't do it, Robin-chan!
It's like a ghost town here!
Everyone's already there!
Yeah! I know our duty is to ensure the
train leaves safely, but I can't believe
that we're late for the party
held for the entire town...!
But... I can't... run anymore!
Don't give up!
We have to go to Paulie-san's
party no matter what!
What?! It's Paulie-san's?! I didn't know!
Of course it is!
The town is still in the
process of being restored,
and yet Straw Hat is holding
a big party at Galley-La!
No matter how you look at it, it's...
With that girl?!
That's right!
It's a wedding party!
If that's the case, I can't
just sit around like this!
After all, we're important to them,
since we witnessed that precious moment...
--Am I wrong?
--You're not wrong!
We may even end up having to deliver
a congratulatory speech! Tada!
Seriously?!
Yes, seriously!
I'll do my best!
Let's do our best!
Yep!
Now, let us go, my friend!
Yow! Entrant #9985, Sogeking!
I'll sing about the pride of
the man hidden behind the mask.
♪ I was born on the island of snipers! ♪
Yow! Yow!
--♪ I never miss my mark! Lulu lala lu! ♪
--Yow, yow, yow, yow!
Whoa!
This is far from over!
Guys! Let's all party!
"Shanks Makes a Move!
The Linchpin to the Reckless Era"
Five Elder Stars! Five Elder Stars!
Something terrible has happened!
What's the matter?
The fleet we sent out to the New World
the other day has been defeated...
Also, Red-Haired Shanks and Edward Newgate,
aka Whitebeard, two of the Four Emperors,
are finally about to make direct contact!
What?!
Shanks?!
Old man! Old man!
Red Hair wants to see you!
Yeah... Let him come aboard.
That brat better have brought good booze.
"Navy"
Is it true that the fleet has been defeated?
Yeah, it seems like it.
So Red Hair and Whitebeard will be in contact?
Attention!
Listen up! We don't know
what will happen next!
Stand by on maximum alert!
Yes, sir!
Destination straight ahead! Furl the sails!
Captain! Red Hair is here!
Red Hair is coming.
Greenhorns oughta stay back...
...unless you wanna get knocked out.
Knocked out?! What're you talking about?
Just go to the back and stay there.
Ah!
Hey, guys, what's the matter?!
What's going on?!
Oh... I guess it's already too late.
--Hey, guys! Say something! Hey!
--Don't make a fuss!
They've just been knocked
unconscious, that's all.
Those who lack the mettle can't even
stay conscious in front of that man.
As always...
...he's got an incredibly strong Haki...
Pardon me... for the bit of intimidation
I gave off, since I'm on an enemy ship.
Whenever I see your face,
the scar that guy gave me throbs.
"Alcohol"
I brought some healing spirits with me.
I don't intend to fight.
There's something I want to discuss with you.
Says the man who shows up
throwing his Haki around?
You fool.
Hey, Red Hair! What'd you do that for?
Oh, you're Marco of the first division, right?
Why don't you join my gang?
Shut up!
Old man, what should we...
Yeah, looks like there won't
be a battle. Leave us alone.
This booze is from the West Blue...
This is the cheap stuff, isn't it?
Having traveled around the world,
I find nothing's better than the booze
made from the water I grew up with.
It's booze from my hometown.
Please try it.
Not too bad.
Roger, Garp, Sengoku...
There aren't that many people
left who know about that era.
It's been 22 years. That's just natural.
You sure have worked your way up the ladder.
You were just a young apprentice
on Gol D. Roger's ship.
Since we were fighting Roger's
gang all the time back then,
you and I got acquainted in an unusual way.
There you are, Whitebeard!
Now we've found you!
You can't escape anymore!
We're gonna dye that beard of yours blood red!
Hey, my nose isn't blood red!
Has that funny Red-nose who was
with you kicked the bucket yet?
Oh, Buggy? That brings back memories.
We parted in Loguetown
on the day our captain was executed,
and I haven't seen him since.
Come with me, Buggy!
I refuse to be your subordinate, you moron!
I heard that he's still a pirate.
To me, the time seemed to flash by.
Many pass down stories about the days when
you and Hawk-Eye used to duel like legends,
but those days seem like yesterday to me.
When someone of your caliber lost
one of his arms in the East Blue,
everyone was surprised.
What enemy did you give your left arm to?
This...?
I wasn't gonna take you anyway!
You'll never be a pirate!
I will too!
Someday, I'm gonna gather a crew
every bit as good as yours,
and I'm gonna find the greatest
treasure in the world,
and I'm gonna be King of
the Pirates! I'll show you!
I bet it... on a new era.
Fine, as long as you have no regrets.
Whitebeard...
I've experienced many battles
and received many scars,
but the scar that throbs right now is this one.
This wasn't a wound from an adventure
or one received from Hawk-Eye.
The one who gave me this scar
was one of your men...
Blackbeard Teach.
I didn't let my guard down.
Do you get what I want to say, Whitebeard?
He was quietly waiting for the right moment.
He didn't become a
commander or make his name.
He kept his true self hidden
and stood in the shadow of the
great pirate Whitebeard all this time.
And now, he's gained power
and started to make his move.
In the end, he'll aim for the top.
With his own will...
...he'll eventually come
to take even your position.
What do you want me to do?
That's what you came to talk about, right?
Please stop Ace!
Although he's young, you made him
your second division commander.
Ace is strong!
I know that much.
But that fame and trust
make the matter complicated.
It's still too soon to have those two fight.
Stay away from Blackbeard Teach!
That's all I want to ask.
The old man's laughing?
To think you'd talk to me like that...
That snot-nosed brat sure did grow a pair.
His crime was killing one of his crewmates.
That's the worst sin you
can commit on a pirate ship.
He broke the golden rule.
Once I let them board my ship,
they are all my sons,
no matter how foolish they are.
Where can my killed son's soul go?
It's my responsibility to show that idiot Teach
that you can't make your way in the
world if you lack a moral code, right?!
You got that, you idiot?!
It's 100 years too soon to tell me what to do.
No one will be able to stop...
...this reckless era!
It's nothing to fear!
I'm Whitebeard!
R-Red Hair, that bastard!
What's he doing to the old man?!
Hold on. He's not the type
to pull a stupid stunt.
But whatever discussion they
had seems to have fallen apart.
Look above.
The clouds have... No, the sky has been split!
Ahhh...!
Geez... Give it to me.
Hey!
Look! I got today's newspaper!
It's talking about Enies Lobby!
S-So it's finally in the news?!
Hey, what's it saying?!
It's an article that'll determine our fate!
--Well...
--W-Well?
It's not...
...talking about us at all.
Ahhh!
I knew it! We have no choice
but to leave this island!
Wait, what?! It's not talking about us?
R-Really?!
--Yeah!
--Not at all?! Is that possible?!
There's no mistake about it!
All right! I thought we had to
live life on the run! I'm so glad!
What's the deal, when the Franky
Family went on such a rampage?
Maybe your grandpa spun
the information by saying
that they were regular people
who got dragged into the incident?
Well, I don't think he'd even think of that.
I don't think he would, either.
I bet it's Aokiji who did it.
He's hard to figure out.
At any rate, that's good news.
We're pirates, but they're not.
If they had to live life on the run
from here on out, I'd feel bad.
Instead, they wrote terrible things about us.
According to this, we declared
war on the World Government.
Even burning down the island
was our doing, it says.
Looks like our bounties will go up again.
Whoa!
D-Do you think I'll get a bounty, too?!
Well, it's not impossible...
...but I'm the one who's gonna be in trouble.
"A superstar appears."
Why are you guys happy about it?!
Are you stupid or what?!
Bro, Iceberg is here.
He's here.
Working hard, Franky?
--Ribbit!
--Hm? What're you doing here?
Well, so what, you don't want
help from the likes of me?
Ha! Can you keep up with my ship design?
How about you? Do you still have the
skills after doing demolition for so long?
Show me the blueprints.
Everyone from Tom's Workers is here, huh?
You guys don't have to build a ship
in a place like this, you know.
I heard that it's a ship for the Straw Hats!
Is there something we can do to help?!
It's not good if you rush through it all
by yourself and do a sloppy job, so...
Well... You guys don't have
to work on the backstreets?
The others said that since they
couldn't come, at least we should go help,
if he was working on a
replacement for that pirate ship.
You guys are all...
What a nice story...
It is.
Don't stand in my way, okay?!
All right! We'll show you
the skills of those at Dock #1!
Huh?! What?!
Franky's building a ship for us?!
Oh, that's right. You were sleeping.
All right! I'm glad to hear that!
Oh, then, he's a nice guy after all!
--He's a nice guy! Yep, he's a nice guy!
--I'm looking forward to seeing the new ship!
--He's a nice guy!
--Well then, why don't I go
out shopping while we wait?
So when will that ship be finished?
When he came by yesterday,
he said he needed five days.
So, four more days.
I can't wait!
That's a strange dance.
Do you call that a dance?
Where did the 100 million
Berries we had in here go?
Oh, that. I gave it to them to buy meat
and booze and stuff for the party.
Gave it to them? It was our money!
It was our party, wasn't it?
Hey! We don't have much left!
Yeah, I can imagine! In the end,
everyone in town showed up!
It was a real blast!
Well...
...we got a good deal with the ship,
so there's no problem, right?
I wanted to get gorgeous furniture for the ship.
Let's go hunt for a bargain.
Oh, Nami! I'm gonna go out and have fun,
so give me some spending money.
@#$%&!!
You're not getting anything!
Yes, ma'am!
Boy, why does water-water
candy taste this good?!
It's the best, you jerk!
If I put it on top of cotton candy and eat it,
I don't know what'll happen to me!
S-Straw Hat!
--Hm?
--My... Um...
I have a favor to ask!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Girl in Search of Her Yagara!
Great Search in the City of Water!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!