Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has rushed to Marineford,
scene of a battle between the
Whitebeard Pirates and the Navy...
...to rescue his brother, Ace!
Attention, all ships and soldiers!
When you are all set, we
move the schedule forward...
...and execute Ace immediately. That's all.
--Luffy-kun...
--Let's move!
Let's go!
H-Hey!
No! That's not the side!
Ace!!
H-Hey, don't tell me that's...!
Crocodile!
That's not all! Who is in that lineup?!
All forces are here on both sides!
There are a lot of big names!
The world's got to be ready for it!
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
We're here for you!
Garp! It's your family again!
Luffy!
The grandson of the hero--Garp and
the son of the revolutionary--Dragon.
I'll take care of him for good!
Where's Croco boy?
Oh? I think he chickened out and...
There he is!
He went ahead of me!
Long time no see, Whitebeard.
You never learn.
Now that we are here, our
agreement has been fulfilled.
Why do you want to protect Whitebeard?!
As I thought--this old man is Whitebeard.
Then leave him alone! Ace likes this old man!
Ace's brother is quite a fighter.
You came here to rescue your brother?
Yeah.
Do you know who you're messing with?!
A squirt like you will be dead meat!
Shut up! That's not up to you to decide!
I know what you're up to!
You wanna
become the King of the Pirates, right?!
But I'm the one who'll become the King!
How saucy you are!
I won't forgive you if you
cause me trouble, spoiled brat!
I'm gonna do as I like!
I'm gonna rescue Ace!
"Even If It Means Death! Luffy
vs. the Navy; The Battle Starts!"
He's the... rookie--Straw Hat!
How does he know Whitebeard?
I don't get it!
He should hide after
breaking out of the great prison!
Why bother coming to this living hell?!
--Because he is Luffy-san.
--Huh?
That's the way he is!
Pops! Luffy!
So he is Straw Hat.
--Old man.
--Hmmm?
I heard while on a Navy ship that...
He's such a bonehead!
I wish he'd just get his
ass kicked already! Stupid!
How brave he is! Only his son could do it.
So they're gonna execute Ace immediately?
Are you sure?
They said they would  after getting
"all set" for something...
...but they were using codes
so I couldn't understand.
I know that you wanna rescue Ace, too,
so I wanted to share that with you!
I see. That was important information.
Thank you.
No problem.
How can he talk on equal
terms with Whitebeard?!
Okay! Ace, I'm coming now!
Why is he so confident?
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Get outta my way!
So he is Ace's brother.
Keep up with the boy! Let's go, 3rd division!
We should go, too!
Wh-Wh-What?!
Really?!
14th division, let's charge ahead!
Yes, Commander Jill!
Luffy...
They're so encouraged by just one daredevil?
But our strategy is airtight.
Don't hesitate! Do as I said!
Damn Sengoku!
I bet he thinks that he doesn't need
to stick
to the schedule for the execution of a mere pirate.
The key is--after they're "all set" for what?
Pops! I heard that they're
moving Ace's execution forward!
I heard. How're Squard and the others doing?
They're tied up with the vice admirals at
the bay head. I'm gonna fly there and help...
No, wait.
I bet it must be a part of his plan that
we'd get some leaked information and advance.
Sengoku wouldn't let his enemy
know his strategy so easily.
He's not that foolish.
Keep going!
A kick at the speed of light?!
Don't push your luck. I won't
let you invade that easily.
It's Admiral Kizaru!
You're the guy from Sabaody!
Yes, I was gonna ruin you there because
the Celestial Dragons wanted it.
Straw Hat Luffy.
S-Straw Hat is dead!
Death...
...Wink!
No! I wanna go home!
--What, Captain Buggy?!
--I can't believe what you just said!
You mean you wanna destroy Kizaru
quickly so you can rush home?
Only a legendary pirate could
face Admiral Kizaru without fear!
You guys are too positive!
Straw boy, are you okay?
That was close! Thanks, Ivan-chan!
My only mission is to save you!
Kizaru, again!
Huh? No, it's not! That's...
Kuma!
He's the bear-like guy who blew us all away!
Rolling Spa!
Bartholomew Kuma!
How despicable you are!
I know that you have a
role as a Warlord but...
...we've known each other so long.
How can you just fire a laser at me?!
Hey, how could you...
A hole!
Ivan-chan!
Don't worry about me!
Leave this to me and just go ahead!
Okay!
Let's do this!
It's so unlucky of you to run into us!
Straw Hat, you're gonna die here!
Huh? Who are you?
I'm Fullbody!
You gotta pay for what happened at
the on-the-sea restaurant--Baratie!
Oh, Sanji beat you there.
You should remember this chakram.
You're the hypnotist from Usopp's
village. Why're you here?
I honed my skill in the Navy.
With two chakrams, it's twice as effective.
When I say "one, two, Django,"
you're gonna get tired.
One, two...
...Django!
What are you two doing?
Hina disappointed.
I know you from Alabasta, don't I?
I have no time to play with you people now!
I won't let you get away! Kimono Sleeve Cage!
I will bind anyone who passes through me!
--That's her signature phrase!
--Miss Hina is so captivating!
I'm sick of being in bars! Second Gear!
Th-That was fast! I couldn't see him!
Hina failed!
We failed, too!
We're bound by Miss Hina--body and soul!
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
Don't fight the vice admirals
alone! They'll defeat you!
Captain Squard! It's getting
frantic inside the bay!
I know!
I gotta hurry up and get to Ace.
The wall that Oars broke.
If I sneak in from here,
maybe I can outsmart them.
You are...!
Stop!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
They're all strong!
Straw Hat! He's high-spirited as usual!
Oh yeah! I'll cut his shadow off
and implant it in Oars again!
Come on, zombie soldiers!
Alright, zombie soldiers!
Go ahead and capture Straw Hat!
Moria! I don't wanna deal with him now!
Take your bullets back!
They're multiplying!
Yes, because this is a battlefield and and
all the corpses provide fresh zombies!
--Capture Straw Hat!
--He's the main suspect of the escape!
Keep going!
He's got to fight all these officers!
I wonder how long he can hang on!
Luffy!
Stay away, Luffy!
I know that you know it!
We're both pirates!
We both sailed on the sea as we liked!
I have my own adventures!
I have my own friends!
Ace!
I want you to...
...keep your hands off of them!
A wimp like you wants to save me?!
Outta my way!
You think that I'll allow you to do that?!
It's so humiliating!
Go back, Luffy! Why did you come here?!
I beg you, Luffy! I don't
want you to share my fate!
This is all my fault!
I'm...
...your brother!
Did you know?
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
From now on, we're brothers!
--Did he just say "I'm your brother?"
--He's also a son of Roger?
When Ace was born, both of his
parents died. That's impossible!
I don't give a damn about...
...the rules of pirates!
You hardhead!
Go, zombie soldiers!
S-Seawater?
Jimbei!
If I remember correctly, Moria, your
zombie soldiers can't take salt.
--Luffy-kun, let me handle them!
--Great!
--"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
--The former Warlord.
What are you doing?! Don't let this
rookie take control of the war!
Move out of the way!
I'm gonna crush him up!
He's also a loose cannon!
He grew up together with
Ace as his step-brother
and he's a biological son
of the revolutionary Dragon!
The revolutionary Dragon?!
The worst criminal in history?!
--Sounds very familiar!
--His daddy's got such a big name!
--He revealed it!
--Luffy-san...!
Luffy...
I couldn't care less even
if you were the devil's son!
I didn't know that!
That explains everything!
You bastard! Gum-Gum Pistol!
I finally understand  what
happened at Loguetown!
That's why Dragon saved Luffy.
Did you hear that?
They mean that Dragon?!
Head Office! I'm calling from
Sabaody! We've got big news!
Spread this all over the world!
We can't allow him to live!
Kill him at any cost!
Who cares? There's no need to hide it anyway.
That label won't hurt him because
Luffy is already a notorious outlaw.
You brothers are both fools.
Third Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant...
...Rifle!
Ace!
You can say whatever you want!
I'm gonna save you even if it means death!
--That brat!
--We all feel the same way!
--We're Ace's family, too!
--We're gonna save him at any cost!
Marco, we can't let that kid die.
Alright.
Luffy!
Luffy and the Whitebeard Pirates
continue to run forward.
As he watches his friends face off
against foes with awesome powers,
Ace comes to a decision.
Meanwhile, the Navy enacts a new plan.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Hard Battles, One After Another! Devil
Fruit Eaters vs. Devil Fruit Eaters!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!