Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
Wicked rain will get in my way
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
After losing his brother Ace during
the War of the Best against the Navy,
Luffy made it to the Maiden Island
where he was consumed with unbearable sorrow.
There is, however, an untold
story of the brothers...
...10 years ago in the East
Blue - Luffy and Ace as boys.
Luffy has been left with Dadan -
the mountain bandit of Mt. Corvo
and met 2 precocious kids named Ace and Sabo
with whom he pledged to be brothers forever.
Our brotherhood will always be with us!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Yeah!!
I'm gonna become a pirate before
you do so just forget it.
That's not fair! I'm gonna
become a pirate first!
You're still saying a crap like that?!
Can't you both understand that
you must become Navy soldiers?!
"We will stand on our feet."
This is nice!
Yeah, it's great!
This is our hideout!
Here they are!
"Luffy Becoming an Apprentice?! A Man Who
Fought Against the King of the Pirates!"
Seasons come and go and now it's winter.
Sabo! He's coming to you!
Don't let him get away!
Okay! I won't!
Yes! We drove him to the bay!
Luffy! Get ready!
Here he is!
Let's go!
You can't get away!
Yes! I got him!
Good job, Luffy!
We got two of them today!
We can have a lot of danpa soup!
Yeah!
I did it! I did it! I did it!
I made a kill for the first time! Yeah!
Hey, look!
Luffy, watch your back!
Back?
A big tiger!
He caught wind of our prey!
Luffy, get away from there!
He just wants the danpa!
That's my prize! I'm not gonna let you...
...h-h-have it!
He's too tough for you! Get away now!
No! Go away, stupid!
Otherwise, I'm gonna beat you up!
--That fool!
--Luffy!
You bastard! Gum-Gum...
You bastard...
Gum-Gum...
Wait, wait, wait!
Let's run while he's distracted!
Okay!
I'll get even with you!
Sorry about your first prize.
Leave him alone. We had no
chance against that tiger.
But that was my prize!
He can't just steal it!
Y-Y-You fool! Don't shake it!
--You little...!
--Stop, Luffy!
Sabo! Pull us up now!
I-I got it!
Sorry!
We're home finally! Let's just
go to bed on such a bad day
Go to bed on a bad day?
Oh, I'm starving!
--It's your fault!
--Ouch!
But if someone steals the prize you
caught by yourself for the first time,
I can see why someone would get angry.
--But it's reckless to fight such a big tiger...
--That's something you would do!
Humph! Shut up!
It's great to have brothers!
If they come aboard my ship...
Captain, you keep out of this!
Leave it to us!
No, I'll fight too because I'm a captain!
Why are you laughing?
That's not gonna make your stomach full.
I made up my mind!
Ace! Sabo! You guys gotta come
aboard my ship! Okay? Say yes!
That's so sudden!
We decided to leave it to the future.
But it'd be fun to be with each other
and you'll need my help, won't you?
You're the one who needs help, aren't you?
Yeah.
No!
I'm gonna help you!
You guys are welcome to come aboard my ship.
--No, my ship!
Then, this is not gonna work.
--Are you sure about it?
--Yeah.
Sabo?
I'm not gonna work for anyone. Forget it.
Come on! It's gonna be fun!
Oh yeah! How about this?
The one who beats the big
tiger can be the captain!
The big tiger? Are you serious?
The chances of you becoming
a captain are pretty low.
That's not true! None of us
can compete against him now!
--Good idea!
Yeah! Let's do it!
--Alright!
Are you ready?
Yeah!
We went through so much to
catch these. What a waste!
Don't complain. We caught
these to use them as bait.
Oh? There he comes!
What a greedy bastard!
He can't have them today!
He's here!
Is that the tiger?
What?! It's a bear!
That's not what we expected!
Go away! Shoo! Shoo!
Wait, it seems like he's
as strong as the tiger.
We can't beat the tiger if we can't beat him.
I see! So he's perfect for practice.
--I go first!
--That's not fair!
That's cheating!
Oh no! He's not cooling off!
He's gonna kill us!
W-Who is it?!
He better run - that old man!
That's Naguri from Gray Terminal!
Run! He's coming to you!
What're you doing, old man?!
You know that you don't belong here!
Go back to the forest now!
Cool!
It's like that time before!
What?! You were a pirate
and a captain, Naguri?!
Yes, indeed.
I knew it! Only a pirate
captain could do that!
"That"?
You made the big bear turn away
just by staring at him like Shanks!
You're cool, old man!
You think so?
I can't believe that Naguri
was a pirate because...
He's always collecting junk, hammering
away at them all day long,
making weird stuff,
and getting teased by the people
at the Gray Terminal and by Bluejam's crew.
He looked pathetic.
You know nothing, Sabo!
That's how pirates are!
You don't know anything, either!
What do you know about pirates?!
I know pirates! Shanks doesn't
do needless killings!
Shanks, again.
Hey, it's cooked.
--Ow, ow, ow...!
--Ouch!
Oh, you got more than me!
You got to pay attention.
Have some, Naguri. You helped us.
Oh, thank you.
So, what is a pirate captain
doing in a place like this?
How could you ask me that?
You don't have to answer
if you don't want to.
No, I'll tell you.
Do you guys know Gold Roger?
Roger?
I know him! He was the King of the Pirates!
We challenged Roger, the King
of the Pirates, to a fight!
Really?!
But we lost the fight and split up.
And everything just went downhill after that
and I ended up like this.
That's basically what happened.
But you fought with the King of
the Pirates, right? That's cool!
No, no, we were no match for him.
We got beaten badly.
Oh really? Even you were no
match - that's how much he...
Yes. And not just Roger, his
crew was also very strong!
Most importantly, their teamwork
was in perfect coordination!
It was our honor to fight with them.
I see! I still have a long
way to go to become a pirate.
Are you interested in pirates?
--I'm gonna become one!
--Become a pirate?
Yes, a pirate! Oh yeah, old pirate
man, could you give me some tips?!
I want to get stronger!
I have to become a captain
to lead Ace and Sabo!
A captain?
Hey, say yes! You're a pirate master!
--Okay!
--Okay?!
Yeah! Then, let's start from tomorrow!
Where did Ace go?!
Yeah, about that...
What?!
The King of the Pirates is his father?!
Yeah. But you can't tell anybody.
Don't mention it to Ace. He's gonna kill you.
Why?
I don't know why but he
doesn't like Roger for sure.
But that's his father, right?
So what?
I'm sorry for both of you but I was
all by myself even if I had parents!
Oh yeah. Your parents...
Children don't always get
along with their parents.
But, what a shame! He's
the King of the Pirates!
I can understand that you
wanna ask him about Roger
but just don't, okay?
Uh-huh! I got it!
And... you too, Naguri.
Okay, I got it.
But I can't believe that
that boy is Roger's son...
There he is. Hey, just act casually.
Yeah.
--Don't mention...
--I know! Don't worry!
Oh, Ace! I didn't know that you were home!
Oh, Ace! I didn't know that
your father was Roger!
I knew he'd say it!
You idiot, Luffy! I told
you to not to mention it!
--Luffy!
--Yeah!
Who told you that?
Sabo told me!
Hey Ace, what was Roger like?!
No!
How stupid are you? Don't
just say it casually!
Let me go! I am acting casually.
--Ouch!
Don't you ever mention
that name when I'm around!
Why did you hit me?!
Don't be mean - just tell me!
Give people a chance to explain first!
Shut up!
Tell us about him! You're so mean!
He's right! You can't have
a secret from your brothers!
Shut up! I don't care about my brothers!
Roger, Roger, Roger! Ace's father
is the King of the Pirates!
Shut up! Don't provoke him!
When you get down to it, it's
your fault for being a bigmouth!
Ouch! What did you say?!
What are you doing?!
We're no longer brothers from today!
--That's what I was gonna say!
Alright, I'm counting on you.
Yes, I'll leave no stone unturned.
You know what you should do.
We'll get to it!
Yeah, but if you find him,
don't do anything yet.
What?
Can't you see? We have to make
his father feel indebted to us.
The longer he worries, the more he'll
appreciate us when we find Sabo.
I see.
Until the time comes, don't do
anything - just monitor him.
"We will have a visit this spring"?
Dogra! Magra! Where is
the country called Goa?!
Mt. Corvo, Gray Terminal,
and Windmill Village
are part of Goa Kingdom supposedly.
That's what I thought.
Easy, easy, boss.
It's rare to see you reading a
newspaper. Hell must be freezing over.
Ouch!
Somebody's gonna visit the Kingdom?!
It's making the headlines...
What's going on here?
Are they that big a deal?
A CELESTIAL DRAGON WILL VISIT
These Celestial Dragons?
Curious after Luffy is taken in as an
apprentice, Ace and Sabo visit Naguri again.
Seeing that the boys only care about
getting strong enough to beat a tiger,
Naguri tells them that they can't become
pirate captains just by being strong.
What does it really take
to be a pirate captain?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battle against the Big Tiger!
Who is Going to be Captain?!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!