Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's okay... Robin.
You'll be fine.
You're still hiding something, aren't you?
That's okay.
But a pirate... cannot leave their group...
...without their captain's... permission.
So...
...believe...
...in Luffy.
F... Frog!
Ribbit!
Since...
...that day eight years ago...
Since that incident where
Tom-san was taken away...
...you've been challenging
the sea train every single day.
So that you won't lose those you love again...
So that you can protect those you love...
Ribbit...
Yokozuna... Then now's the time for
you to show the result of that training!
Ribbit?
At any rate,
the Government has now successfully
obtained the two keys...
Me, who owns the weapon's blueprints,
and you, who can revive the existing weapon.
So, even if I could escape,
it's pointless if it's just me alone.
You, too, somehow go back to Straw Hat!
That's not possible.
I hurt them just by being with them.
The people from the Government
say your existence is a sin,
but no matter what weapons you're carrying,
your being there isn't a sin.
Your existence isn't a sin!
Open the main gate!
Whoa...! What the hell is this place?!
Is this... a waterfall?!
I can't see the bottom!
How noisy.
Looks like Lucci and the
others are headed this way...
...bringing the best possible gift to us.
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Landing Operations Start!
Charge in, Straw Hats!"
Hurry!
Can't we go any faster?!
Hey... Hey, then, Big Bro Franky
sacrificed himself and...
Yeah, that's right.
He tried to save Robin-chan.
What an amazing guy Bro is!
We'd better hurry up or it'll be too late.
Hey, we can now see the lights of
the nightless island! It's Enies Lobby!
What?! Is that true? All right!
We can go rescue Bro!
Nightless island?
Yeah. They don't have nights on that island.
It's also called a day island.
That's the judicial island.
Day island?
We found them! Huge Yagaras!
--Ribbit!
--Ahoy!
Luffy!
--Ribbit! Ribbit!
--Ah! Sanji!
Huh? Who's that?
It's been a while...
It's Straw Hat!
It seems that we were able to
join up with them smoothly, huh?
Looks like they're ready and willing
to march into the entrance
to the World Government!
That sounds reassuring!
Okay! Enies Lobby has come into sight!
Everyone, get ready for the showdown!
Well...
Today is a joyous day when all
eight members of CP9, including me,
are to gather together in one place
for the first time in five years.
And yet, what's up with this article?!
The orders to assassinate
the heads of the local branches
of the revolutionary army only
required you to kill three of them,
but twenty-three of them are dead!
If you have an excuse, I'd really like to hear it!
Yoyoi!
I am very sorry, Chief!
It is all...
...my fault!
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Jabra"
Stop it, Kumadori!
A man shouldn't apologize so easily!
I'll explain what happened
to Chief, so just sit tight!
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Fukurou"
Yoyoi! I'm sorry, Chief!
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Kumadori"
Now that it's come to this, I'll take
responsibility by committing hara-kiri!
--Don't be ridiculous!
--Yoyoi!
You've got it wrong, Chief!
On the instructed day, we infiltrated
them to carry out the assassinations,
but somehow they managed
to find out about our plans.
I talked about the assassination
plan in town, chapapa!
What?! You again, Fukurou?!
What's the point of that zipper on your mouth?!
And when will your
"foot-in-mouth" problem go away?!
We're intelligence agents who
have to strictly keep top secrets!
I talked about it, chapapa!
--Don't "chapapa" us!
--Yoyoyoi!
Please don't blame Fukurou!
I'll take responsibility by committing hara-kiri...
Iron Body.
How regrettable...! I can't die.
Just die already, you jerk!
You guys, that's enough...
Ouch! I spilt my coffee! Dammit!
Also, they said that Nero was useless.
Oh, well...
"Sniping"
I was born on the island of snipers
"Sniper Warrior
Sogeking"
I never miss my mark
Lulu lala lu
Whether it's a mouse's eyeball, lock on!!
Or even your heart, lock on!!
The man who hails from the island of snipers
Lululu, lulu lala
Now... run away!
Sogege, soge, soge
"Sniping"
Sogeking!
Sogeking from the island of snipers?!
That's right. I'm Usopp-kun's best friend.
I'm here because he requested that I assist you.
H-Hero!
Since you're wearing a cape,
I thought that might be the case...
Amazing! I've never seen a hero before!
I see... He's a hero because
he's wearing a cape?
That's right! Cape buffalos are heroes, too!
Really?!
--Yeah, if someone is wearing a cape,
--Hey, that's Usopp.
--they're usually a hero.
--Usopp... I'm glad he was okay.
That's the long nose who
marched into the Franky House.
That's the long nose who got caught with Bro.
Yeah.
N-Nice to meet you.
Ah, yes.
That's one of the guys I met at Shift Station.
May I have your autograph?
Sure.
"To Chopper-kun"
But then, where did Usopp go?
He's fine. You don't have
to worry about him at all.
Anyway, he told me to put all my
energy into rescuing Robin-kun and left.
Yep. He's right.
Wh... Where is this island of snipers?
Yeah...
It's...
♪ I was born on... ♪
...in your...
...hearts.
--♪ ...the island... ♪
--Our hearts...!
♪ ...of snipers... ♪
Where's that?!
♪ I was born on... ♪
♪ "...the island of snipers..." Go! ♪
♪ ...the island of snipers... ♪
--Nami-san...
--Hm?
What is it, Sanji-kun?
And all you idiots here with Nami-san...
Before we go rescue Robin-chan,
let me tell you one thing.
That Buster Call is indeed the problem.
Many years ago, an island ceased to exist.
Five vice admirals and ten battleships...
To that woman who witnessed their
overwhelming military power,
Buster Call is an inexpungible nightmare.
If the terror planted in
her heart during her childhood
is directed towards her friends, she can
no longer have the spirit to resist us.
Don't tell me...
...you're doing this knowing all that...
Of course.
So, CP9 is taking advantage of the root
cause of Robin-chan's vulnerability.
It's not that I'm trying to make excuses
for not being able to get her back.
But even if we march into our enemy's territory,
it doesn't necessarily mean
that she'll let us help her.
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
That doesn't matter!
I'm not gonna stand for this!
That darn Robin!
Why Robin?!
Why not?! Why the heck doesn't
she want us to come rescue her?!
She's suffering thinking about what
might happen to us after she's rescued!
Who cares about that?!
If we don't do anything, she'll be killed, right?!
There's no way she wants to die,
so we'll rescue her!
Of course that's true, but...
Don't bother. Either way,
what we have to do is the same.
We'll just rescue her.
We'll bring down the whole place!
There's a technique that I wanna try, too!
Guys, take a look at this.
I've been to that island once
for railway maintenance.
I drew this based on my vague recollection of it.
This is a rough sketch of what the
geography of Enies Lobby looks like.
The Gates of Justice are
in the back of the island,
and they seem to be accessible
only via the Tower of Law.
What the hell is this? What's this dark area?
It indicates a waterfall.
A waterfall?
Well, you'll know what I
mean once you go in there.
If we can't recover Nico Robin
and Franky on this straight path
"Iron Fence" "Main Gate"
from the main gate to the Gates of Justice,
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
"Gates of Justice" "Tower of Law"
we will have lost.
Why?! No matter where Robin is taken to,
we can just keep going after
them until we get her back!
I explained this before we
left Water Seven, didn't I?!
The only destinations beyond those gates
are Navy Headquarters and the deep-sea prison.
So we have to settle this matter
before that at any cost.
She's right.
That being said, even if we all rush in,
if we encounter CP9, you guys are
the only ones who can defeat them.
After the train ride together, I now
know well how strong you guys are.
So, you guys stay and wait
on the sea for five minutes
and charge in to the main island in
Rocketman through the main gate.
We'll go in first and break open the
main gate and the main island front gate
so that the train can pass through.
After that, we'd like you to keep on
moving no matter how many of us fall.
We're only a little over 60 people,
but our enemy's forces are
probably well above 2,000 to 3,000.
We'd like you guys to go after only CP9,
avoiding unnecessary battles.
Okay, got it.
Okay, guys! We're now
at the front of the island!
Take a good look at the sky behind Enies Lobby.
Those are the Gates of Justice.
Whoooa! That's huge!
They never open all the way.
When criminals go through them,
they open just a little.
And, behind those doors is a nest of
large Sea Kings, just like the Calm Belt,
the sea areas that lie on
both sides of the Grand Line.
So no ordinary ships can go in there.
I don't know how, but the Navy has a
means of passing through there safely.
In other words, just like the pirate girl said,
if you want to get back
the criminals taken away,
you've got until the moment before
they go through those gates to do it!
Now, there's no time to lose!
Well then, as we planned,
we're gonna go in first!
Leave the backup to us!
Hey, you two! Aren't you
supposed to be with us?!
Hm? Where's Luffy?
What? He was right here up until now.
Hmph!
Is that Straw Hat?
What?!
Oof!
Why the hell is he doing things on his own?!
That man doesn't have a
clue about the plan at all!
That was a waste.
He said he got it, didn't he?
He's not the type who can wait five minutes.
We should've known.
What an impatient guy he is.
Go! Pirate guy!
Ribbit, ribbit!
Don't fall behind! Sodom! Gomorrah!
Climb up the iron fence and
break open the main gate!
Yeah!
Gum-Gum... Rocket!
Hm? What was that?
I just saw something flying!
Ah!
Whoa! What the heck is this place?!
What a huge hole! It looks
like the island is floating.
I see a town there, too. I wonder
if Robin is around there...
There's someone up there!
It's an intruder! Shoot him down!
Oops, they found me.
He went inside the gate!
This is the main gate! This is the main gate!
This is a report to Chief
and the main island front gate!
This is the main gate! Please come in!
What is it? What's going on?
An intruder went over the main gate
and is currently dashing towards
the main island front gate!
Oh... It's just an intruder.
Calm down and take care of him.
Yes, but...
This is the main island front gate.
We confirmed the intruder.
We'll take care of him right away.
Please do not worry.
Hey, hey. Stop.
Do you know what this place is?
Deal with him carefully. If my eyes
didn't deceive me, that man is...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
What?! What did you just say?!
I think that's Straw Hat...
A pirate with a 100 million-Berry
bounty on his head!
Robin...
Where is Robin?!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
What?! You let Straw Hat
enter the main island?!
What the hell is going on?!
Outta my way! Outta my way! Clear the way!
Is he trying to pick a fight
with the World Government
just to get one crew
member back?! How stupid.
Robin, just wait!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Cuts Through!
Big Showdown on the Judicial Island!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!