Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
But I won't walk away
nigedasanai kara
Oh
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ
to rescue his brother, Ace
who will be executed in public!
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard
Pirates storming Marineford...
...begin an all-out war with the Navy!
Oars!
Just a little more to get to Ace-kun!
Doppelman!
Spiky Shadow Lizard!
"Justice for the Winners!
Sengoku's Strategy in Action!"
See? This is how you kill a person!
Captain Oars!
Damn you Warlord!
Captain!
Oars!
Ace-kun...
Ace-... kun...
Ace-...
...kun...
Oars!!
I'll create the most powerful
zombie soldier out of his corpse!
Oars...
Your guard is down, Whitebeard!
Vice Admiral Lonz!
H-He beat the Giant -
the vice admiral of Navy so easily!
Oars...
Climb Oars' body and advance!
INSIDE THE BAY OF MARINEFORD
This is great!
Doflamingo! How could you do that to Oars!
I'll make you pay at any cost!
What's so funny?
This feeling that I'm in
the center of history!
This place is the turning point now!
What are you talking about?!
That's our commander!
Doflamingo can't do anything but run now!
R-Rear Admiral Yukimura!
I can't! I can't! I can't!
I'm scared and I can't do anything!
Even those strong fighters
falling one after another!
I can't take this! A loser like me!
Wait, Coby! I'm coming with you!
Get back to the battlefield!
Let me go! Please!
Admiral Akainu! Why is he here?
I'm scared of dying
and when I think about my family,
I feel weak at the knees!
Please! I'm begging you! Please!
We Navy soldiers are...
...fighting pirates with the "justice" of
the world emblazoned on our own backs!
Anyone who turns tail and runs
cannot be called a Navy soldier.
I would call him...
...a speck of dirt!
If you truly think about your family,
don't live in disgrace!
N-No! He can't kill a man who's on our side!
Admiral Sakazuki!
We are ready to proceed with the strategy.
Good! The time has come!
"The strategy?"
Ace!!
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
Use the space that Oars opened up!
Get into the bay!
Let's destroy the bay
head to open more space!
Fire straight ahead!
Damn! Not even a scratch!
Leave it to me!
An ice cutter?!
That's "Ice Witch" Whitey Bay!
That was quite easy for us.
Alright, everyone! Let's go!
Thanks!
We must move into the bay, too!
What's the matter, 13th division
commander Water Buffalo Atmos?
M-My body... What did you do, Doflamingo?!
Commander Atmos!
Don't! Stay away from me!
--What's wrong?
--Now!
Commander!
No!
Commander Atmos... Why?
I can't control my body!
Don't do this, Doflamingo!
Commander!
"Pirates are evil and the Navy is justice?"
That has been rewritten
many times  in the past!
Values are different to kids
who don't know what peace is
and kids who don't have
firsthand knowledge of war.
The one who ends up on top will rewrite
what's right and what's wrong.
This place is the turning point!
"Justice will prevail?"
Of course, it will!
Because the winners claim justice!
They've broken through
the bay head at 2 points!
The bay will be flooded by allies
of the Whitebeard Pirates!
Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
No problem.
Tsuru-san, let's put it into action.
THE BAY HEAD OF MARINEFORD
It's a suitable time.
Outta our way!
If not, you'll get more than a wound!
Outta our way, old bag!
I got washed!
I got hung!
But I feel so good!
You're a million years
too early to defeat me.
Connect to all ships and soldiers!
Ring, ring, ring...
He's up to something.
A resourceful admiral--"Buddha" Sengoku.
His name is Gol D. Ace.
Old man!
What are you doing here?
Disagree with the strategy?
No, they're pirates.
There's no room for pity!
Then...
Shut up!
It's no big deal.
I just wanna be here.
Stupid!
Ace!
What's wrong with you, old man!
"I wanna go out to sea?"
I won't let you at any cost!
Don't be bossy, you're not even my father.
I don't have to listen to you, old man.
You better call me grandpa!
Old man.
You wanna get another fist of love?
Grandpa!
I'm gonna be a lot stronger and...
...I wanna go out to sea with Ace!
Ouch!
Stupid! I don't wanna hear it from you, too!
Don't hit Luffy!
Shitty old man.
Shitty?!
Hey, Ace! Come here!
Listen, to be prepared for unexpected battle,
you got to eat to the fullest when you can!
That's important for a Navy soldier!
Both of you, keep that in mind!
Navy?! You can't just decide that for us!
What?!
I'll become a pirate!
You'll join the Navy!
--Pirate! Pirate! Pirate! Pirate!
--Navy! Navy! Navy!
Yum-yum!
No! He ate everything!
It was good!
So quick!
I'm gonna become a pirate...
If Luffy becomes a Navy soldier,
the food stock of his ship
will be gone within a day.
He would be a bigger
handful than the pirates!
I have no pity for villains but...
...family is a different story.
What am I supposed to do?!
Ace, you fool!
Why didn't you lead your life as I said?!
Ace.
You two should become strong Navy soldiers.
Okay?
Become a strong Navy soldier.
Old man...
If you have your doubts at this final moment,
I take no pity on even you, Garp.
If I had doubts,
I would've done something already!
Did you just hear that,
Helmeppo-san? Their strategy...
Yeah...
They're gonna forget the schedule
and execute "Fire Fist" Ace.
If they do that...
What's that?
Something's falling from the sky.
Is that a surprise attack
of the Whitebeards?!
I said that you were doing it too much!
It's because of his wink!
Is it my fault, Croco?!
Doesn't matter, we're gonna die!
It's frozen all over down there!
Heehaw!
Oh! I'm a rubber man so I'll be fine!
You just care about yourself?!
Do something!
I don't wanna die like this!
Somebody, stop me!
I shouldn't have listened to you, Straw Hat!
Dammit!
Ace!
Luffy and his friends suddenly
appear out of the sky
and drop right in the
middle of the battlefield.
Luffy finally spots his brother, Ace,
and cries out to him.
The final battle to save Ace begins now!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Straw Hat Team Arrives!
Tension Grows at the Battlefield"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!