Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law
who's been captured by Doflamingo.
Meanwhile, underground Dressrosa,
Usopp and the others started the
operation to take down Doflamingo!
Tail Hammer!
Maybe we can pull it off
without me fighting!
All right, guys!
I, Usoland, am taking command now!
Our target is a girl!
Let's go frighten her out of her wits!
Follow me!
Yes, sir!
I mean...
You lead the way!
Let's get to the Executive Tower!
Yeah!
Freeze! I'm taking over this lift!
Too slow!
I don't wanna learn to fight anymore!
Protect me to the end!
I'm a toy.
Rain and wind will rust my body!
Why're you doing this?!
You're just a toy, what do you want?!
I want a peaceful country where...
...my child can live happily!
I will take Dressrosa back
for the King Riku Family!
Wh-What just happened?!
I-I can't believe this!
Everybody's collapsed!
It all happened in a blink of an eye,
in the Block D match!
Oh, wait!
Somebody is about to stand up!
"The End of the Match?!
A Surprising Result of Block D!"
This is a very bizarre ending for a battle!
All 20-some surviving tough
fighters have suddenly
been knocked out for an unknown reason!
It's never happened before
in the long history of the Corrida Colosseum!
But, in the center of the ring,
we can see the shadow of someone
who is struggling to stand up!
Is that the winner?!
That person of the shadow has done all this?!
What?!
R...
Rebecca?!
It's Rebecca who just stood to her feet!
The well-known warriors who we thought
would dominate the Block D match,
they're all still lying down on the ground!
The Corrida Colosseum Battle Tournament -
the last winner moving to the finals is,
unbelievably, a convict gladiator
and a granddaughter of King Riku,
the blot in the history of Dressrosa!
Rebecca!
--Screw you!
--I know she cheated!
What kind of trick did you use, Rebecca!
Check her body!
You did it! Rebecca!
What happened?
A cloud of dust enveloped the ring
all of a sudden.
Who cares?!
In any event, Rebecca has won!
I can't believe it!
What did she do to Cavendish-sama?!
Admiral Orlumbus couldn't be
beaten by such a little tramp!
It was The Slicing Winds of Rommel!
The Slicing Winds?
That's right.
I bet you've never heard of it-dara.
There was a mysterious incident
that took place in the Rommel Kingdom...
They say winds that cut people
blew there every night.
What a bizarre story-dara.
They dispatched the Navy soldiers right away.
But the winds killed a lot of them, too.
The only thing they found
out at the end was...
...that the wind was actually a man
who called himself Hakuba-dara.
He is still at large.
Even after he left the Rommel Kingdom,
Hakuba kept terrorizing
people in various towns.
But wherever Hakuba appears,
this pirate is always there
at the same time-dara.
What?
You can't get away from me!
You little bitch!
Go away!
He's acting strange!
He fell asleep?!
H-He's a sleepwalker?!
Yes-dara.
Hakuba is, indeed,
an alter-ego of Cavendish
that awakens while he is sleeping.
Because Hakuba committed a crime,
Cavendish had no choice but set out to the sea
and became a pirate-dara.
Poor guy.
Don't feel sorry for him!
He's enjoying the situation!
He'd take advantage of your sympathies!
Yes, sir!
He is a great swordsman.
But Hakuba is far stronger!
Having said that, he falls asleep
when his alter-ego appears
and that nature wasn't suitable
for a battle royal, I guess.
--Rebecca can't be a winner!
--I'm sure she used a pistol or something!
Check her out already and eliminate her!
What should we do?
What do you mean?
Should we inspect Rebecca?
That's not necessary!
We always check her
more strictly than the regulations demand.
Her equipment is the poorest
among all the competitors.
In the Corrida Colosseum,
the winner is the winner no matter who it is.
It's not our job to manipulate the facts
and spoil someone's victory!
She won without landing a single blow!
That's one way to win a fight.
Plus, she wasn't just lucky -
she was the only one
who fended off Hakuba's attack.
What?!
I couldn't see anything!
Only you my great senpai could see it!
No matter who it is, though,
I can't let anybody have the Flare-Flare Fruit.
I couldn't wait any longer!
I can finally fight now!
It's the finals next!
Strong Right!
He's doing it again!
So cool! He's totally messing around with
that mechanical guy!
Señor! Just kick that geek's ass already!
You poor girls don't get
how cool cyborgs are!
Look how pretty my mechanical body is!
Huh? I don't get it at all!
What's so cool about that?!
Señor's look is
ten-thousand times prettier than that!
Shut your mouth.
Don't make fun of the way a man is,
you immature flappers.
The way a man is?!
That's right.
This pacifier!
And this drool bib!
I'm not wearing them to attract you tramps.
This is my style and...
...it represents the way I am!
Oh, I'm sorry!
I guess we were wrong!
I kind of like the way you are!
Because I am a man, too.
What are you...
But...
You're my enemy.
I've still got to take you down!
I thought so.
DRESSROSA ROYAL PALACE
THE SUIT CHAMBER
Did you just see that?
Your granddaughter sure is lucky.
I didn't expect you to enter the competition
along with her.
Hey, King Riku.
I can't believe a man who was once a king
fought for the Devil Fruit.
I guess you're quite desperate.
Rebecca!
Anyway, the members of your family are
going too far today.
There was also Violet's betrayal.
It's too much to be a coincidence.
Is it some kind of anniversary?
I know you're not aware of it.
But what you did this morning...
About the report on Doflamingo's abdication
from the throne and the Seven Warlords
that spread all over the world...
It was a mistake. Just a false report.
When I learned that the slight hope was
just a hoax,
it made me want to fight for everything
in this country again.
That was it.
Oh!
I see. That was why you made a move.
But Viola was different.
Unlike you, she is a calculating tramp.
She'll never act purely on her emotions.
I'm sure she's weighing her options.
There is this top rookie
who came to challenge me.
A Warlord,
Trafalgar Law!
Plus, there is someone who has
demonic blood in his veins
and grabbed all the limelight two years ago.
Monkey D. Luffy.
That bitch is wishing those two
allied pirates will defeat me!
But Law is barely alive now.
And Straw Hat Luffy will never come
out of the Colosseum as a human.
And right now, as for the other
members of the Straw Hats,
Cyborg Franky is attacking the Toy House
on his own.
But I don't think he can beat
the executives of my family.
The rest - Pirate Hunter Zoro,
Foxfire Kin'emon, Nico Robin,
and Sniperking are still here.
But I don't think they can even reach
the underground level.
--Hello, sir!
--Oh! New recruits?
Yes, sir!
Good for you! The job here is easy -
you just push around the toys!
Oh yeah? That's good to know!
I don't know anything about this place
so can you teach me?
AT THE FOOT OF THE "KING'S PLATEAU"
There is a lift up there!
LUFFY IN A CARP SUIT
ZORO IN A CAT SUIT
KIN'EMON IN A FROG SUIT
Listen, you all!
The Palace
The palace where Doflamingo
is and the Toy House
The Palace
The Toy House
and the trade port where the
SMILE factory are located -
The Palace
The Toy House
The Trade Port
they are all connected.
You mean, if we can get into the palace,
we can go to the Toy House and the factory?
That's right!
To go to the factory,
you have to pass through
either the palace or the Toy House.
But my colleagues must've
snuck into the trade port
through the secret passage that we dug.
We gotta go to the palace first!
All right. Understood.
But I still can't get over how
there are such small people
even though I see one now.
Yeah, she looks like a toy!
How interesting!
There were tons of them.
Oh! Let me meet them later!
We don't do this often!
We only show ourselves
to the Big Humans of the royal family
but you Usolanders, aka the Straw Hats,
are the exception!
Usolanders?
I'll explain everything later!
Operation SOP is already underway!
Look! There it is!
That's the lift to the
entrance of the palace!
We can go that high with it?!
To enter the lift, we have to show a pass
to a security guard.
Let's just kick his ass!
No!
If you do such a thing, it's gonna be messy
and we'll have to face more enemies!
What's so bad about that?
You bubblehead!
I'm not sure about these people.
In addition to the blockhead who gets lost easily,
I'm with a witless bubblehead!
Who did you call a blockhead?!
There is somebody there.
They already know that we're here?!
Who are you?
You're Straw Hat Luffy, aren't you?
Yes, I am!
Shut up!
I've been waiting for you.
I'll help you enter to the palace!
What?!