Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I won't go easy on anyone
who tries to harm the lady!
What's going on here?
Isn't that dog-penguin hybrid our enemy?
The fighting style he just used...
He couldn't be...
Bastard!
Rookie, you're stepping way out of line!
That woman is the enemy!
What is wrong with you?!
I will beat table manners into anyone
uncouth enough to harm a lady...
...you damn zombies!
I'm sure of it! That dog-penguin is...
Dang, they're persistent!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
One-Sword Style...
...Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
That move... Zoro?!
Hey, Zoro! What was that for?!
That was dangerous!
Scars on the back are a swordsman's shame!
That hurt, you bastard! Lemme out, dammit!
--What was that?
--Bastard, lemme out! I mean it!
I'll let you have it if ya don't
let me out! Open the lid!
--A casket?!
--Lemme out, bastard! I want out!
Open the lid right this second!
Lemme out right now! C'mon!
That voice...!
What's he doing?! Sheesh!
Did that idiot get caught?
Straw Hat!
I won't let you go after him!
Hey, hey! Monkey, monkey, monkey!
I'm the spider monkey that you were
talking about back at the harbor!
It's a giant spider!
This ain't an arachnid
anymore! It's a monster!
Lemme out, you jerk! Lemme out, dummy!
Open the--
And there goes another one!
Shit! There goes the casket!
What are you gonna do to him?!
Don't you worry!
You'll get to personally experience
what is about to happen to him.
I'd be more worried about
myself if I were you!
You're trapped with me in front
and the armored warriors in the rear!
With this, your crew is finished!
"Chivalry Remains! The Traitorous
Zombie Protects Nami!"
Hey! What's gotten into you, rookie?
I thought it was impossible for a
zombie to defy the master's orders!
Why is he able to pull it off?
He's as strong as a General to boot!
You cannot use logic to measure this power.
It is the power to make the
impossible become possible!
The hurricane that blasts
everything in its path is known as...
...love.
Sure enough, that "dog penguin"
is spouting out a bunch of nonsense.
He sounds just like Sanji-kun.
You're right!
Hey, Dogguin! Do you know Sanji?
See, we're Sanji's best
buds! Could ya lend us--
Shut the heck up, you stinking pirates!
"Evil Be Gone"
Scary!
So he really is our enemy after all!
Wh-What's that?
Something is headed this way.
What now?!
Wait, Lola!
Huh? A boar?
Wait, dammit! Lola!
Catch me if you can!
Don't be stupid! You're going to stop!
Nothing in the world could make me stop!
That's what I'll make you think, and then...
What?!
Bride Fu! Princess Carry Vow!
What the heck?!
Wh-What was that?
Ab-sama! Accept my burning love!
H-Hey! Wait, Lola! Knock that off!
--How many times must I
spell it out for you?
I'm marrying that woman!
What was that? I couldn't hear you!
I love you!
Liar! There is no way you couldn't
hear me when we're this close!
Really, you can be so shy!
Listen to me!
Give up already!
I love you! I love you! I love you!
I love you! I love you!...
You'll never get me!
--I won't let that hit me!
--Uh, are they fighting...?
Beats me...
--You're being pigheaded.
--Stuff it!
Then marry me.
That makes no sense!
Snatch a Kiss with Love!
It's high time you gave it a rest!
Oh, my!
What?!
I found you, wretched Cat Burglar!
Nami!
Crap!
Who?! Me?!
W-W-Wait just one second!
I haven't stolen anything yet.
Save it!
I won't let you take Ab-sama!
--Nami!
--Look out!
Don't lay a hand on this lady!
How dare you get in my way?!
--Look out!
--Dogguin!
Dogguin!
Are you okay?
"Evil Be Gone"
Why didn't you attack her?
I won't kick a woman...
...even if it kills me!
Impressive!
You're willing to consider this beast
a woman? You're brilliant, man!
Excuse me?!
No! Usopp! Chopper!
I'll be taking my bride.
Eh?! Nami's flying? That's awesome!
No, you morons! I'm being kidnapped!
What? By whom?
H-Hey, wait!
Now then, we'll hold the
wedding ceremony right away.
I've already dealt with the preparations.
Put me down! It was you, wasn't it?
You're the invisible man
who was in the bathroom!
So there really was an invisible man?
Nami!
I knew it! It was you back there!
I had to appraise your wares.
You are worthy to become my bride!
My name is Absalom.
It is the name of your future husband.
You'd best remember it!
Don't try to sound so macho
after you looked me up and down!
I haven't been babying my skin
every day for a perverted beast!
Thunder Charge!
Nami!
Thank goodness! Now start running!
We're getting out of this forest.
What gives? He isn't blacking out!
Going by the looks of it,
he clearly isn't a small fry!
Hurry!
Wh-What could the shock
coursing through my body mean?
It feels as though I was
suddenly struck by lightning...
Could this be...
...love?!
I won't let you escape!
H-Hey, this is no time to be spacing out!
Our job was to catch those three!
That's right! If we fumble this,
Perona-sama will punish us!
Right, she sure will!
We shouldn't be standing here!
Crap! That lady is in trouble!
But why do I want to protect her anyway?
And my body won't move...!
This body is too weak!
Hurry and catch all three of them!
Wait, Wild Zombies!
Don't touch that woman!
Shut up, Erosalom!
The master ordered us to serve
as Perona-sama's subordinates!
We don't fall under your jurisdiction!
--Beat it!
--Yeah, you heard him!
Shut up! Keep your nose outta this.
I told you to wait!
I am fully aware that you
fall under Perona's domain.
However, you should also know
better than to incur my wrath!
I will only take so many snide remarks!
Do you understand?!
Who are you?
I won't let you go after that lady.
What was that?
H-Hey, rookie! Bite your tongue.
Don't make Absalom angry!
C-Crap!
H-Here it comes!
I warned you not to make me angry!
Wait, Cat Burglar!
Hey, Nami! Doesn't it seem
like everyone's after you?
Seriously! What's up with that?
Sheesh!
So, like, I've got an idea.
Wh-Why don't we split up?
I'm not a decoy, you heartless brute!
No!
Wait up, dammit!
Boars are scary!
Like anyone is gonna wait for you!
N-Nami?!
Wait! Don't abandon me!
Wait!
Here she comes!
No!
Wha--?!
Gah! I'm finished!
It's game over. Farewell, everyone.
Please scatter my ashes in the East Blue...
I won't forgive you!
Huh? What just happened?
We survived?
She doesn't care about
anyone other than Nami?
Phew! That's a load off...
Shoot! Nami!
We've gotta stop her, Chopper!
--Yeah!
--Hi-yo!
Give Absalom back!
What is your problem?!
Nami!
Man, you're one nasty...!
Get away from her!
Run for it, Nami!
Wait, fiend!
Damn it! Stop!
By any chance, did they also...
Lemme out, bastard! I want out, dammit!
Lemme out!
...get sucked into that wall like
what just happened to Straw Hat?
Monkey, monkey!
Yep! You guessed right.
And you will share their
fate in just a moment.
Immortal zombies are blocking the
paths in front of you and behind you.
Now say your prayers!
I'm not sure if you're a stupid
spider or a stupid monkey,
but aren't you responsible
for the massive web
that got all over Sunny at
the entrance to the island?
You’ve been keeping tabs on us;
you were out to get us from the beginning.
Yep! Don't underestimate the
power of our information network!
We knew exactly what you were up to
thanks to Perona-sama's Ghost Network!
Do your large ears also play a
part in collecting information?
They look like they have exceptional hearing.
Eh? What was that? What did you just say?
They're for show!
Franky...
Yeah, I know.
This situation bites. This is what
it means to be "up against a wall."
This calls for quick thinking...
Want me to handle it?
Be my guest.
I'll try to keep up.
That's mighty reassuring!
What's up?
Well, here I go!
Hey, wait! What're you doing?!
Coup de...
...Vent!
What?!
You've demolished the breezeway!
And there you have it.
You're rather violent.
Cien Fleurs!
Wing!
What?!
Dude, you can fly?!
Yes...
For about five seconds.
That's not long!
But it's long enough.
Strong Right!
Sweet! I latched on.
If we can make it to that entrance,
we'll be able to go after Straw Hat!
I'm sorry. I can't keep this up...
Reel back in, arm!
I hope we make it in time!
What?!
All of them fell into the courtyard.
I doubt that finished them off...
...but we won't have to
worry about them for a while.
That worked out nicely.
Man, you're horrible!
How dare you step on me?!
Who do you think you are?!
We can't go back this way.
Hey, you! I know you can hear me!
Don't blow me off! Hey!
What is it?
Tch! They sure are tough.
Curse you! I'll get you scumballs for this!
I'm a spider! I can climb
right back up there!
You'd better prepare yourselves!
Huh?
Something's falling?
No, someone's raining down on us!
What is that?
This bag of bones goes...
Ka-bone!
Hey, hey, hey! Who just flew in from the sky?
Wait. Look at his outfit.
Oh, I see! That cane!
Right! And that hair...!
Well, I have a good idea who it is now.
And from the sky! In-cane-ceivable!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Appearing from the Sky!
That Man Is the Humming Swordsman!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!