Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
saa yukou
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards finally got over the
encircling walls to make it to the scaffold!
As an all-out battle between the Navy and
the Whitebeards continues at the Oris Plaza,
Luffy runs toward Ace!
If you wanna see the future,
I'll show you now, Whitebeard!
Do it!
Ace!
It's no use!
Do you think that I can't
stop you for doing it?!
Don't do it!!
Hey, was that...?!
Conqueror's... Haki!
Hey, come on! For real?!
That was surprising!
That brat...
"The Scaffold at Last! The
Way to Ace Has Opened!"
Yeah! Ace is alive!
Hey, stay with me!
Was that Ace's brother?!
--Look at this!
--I almost passed out!
Like Pops and "Red-Haired,"
he used the Conqueror's Haki!
Was he the one who did it?
Seems like he used it unconsciously.
I didn't know that  he had
such tremendous power!
He was born with it as I thought!
He uses it, too!
Back down if your heart is weak!
He is not just another rookie!
Conqueror's Haki!
But it's not surprising because he's
the son of the revolutionary--Dragon!
Vice Admiral Doberman!
Hey, where did you get the power from?!
Huh?! What power?!
Never mind!
He's not aware of it!
So it's not ready to be used!
But it's no wonder that he attracts people!
This is why they say "blood
will tell," Dragon!
Don't let him escape this battlefield! If
you do, he'll prove a formidable foe for us!
Make sure he dies!
You Navy soldiers are a bunch of cowards!
You need such strength to fight a fledgling?!
I thought you wanted to kill me!
Let's get Whitebeard first!
He's a monster but he's wounded
badly! Bring him down at any cost!
Bring it on!
We're gonna back Pops up!
Don't be afraid! Get him!
Straw boy, now is the chance!
Don't let Straw Hat go!
Damn! Navy soldiers have started regrouping!
--Push it through by force?
--I wonder how long he can hang on!
Pops!
Damn! If I could only take these off!
Pops! Don't push yourself
too far, you're wounded!
You guys!
Pops?!
From now on, back Straw Hat Luffy up...
...with all your strength!
Ace's brother?!
Pops!
Take care of Straw Hat right now!
Straw boy! Watch out!
You're...
...the allied pirate of Whitebeard
- Bohemian Knight Doma!
Nice to meet you, Vice Admiral Momonga!
DeCalvan Brothers!
--You got to fight...!
--...Against us!
"Thunder Lord" McGuy
I need you to fight me,
Vice Admiral Doberman!
I-Is this...?!
We pirates from the New
World will assist you!
Ace-chan's right there! Let's go, Straw Hat!
The allied pirates of Whitebeard
are surrounding Straw Hat!
--What are they doing?!
--Hurry up, Ace's brother!
Navy forces are focusing on Pops now!
This is your only chance
to get beyond the admirals!
Let's break through all
at once! Come with us!
This is a big deal, Straw boy!
The world's greatest pirate
is putting you to the test!
Huh?
Heehaw!
Whitebeard put all his hopes
on you! That's a big thing!
Are you ready to respond
to his expectations?!
I don't know what Whitebeard wants!
But I came here for...
...only one reason, right from the start!
The pirates are gaining vigor!
They're gonna break through!
We need more troops!
Vice Admiral-dono!  Let's
get Straw Hat first...!
Wait!
They left Whitebeard alone!
Attack Whitebeard now!
If we can bring Whitebeard
down, we can stop all of them!
They think that they can beat me
if they attack me all at one time!
Whitebeard! Is he invincible?!
Do it, brat!
You just stopped them from
executing Ace on my behalf!
You have the middle initial D,
so show me how the world
will be in years to come!
That's...
"Hawk-Eye!"
Heads up, Straw boy!
What are you...?!
It's the president's order! We consider
the Navy as our enemy for now! Go!
You're Daz Bonez, aren't you?
Straw boy!
Crocodile!
You're sleeping too much, Mr. 1!
I got out of shape by being in prison.
I don't need you here, Straw Hat! Off you go!
Why are you standing in my way, Crocodile?
I'm not in the best mood now.
So you better watch yourself, "Hawk-Eye!"
Luffy!
I want to help you, too!
Shoot Monkey D. Luffy.
Boa Hancock. Friendly
operative. Abort attack.
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
You're a Warlord, aren't you, Boa Hancock?!
Why do you keep stopping the Pacifistas?!
I thought you were on the Government side!
You're such a senseless man!
You don't know anything!
What?!
Let me tell you one thing.
Love is always a hurricane!
What're you talking about?!
Damn Straw Hat!
Buggy!
Captain Buggy! How's everything going?
It doesn't look good, guys.
I appeared sensationally in front
of the whole world a while ago.
But now people are paying attention to Straw
Hat who is running to the scaffold like a fool!
Guys, who should be today's leading star?
Captain Buggy!
That's right!
I gotta do something flashier
than Straw Hat one more time!
Hey, let me use the Transponder Snail!
Captain Buggy! I'm afraid that
the Snail is still frozen...
What?! Defrost it right away!
It'll melt if you soak it in the seawater
that is heated by Akainu's lava!
It melted!
--Good. Bring it to me!
--Okay!
Here you go!
Please!
It's shrivelled up!
Oh, we shouldn't soak it in seawater!
What the hell, I think it still works.
We've taken the trouble to steal it from
the Navy,
we have to take good care of it.
Transponder Snail-san, could
you wake up for a minute?
Good morning, sir!
No, he pulled in his head!
It's because of your uncanny faces!
Please excuse us, we were born this way!
Damn! Straw Hat will reach the scaffold any
minute while I'm fooling around like this!
Fire!
Not very much longer - make
a path to the scaffold!
They're desperate!
You bastard!
Whitebeard!
Fish-Man Karate!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Jimbei, what the hell are you doing?!
Didn't you hear that I said
"back Ace's brother up?"
I don't belong to the Whitebeard Pirates
so I don't have to obey your order!
Stupid!
They made a path!
The scaffold is close now, Straw boy!
You just run straight!
Alright!
Now is our chance to do it.
I'm sorry that you must do this when you're
not fully recovered.
But we need you!
It's nothing, Ivan-san.
Don't worry about it.
Crab-chan!
Whoa! Wh-What is it?!
Inazuma of the Revolutionaries
army! He did it!
There's a bridge! Alright!
Straw Hat is heading straight
towards the scaffold!
Do something or he'll reach it!
Don't let him!
We can't! These pirates aren't letting us by!
Gah! Use guns! Fire at Straw Hat!
What?! Th-They are...
...commanders of the Whitebeards!
Ace's brother! Just run straight, don't stop!
Break through all at once!
Don't let him pass through!
Gum-Gum...
...Battle Axe!
Luffy-kun, go ahead!
Alright, thanks!
Don't let him go!
Death Wink!
No one will pass by here!
Heehaw!
Just advance, Straw boy!
Straw Hat will make it!
Yeah! Keep going!
Yank Straw Hat down!
Go, Straw Hat!
Set Ace free!
I can't believe that you use that
kid as a trump card, Whitebeard!
But I won't let him go any further!
Whitebeard!
Why don't you stay quiet and watch?
Luffy!
I'm here, Ace!
It's Garp the hero!
Grandpa! Move out of my way!
I'm not going to move!
Because I'm a vice admiral of the Navy!
I've been fighting against pirates
since long before you were born!
Old man!
If you wanna pass through here,
you have to kill me first!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Because of the path you two...
...have chosen to live!!
Luffy runs down the path Inazuma created
intent on reaching Ace, but
Garp stands in his way.
The Navy and pirates...
When a grandfather and grandson who walk
different paths meet again in battle,
what feelings are packed into
the blows they exchange?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Each on Different Paths! Luffy vs. Garp!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!