Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Whoa...
"I'm Luffy! The Man Who's
Gonna be King of the Pirates!"
No worries!
A whirlpool of that size
poses no problem to this ship!
Miss.
May I have this dance?
Alright!
Not again...
Batter out!
What're you doing?
You suck!
This thing's heavy!
Must be filled with booze, then!
It's all ours now!
Ship off the starboard stern!
There's a pirate flag on its mast!
It's a pirate ship!
Enemy raid! Enemy raid!
Captain! Pirates!
What?!
Everyone, stay calm!
Stay calm!
Follow instructions
in a calm manner!
Fire!
Coby!
Y-Yes, ma'am?!
Who's the most beautiful
of all on these seas?
T-This ship's captain,
Alvida-sama, of course!
Well done!
T-Thank you!
Alvida-sama.
This is our first prey in a while.
That's right!
Alright! Start pounding the ship!
Men! Show them the terror of
Iron Club Alvida, the woman pirate!
Coby! What're you doing?!
I-I'm not good
at this sort of thing...
Hmm?! Are you tryin'
to give me backtalk?!
P-Please, anything but the club!
Then get yer ass in gear!
We won't take yer lives, but
we will take all yer valuables!
Anyone who tries to fight back'll
wind up at the bottom of the ocean!
Hello...
There's no one in here, right?
What a relief...
That's a rather large barrel...
Who're you?!
Never seen you before!
Hey, coward!
Are you hidin' out in a
place like this again?!
N-No! I thought I'd haul this
big barrel of alcohol over...
We'll lighten it for ya!
I was just feelin' thirsty!
You can't! Alvida-sama
will kill us if she finds out!
Then you just need
to keep yer mouth shut!
Right, Coby?
Y-Yes! You're right!
Thing's pretty heavy!
Can't wait!
Hold yer horses!
I'll bust it right open!
I slept great!
Huh?
Who're you guys?
No, who are you?!
That guy's gonna catch cold
if he sleeps there, y'know.
You did that!
Are you toyin' with us even
when you know we're pirates?!
Man, I'm hungry!
You got any food?
Listen when people are talking!
You damn kid!
Die!
What's the big idea?
W-Who are you?!
Me?
I'm Monkey D. Luffy.
Nice to meetcha!
What the...
What just happened?
What's with them?
R-Run, hurry! If they come back
with their friends, you'll be killed!
But man, I sure am hungry!
How can you be so carefree?!
There are still lots
more of them up on deck!
C'mon! This way!
H-H-Hey! Not this way!
Food! Food! Food!
Yes! Food!
Actually, they might
not find us in here!
Which should I choose?
This box?
Ooh, jackpot!
These look great!
M-My name is Coby.
You're Luffy-san, right?
That was incredible just now!
How did you do that?!
These things are great!
Is this a pirate ship?
No, it's a passenger ship that's
being raided by Alvida-sama.
Well, it doesn't matter.
Do you know if there
are any boats onboard?
I-I think so...
My ship got swallowed
by this giant whirlpool...
You mean that whirlpool?!
No one could survive that!
Boy, was that a real surprise!
Are you one of those pirates, too?
It was on that fateful day...
That day, I got in a boat on
the outskirts of town to go fishing...
...but it turned out the boat was
actually headed for a pirate ship.
It's been two years since...
In exchange for my life,
I've been forced to be a chore boy.
Man, you're dumb and stupid!
You're brutally honest...
If you don't like it, then run away!
I-I can't! No way! No way!
Just the thought
of Alvida-sama finding me...
...frightens me and makes
me weak in the knees--
Oh, you're a wimp, too?
Man, I hate you!
Hey, now! Quit dawdling!
Haul it all off before
the navy gets here!
Anyone caught dawdling
gets a taste of my iron club!
--What a haul!
--Seems like a pretty rich ship!
Hey! You'll get the club
if she catches you slackin' off!
Oh, whoops!
Yeah, one hit from
that and you're a goner!
Alvida-sama!
It's bad!
What is it?!
You're annoying me!
A b-b-barrel!
M-M-Monster!
Huh?!
Who're you calling a monster?!
N-No... Some weird guy
popped out of a barrel...
He might be...
a bounty hunter...
What?!
Yeah... That's right...
If only I had the courage to
drift the ocean in a barrel...
...there's actually
something I want to do, too...
Umm... What compelled you
to set out onto the sea, Luffy-san?
I'm gonna be
the King of the Pirates!
--K-K-King of the Pirates?!
--Yep.
--Are you serious?!
--Yeah.
Wait, you're a pirate, Luffy-san?!
Yep.
What about your crew?!
Don't got one.
I'm just about to look for one.
K-K-King of the Pirates is
the title given to the person...
...who obtains everything in this world!
That means seeking the great
treasure of wealth, fame, and power...
...the One Piece!
Yup!
Yup?! Pirates all over the
world are after that treasure!
Me too!
No way! No way, no way, no way!
Absolutely no way!
There's no way you can stand at
the apex of this Great Pirate Era!
No way! No way!
Why did you hit me?
Just because.
But it's all right.
I'm used to it now...
It's not about whether I can or not.
I'm gonna do it because I want to.
I've decided to be the King of the Pirates,
so if I die fighting for that,
that's fine with me!
Now, then! My belly's full--
guess I'll go get me a boat!
I wonder if they'll give me one if I ask.
Hopefully they're generous.
I never once thought about it...
Do you suppose I can do it, too?
If I'm prepared to die for it?
Do what?
Do you think...
even I could join the navy?
Navy?
Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
It's been my dream ever since I
was little! Do you think I can do it?!
How should I know?
No! I'll do it! If I'm gonna be a
chore boy for the rest of my life,
then I'll break out of here and
catch even Alvida-sama-- no, Alvida!
You're gonna team up
with him to catch who?!
Huh, Coby?!
You don't seem to be Zoro, the pirate hunter.
Zoro?
Coby!
Who's the most beautiful
of all on these seas?!
O-Of course that would be--
Who's this big chunky lady?
--Chunky?
--Not good...
You runt!
Let's go!
Why, you...
Whoops!
It's not fair to attack from behind!
It's not fair to attack all at once!
Gotcha!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
What?!
L-Luffy-san... What are you?
Me?
I'm a rubber person!
A rubber person?
You can't be serious!
You've eaten a Devil's Fruit, haven't you?
Yeah! The Gum-Gum Fruit!
I see! I'd heard the rumors,
but I guess they really do exist!
You also seem pretty skilled.
You a bounty hunter?
I'm a pirate!
A pirate?! Hah!
All by yourself?!
It's just me right now, but I'll
find some more sooner or later!
Yeah... Ten crewmen sounds good to me!
Ah, so you're a pirate too, huh?!
Then that means you
and me are enemies, huh?
--L-Luffy-san! Let's get out of here!
--Why?
You saw how powerful her club is!
In these waters, she's the most--
I've decided to be
the King of the Pirates,
so if I die fighting for that,
that's fine with me!
I'm the most what?!
T-T-The...
The most ugly,
cragged old hag ever!
What did you say?!
I... I'm going to join the navy!
And then I'm gonna beat up pirates!
Do you even know
what you're saying?!
I do! I'm gonna do
what I want to do!
I'm gonna...
I'm gonna join the navy...
...and catch your lousy ass!
You damn pipsqueak!
No regrets! No regrets!
I said it! I fought! For my dream!
Well said!
That doesn't work!
What?!
'Cause I'm rubber!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
The sky is so blue...
Hey!
--Yes?!
Give Coby a small boat!
He's gonna join the navy!
Keep your mouths shut and let him go!
--R-Right!
Luffy-san!
It's the navy!
Oh, perfect timing!
You should go see 'em!
But I'm a pirate! I'm outta here!
Get serious!
I can't just join the navy like this!
I'll be captured instead!
Looks like we managed to get away...
Whew, that was fun!
Umm, Luffy-san.
If you're heading for the One Piece,
--that means you're going
to the Grand Line, right?
--Yeah.
That place is also referred to
as a pirate graveyard, you know.
Yeah. That's why I need a strong crew.
What about that pirate hunter guy?
What's he like?
You mean Zoro?
I heard he's
being held prisoner at a navy base.
Aw, he's a weakling?
Nothing of the sort!
He's as terrifying as a demon!
Why are you asking about him?
Thought I might have him join
my crew if he's a good guy!
You're being reckless again!
C'mon, he might be a good guy!
He's been caught
because he's a bad guy!
No! No way, no way, no way!
Absolutely no--
Why did you hit me?
Just because!
"To be continued"
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Hey! I'll untie your ropes,
so join my crew!
I refuse to team up with a pirate!
Oh, come on. You're already
known as an evil bounty hunter.
Screw that! I ain't done a single
thing I regret! And I never will!
So I ain't gonna be a pirate!
I've decided you're gonna join me!
Quit deciding on your own!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Enter the Great Swordsman!
Pirate Hunter Roronoa Zoro"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!