Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
Zoro and Sanji have teamed up
in Round #2's Groggy Ring
in order to win Chopper back.
Hamburg catches Sanji! Incredible!
He's within range of the ring!
I ain't gonna...
...let 'em score!
I can't let that damn swordsman snub me...
...by saving my hide!
Now I'm mad, Leader!
Hamburger Hammer!
Punk...
...Attack!
Sling Tackle!
Size Attack: S!
M!
L!
The opponents literally are "groggy"!
All that remains now is to stuff
the ball man into his ring coffin
and this will be two wins in a row!
Hey, cook...
Lend me a hand for ten seconds...
Sounds like... a reasonable length of time...
"A Barrage of Red Cards in Groggy Ring!"
This is Round #2 of the
Davy Back Fight, Groggy Ring!
The outcome of the match is now clear as day!
No one is a match for our monsters!
Although Team Straw Hat was defeated,
I can't help but applaud them
for putting up such a gallant--!
Hey! Look!
Wha...?!
They're up! Team Straw Hat is standing again!
Roronoa the swordsman and Sanji
the cook are terrifyingly tough!
They really know how to make a game exciting!
They're back up! Now get those jerks!
But do these two have
enough strength left to fight?!
Hey, you guys...
One Monster Burger, please!
--Wh-What?!
--What could that mean?
Huh? Do they sell burgers here?
Obviously not!
My word!
Our boss has just ordered a Monster Burger!
Hold on! They're clearly using weapons now!
Grind 'em up like a burger patty...
And slice 'em good like fresh pickles...
Who are the guests?!
Green lettuce... and yellow cheese!
Crush it all between big pans and you get...
...a Monster Burger!
There it is! Their utterly
horrific triple weapon attack!
There's no escape! Foul play
like this clearly calls for red cards!
Team Straw Hat is in a tough bind!
Oh, but wouldn't you know!
The ref just happens to have
his back turned as he stretches!
What are you doing?!
--Stop, Luffy!
--But...!
They want us to butt in!
We need to grin and bear it, Luffy!
Everything's set! The Groggy
Monsters commence their attack!
Whatever happens now, don't blame me!
Naturally, they go after Sanji, the ball man!
Will he be ground up, sliced,
and crushed into a hamburger patty?!
I can't make much with
third-rate ingredients like you guys,
but I'll cook each and every one of you!
You're mincemeat now!
Troisième...
--He's fast!
--...Haché!
Bouquetiere...
...Shoot!
Oh, no!
Stop crushing!
Leader!
How dare you...?!
Don't forget this is a team battle.
Why, you...!
I'll cut you up!
No-Sword Style...
...Tatsu...
...Maki!
M-My word! Big Pan has fallen
victim to Pickles' spinning blades!
Oh, no! Dammit...!
Bad Manner...
...Kick Course!
I-Incredible!
The gigantic Big Pan was falling over,
but is now upright again!
A tremendous kick has kept
Big Pan on his feet and in a daze!
What will Pickles do now?!
Team Foxy is in a pinch!
Oh! Now Zoro the swordsman charges in!
Naturally, he's going after
Big Pan, the ball man!
You're not getting past me!
I've had enough of you and the ref!
The crowd-- no, the referee-- takes a direct hit!
Sanji the cook is truly fearsome!
That was on purpose...!
How dare he... hurt the ref...?!
Red card!
Huh?
My cards and whistle... They're gone...
You're a naughty girl.
Couldn't help it. It's an old habit of mine.
Oh! What's this?!
Is Team Straw Hat arguing again,
in front of the lone Big Pan?!
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
I-Incredible!
Big Pan...
--What?!
--No way!
...the gigantic wotan...
...is airborne!
Go!
They're headed for the goal ring!
No!
Goal!
I-Incredible!
He's airborne!
Go!
No!
It goes in! Goal! Goal! Goal!
Nice, Zoro! Sanji-kun!
All right! Zoro! Sanji! You're awesome!
You bums actually did it!
Y-You did it!
Aww! But I don't wanna give Choppy back!
Zoro! Sanji! Way to go!
Whoa! They're awesome!
Bravo! Bravo!
I'm totally moved to tears!
You guys really are the best!
You dimwits! Who the heck
praises their enemy?!
I can't believe this! No one
defeats the Groggy Monsters...!
Oh, hi, Ref. Wakey-wakey.
Hurry and blow the whistle! Go on!
O-Oh, right.
His behavior toward me was a flagrant foul!
He's outta the game!
And there's the final whistle!
The Groggy Ring match is over!
You did it!
Hurray! We won!
Way to go! Zoro! Sanji!
Thanks for your hard work!
In Round #2 of the Davy Back Fight,
Team Straw Hat has
unbelievably snatched victory away
from the previously
undefeated Groggy Monsters!
Of course we won!
Zoro and Sanji would never lose!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Did you see that?! Did you fall for me?!
You were wonderful!
You jerks! Don't scare me like that!
That hurts.
You did great! You did just what I said!
You didn't do a thing.
Now that Team Straw Hat has
won Round #2's Groggy Ring game,
they're allowed to swipe either a
member of the Foxy Pirates' crew
or the Foxy Pirates' symbol!
Who does the Straw Hat captain want?!
Isn't it obvious?
Huh?! Is it me...?
They wanted me from the very start...!
Oh, man... I'm not ready to go yet...
Crap, it must be me! Our eyes just met...!
I bet it'll be me...
Could be me!
If he chooses me, I'll say goodbye
to these guys with a smile...
They like me, I just know it...
Come on, Luffy... Hurry...
--Okay! I choose--!
--Hold on!
What is it, Nami?
Their boss will probably take
part in the next round, right?
Yeah...
With that Slow-Slow Beam of his,
we won't stand a chance in any game,
no matter what the rules are!
But if we take him now,
we'll have the upper hand in Round 3!
If we take Chopper back now
but lose in this next round,
they could just steal him again!
In which case, taking their boss now
and playing the next game in tip-top condition
is the best way to get
Chopper back and keep him.
U-U-Unbelievable! Is he going to
call for the Foxy Pirates' captain?!
Th-That's the Peanut Strategy!
You guys are the lowest!
You lousy Peanutters!
Fight us fair and square!
There's no rule against it,
but suddenly calling out an opponent's
leader after the second round
is an obvious attempt at avoiding
a fair-and-square, head-on match!
I can't believe my ears! This is the
devilish idea of an inhuman woman!
Her name is Nami, the heathen navigator!
How dare you insult Nami-san?!
I oughta filet you!
In the long history of Davy Back Fights,
no one has ever tried to
pull this wretched trick!
Let me ask you all! Is a win against
a leaderless team a true victory?!
No!
After swearing to Davy Jones
to hold a fair match,
is it okay to turn it into a lie?!
No!
--Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts!...
--I hate them...
Even if it doesn't go against the rules,
it seems it would go against pirate aesthetics.
Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts! Peanuts!...
What's with them?! They're making me mad!
I'm with Nami on this!
Their reaction's only natural.
You're in the wrong, Nami.
Will you shut up already?! Quit actin' cocky!
Our apologies!
Still, like it or not, Monkey D. Luffy,
captain of the winning team,
gets to decide how this game will unfold!
He's free to choose anyone
he wants from Team Foxy!
He'll choose me, I just know it...
I bet an adventure with them would be fun...
It's obvious I'm the only choice here...
No, don't look at me! Please! Don't!
Is he gonna choose me? These guys are cool!
Is it me? Is he gonna pick me?!
Wha...?! It's gonna be me, huh?!
Straw Hat... You're...
You're going to choose me, aren't you?!
Yes, yes... It's obvious you are!
Farewell, Foxy Pirates.
Farewell, wonderful crew!
When he picks me, I'll say goodbye
to them with a smile on my face...
Oh, having such a marvelous personality
and beautiful looks is a sin!
That's definitely something
the Straw Hat Pirates lack!
Oh, there's no doubt they like me!
Say, Navigator.
Your proposal does give us
an overwhelming advantage,
but that also makes their boss part of our crew.
No, thanks.
Our boss has sunk into the ground
from the weight of his feelings!
I can't believe they all
rejected our boss like that!
Oh, Boss! It's okay! We need you!
We do, Boss!
G-Guys...
Let's teach these guys a lesson!
Yeah! I can't wait for the next round!
We love you, Boss!
Boss!
Guys...
Yes! You are my only true comrades!
Thank you!
Cut the crap, will ya?
Boss!
Now that Team Straw Hat's
harassment of our boss has ended,
it's time to pick someone!
Who will he choose?!
All right, then. I wanna take back...
...Shelly!
Wh-What's this?!
Captain Monkey D. Luffy has
chosen Shelly, Tonjit's former horse!
What in the world is he thinking?!
Do you know what you just said,
you dumb captain?!
Of course.
Seriously! What are you thinking?!
Urgh! You always pull this nonsense!
Umm, could you not pull my face?
Looks like you're staying with us, Choppy!
If you weren't going to take their boss,
then you should've chosen Chopper!
But...!
Old stilts guy. I took Shelly
back from those guys.
You guys...
Now you can always be together.
Say, what happened to you two in the back?
You're really hurt. Are you okay?
Some idiot with crazy eyebrows
slowed me down, that's all.
Huh?!
They're certainly full of life...
I appreciate it. Thank you...
It's nothin'. Don't worry about it!
That's a good girl!
Well, that explains that.
Guess it couldn't be helped this time!
Let me treat you all! How about
some cheese at my place?
No, no more of that!
I truly appreciate this.
Thank you.
I'm glad for you, old guy!
Are you sure about this, though?
Your friend is still...
Yeah, Luffy! You need to
consider Chopper's feelings too!
Luffy...
Chopper...
Sorry, Chopper!
We will win the next game and get you back!
So just hang on a little more!
You're a man, right?!
Got a problem with that?
Nope!
Chopper...
Leave it to me! It'll be just fine!
Yeah, sure. Uh-huh.
I wonder what the next game will be.
Let's get started!
We will win Chopper back!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Round #3 is the Roller Skate Race!
A five-round match on a track!
They'll take me if we lose! Because I'm cute!
You gotta be kidding-- Oww!
You're absolutely no
match for us! For you see...!
--Okay, guys! Let's get Chopper back!
--Yeah!
Ignored again...?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Round 3! The Round-and-Round Roller Race!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!