Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy is heading to the
Great Prison - Impel Down
to rescue his brother Ace, who's
been captured by the navy.
Meanwhile, his friends have
been sent to separate islands.
"The Friends' Whereabouts! An Island
of Giant Birds and a Pink Paradise!"
How many times do I have to tell you?!
M-My shin! You kicked my shin!
Why couldn't you get it, you blockhead?!
I require at least 100
kilograms of food per meal.
Anything less than that won't suffice.
Do you want to be turned to stone again?!
N-No! I'm very sorry! I'll be careful!
Bring her another meal to replace this one!
Here, Luffy! Bon appétit!
It's extremely delicious!
When I'm fed by you, the food tastes
sweeter than it actually is!
Oh, I'm glad!
...A-And that's how it'd all play out!
What're you doing over there in the corner?
Aren't you gonna eat? This
Sea King ham is good as hell!
I-I-I'm okay! You eat it!
I'm totally satisfied as I am!
Damn! I can't see anything.
The curtain's closed.
Yeah, it's totally covered! Oh,
there's an open space here!
Love-Love Beam!
Something wrong?
There were two bad-mannered rats
so I just taught them a lesson.
I see!
T-This is...
This must be a warning!
If we ever try to look into her
room, she'll do this to us!
She's scary!
Meanwhile, a few days ago...
On an island in the South Blue...
Luffy!
Everybody!
Oops!
Why isn't anybody here?
Did they kill them?
That can't be it! I won't believe it!
Everybody!
Chopper!
Luffy!
Everybody!
I wasn't scared at all when you guys
weren't there. I really wasn't!
Ow!
Ouch! Stop it, Luffy, Usopp!
I said stop, damn it!
Ouch! You jerk!
What are these birds?!
They're huge!
Are you gonna eat me?!
I-I can't move my body!
I gotta run!
Oww! Stop it!
Oh, my head is spinning!
No! Let me go!
You bastard!
What's wrong with this island!
Is this a dream?
Please tell me this is a dream!
No, stop it!
Stop it!
I am not your toy!
It's over... right?
What is this place?
Isn't there anybody here?
Luffy!
Everybody!
I'm the only one on this island.
What am I gonna do?!
I'm thirsty and hungry...
If only Luffy and everybody else were here,
even on a deserted island like this,
we'd have a banquet!
Banquet, banquet!
Maybe I'll never see them again...
I can't take it!
Where is everybody?!
Luffy... Everybody...
Oh yeah!
There's this!
We made a promise to meet up
where this Vivre Card leads us!
Luffy and others will be there!
I know that nothing can stop them!
I will make it!
This is no time to give up!
I'd eat anything to survive
to see everybody again!
This fruit is bitter!
But it's juicy!
This one's too sour!
Gotcha! I need some meat, too!
But this doesn't look so appetizing.
No, I can't expect too
much on a deserted island.
Wow! You can't run!
You can't get away from me!
Who the hell... hit me?
Ouch!
Why is it so hot?
Am I gonna be dinner?!
Wow, it's so rare to find a raccoon!
We'll cook raccoon hot pot!
I rather get some birds
and do chicken hot pot.
We would've done it, if it were that easy.
We'll just have raccoon for now.
Stop it! I'm a reindeer!
Then it looks like we'll
have reindeer hot pot!
Oh wait, did it just say something?
Do reindeers speak?
Let me go! Just let me go!
I-It's a crisis! We tried to
sneak into the birds' nest
but they caught us!
The birds are coming!
Let's shoo them away!
--Let's go, everyone!
--Let's go!
H-Hey! Wait! Set me free before you go!
Looks like the birds are stronger!
Oh no!
Augh! Ow! Ow!
Ouch! Ouch!
Those birds treated me like a toy
and the humans tried to eat me in a hot pot!
What's wrong with this island?!
One legend suggests this
island is a treasure island.
This is Birdie Kingdom,
where birds reign supreme.
What is Chopper's fate?!
Behold! A dream island in the Grand Line
called Peachy Island.
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,"
"how are you both doing?"
"Right now, I'm... I'm..."
- A FEW HOURS BEFORE -
W-Where am I?
Damn! This is all because of that Warlord!
Excuse me! Mister! Mister! Are you all right?
Mister! Mister! Are you all right?!
I can feel something...
and smell something sweet.
I'm in the hands of a beautiful woman!
Is it... Nami-san?!
No, is it Robin-chan?!
No, I must be dreaming.
But it's doesn't matter. I
just wanna be here forever!
Oh, w-wait a minute!
What's this?
You forgot your handkerchief! Oh?
So it wasn't a dream?
Elizabeth?
Anyway, where the hell am I?
Don't tell me that I'm in heaven!
Her name is Elizabeth...
If this is heaven,
is she an angel?
Oh, my heart aches!
Why is my heart beating so fast?!
This...
must be love!
I can see that romance is blooming!
Sanji-san!
Wait!
Oh no no!
Nami-san and Robin-chan are waiting for me!
No but...
I gotta say thank you to her!
I'm not the kind of guy
to forget his manners!
Nami-san! Robin-chan!
Forgive me for being unfaithful!
Elizabeth-chan! Oh?
This house has the same
design as this handkerchief.
Well then, maybe this is Elizabeth's...
Is Lady Elizabeth here?
My name is Sanji. You were
looking after me a while ago.
I came here to return your handkerchief...
Isn't that a bit cruel, Elizabeth-chan?!
No, don't rush it.
She's a shy, naive girl.
I got to be cool - have patience.
I'm really sorry about the
way I acted back there!
Your hand was so attractive
I couldn't help it!
Excuse me for being so forward but
may I make it up by cooking
something for you?
You can tell me whatever you want to eat!
I may not look it, but I'm a good chef!
Ah, this isn't working.
Do you like to cook?
Oh yes! I love cooking!
Then, do you like clothes?
Clothes?
Yes, yes, of course!
Unlike some stupid swordsmen,
I care about how I look!
Really? You like clothes?
Yes!
Then what about dresses?
Dresses?
I got it!
She keeps asking what I like because she...
Maybe she has a thing for me!
How's this dress? Do you like it?
I like dresses! I like them! I love them!
I'm really fond of it!
How about flower prints?
Flower prints! They're wonderful!
They are really cute!
All right...
Finally, the door to
Elizabeth-chan's heart has...
You have a good taste, Elizabeth-chan!
Don't be shy! You've already
opened up the door of your heart.
Sanji-san!
Now, don't be afraid and
just come into my arms!
Elizabeth-chan!
I think...
...this will look good on you!
Oh, ow, ow, ow...
Despite your appearance, you're
very strong, Elizabeth-chan!
I-Is this a dream? Then it must be...
...a nightmare!
I thought that you were one of us!
You were suffering, weren't you?
You don't have to pretend anymore!
Yes, this is a free country!
Now, put this dress on and open
up the door of your heart!
I-I-I don't wanna open anything!
Wait!
This island is known as
the second Maiden Island.
Everything is pink here.
All people and animals
who come to this island
have girlish hearts.
This can't be heaven!
Hey! Wait!
--Aren't you one of us?!
--You are one of us!
Shut up! Don't come after
me! I told you I'm not!
"Dear Nami-san, Robin-chan,"
"how are you both doing?"
"Right now, I'm..."
"I'm..."
--Wait!
Why don't you wait, man?!
Why should I? Stupid!
Welcome to Kamabakka Kingdom!
"Right now, I'm..."
"...in hell!"
In a certain land where snow silently falls,
the people have been forced to
work day and night for 700 years.
What has Robin seen there?
Around the same time,
Usopp is about to be eaten
by mysterious plants!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Friends' Whereabouts! Bridging
the Islands and Vicious Vegetations!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!