Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that’s what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training
and boarded the newly coated Sunny
setting sail for the Fish-Man Island...
...located 10,000 meters below the sea level...
...in order to go on to the
next stage - the New World.
Okay, that's good!
That's the extra-vehicular Flutter Kick Coating!
An extra-vehicular diving suit!
Wait! You have to attach the safety rope!
Rocket Launcher!
Another arm!
Guard Boost!
Are you guys okay?
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
They did great.
Alright, it's my turn!
"Lost in the Deep Sea!
The Straw Hats Get Separated!"
Third Gear!
Armament; Hardening!
What is that?!
It wasn't like that before!
I feel weak because of the sea!
Damn that octopus! Is it trying to stop him?
Blue Walk!
Whoa, Sanji-san got out of the bubble!
That's really fast!
He's like a Fish-Man! That's so cool!
I've been running and running
in order to get away from those hideous people for 2 years.
Compared to them,
the monster is nothing.
It actually looks rather cute to me.
Diable Jambe!
Bien Cuit...
...Grill Shoot!
I need to breathe!
Three-Sword Style technique;
Crossing the Six Paths!
The demon that rules the
realm of water... So weak!
I feel grateful when I think about it.
I got to fight every single day for the past 2 years.
To top him...
I'm still gonna get stronger!
That was great...
I-I couldn't see his movement!
He shouldn't have done it!
Did you say something, No. 7?
--I'll kill you!
--Bring it on!
Hey hey, Zoro! Sanji! You can't cut his arms!
Gum-Gum...
...Elephant Gun!
He blew it away!
He's gotten so much stronger!
Even while he's in the sea...
Hey! Something is in there!
A shark?
--A shark?
--Isn't that shark wearing something?
That's fairly big.
What is it?
Thanking us for helping him?
What a polite shark.
What?
We're being drawn into the sea current!
Luffy, let's go back to Sunny!
Yeah!
They've been swept away
by the downward current!
Oh no! Follow them! We have to stay together!
Okay!
--I don't wanna die here!
--You've got to be kidding me!
--You're still here?
--You're too calm!
My eyes are spinning! But I don't have eyes!
Keep the yard level! Hard to Port!
We're gonna crash into the continental shelf!
I got it!
Don't lose your concentration,
or the ship will wreck!
What?!
Don't get thrown off!
Stay in the center of the current!
Alright!
It's really fast!
This is fun!
Usopp!
Oh, ow, ow, ow!
I'm alive!
What? Why are you all so glum?
Oh I know! You guys can't
do anything without me...
It's so cold here!
We can't find Luffy and the
other two. We got separated.
What?!
I hope they haven't been
shredded to pieces by the monster.
Your imagination is terrifying...
It's too dark - I wanna look for
them but I can't see anything!
I'm not good with darkness.
I feel something, don't you?
We probably submerged around 7,000 meters.
Even the Shark Submerge can't
take the pressure this deep.
Are we near the Fish-Man Island?
Maybe they got there already...
Camie-chan said it's located
at 10,000 meters below sea level.
We have to submerge 3,000 meters more?!
All they have is a small bubble.
Even if they're alive,
there isn't enough air so it's dangerous!
That's why I told them to
attach the safety rope!
We won't accomplish anything
standing around like this.
Let's look for them. I now have a search light.
What?!
Is it your eyes?!
Franky...
...Nipple Lights!
Why there?!
Oh?
Th-That's huge!
Terrifying!
No way...
That's...
Let's get away!
Just look all around.
They must be looking for us too.
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji!
Where did you go?
Come back!
Luffy-san! Zoro-san! Sanji-san!
Dammit!
In this vast, submerged expanse,
the Sunny Eyes don't help that much.
We're stuck...
The darkness is stirring up our anxiety.
In fact, we're not getting
anywhere. What should we do?
We can't stop the ship so try
not to overlook anything.
There should be some trace of them.
Let's find them.
Yeah.
Oh, it's a jellyfish! There's a
massive jellyfish above us!
That's huge! You're right!
They're twinkling! Like stars in the night!
That's beautiful!
Oh, a tentacle!
D-Do you wanna be my friend?
Don't touch it, Chopper!
It's probably venomous!
Oh no! A little...
...Coup de Burst!
Wh-What?!
The jellyfish got eaten!
Oh, we lost some air.
Better than getting eaten!
Coup de Burst is a weapon that
shoots a fair amount of air.
But since we're in the water,
we only have a limited amount of air.
So when we shoot the air
out, the bubble shrinks!
I see. But it makes me nervous
to see the bubble shrinking.
That fish that got bitten
turned upside down!
So they contain a neurotoxin as I thought.
The deep sea's scary! It's dark too...
There are a lot of fish with
white eyes... It's creepy here!
Since the deep sea is always dark,
there are many creatures with rudimentary eyes.
So they can't see well.
Fools! See this? Come here!
But there are some with developed eyes too.
What's that? How can I see things without eyes?
Do you people wanna know why?
The answer is... Tum, tum, tum, tum, tum...
...a secret!
Are you talking to yourself?
No problem. I'm used to being lonely.
Hey! Stop fooling around and look for them!
Why did I get hit?
Luffy! Zoro! Sanji! Where are you?!
Oh?
This rope must be...
Everyone.
Have you seen that pirate guy?
Oh yeah, he's still here!
I totally forgot about him.
Where did he go?
I haven't seen him since we got this deep.
Maybe he got thrown off
during the downward pull.
That could be it!
His hands and legs were tied up so
he couldn't hold on to anything.
Well but...
...he untied himself. See?
Th-Then, he's somewhere
on the ship? Where is he?
He's got to be hiding somewhere...
What?!
Oh no...
I'll sneak into the girls' room--
if that's what you want, honey.
Damn! We have enough problems already
but now we have to look out for him too.
Who cares! He's not that strong anyway.
It's great.
Those formidable 3 who were fighting
against the Kraken went missing.
There's no way they could have
survived after getting lost
with just those bubbles to protect them.
It's a shame that I couldn't kill Straw Hat
but I can prove that he's dead by killing
these crewmembers and taking their heads.
But don't rush, Caribou!
You can't rush!
If I kill them here, there's no one else to sail the ship.
They navigate the ship pretty well.
As soon as you get to the Fish-Man Island,
you all will be dead!
Here he is!
--Oh no! Shoot! Dammit!
--Now he can't get away.
How did he get in there?
We weren't paying attention. If he
wasn't so stupid, we could be in danger now.
His body wasn't taking form.
It has melted like mud.
--Like mud?
--Yeah, I'm sure it's a Devil Fruit power.
He must've eaten a Logia-type fruit.
He was only pretending to be caught.
Hey, get me out of here, mister!
Mister in swimshorts!
I'll become your servant!
What's the matter, Chopper?
I don't know. I feel hot all of the sudden.
I can't stand the heat.
It's hot! What happened?
Wh-What's this? Smoke?
It's blocking our view forward!
Smoke from the sea floor? Why?
It's...
It could be...
Hydrothermal deposits!
--A volcanic area in the sea!
--What?!
Look, you can see that there
were volcanic eruptions here!
Let's get away from here!
If it erupts, we're gonna die!
It's hot... It's hot...
Something's after us!
Carnivorous Tubeworms!
We have no choice.
A little Coup de Burst!
Faceless Crabs!
I don't even know what they are!
A little Coup de Burst!
The deep sea's scary!
Luffy and the others can't survive here.
I'm starting to get sad.
I finally got to see him after 2 years...
Cut it out! They're not gonna die so easily!
I used Coup de Burst little by
little but we lost so much air.
What is that?! It's so bright!
Is that the Fish-Man Island?
Do you think Luffy and the others are there?
We haven't submerged
another 3,000 meters yet.
"WHO-ARE-YOU?"
Hey! What are you sending
the flashing signals with?!
--Do you see anything?
--No, it's still too bright.
Oh no!
It's an angler! He tricked us!
We were fooled by the deep-sea hunter!
That was close!
We're totally trapped! Can we get away...?
What is it this time?!
I-Is it a human?
What the hell is it?!
A monster in the sea that looks like a man...
It's a Sea Bonze!
He's gonna capsize the ship!
That?!
Hey, Ankoro! You can't do that!
Don't eat ships! How many
times do I have to tell you?
Captain Vander Decken-sama won't like this!
D-Did he help us?
Let's go! We have to get away
anyway! He is a monster too!
What the hell is that?!
The infamous ghost ship, the Flying Dutchman,
emerges from the dark.
But suddenly, a submarine volcano erupts,
creating yet more danger.
Evading falling rocks,
they make it to the ocean floor,
where a scenery not expected
in the Deep Sea awaits them.
On the next episode of One Piece!
Undersea Volcanic Eruption!
Drifting to the Fish-Man Island!
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!