Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal,
they landed on Punk Hazard Island.
It was a strange island
divided into two parts;
the Burning Lands and the Ice Lands.
Sink to your death, Devil Fruit eaters!
Cut that crap. Let us see
inside the laboratory.
I'm the only one here!
If Straw Hat comes, I'll
chop his head off for you.
If that's all you have to say, go home!
I made it out!
One, two, three...
Super!
The Straw Hats?! Children?!
I got out of the building! I can go home!
Oh, you're...!
I was wondering who this
villainous guy was! Smoker!
And you, cutie!
This is not good! The Navy's here!
We can't escape from here!
Let's look for another exit!
Get inside!
What brought the Navy to such a place?!
I don't know! Just run!
Hurry up, kids! Go to the back!
There should be a backdoor!
Everybody, let's catch the Straw Hats!
Room.
Takt!
No way!
"In a Real Pinch! Luffy Sinks
into the Ice-cold Lake!"
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND - THE
MIDDLE LAKE LUFFY'S GROUP
Fire!
Aim at the bottom of the boat!
Let's go back!
What're you talking about, Usopp?!
Advance!
You have no idea what's going on, do you?!
They're trying to make us fall into the lake!
You can't get away from me - Brownbeard-sama!
Who are you, again?
Don't tell me you don't know who I am!
I'm a former pirate with an 80
million 60 thousand berry bounty!
Brownbeard-sama!
Brownbeard-sama! Sama...
Sama... Sama... Sama...
We've never heard of you!
How can they be so ignorant?!
Take this! An angry shot!
Damn, those bastards!
We're gonna fall!
Oh no!
--Yes! He did it!
--That's our Boss!
The boat capsized!
How's that?! Struggle as much as you like
but you'll be swallowed by the water!
It's cold!!
My body's gonna turn to ice
in a matter of minutes!
Dammit!
I'm losing my strength...
You could've fought back, Duffy!
Bud you didn't shtop recruiting zem!
Oh no! My mouth is freebing...
Zorry. I give up.
I don't need zem to join our crew.
All right! Let's finish them!
Get ready!
Hey, Usopp!
Hold these two!
I'm gonna slice them up!
Please hurry up... O-Or I'm gonna...
It won't take long!
Huh? Hey, what happened, Roro?!
Sharks!
Why are sharks in a lake?!
Fools!
It's technically a sea.
The fight between Akainu and Aokiji left
a crater just like after an explosion.
And then seawater streamed in from
a big crack and created a lake.
Of course, so did a lot of sea life.
Zoro!
Sharks! Scary! Sharks! Zoro
got bitten by a shark!
Aim carefully! There is
nothing they can do now!
We have no place to go!
Blow them to kingdom come!
What?! I've never thought
my life would end like this!
This is it!
Fire!
Huh?
What? What happened?!
Brook!
What is colder than a freezing blizzard?
It's the wind from the underworld.
You bastard!
Oh, did I mention I froze your gun barrels?
So they'll explode if you shoot!
Who are you, skull mask?!
My name is not worth mentioning. It's Brook.
You just mentioned it.
I'm a skeleton who came back from
the dead and put my second life...
...in the hands of the Straw Hat captain!
People call me Soul King!
When did he freeze our guns?!
That's unforgivable!
"Unforgivable"? Right back at you!
--You bastard!
--How dare you?!
Losing friends - I'm sick of it (korigori)!
What?
And it sounds like ice (koori)!
He's fast! He sure can fight!
I didn't know they had another crewmember!
But it doesn't matter now!
Because they already became shark food.
See for yourself!
The sharks got their butts kicked!
Hey, where did they go?
We're here!
You're just in time, Brook.
I'm glad that you're okay!
I was chased by a strange thing
and happened to come this far.
Nice try, you part-human-part-animals!
But sharks can't stop us!
We're way stronger than that!
But no matter... how strong we are...
we can't stand the cold!
It's freezing! I'm gonna turn to ice!
"I TOLD YOU GUYS..." I rold you guys...
"WE CAN'T JUST GO TO THE
COLD SIDE LIKE THIS...
We can't hust go to the
cold shide like this...
But look. We're lucky.
We should be glad that we ran into them.
Boss, they're right on top of us!
Wait! They look familiar!
He looks good!
I'll take the fourth guy from the right.
All right!
I'll take the guy next to him.
I'll take that one.
The girl at the far left.
What are they talking about?
Their clothes look warm!
"ALL RIGHT... PLEASE GET ME ONE, TOO!"
All right... flease ket me one, too!
Are they looking to rip our coats off?!
They're terrible! Do they wanna rob us?!
I know! That hat!
He is the rookie of that worst
generation from two years ago!
What?!
Yeah!
He is Fire Fist's brother!
Whaaat?!
A pirate with a 400 million
berry bounty - Straw Hat Luffy!
4... 400 million?!
Mil Fleurs!
Wh-What is that?!
No!!
Give me your clothes!
You'd better not fight back!
Then I won't have to hurt you so bad!
Oh, my friends. You're in
better shape than I thought!
Help me!!
THE LABORATORY - IN FRONT
OF THE MAIN ENTRANCE
I told you, Smo-san!
This is why I said I didn't
want anything to do with him!
What should we do?!
Hurry up! Hi-ya! It's this way, kids!
We gotta find a backdoor!
Wait!
Go back! It was that man who cut me up!
What? Really?!
Then he may have the rest of your body?!
No, I don't think so!
Then, it can wait!
Wait a minute! Maybe I can get a clue!
We have to find a backdoor!
We can't go back to face the Navy again!
I don't see any exit! Where is the backdoor?!
All right! Super count on me!
You got some kind of sensor on you?!
There's no such a thing!
Then why did you take the lead?!
That was that samurai...
Let's go! Let's go!
...And the Straw Hats.
I can't let them escape!
Room!
What is this?! It's like a thin film...
Shambles!
What was that? I felt something weird!
No time to think about it now!
Alright, keep running, brats!
Oh? Did I drop my cigarette?
Follow me!
What is this?!
Hey, this is no time for you
to fool around, Sanji-kun!
In this week's episode, I'm super!
I'll find a backdoor in a moment!
What?
--Everybody?
--There's something wrong with you!
Huh? What is it?
Come to think of it, my
breasts feel lighter...
What happened?!
These are...! I got big breasts!
I-I turned into a human!
When did it happen? I'm a racoon now?!
E-Everybody, calm down!
Let's do a roll call!
--Chopper!
--Here!
--Franky!
--Yeah!
Sanji-kun?
What?
Nami-san?
You're Nami... aren't you?
Uh-huh!
What is going on here?!
Law, you bastard!
What do you want?
Give us back our ship.
All right.
Really?!
But you can't have it as it is now.
--It's falling toward us!
--Run!
Let's retreat for now, Vice
Admiral! His power is too creepy!
We can't fight him!
I won't let anyone leave!
It's been fused to the rocks of the island?!
He made some sort of strange
artwork with the ship!
Damn! We can't make it back
to the base without the ship!
The Warlords work for the Government!
You're breaking your
contract by attacking us!
Trafalgar!
--We'll report this to headquarters!
--They'll strip you of your title!
Don't worry about me.
Scan!
What's this?! Stop!
Huh? Transponder Snails?
Oh? Mine's gone!
No way... So is mine!
Those are ours!
He took all of our Transponder Snails!
I won't let you tell the
headquarters or the Government
about anything that you've
seen on this island.
You stupid pirate, don't push your luck!
Smo-yan!
You ate the Op-Op Fruit and you're
the Modification Man, I believe!
Stay out of his sword's reach!
I got cut!
Huh? But I'm alive!
You guys are in my way!
Get out of the circle!
The circle?!
While you're in the circle he created,
you're like a patient on an operating table!
This is his operating room.
He has total control over it and can
manipulate anything as he pleases!
He's the Surgeon of Death!
Trafalgar!
If you really wanna do this...
Don't do it, Tashigi!
Your Haki is not strong enough!
Captain-chan!
With Tashigi being cut down,
the thugs of the Navy's G-5 unit were
also about to face annihilation.
But then Smoker faces Law.
A duel between a Warlord and a
Navy Vice-Admiral finally begins.
Their fierce battle that destroys
everything around them
suddenly takes an unexpected turn.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Meeting Again After Two Years!
Luffy and Law!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!