Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
but Law has been captured by Doflamingo.
Luffy snuck into the Royal Palace
to take back Law.
Hey Sugar, what are you doing?!
Keep your senses!
Meanwhile, Usopp knocked Sugar out
and freed the toys who had been
forced to labor as slaves.
Mingo's dead!
Disgusting!
Ow, it's hot!
I really can generate a fire!
Ace!
I take over your ability!
You are...
Fire Fist!
"Dashing onto the Scene!
The Chief of Staff of the Revolutionary Army, Sabo!"
The ring is disappearing.
Who are you?
I got in touch with Hack.
Let's meet up with him!
All right.
God Usopp! God Usopp! God Usopp!...
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Usoland! Usoland!
Guide us, God Usopp!
What are we supposed to do?!
Then, why don't you destroy
the factory behind me
and rescue our little friends?
Be careful!
Devil Fruit eaters are
weakened by touching water.
Oh yeah.
God Usopp gave us guidance!
Destroy the factory!
"Destroy the factory"?!
I won't let you do such a thing!
God Usopp. Leave the rest to us.
More importantly... I want you to...
...put me down.
This way!
Sorry!
That's...
Shit!
That guy was not Straw Hat!
How dare he eat the Flare-Flare Fruit
that was supposed to be mine!
Damn!
How can I tell Doffy about this situation?
Who are those bastards?!
--Look! He's a Doflamingo operative!
--Thank you for turning us into toys!
Take him down together with the factory!
I see! They were the toys underground!
Here! I'm here!
Hack!
Feels like I haven't seen
you for a long time.
It's strange.
Oh?
What happened to your hand?
This is...
I just fell down!
Fell down? You? Really?
Wh-Why would I have to tell a lie?
I can't believe there was a
space like this underground!
--Oh yeah! Here are your clothes.
--Thanks.
Bloody hell!
It caught fire! This is hard to control!
--Excuse me...
--Hey!
How could you leave me behind like that,
my great senpai!
Yes, I'm a man and
I can create barriers but...
That guy is...
Who are you really?
Me?
My name is Sabo.
KOALA - THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
SABO - THE CHIEF OF STAFF OF THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
HACK - THE REVOLUTIONARY ARMY
We're members of the Revolutionary Army.
The Revolutionary Army?!
What? Then, the first Lucy, too?!
The first Lucy has a bounty of 400 million.
He's the man who'll become
the King of the Pirates someday!
Straw Hat Luffy!
A pirate?!
Yeah, he's my brother. Take good care of him!
--Wh-What?!
--Yep, yep!
Luffy is a nice guy, isn't he?
You guys! Are you gonna become pirates?!
I'm gonna become one, too!
He hasn't changed a bit.
Well, let's just leave
it until the time comes.
Maybe we'll set out independently.
Oh, you stole that from Dadan!
Did you guys know?!
We can become brothers
if we exchange this cup of sake!
Brothers? Really?!
When we become pirates,
we might not be on the same ship
but our brotherhood will always be with us!
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
we'll always be bonded together!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Yeah!!
He's still reckless and everything.
Sabo-kun, you do very reckless things, too!
Do I?
Well, I think it through before I let loose.
What do you mean?
Luffy, however, merely follows his instincts.
What's the difference?
But what brought you Revolutionaries
here to this country?
Those are...
These weapons that they export from this port
aggravate wars around the world.
We're here to...
...stop it!
The Revolutionary Army has sent soldiers
to this country many times
but because they all got turned into toys,
we couldn't find out about this black market.
Hey, that guy's troublesome!
Yeah, that's Sabo, isn't it?!
What is the number 2 of the
Revolutionary Army doing here?!
Gotta tell the Young Master!
But I guess they're manufacturing
weapons somewhere else.
Where do they come from?
If we can find that out,
Dragon-san will be pleased.
Things are getting messier!
Issho-san, what should we do?!
Son of a bitch!
THE KING'S PLATEAU - IN
FRONT OF THE RAMPART TOWER
Quite a ruckus.
I guess something is going on down there.
Anyway, where did he go?
The stone man!
What?!
Doflamingo!
Hey, sorry! Let me through!
You jerk!
What the...
How dare you turn us into toys!
Now I'm gonna get my revenge!
Prepare to die, Doflamingo!
Doflamingo's gone!
No way! It's impossible!
Dammit! Where did he go?! Doflamingo!
I bet he hasn't made it that far yet!
Look for him!
That was close.
I thought this was Doflamingo's stronghold.
Why was I targeted?
Could it be...?!
The toys must've turned back to their original forms!
They accomplished Operation SOP!
--What?! They pulled it off?!
--Yeah, yeah! They did it, they did it!
--That's great!
--They did it!
You'd better turn back to yourself
or you'll be targeted again!
Oh! You're right!
Poof!
Kanjuro! I'm coming to save you!
Koala!
Robin-san!
I thought it was you! How've you been?!
Great!
Sabo! Hack!
You all haven't changed a bit!
Yo!
Ro... R-R-R-R-R... Robin senpai?!
Did you see Luffy?
Uh-huh.
Oh! The guy from earlier!
He's one of our crew! He's Usopp!
H-Hi'm Ohahho (I'm Usopp).
He can stay down.
Usopp?! One of their crew?
No, no, no, no!
I didn't see such a name
on their wanted posters!
D-D-Don't tell me he is...!
What is wrong with you?
THE ROYAL PALACE
You bastard!
How dare you kill the Young Master!
Prepare to be blown away!
Dasu...!
Buffalo!
You asshole!
Damn!
Tra-guy!
I'm here to save you!
Straw Hat?!
I'm glad that you're alive!
You have no business here, Straw Hat!
What about the factory?!
Did you destroy it?!
Here's the key to his handcuffs!
You have everything prepared!
Wait, Straw Hat! Violet!
You can't lay a finger on the Young Master...
Young Master?
What... happened?
King Riku-sama! Sorry to keep you waiting!
Give me a minute! I'm gonna rescue you!
Thanks, but the alliance
between me and you guys is over!
Get out of here!
Huh?! How selfish!
I'll make those decisions,
not you, so shut your mouth!
That makes you more selfish than me!
Unlock it!
Oh yeah.
If there's no alliance,
we're not on the same side!
If you set me free, I'll kill you!
Stop moving!
It's hard to unlock it
since I can't touch Sea Prism Stone!
You can do it!
You two are not listening to me!
I can't!
Why don't you do it?!
I can't! I'm a Devil Fruit eater, too!
Oh, the stone guy!
Pica!
I never thought I'd be taken in like this.
Mingo's alive!
--Young Master-sama!
--Young Master!
How could he still be alive?!
The whole country is thrown into chaos
after the toys have been freed.
And for whatever reason,
the Revolutionary Army is here secretly, too.
And the Royal Palace is a mess.
It's a difficult situation.
I have no choice but to use the "Birdcage."
The Birdcage?!
Right, Law?
Luffy lands in a fight with
Doflamingo, risen from the dead!
In the heat of the fierce battle,
the worst extermination plan in the history begins,
meant to hide the true history of the country
and plunge the island into terror!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Devil's Trap! A Dressrosa Extermination Plan!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!