Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
This is your punishment.
There is no way to neutralize the
amount of poison you have absorbed!
What do you think you're doing to...
...Bon-chan?!
Leave Bon-chan...
...alone!
After fighting the Army Wolves,
Luffy and Bon Clay lost consciousness
and a mysterious man named Inazuma
rescued them and took them to...
Welcome to...
...Impel Down--Level 5.5!
It's a secret garden for prisoners!
New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
"Luffy's Treatment Begins!
Ivan-san's Miraculous Power!"
Yeah! Yo! Wow!
Ah hey! Hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Third district, third district, wow!
Fourth district, fourth district, wow!
Gay district, gay district, wow!
You're wonderful!
Heehaw!
Is he...
Heehaw! Haw!
...Ivan-san?!
I got a little too excited...
I'm starting to get a little dizzy...
Ivan-sama, are you alright?
I'm gonna... collapse...
...Or not!
That was a joke?!
You sure fooled me!
You're Ivan-san, aren't you?!
Oh dear!
Do you know about me?!
Hey! Calling him Ivan-san
is so disrespectful!
She's right!
He's the king of New Kama Ivan-sama!
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama!
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama...
Hush, now, candies!
Don't sweat the small stuff!
It's just a little thing!
They can call me whatever they want!
Even "Dooky" is fine!
No, don't call me "Dooky!"
Then why did you say it?!
You got me again!
H-He is the miracle-worker?!
The one that I worshipped for so long?!
Not "Dooky!"
Emporio Ivankov!
You were the queen of
Kamabakka Kingdom, weren't you?!
15 years ago, my father who was
once king of a country himself...
...went to Kamabakka Kingdom and...
...came back as a queer!
Aak!
Because the king became a queer,
both his country and family were ruined
and I fell from my princely status
to become a lowly pirate!
I'm glad to have found you!
You'll pay the price for ruining my life!
No! No!
Don't do that! Where did you get that thing?!
Watch it!
I said "watch it!"
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna die!
If I get shot, I'm gonna...
I'm gonna die...
...Or not!
You're such a character!
You were pulling my leg?!
Death Wink!
Yes! That's how Ivan-sama blinks!
He was able to turn back that
bullet with only a wink?!
Emporio Female Hormone!
What did you do?!
You bastard! Don't tell me it's...
Your father wanted to become a woman!
What's wrong with that?!
Oh no!
I'm gonna lose it!
Two mothers and one daughter!
What's wrong with that?!
It's your family!
No! Please don't...
...do it!
What?!
What happened?
Way to go!
You can become a woman or a man,
heehaw!
Even a fairy!
You can become whoever you want!
Don't you think so?!
The border called gender!
I... No, everyone here,
heehaw!
We've all crossed that border!
So we're the new human race!
New Kama!
This is the garden of freedom -
New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama!
Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama! Ivan-sama!
He transformed a man into a woman!
He is a miracle-worker! What great power!
Welcome to our New Kama Land!
Heehaw!
I'm so embarrassed!
Heehaw! She's embarrassed!
She's still got a long way to go
to become a New Kama!
Bon boy?
The miracle-worker, Emporio Ivankov!
It's my honor to meet you!
I'm glad to see you! I'm so glad!
If you don't mind, I have a favor to ask you!
A favor?
Can you save my friend's life?!
He was poisoned by Magellan!
No antidote can help him and he's just dying!
I'll do anything for you if you'll save him!
Are you talking about Straw boy?
Bon boy?
Huh?
Do you know why you've been treated already?
Oh yeah! When did you do it?!
We're just prisoners!
We don't just take in and
care for anyone who we find injured.
We're just not that nice!
I treated you because Straw boy begged me to.
Straw-chan begged you?!
We've been watching you guys on the monitor.
Straw boy,
I can't believe that you made it this far.
I've never seen people as lucky as you guys!
Bon...
Bon-chan tried to help me
and got bitten by the wolves!
Take care of him!
I beg you! He's my friend!
You wouldn't say something
like that when you're dying.
So some friendships can't
be ruined even in a prison.
When someone begs you like that,
you gotta do it unless you're
a demon in human skin.
Straw-chan!
I already began the treatment
of Straw boy 10 hours ago!
Really?!
But, in a rough way...
Hey! Those of you born after the 90's!
These are old-fashioned bamboo stilts!
You gotta try these! It's fun!
I mean, I made these with wax,
so we should call them wax stilts!
How much longer can they keep this up?!
Go away now!
It's not good!
We gotta get off of this floor
in order to lose them!
Just keep running!
Tell me somebody! Where's the exit?!
What's going on here?!
Is this the treatment?!
He's been screaming for 10 hours
since we put him in this chamber.
It'll be two more days before he is treated.
What?!
10 years of your life.
I'll have to use 10 years of
your future for this treatment,
Straw boy.
Alright!
But there's no guarantee
that it's gonna save your life.
Now you have no chance of survival
and all I can do is give you
a 2 to 3% chance for survival.
And then it's up to your spirit,
if it's possible or impossible
for you to survive.
If the poison takes over, you will die.
But if spirit wins out
you will survive!
Alright now, have a nice trip to...
...the valley of the shadow of death!
Emporio...
...Healing Hormone!
10... 10 hours?!
Straw-chan has been screaming
like this for 10 hours?!
Spirits and hormones,
these are the vital forces of the human body.
They bring out the power to heal oneself!
I have drawn out his latent
immunity and changed his body...
...to enable him to battle
with the deadly poison.
There is a lot of destruction and recovery
raging at an extraordinary
speed inside of his body.
He will survive only if he can
make it through the pain!
W-What?!
You can take a look inside if you want.
Where... Where is it?!
Straw-chan...?
H-He's gonna die!
It's gonna tear up his body and
it's gonna be all messed up and...
No, he's already dead!
How could you?!
Help Straw-chan! Please! Help him!
Untie the chains and stop him bleeding!
T-That's horrible! Please!
Please do something!
Shut up!
I'm helping him now!
Don't underestimate human life!
Huh?!
Don't you know what it takes to
strive against one's own mortality?!
I'm not the God or Buddha!
A miracle-worker?!
You can call me whatever you want, but...
...I could never save a fool who
only depends on other people.
I saved an impoverished country
and a country that was defeated in war
but all I did was draw
out their spirit to live.
Miracles only happen to
people who don't give up!
Don't underestimate miracles!
Ace!
THE PUBLIC EXECUTION OF ACE IS IN...
...16 HOURS!
Luffy fights the poison treatment himself.
The chance of survival is so slim,
it would be a miracle for him to survive.
Trusting his friend,
Bon Clay continues to cheer for his survival.
And then, the time of Ace's
execution is finally at hand.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Believe in Miracles!
Bon Clay's Cries from the Heart!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!