Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
"Back to the Present!
Hordy Makes a Move!"
Jimbei!
Damn! Who shot our queen?!
Look for the shooter!
Leave no stone unturned!
Brother Tai! Queen Otohime! I... I...
What should I do with this anger?!
Shit! Dammit!
There he is! We found the shooter!
Go! Get to the rooftop now!
Is he the shooter?!
He had a gun in his hand. There is no doubt.
What?
Where is he?!
Jimbei-san! We just killed him.
Who was it?
Well...
It's a...
...human!
Hide the body!
What? Boss Jimbei!
It will ruin the Queen's efforts!
She won't be able to rest in peace like this!
But it is what it is.
No, because he was a pirate!
It doesn't matter if he was a pirate or not.
No, Hordy! Don't do it!
Listen, everyone!
It was a human...
...who killed our queen!
Queen Otohime was killed by a human!!
She didn't deserve it!
A human...
...killed the Queen who wanted
nothing but peaceful coexistence
and broke our hearts just when we were
inspired by her words and about to...
...extend our friendship!
He took our beloved one's life!
Even by taking your life,
Otohime-sama can never come back, human!
Is there no justice in this world?!
It's so sad! Unbelievably sad!
Is the King still in the Hard Shell Tower?
Minister of the Left!
Can you hear that? He's lost all control.
King-sama!
Lock the door!
Don't open it while I have
this urge to kill someone!
King-sama, it's me.
Minister of the Left.
The shooter had a gun in his hand so
one of our soldiers shot him dead.
It was a human.
I would have killed him
even if he were unarmed.
But Otohime would not allow that.
I don't know when this
cycle of revenge started.
But if I kill somebody, I would
only perpetuate that cycle.
Witnessing my actions would
make children's eyes cold
and they would harbor
hatred and become bitter,
the cycle of revenge spiraling on.
I could relate to what Otohime was saying...
...as long as it was somebody else's problem!
But...
...why shouldn't I kill the man
who shot my wife to death?!
I can't understand that-jamon...
As a soldier, I have taken many
lives in reprisal for my friends.
I killed many humans who besieged us!
That is why I thought I have no place
helping Otohime in what she was doing
so I just stood by and watched.
Why should an innocent one like
her die and a man like me still live?!
I can't take over her quest
because my hands are sullied
by what I have done in the past-jamon.
B-But we all change and we all
are full of contradictions.
We Fish-Men, and humans too. And there are
things that only soldiers can protect.
A FEW DAYS LATER
King-sama!
Thank you all.
It's my own wife's funeral
- I have to attend it-jamon.
Father-sama! Father-sama!
Shirahoshi...
Father...
My sons.
I'm glad to see you.
I'm sorry to make you feel so left alone.
TO SHIRAHOSHI
Um... Father-sama, look at this.
What is it?
These letters keep flying in wherever I go.
There are already 5 of them, Father-sama!
It's...
I'M IN LUV WITH YOU. I SUSPECT.
MARRY ME. VANDER DECKEN
...a love letter!
But Shirahoshi is only 6 years old.
Who is Vander Decken?
That is the name of a pirate family.
My children won't attend the funeral!
What?
There could be an accomplice
still lurking around.
And catch this pirate named Decken now!
Yes, sir!
Everyone!
Look at the monitor!
--Prince Fukaboshi!
--Prince-sama!
Fukaboshi...
Citizens of the Fish-Man Island.
There is something I
want to tell you all today.
So please give me your attention.
In her last moment, my mother said happily,
"We are almost there at that
place under the real sun."
We have decided to take over
our mother's dream and dedicate
our lives to seeing it through.
Princes...
You probably are not going to be
ready for the World Summit in 2 years.
But there will be another one in
6 years and another in 10 years.
I'm sure this tragedy made you
change your view of humans.
So I will get rid of all the
signatures that were left unburned.
Let's start from the beginning!
And when your emotional
wounds heal someday,
let's dream about the sun together again!
And for the decade that followed,
not just Fukaboshi, Ryuboshi and Manboshi
but also the King and the Princess spoke
to the nation through the monitor
all while signatures kept mounting up again.
So that was how we have been fighting against
discrimination for the last 16 years
and the beginning of the Fish-Man Pirates.
Arlong, who did horrible
things to your hometown,
was like a brother to me.
If he engaged in violence, we were willing to
go anywhere in order to stop him ourselves
but he always paid off the
Navy soldiers around him...
...to keep his actions secret from the Navy.
As a result, I made you
and many others suffer.
I feel responsible!
Oh yeah?
Then why don't you cut your own belly?!
Sanji...
Pay her with your life!
I still won't forgive you but it
could relieve Nami-san of her pain!
Stop, Sanji-kun!
But Nami-san, what they
have done to you was...
That's a different story!
This man didn't mean to hurt us.
Nami-san...
I will take any punishment!
If it makes you happy...
Stop!
Stop. The only one I hate is Arlong.
Anyway, I'm glad that you are not the
mastermind of the Arlong Pirates.
Because you're Luffy's friend, aren't you?
It's true that I've gone through
hell because of the Arlong Pirates
but I met my friends in
that horrible turmoil.
One thing led to another
and I am who I am today.
I'm not gonna hate you
because you're a Fish-Man.
So don't pity me because of my life!
It's not so bad because I'm
enjoying it in the present!
So it doesn't matter who did this...
Don't get angry on my behalf.
Don't tell the people
on the island anything!
Neither the tragedy we endured
nor of our anger towards humans!
Don't worry, Jimbei.
You two grew up together and
he's like a brother to you.
No wonder you couldn't just kill
him even though you were justified.
I don't deserve such words of kindness!
Thank you!
Nami!
Boss Jimbei-sama...
Oh! I know how hard it is to be a big brother!
You're the man, Jimbei!
I like Tiger and Otoshime
and everybody very much!
Shut up, Franky!
He must've been feeling so much pain...
What?
Luffy?
What?!
Hey, wake up!
That was a good nap.
I can't believe it! I thought it was
unusual for you to listen so quietly.
Huh? Jimbei, are you crying?!
What are you saying? I am not crying!
Why is that?
Cut it out! I said I am not crying!
Hmmm... Oh, well!
And Jimbei, what did happen to the
thief that Coward's mother caught?
You must've been sleeping most of
the time! That was the very beginning!
--Was it?
--It was!
Hey, so your name is Shirahoshi?
N-Nami-chin, she's the Princess!
You can't say "Hey"...
Yes. Oh, excuse me.
I was crying remembering my mother.
She was quite a woman, wasn't she?
Yes!
So you are Nami-chin-sama.
No, Mermaid Princess-sama!
Nami-chin is like her nickname.
Her real name has no "chin."
It feels like I have known you since I was a
kid although we just met for the first time...
I feel comfortable with you.
Yeah? Maybe that's because we've
been through similar things.
Now, excuse me.
I took too much time. I need to know
who is still at the Ryugu Palace now.
Hordy and his crew invaded the palace
and captured the King and his soldiers.
And you don't know what
happened to four of your crew.
That's all the information we have so far.
Jimbei-san.
If things are going as Hordy planned,
the whole country might be
in a terrible state by now.
Do you know what his plan is?!
I suspected he was up to something
in the Fish-Man District
after retiring from the army,
but he never revealed it to me.
Yeah, I know.
Hordy hates humans more
than Arlong-san did.
He has been living on the resentment and
anger of the Fish-Men, and nothing else.
And there is something about him
clearly different from Arlong-san.
Arlong-san would look down on humans
but he would never hurt other Fish-Men.
But Hordy will attack those Fish-Men
who are sympathetic to humans...
...without mercy!
This year is the World Summit which
takes place every four years.
Since they gathered enough signatures,
King Neptune will express his
intention to the world finally,
to relocate the Fish-Man Island.
Don't tell me he is planning to block it!
No, he wants more than that.
Wh-What is that?!
That's a big Transponder Snail!
It's a Video Transponder Snail!
Why is it here?
Look! It's activated!
Oh, it's projecting something on the bubble!
That's...
He's the...
Nami-san, do you know him?
Hordy!
What?! That's him?!
Hatchin!
Uh, everybody on the Fish-Man Island.
Can you hear me?
I'm the captain of the New Fish-Man
Pirates from the Fish-Man District,
Hordy Jones!
Hordy broadcasts his ambition
across all of Fish-Man Island.
His shocking intention is
to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
and establish himself as the new king.
The citizens of Fish-Man Island
had been deeply unsettled already,
but Hordy's announcement has
further filled them with dread!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Kingdom in Shock!
An Order to Execute Neptune Issued!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!