Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner (･∀･)
Wanted->means Winner :D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
the future that I’m aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled
by the Four Emperors.
After receiving an emergency signal,
they landed on Punk Hazard Island.
It was a strange island
divided into two parts;
the Burning Lands and the Ice Lands.
Whether it's the Straw Hats or Smoker,
we can get rid of all those troublemakers
who are learning what's
going on on this island at once!
Call Joker.
Yes, sir!
I never understood why you joined
the Warlords in the first place!
What are you up to?
There are things that you can't see
unless you change your standing, Smoker!
Scalpel!
My heart!
I don't have to tell you anything.
"Meeting Again After Two Years!
Luffy and Law!"
No!
Tashigi-chan!
He's way too strong!
Let go of me!
I didn't join the Navy
to cower behind rocks!
You will get chopped up again in that film!
Leave it up to Smo-yan for now!
Oh? The film is gone!
Now is our chance!
Go, Alliga-taur!
What is that?
A ship?
Isn't it a warship?
So the Navy's here?
What? I didn't see anything
around here little while ago.
What's going on?
Is the Master okay?
Hey, somebody is there!
Oh? It's...
Hey! Hey!
It's you! Do you remember me?
Thank you for your help the other day!
Straw Hat-ya.
He's...
...the guy we met at the
Human Shoppe in Sabaody.
His name is Trafalgar Law.
He is now...
Yes, he's Traf... Tra-guy!
Yeah, that's his name!
He helped me get away from the battlefield
and treated my wounds!
Your wounds?
Yeah!
Like Jimbei, he saved my life!
Hey!
I didn't expect to see you here!
Thank you very much for helping me!
Oh?
Where are the talking bear and the others?
Put Straw Hat-ya on my ship!
I'm gonna help him get out of here.
Let me take care of him for now!
I'm a doctor!
Where's Ace?!
What is going to happen
if we leave him like that?
Well, it's simple.
Like I said when we got here,
if his wound opens up, he will die.
Straw Hat-ya must take a
complete rest for two more weeks.
All right. Thank you for everything.
So you made it, Straw Hat-ya.
But you don't have to thank me for that.
I just did it on the spur of the moment.
We are both pirates.
Don't forget that.
Yeah.
We're all enemies when it comes
to the fight for the One Piece
but I owe so many people for
helping me two years ago.
I just saw Jimbei and now you - I'm so lucky!
Thanks again!
Hey, there is a Navy soldier on the ground!
Is it...
Could it be...
Hey, help me, Trafalgar.
Smoker-san!
No!
Smo-yan!
The Navy?!
Oh? Is she...
Oh no, Luffy!
The Navy's here!
Yeah!
Captain-chan, what happened?!
You alright, Smo-yan?
Smoker-san!!
I thought so! It's Smokey and his clan!
It's been a while!
There is a hole in his chest!
Smoker-san!
To become a member of the Warlords...
...he delivered the hearts
of one hundred pirates
to the headquarters!
He's crazy!
How dare you!
How dare you!!
Whoa whoa, don't.
I don't like these lame
tearjerking scenes.
Room.
Tashigi-chan!
Shambles!
Damn! He took her down again!
Smo-san's on the ground, too!
What did he just do?
She never learns.
Don't get so serious.
Tashigi-chan!
Luffy! Let's go!
It's dangerous here!
Uh-huh.
Oh yeah.
Hey, Tra-guy, I wanna ask you something.
Go round to the back of the laboratory.
What you're looking for is there.
We'll see each other again later.
We both have something we want to take back.
Good. He was talking about me.
I shouldn't be here.
I'm a former pirate!
Alright, Luffy, let's get away from the Navy!
I wonder if Smokey and his clan will be okay.
Did they lose to Tra-guy?
That's Straw Hat Luffy!
Shoot!
Stop! This is no time for that!
Smo-san and Captain-chan are injured!
It's freezing!
A MOUNTAIN BEHIND THE LABORATORY
SANJI'S GROUP
What should we do?!
The kids can't take it anymore.
Alright, let's remove this fur and...
No! It's my body!
But I don't think we can find
any warm coats around here...
Isn't there a lodge or something?
On top of that,
I need a camera and a mirror -
and a sh-shower would be nice!
Shut up or I'll tie you up!
Who's who?
The robot is scary...
Since it's come to this, you people,
I need you to put a leaf on your head.
Huh? What are you talking about?!
The kids are collapsing from cold!
And I don't see any plants on this island!
So there are no leaves!
Then a stone or whatever is fine! Hurry up!
If you insist.
I hope you have a plan.
I'll get them for the kids!
We got it. Now what?
If it's a spell-to-make-it-not-cold
kind of bullshit, I'll kick your ass!
All right!
Poof!
What?!
What's this?!
I got a coat and boots!
Why?! How did you do it?!
Gloves!
It's warm!
Very warm!
The thing is I ate an unusual fruit one day
and since then, I can use magic
which allows me to disguise myself
or everyone else in any way I please.
I don't know much about foreign
clothes but will these suffice?
I have to warn you.
Since it's magic, if you take those
clothes off, they'll disappear.
Cool! Head man! Thank you!
He shouldn't have done it!
So he's a Devil Fruit eater?
What? Devil?
But, wait a minute.
If you had such power,
why didn't you do it sooner?!
I-It was nice to see her in a breast-band.
I didn't wanna cover it up.
You fool!
I-It itches! Itchy!
You'll never say "ouch" or "I'm cold," will you?
I'm a warrior!
There you are! Guys!
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
Why are they here?
Are you all okay?
Oh, it's them!
Luffy and the others!
Zoro! Usopp! Robin! Brook!
I'm glad to see you!
Why is that jackass cook jumping around?
He went nuts from cold?
Oh? They look like giant children to me.
Shh...
Huh? Hey, what are you doing?!
Don't do it, Franky!
Hello...
THE STRAW HATS' ENCAMPMENT
We're here! This is good.
This building has a similar style as the other one.
But it's crumbling.
It looks like there was a
huge explosion or something.
It's fine as long as it'll
shelter us from the blizzard.
Now, where should we begin?
I hurt my own delicate body!
I'll treat it right away!
Hey, Sanji-kun!
What are you doing to my body?!
I'm Chopper.
I got my legs back!
Leg-maro! Oh my hind legs!
I told you there is no creature like that!
How surreal.
He's quite original.
Th-The skeleton...
...Just talked!
Are you okay, Nami-Sanji?
It was weird.
I had a dream of crossing a river.
There was a river running
through giant boobs...
It's not the time for that!
Hey, do the tank thing!
Show us the laser beam!
Shut up!
Who was it in his body?
Huh? You sure?
You want to smoke, don't you?
Let's talk like adults, everybody.
Alright. Now, who is who?
I'm Franky!
Don't come to me when you get wounded.
I'm Chopper.
I'll treat your wounds.
I'm Nami.
I will never shoot the laser beam!
And this is our...
...Nami-san!
Yeah! There you are!
Was I always that indecent?!
I won't do it again!
Don't hurt Nami-san anymore!
Don't, Nami!
Nami's gonna die!
If you touch my body,
I'll make you pay 200,000 berries.
Peeping will be 100,000.
That's so cruel!
Stop laughing!
Wouldn't be so funny if it happened to you!
Let's get it straight from the beginning.
He is the samurai from the Wano Kingdom.
The signal that we received was...
...meant for the Alliga-taur
who they call "Boss" from one of his men.
It all started when this samurai
sliced up all those centaurs.
But I just wanted to rescue my missing
son - Momonosuke and cut those people
because they were standing in my way!
In fact, look!
That many children were
held captive in the facility.
I'm sure Momonosuke is still there!
Uh-huh, there were more children.
We don't even know the
newcomers that well yet.
But the question is what
happened after the signal.
It's that man we just saw!
People were saying that he is a Warlord.
What?!
You mean Tra-guy?!
Did he become a Warlord?!
Yes, he joined them within past two years.
He chopped me up into three
pieces before I knew it!
My head was kept in the facility!
My torso was left there.
And my legs were chased by a beast.
When my legs were trying to
get away using their wits,
they stuck onto something.
And that was the back of the dragon's head!
Oh yeah, you were cursing about a Warlord!
What? There were just legs, weren't there?
How did he speak?
Oh? You're right.
Oh, that was...
...my farts.
It has always been my specialty.
So you were fart-talking?! Yuck!
Yes, I was!
Oh, it smells when we're in a room.
How funny to see a person
with just a head and legs.
By contrast, I just saw
someone with just a torso.
That was his torso, obviously.
You're right!
You saw it?!
Where?!
Where did you see my torso?!
Um... Are you... Tashigi-chan?
Y-Yes.
What?! So you're really Tashigi-chan!
They got switched?!
What's going on?!
How did this happen?!
I mean, are you okay without
a heart, Tashigi-chan?
Yes, strangely.
It's hard to talk to Captain-chan...
That means...
This one is so scary!
Smo-yan with Tashigi-chan's body!
It says "CC" on a ship hidden
beside the laboratory.
What? There was such a ship,
Vice Admiral Smoker?
Yeah. If it's left over from old days,
the mark should be "PH"...
...standing for Punk Hazard.
If there is some mastermind behind Law
and if "CC" are his initials,
I think I know who it is.
If he's here on this island,
it makes a lot of senses!
He is the former colleague of Dr.Vegapunk.
He is a scientist
named Caesar Clown!
What the hell have you done, Law?!
I'm the one who should be complaining here!
Caesar!
In the tumultuous New World, the ruler of Punk Hazard...
...turns out to be an unexpectedly well-respected figure.
As the Straw Hats recoil from this shocking fact...
...Smoker tries to discover the true identity of this mysterious master.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Worst in the World!
A Scientist of Terror - Caesar!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!