Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Sogeking, who was left alone
at the main island front gate,
heard something shocking from
one of the giant gatekeepers.
One day on some island...
...the two bosses started a duel.
It's a big fat lie that they
got caught 50 years ago!
"Main Island Front Gate"
Meanwhile, just when the courthouse
came into view for the Straw Hats
"Courthouse"
on the back of the King Bull...
Crap! King Bull!
Sodom!
Sodom! Stand firm! Don't fall yet!
Guys! Move over right away! Hurry it up!
It's coming down!
Around that time, Luffy and Blueno were
facing off on the courthouse rooftop.
"Courthouse"
So Robin is in that building behind you, huh?
Get out of my way, bull guy!
It seems that you guys haven't noticed...
...that what you're doing is a world-class crime.
Hm?
The Government will expose
all of you to public ridicule
and bestow a merciless death upon you.
Gum-Gum...
Iron Body.
...Rifle!
What?! I don't remember him
being as powerful as he is now
when I fought him at the mansion!
Gatling!
Shave!
We just came here to get Robin back!
The battle against CP9 has finally begun!
That's...
Geez... They're reckless, aren't they?
Grandma! Grandma!
Hm?
What is it, Chimney?
Listen... Listen!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Don't Stop! Hoist the Counterattack Signal!"
"Courthouse" "Rocketman"
It's coming! Aim well!
Let it get closer!
That's a trench mortar! Dodge it, Gomorrah!
This center path isn't good. They're fully
prepared and waiting in ambush!
We're gonna change the route!
We're not gonna let you get away!
Sodom...
Stop right there!
Chopper...
Hm?! The portable
transponder snail is ringing?!
Hello? Who is it?
It's me.
That's Granny Kokoro.
What're you calling for?
Sounds like you guys are still alive.
Where are you right now?
We're getting closer to the courthouse. Why?
Good timing. There's something
I forgot to tell you.
Something you forgot to tell us?
I'm sure you guys are busy,
so I'll make it quick. Listen carefully.
On the map drawn by Paulie,
there's no path from the courthouse
to the Gates of Justice, right?
That's right. I was just thinking about that.
Look at the courthouse.
There's a tower on each side, right?
Yeah, there is.
There's a lever on the top floor of each tower.
When you pull them,
a drawbridge will come down
from the courthouse to the Gates of Justice.
Granny, how come you know that stuff?
I came here with Tom-san to
fix the bridge a long time ago.
That damn ungrateful, stupid Government!
Don't take it out on me.
Chimney wants to talk to you, too.
Hello, pirate lady! Can you hear me?
Whoa! What is it, Chimney?
Listen. I saw the rubber pirate guy
on the rooftop of the courthouse.
Really?! Luffy was there?
I saw rocks collapsing there, too,
so it looks like he's going on a rampage.
On the rooftop? Got it. Thanks.
Pirate girl, keep the
transponder snail connected
so that I'll know what's going on over there.
Okay...!
So they said.
Now we know where we have to go.
Yeah!
All right, you guys go straight to
the courthouse and join Straw Hat.
Okay.
We're gonna split into two
and bring the drawbridge down.
Take us to the courthouse, Gomorrah!
Gomorrah!
Dammit! Who are they?!
"Guilty"
Not gonna be that easy... you damn trash.
All right! The second one is down, too!
The pirates no longer have
a way of getting around!
Surround them and bring them down!
To all the guards in Enies Lobby!
At the center of Block D in the southeast area,
we brought down the King Bull
that the pirates were riding on!
Call in all the soldiers
and fully blockade Block D!
I repeat! All guards, fully blockade Block D!
Looks like the jury delivered the verdict.
No one can beat them.
Say something!
--Yes, sir!
--We'll capture them right away!
"Courthouse"
The guards that we passed are
now catching up. This isn't good.
More and more are coming
from the front and the sides.
The trench mortars are aiming at us, too.
Ahhh! This is terrible!
There are thousands of them!
If we get surrounded by them in
a place like this, we'll be goners!
"Courthouse" "Rocketman"
What?! An earthquake?
Th-They're...
Amazing!
Hey, look!
All right! Oimo and Kashii are back in business!
Oh, no...
We don't have much energy
left to fight guys like them.
Is this it for us?!
Hurry up and stomp on them!
Take care of those three, giants!
Go, Kashii!
Beat the crap out of them, Oimo!
Now, crush those three, giants!
How...
...dare you...
Huh?
...deceive us?!
Wh-What the heck?! Those two
went over to the enemy's side!
Before we rejoice over
the safety of our bosses...
Before we grieve over our wasted years...
We'll take out all our anger
on them in a furious rampage!
Let's go together... king of snipers!
No need for formality! Hoist the
counterattack signal this time for sure!
Hurry to our comrades!
You're a lucky person.
Most people don't get a
rescue squad, you know.
Refrain from talking!
Got it!
Well, it's not like I'm jealous that my
underlings aren't here to rescue me.
Oh, wait a minute, you guys.
I forgot something.
Take these with you.
Ahh! Wait a sec! Those are Devil Fruits!
Yoyoi! Is that...
...true?!
Chapapa...
I've never seen them before!
Me neither!
This is bad! Keep them away from me!
What's the big fuss, Jabra?
You idiot! You don't know?!
Those with Devil Fruit powers have
a devil dwelling in their bodies!
For example, if I get closer to one of the Fruits,
a devil jumps out of the Fruit and starts
fighting the devil inside my body,
which then causes my body to explode!
Is that true?
How foolish...
It takes a pretty sloppy intelligence
agent to be misled by a rumor.
Grand Line scientists have already clarified
the transmission conditions
of the Fruits' powers.
What you're talking about is an example
of those who have eaten two Fruits...
...in which case, the person dies
because his body bursts into pieces.
Greedy idiots bring ruin upon themselves.
If they think about the risk that
they carry with just one Fruit,
you'd think that they could
guess how much of a curse
the second one would bring them.
Coo coo!
What?! Is that right?!
In any case, I'm surprised that you were
able to obtain two Devil Fruits, Chief.
Where on earth did you get them?
I have all sorts of connections.
Eat them to prepare for the future.
Become stronger, CP9!
But let me tell you one thing.
I don't know what kind of
devils dwell in those Fruits.
It's hard to believe that these
are fruits from this world.
I feel a mysterious power,
kind of like gravity, from them.
They're not listed in encyclopedias, either.
That seems to be how they normally are.
It's said that you can tell the name
of the Fruit from the powers you gain,
but what kind of powers you'll gain is a gamble.
It'll be a terrible life if you gain
weird powers with this gamble.
On top of that, to think that
you'll become unable to swim...
No matter what powers they are,
it all depends on how you use them.
In all likelihood, you won't become weaker.
There's no inconvenience in
becoming unable to swim, either.
There are tons of sailors who'd sail out
to find just one Devil Fruit
and die without any success.
Why don't you eat them? It's interesting.
Kalifa, don't do it!
Nothing good will come of this.
It tastes like crap. Crap!
Jabra doesn't want Kaku and Kalifa
to get stronger. Chapapa...
That's right! Jealousy hurts a man's name.
Yoyoi!
Shut up, you jerks!
Hey, you two! Think about it carefully!
If you sell them in the right way, you can
get several hundred million Berries!
One bite of Fruit will become a
problem for the rest of your life!
Chapapa...
That sounds interesting.
If this is a winner, I'll welcome it.
Ahh! They ate them, dammit!
Coo coo! Coo coo!
Chapapa...
What's the matter?!
Yoyoi! Have you noticed
any changes in your body?!
Chapapa...
This tastes terrible.
Couldn't you say that sooner?!
It tastes terrible.
We've already heard that. Chapapa!
Don't say it after you ate the whole thing!
Hey, try doing something!
What kind of powers did you get?!
I don't feel like anything changed.
You'll soon notice how big the change is.
This is the birth of new
Devil Fruit power-holders.
I look forward to seeing those powers.
Get a handle on your own powers
at least, while you have a chance.
Depending on the Chief's command,
you may be able to try them
in a real battle immediately...
...though it seems that Blueno couldn't
wait and joined the festivities before us.
"Courthouse"
I underestimated you.
Don't!
I never thought that he'd
keep up with the speed of Shave.
I'll fight with my guard up.
Since he's a rubber man,
hitting him wouldn't work, right?
Moon Walk!
Gum-Gum...
Tempest Kick!
Iron Body!
Wheel!
Door-Door!
A-A door just opened on the ground!
Door-Door.
Wh-What the heck?!
Were there small doors here?!
Crap! I got stuck! Dammit! These things...
You! What's this?! What'd you do?!
Is this a Devil Fruit power?!
I'm a Door human with
Door-Door Devil Fruit powers.
A Door human?!
I can change all things that partition into doors!
Revolving Door.
What?! What?!
Wh-What's going on?! I feel dizzy!
Wh-Wh-Which way is forward?! Stop!
Tempest Kick!
Hey, Cook!
Yeah, I saw it.
Luffy's already fighting CP9.
--What?!
--I-Is that true?!
Dammit! We got off to a late start!
But how do we get through
this complete encirclement?!
Gomorrah was hit with iron balls
and can no longer move!
Fire! Shoot all the pirates
down from the monster!
There's only one path left!
Yeah, we're gonna make
a dash for the courthouse!
That's the only choice we have.
All right, let's go, guys!
--Yeah!
--Wait!
All of you, don't get off!
Chopper?!
Hold on tight!
Gomorrah... Gomorrah says so!
Th-The monster is...
...still alive!
Fire! Kill it with trench mortars!
Shoot the monster!
Fight back! Back up Gomorrah!
Go! Gomorrah!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
I have a report! The pirates who invaded
have pushed into the courthouse plaza!
Our casualties are already over 2,000!
Huh? What do you mean?
This is the worst situation we've
had in the history of Enies Lobby!
What the hell is happening
on this island right now?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Almost to Luffy!
Gather at the Courthouse Plaza!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!