Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can't stand still, I can't stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that's what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We won't left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
After a fierce battle on Punk Hazard,
the Straw Hats along with their pirate ally -
the Warlord - Law...
...finally captured Caesar and
headed out for their next destination - Dressrosa.
Let's negotiate.
Resign from the Seven Warlords.
I'm expecting to see it in the newspaper
tomorrow morning.
Goodbye.
Clank.
Wait a minute! Law!
Damn squirt!
We found you!
"Caesar Goes Missing!
The Pirate Alliance Makes a Sortie!"
Doflamingo! I know he's gonna make
a raid in the darkness of the night!
Just bring it on! I mean, don't!
I-I can't sleep!
Calm all the way to the horizon!
Go.
--What's that?
--What?
What's going on?!
What?! Who is it?!
What happened?!
You bastard!
Where did they come from?!
There are about thirty of them!
Watch out!
Thirty?! Really?!
I can't see - it's too dark!
They're quite strong!
Who are they?!
What? What did you just say?
Hey, you guys! Keep it down!
What?
Huh? What was that? What's going on?
Nice to meet you, ladies and gentlemen!
Who are you?!
My name is Breed.
I'm a Peto-Peto Fruit eater!
Peto-Peto (sticky)?!
What's that?! Are you
some kind of slimy man?
That's not Doflamingo?
I guess not.
Oh no!
Caesar!
Fools! You can't keep me as a prisoner!
Don't underestimate Doflamingo!
So that guy's working
for Doflamingo, huh?
Wait!
Luffy?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Your body is rubber, it can't hurt!
Unless that thing can...
...use Haki!
You bastard!
I'll take Caesar! Goodbye!
Dammit!
What now?!
Giant waves!
Is that a Rabbit Wave?!
Oh no! The ship is bouncing up and down!
I can't control it!
What's that?!
Guys, look!
What the hell is that?!
An enormous island?
A Jolly Roger?!
That means it's a ship?!
That guy was a pirate?!
Let's chase him!
We can't let Caesar get away!
Luffy! Take the Shark Submerge!
It only can carry three people
but it can travel underwater!
Okay!
Luffy, I'll come with you!
There's something that concerns me.
Alright!
Hey, Luffy! What about us?!
Look after the Sunny!
Gotcha! Don't worry about the Sunny!
Nose-ya, stay alert!
Doflamingo himself may come and attack!
Be careful!
Attack?
Who did you call "Nose-ya"?!
Did they leave already?!
Are they gonna be okay?
What?
All three of them are Devil Fruit eaters
so if the unexpected happens...
Are they going to be alright?
There they are!
Alright, Chopper, go faster!
Luffy, don't they look like Lapins?
Lapins?!
The big rabbits you encountered
at the Drum Kingdom,
where I come from.
Oh, you mean those big
bear-like rabbits!
They look a little different
and Lapins can't swim but...
I think they are Sea Lapins.
What?
You know what they are?
I saw them once when I was
sailing across the North Blue.
They don't live in the
New World normally.
Was that why you came
with us, Raccoon-ya?
Uh-huh.
I mean, who are you
calling "Raccoon-ya"?!
I'm not a raccoon, I'm a reindeer!
Keep it in mind, you fool!
Luffy, it's not funny!
I'm sorry!
That's not the only reason I
came with you. That animal...
He said "I don't actually
want to do this."
Raccoon-ya,
can you understand what the animals are saying?
Yeah, I can understand what they...
I said I'm not a raccoon!
That Breed guy who is
leading those sea monsters.
Hey Luffy, stop laughing!
Hey, are you listening?!
Is he really working for Doflamingo?
I hope we're not getting
ourselves into a mess.
Oh, they're going in there.
We're in the enemy's territory.
Be really careful...
Hey, it's brighter over here!
Don't shout, you idiot! Listen to me!
He's right, Luffy! Listen to him!
Wow, how awesome!
It's a big fish tank!
Feels like we're in the sea.
Look, Chopper!
It's a fish tank all the way to the ceiling.
Hey, Straw Hat-ya!
We're not here for fun.
Look, Chopper! A sparkling shrimp!
Wow, cool!
That aside...
What?!
Okay, let's fight!
Room!
I can have more arms than you!
How did you like that?
It's almost morning. Let's move.
What?!
Like we thought, he uses Haki.
We have unfinished business.
If you can use Haki, I'll
fight with the gloves off!
Let's do this!
I win!
Wh-What? What?
What's going on?
He's saying "Master, long time no see."
Oh, don't tell me you're...
You became Luffy's disciple in Alabasta!
The Kung Fu Dugong!
Hey, what's going on?!
I'm the great scientist -
Master Caesar Clown-sama!
Hey, somebody, let me out!
Is anybody listening?!
Hey!
Hello.
How are you?
Oh, good. Thank you!
Now, let me out.
Where is Doflamingo?
Shut up, you worthless human!
Wh-What are you doing?!
Don't tell me you're not
working under Doflamingo!
Stop messing with me!
Who do you think I am?!
You're Caesar Clown - Joker's pet scientist.
Am I right?
Did you say Joker?
Are you connected to the
underground community?
Now, you better wag your
tail for me - Breed-sama!
Use your scientific mastery
to create my dream kingdom!
Huh? No way. I'm a great scientist.
Why should I follow orders from some guy
that I don't even know?
I wonder how much longer
you'll be able to say such a thing.
What are you gonna do to me?! No!
Hey! You bastard!
Oh, I remember you!
You're the Kung Fu Seal from Alabasta!
"It's been a while, Master!"
That's what he said.
It's nice to see you again!
How have you been?!
You two hit it off already?!
What is this all about?
Oh, he is a Kung Fu Dugong
who became friends
with Luffy in a kingdom called Alabasta.
Kung Fu Dugongs like to fight
and will challenge anyone to a duel.
You win.
But Luffy...
I win!
...Defeated him.
When they lose a fight, they have to
become a disciple to the one who beat them.
That's what this is all about.
I see. And what are they doing now?
Huh?
Like this, Seal!
One, two, one, two!
Pull your arm back all
the way - like this!
And use the lower half of your body!
Put more power to it!
One, two, one, two!
They're getting along so well...
You really are the seal!
You got much stronger, didn't you?
Oh, what's that?
"I saw the scar on your chest
in the newspaper and copied it."
Did you hurt yourself?
"I painted it on!"
That's funny!
Now I know that you're
Straw Hat-ya's disciple
but why did you come to the New World
and kidnap our important hostage?
He said "I'm sorry for attacking the ship.
I didn't know it was your ship, Master."
"I have a good reason for that."
"When I met you in
Alabasta, you said..."
Pirates are free.
The sea is vast
and there is so much fun out there!
"Those words inspired me
so I sailed out to the sea all alone...
...dreaming of becoming
a free pirate like you!"
"I came across some very
formidable enemies!"
"I made a lot of friends!"
"We overcame so many difficulties
and formed a pirate
group of sea creatures."
"Then, we finally
entered the New World!"
"But that was when...
...we met that guy, Breed."
Hmmm. A pirate group of sea monsters?
How interesting!
All of you can join my crew!
"We're his slaves now."
"We kidnapped Caesar on his orders."
Breed. So He is the mastermind.
It seems like Doflamingo has
nothing to do with this.
I don't get it.
I know you're pretty strong.
Why do you have to listen to him?
"Because..."
Fall in, all of you!
--What was that?
--That was...
What's wrong?
What?
"Get out of here now"?
How are you doing, pathetic humans?
Hey, you all are too slow.
Listen, here's how pets should be;
First, loyal. Second, loyal.
Third and fourth, loyal.
And lastly, loyal!
When I say "Fall in,"
you have three seconds!
Don't you get it?!
Hey, Kung Fu Dugong.
You have to bring them together!
Why are you being so slow?!
If you let me down, you're
a failure as a pet!
You're no better than those shitty humans!
You're Breed, aren't you?
Give us back Caesar!
Huh?! Shut up, foul human!
Oh yeah, it's you guys.
Yes, I am Breed!
I'm a pirate.
A pirate?
I can't believe a Warlord like
Trafalgar Law is here along
with Straw Hat Luffy, a pirate
with a 400 million bounty!
Thank you for chasing us all the way here,
you pain-in-the-ass, shitty humans!
You can't hit us with that.
I'm not so sure about that!
Pet-peto!
What?
Ouch!
What's this?!
I can't take it off!
How does this work?!
You okay, Chopper?!
Trafalgar! Straw Hat!
You two are strong.
Stronger than me.
But is that enough to beat me?!
Now, you...
Wh-What do you want?
Tear Trafalgar and Straw Hat...
...limb to limb!
What? What's going on?
What's wrong, Chopper?
I can't control my body!
What's this? What's going on here?!
H-Hey...
That's amazing!
Chopper, what's happening to you?!
That was close!
Why are you attacking?!
That bastard!
Get away, you two!
What's going on?!
It seems as though he
hasn't lost his senses.
I can't control myself!
Please! Get away from me!
I have no choice. Room!
Don't do it! You can't hurt Chopper!
You fool! I'm not gonna kill him!
I just wanna control him!
Dammit!
I ate the Peto-Peto Fruit!
Peto-Peto? Don't tell me it's...
That's right!
I can manipulate all living things as I want
with my Peto-Peto power!
Which means I can make them my pet!
Pet? So "Peto-Peto" means "pet"?
I can control any living thing
and bring out all of its power!
You will see how deadly it is!