Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
--A dragon graveyard?
--No! It's not!
Grandpa Ryu said going back to
his nest would make him better!
This can't be a graveyard!
Apis...
Grandpa Ryu was a lost Millennial Dragon...
Luffy?
He was all alone, for a thousand years.
But he made friends with you, Apis.
He said out of the
1,000 years he was alive,
this last year with you was his happiest.
Luffy... You understand
the dragons' language?
I just somehow know.
Geez, talk about half-baked...
But there's no doubt about it!
You liar...
You're such a liar, Grandpa Ryu!
If this is the dragons' nest...
If you've made it back to the dragons' nest,
then open your eyes again!
Talk to me!
Get better!
Grandpa Ryu wasn't lying at all!
He said that Millennial Dragons
return to the nest every 1,000 years
and are reborn again.
Grandpa Ryu said that?
There!
A baby Millennial Dragon?!
Out of my way!
"An Angry Showdown!
Cross the Red Line!"
Man, you're stubborn!
Yeah. I very nearly drowned to death.
Just look at this beautiful radiance!
Isn't it marvelous?!
This is all Dragonite,
the legendary elixir of immortality!
But breaking these
fossilized Millennial Dragons
won't produce anything usable!
Yes, so I hear.
But there is more than enough
live Dragonite here!
What do you say? A pointless
fight would only be tiring.
How about we make a deal
to split this treasure?
No.
--Do you not want eternal life?!
--Not interested.
You lie! There's no one
who's not afraid of dying!
Both of us may have Devil Fruit powers,
but a pirate's life is always
only inches from death!
There's no way you can't be afraid of dying!
I dunno. He's the kind of guy who'd
die smiling doing what he does.
Oh...
Fine, then!
You can sit there and watch
as I take my Dragonite and leave!
No!
Stop right there, girl!
Apis!
U-Usopp!
D-Don't be reckless, Apis!
Even if it's reckless,
I have to protect them!
This is a very important place
for the Millennial Dragons!
I'm going to protect this
place forever and ever!
So you insist on defying me, huh?
In that case, you can all die!
Sickle-Sickle...
...Whirlwind!
Luffy!
I'll deal with him.
--But, Luffy!
--I promised him!
You're fine staying here?!
What kind of wimpiness is that?!
You still haven't accomplished your goal!
What happened to going to your nest?!
Don't give up by saying
you're staying here!
Of course I will! Don't worry about Apis!
I don't think so!
Sickle-Sickle...
Gum-Gum...
--...Whirlwind!
--...Pistol!
You can't hit me, rubber man!
Well? Are my wind slashes
sharp enough for you?
Run or hide wherever you want,
there's no escape!
Now, how will you dodge this?
This guy's pretty tough...
Is Luffy in trouble?!
Luffy...
Sickle-Sickle...
...Wind Slash!
Rapid Fire!
I'm not gonna run or hide!
Fool! Go ahead and get chopped up!
Gum-Gum...
W-What?!
...Bell!
And...
...Bazooka!
I win!
You did it!
--What is this?!
--Creatures like this really exist?!
I-It wasn't just a legend?!
Do you suppose this place'll
sink again after a little while?
When it does, will the Millennial
Dragons leave the island, too?
And I guess that baby Millennial
Dragon will fly off somewhere too?
What do you say, everyone?
Won't you have some of my
special pork buns before you go?
Oh! Thank you! But that's okay!
We gotta get back to our
journey right away! Right?!
We do? I wanna eat some pork--
Oww!
We'll just take the recipe.
I see. That's too bad.
It'd only take three days
to prepare them, too.
I could tell you about the royal
family of Lost Island in the mean--
We've already heard about it!
Alright! Set sail for the Grand Line!
Apis. Want to come with us?
I've made friends with you all,
and I would like to go with you...
...but I'm going to stay on this island.
I'm gonna learn all sorts of
customs from Grandpa Bokuden
and protect the dragons' nest just
like my ancestors did before me!
I'm going to wait for the baby dragons
to come back here someday!
But those baby dragons won't
be back for another... uhh...
A-Another thousand years!
Hey, now! Don't be so cynical!
No, it's okay!
I won't get to see the
dragons all grown up,
but I'm sure my kids' kids will get to!
So I'm going to keep protecting
this dragon nest forever and ever!
That's crazy talk!
You guys kept doing
crazy stuff too, you know!
We did?
See ya, Apis!
Apis! Never forget about Usopp-sama,
the brave warrior of the sea!
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye! Take care, everyone!
--See ya, Apis!
--Bye! So long!
Bye-bye!
Is Apis really gonna be
okay all by herself?
I'm sure Apis will keep the nest safe!
She may be little,
but she's got twice the energy
and motivation of a normal person!
She'll be fine!
You're right, Nami-san.
She'll be okay!
Yeah!
Because she's our friend!
She sure is.
Are you sure you didn't
want to go with them, Apis?
I'd only get in the way if I went with them.
Besides, now I have
something I want to do!
I'm pretty reckless too,
but until I met Luffy and the others,
I don't think I would've felt like
I could protect this island.
I thought Lost Island was just
a story and that it didn't exist,
but Luffy and the others took
Grandpa Ryu on a search for it
without even doubting its
existence in the slightest!
I get the feeling that they taught me
that if you never give up on
your dreams and try your hardest,
your wishes just may come true!
Everyone worked so hard and
risked their lives for their friends,
who all had a heart-to-heart connection!
And I'm one of their friends, too!
So I'm going to try my hardest, too!
He's asleep!
Say? Will you help me with my dream?
Thanks! Let's try our best!
Oh, right! If you're going
to protect Lost Island,
you'll need to know about your ancestors!
First, there was the first king...
I-I've already had enough of that!
Hold on, Apis! Get back here!
Stop!
You need to know about these things!
--No!
--Apis!
Nami-san! I have a report of love!
I see big rain clouds up ahead!
There's a storm under 'em!
Looks like we're back
on our original course...
We should be seeing the
Red Line at any time now...
The Grand Line, at last!
Hey, Sanji! We're finally going!
We're finally going!
That hurts!
Sowwy!
Zoro!
But is it really like how it's drawn here?
Stop that!
Look at this!
I'd heard the rumors about it,
and it's drawn on this map, too!
If it really is true, then the entrance
to the Grand Line is a mountain!
A mountain?
--We gotta crash into a mountain?
--You can't be serious.
I didn't believe it myself,
but the map has canals
that lead to the mountain.
That might mean we have to go up it!
Neat!
What're you talking about?!
Even if there are canals or whatever,
a ship can't climb up a mountain!
But that's what the map says!
Yeah! Nami-san would never
say anything that's wrong!
You stole that map from Buggy, right?
Can we really trust it?
H-Hey! Someone help with the rudder!
--Sanji-kun! Give Usopp a hand!
--It won't budge!
--I can't think with all his shouting!
--It won't move! Someone help!
Yes, Nami-san!
Okay!
D-Doesn't this current
seem a bit strong?!
Eh?! Usopp! What did you just say?
"D-Doesn't this current
seem a bit strong?!"
Current...
--That's it!
--That's what?
They really do go up the mountain!
Are you still saying that stuff?!
Look here!
See? The guiding light was
definitely pointing to here
on the Red Line... Reverse Mountain!
Hey! Little help over here!
See these canals here?
If major currents from the four oceans
all flow toward this mountain...
Then the four currents would go up
these canals, collide at the top,
and then flow into the Grand Line!
Reverse Mountain is a "winter island,"
So any currents that
collide into the Red Line
will plummet from the
surface into the depths.
If we screw up and miss
the entrance to the canal...
...the Going Merry will run smack
into the Red Line's rock face...
...and get wrecked!
And then we'd be at the bottom
of the ocean. Understand?
Oh! Interesting!
So, basically, it's a mystery mountain!
Well, maybe you don't get it...
Anyways, now that we're on this current,
As long as we don't
mess up with the rudder,
we should be able to go straight
to the summit of Reverse Mountain!
Nami-san! You're so amazing!
I've never heard of ships
going over mountains before.
I've heard some stuff before!
Stories about the mystery mountain?
No.
I heard that half of everyone
who heads to the Grand Line
dies before entering it...
I knew getting in wouldn't be easy.
--Sanji-kun! Could you get the sail?
--Yes, Nami-san!
--Luffy! Help out!
--Eh?!
Hey! I see the mystery mountain!
W-What?!
T-That's insanely huge!
The entrance to the Grand Line...
So that's the Red Line, huh?!
I-I-I can't see the top
because of the clouds!
We're getting sucked in!
--Hold the rudder good!
--We're on it!
N-Nami! Where's the entrance?!
We're gonna crash into the rocks
if we keep going this way!
The crack in that cliff...
Nami! What do we do?!
--Keep going straight ahead!
--A-Are you serious?!
Just do it!
Nami! Is that the canal entrance?
Most likely!
This can't be for real!
The damn ocean really is
flowing up the mountain!
We gotta make our way through
those water gates just right!
Otherwise the ship'll
be busted into pieces!
W-We're getting off course!
More to the right! Right! Right!
The right?! Go starboard!
C-Come on, now!
The rudder!
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
Luffy!
Grab on!
We made it!
Now it's just a straight shot to the summit!
Hey! I wanna see! I wanna see!
I'm unstuck!
Hey! Let me see, too!
A-Awesome!
Curse you all!
--Huh?
--It's the Sicko Fruit guy...
--You!
--You're still alive?!
--What tiny eyes!
--Shut up!
Curse the whole lot of you!
Thanks to you, my dream of
Dragonite has been crushed!
I can't just leave things as they are now!
At the very least, I'll have
your 30 million-Berry head!
Just surrender to your fate
like a good little boy!
Now what?!
If he uses his wind slashes here,
there's no telling what he'll rip apart!
We can't act carelessly...
How do you like that?!
You can't lay a finger on me now!
Oh! Dragonite!
Bye-bye!
Oh! Good thinking!
He can't swim either, so I don't
think he'll be following us any more!
Given this current, being able
to swim wouldn't matter anyways!
Way to go, Nami-san!
We're in the clouds!
Awesome!
We're above the clouds now!
Look! The summit! It's the summit!
Yahoo!
To do what Mihawk said...
To find the All Blue there...
To draw my perfect sea charts...
To prove I'm a brave warrior of the sea...
I see it!
This is the greatest sea
in the world! The Grand Line!
The One Piece is up ahead, somewhere!
Go!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Nami-san! I see a mountain up ahead!
Who cares?! Go!
That can't be! It should be
nothing but ocean up ahead!
Huh? A black wall?
Crap! We gotta do
something before we crash!
--No! This is...!
--A whale!
A whale?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The First Line of Defense?
The Giant Whale Laboon Appears"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!