Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
So let's go
saa yukou
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Luffy and the others are fighting
hard to get to the scaffold
but the Navy has activated encircling
walls leaving the pirates no way out!
Hey, what's wrong?!
It should be fully activated!
I-I'm afraid that the wall
can't lift the giant body of Oars!
It seems like his blood is
running down in the system
and making it less powerful!
Oars! Y-You're...
We can't close it but...
...do it, Akainu!
"Execution Order Issued!
Break Through the Encircling Walls!"
Why did it black out?!
Let us see the war!
Hurry and fix it!
They're having trouble with
the Video Transponder Snail!
There's nothing we can do!
Is it true that the Navy and
Whitebeard had a secret deal?!
Do something!
Did Whitebeard sell out his allies?!
What's gonna happen to the war?!
What's gonna happen to the world?!
How ridiculous the Navy is!
This means it was just a
sideshow up until now?
We came back just to see the war!
I can't believe there's
trouble with the snail!
So you're buying into that?
You aren't?
You guys are such fools!
They're not showing it
because there're things...
...that they don't want us
or the world to see.
Captain Bonney...
Shut up! Just leave me alone!
"Whitebeard sold out his allies?"
That's crap!
He wouldn't do that.
That's why he's a living legend!
Let's set sail, Bepo!
Aye-aye, Captain!
Come with us, Jean Bart!
That's right, Head Office! And there's
no chance of recovering the signal!
So I don't know what's
going on at Marineford now!
Meteor Volcano!
They can't get away!
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
The ice is melting!
Th-This water is...
Ouch, it's hot!
The seawater's boiling because of the lava!
Get on the ice!
Hey, look!
They're blocking this side!
Can't we break this wall?!
Whitebeard!
Pops' blow didn't work!
It's no ordinary wall!
Alright, let's finish this up!
The lava hit the back of the Moby Dick!
Put out the fire!
Hurry up, everybody!
Do whatever it takes!
Don't let it sink!
We were looking forward to sailing
the world with Ace again on that ship!
Whitebeard! Your days are over!
The Moby Dick is...
Damn the Navy!
The ship of our glory!
Damn! Our ship!
They sank the ship that
carried the Whitebeards for years!
I'm sorry...
We're running out of ways
to get to the plaza!
What's going on inside the walls?!
You know it even if you can't see it!
They can't advance or back up
and keep being pounded.
The encircling walls are none other than
the casket of the Whitebeard Pirates!
The casket...
The plan is going well!
Now let's move on to...
...the execution of Portgaz D. Ace...
...immediately!
At a place we can't even see...
...We won't let them kill Ace!
Yes! There is still a way!
Just one!
The way that Oars made!
We'll be sitting ducks if we go that way!
The Navy is expecting
us to go there for sure!
There's no time to argue!
He's right! That's the
only way to save Ace...
Ace!
Straw Hat...
We're coming too!
They shouldn't take such an obvious route!
Not yet! Let them approach
as close as possible!
Fire!
Of course they're going to
defend the only way out!
It's more like a trap!
Fire!
Ace!
We're finishing them off little by little!
Ace...
Ace!!
Fire!
Straw boy!
Luffy-kun!
Luffy!!
Shoot everyone who came over Oars!
I'm gonna save you even if it means my death!
Proceed with the execution.
Ace-... kun!
Little Oars Jr.! He's still alive?!
Ace-kun!
Oars...!
I protect Ace-kun!
Oars!!
Oars!
Oars is alive!
Captain!
What guy!
Oars...
Captain Squard!
Captain... Squard!
You all...
Alright!
Are you okay, Luffy-kun?!
Honestly! You're too reckless!
Get ready to shoot!
Fire!
Oars!
They'll beat Oars again!
We gotta do something! We gotta hurry!
They'll execute Ace!
Yes, we have to stop them!
Jimbei!
I need you to do me a favor!
Ace-kun!
How tough!
He's barely alive! Keep shooting!
Oh, okay. Let me do it!
Kizaru-san!
We have to finish the execution already!
I better take out his
head at a time like this!
Oars!
Captain Oars!
Oars!!
It's over!
Ocean Current Shoulder Throw!
Lu...!
Luffy!!
Oh no! You finally made it!
You're standing tall, Dragon's son!
It scares me! His youthfulness!
The guy who jumped over
the wall was Ace's brother!
That brat!
I praise you just for your tenacity.
But you're not good enough
to reach this stage yet.
What makes you think that you can beat us?
I'm gonna get Ace back!!
He's so reckless just like his brother!
Oars, stay there!
I need your power!
Pops!
Jozu, the trump card!
Okay!
Everyone, get ready!
We're gonna charge into the plaza!
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp Gatling!
Luffy finally leads the
charge into the plaza.
But the three admirals form
a heavy wall in front of him,
repelling his advance.
Meanwhile, in the bay, Whitebeard
prepares to deal his final trump card
to change the course of the battle!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Moving into the Final Phase!
Whitebeard's Trump Card for Recovery!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!