Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I saw what you just did!
You're terribly strong, aren't you?
There is a man I would like you to defeat.
If I get my shadow back,
I'll do anything I can to thank you!
Your shadow?
So what? Are you another
person who lost his shadow?
You're just like Brook.
So who the heck stole it?
Who is on this island?
The man's name is Moria.
He is truly terrifying.
Moria?
By any chance...
Are you referring to Gecko Moria?
Yeah, that's him. That's the Moria I meant.
Robin, do you know him?
Gecko Moria is one of the
Seven Warlords of the Sea.
"Evil Be Gone"
Infidels!
He found us!
I made it perfectly clear to
keep your noses out of my lab!
I-I-I didn't see a thing!
N-Neither did I!
Uh-huh! I didn't see anything either.
Honest?
C-Cross my heart! I swear I didn't
see a zombie in the works!
Don't say that!
Well, it's all good.
It doesn't matter what secrets
you uncover. It's too late anyway.
We round up the unsuspecting guests
who wander onto this island.
Then the night raid begins!
Now then, my Soldier Zombie Corps!
The General Zombies will
take those pirates down!
Are you ready, zombies?
Yeah!
This is the land of the
deceased, Thriller Bark!
May you have unpleasant nightmares!
Well, shall we go?
It's a haunted mansion!
"Feast of the Zombie Song! The Night
Raid's Bell is the Sound of Darkness!"
What was that crap about
zombie research, Hogback?!
Instead of investigating them,
you're the one calling the
dead back from the grave!
H-Hey, Nami! Don't blurt that out!
You're free to suspect anything you like now,
but what makes you think that?
I found a newspaper article
about that woman's death!
Victoria Cindry, you died
a good ten years ago!
Fiends! Did you go inside that room?!
Answer me!
Not only did you check out my lab,
but also that room...
Cindry-chan! Samurai Ryuma!
Send them to the World of Shadows forthwith!
"Evil Be Gone"
W-Wait a second!
Send them to the World of Shadows,
never to bask in the light again!
The night raid has already begun.
"Evil Be Gone"
Did you see...
...all you care to of the laboratory?
"Dragon"
My, my...
Upon closer inspection,
I see that you are a truly elegant lady.
You're beautiful!
Huh?! N-No, hardly!
My eyes follow the beautiful ladies.
But I'm a mummy, so I don't have eyes!
May I see your panties?
No way!
This exchange...!
My eyes follow the beautiful ladies.
But I'm a skeleton, so I don't have eyes!
May I see your panties?
No way!
He repeated him word for word...
He's on a completely different level
from the other zombies you've seen!
With his special body,
he is a General Zombie.
This man hails from Wano
Kingdom in the New World!
No one knows if it's true or not,
but it's said this legendary samurai
cut down a dragon soaring through the sky!
Crap! Crap!!
Stay back!
There is nowhere to run!
Cindry-san, would you be so kind
as to open yonder passage?
Also, I would like a midnight snack.
Wh-What gives? I thought
he was going to attack us.
That scared me. What's he up to?
I-It doesn't matter!
C'mon, let's make a break for it!
The door is wide open!
--You're right!
--Y-Yeah!
Hurry!
Splendid!
When a person has been slashed by a master,
the master can casually walk three paces
while humming before the person notices.
Three-Pace Hum... Notch Slash!
Excuse me! I'm coming in!
Give 'em more time!
Huh? The door's locked.
Ah! It opened right up!
You call that "opening right up"?
Gecko Moria! Come on out already!
What do you think they use this room for?
Doesn't look like anyone's home.
Hey! Anyone around?
Gecko Moria!
This is such a huge mansion...
Shouldn't there be at least one servant?
Why does it look like there
was a skirmish in here?
I hope nothing happened to Nami-san...
You've got some guts, coming when
you know our master's name!
Huh? A piggy is growing out of the wall?
There's still more in store for you!
Show our guests a warm welcome!
Oh, jeez! Are these supposed to be zombies?
I think you can find just about any
creature imaginable on this island.
Where the hell...
...did you hide Nami-san?!
It's improper for a lady to
open her mouth gaping wide.
And here you're so pretty.
Huh? Really?
But not when you leave the painting.
Twist!
Now for you.
You snapped my spearhead!
What are you made out of? Iron?!
Stop! Stop! Stop! Stop it!
What the heck are you guys?!
Weren't those weaklings
supposed to be your crewmates?
Yes!
Two-Sword Style... Nigiri!
Nigiri? Like sushi? Sounds yummy!
Flash!
It was nasty!
This island really is fun!
Darn it! You're one fast bastard!
We coulda been friends
if you didn't get in our way!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
B-Bear Rug!
There! That's the last of them.
No, we're not done yet.
There's still one up there.
Perfect! Now carry them away.
Uh... Umm... Those three are
sound asleep in their bedrooms.
Ain't it great? They're safe and sound!
Like hell they are!
It's the honest truth!
All you have to do is check and see!
Just go up those stairs and down the hall!
Hey, wait a second here.
The curly cook is gone.
Huh? He was here a second ago.
Where did Sanji wander off to?
Hey, don't laugh! They'll hear you.
They must have done
something during the fray.
We've lost a valuable man.
Cool it!
Yeah, but... He's right. Sanji'll be okay.
But time may be of the essence
for the other three in this zombie mansion.
Don't get cocky just because
you're a little strong, punks!
What?
Deep inside, you're terrified after
one of your friends went missing!
Serves ya right!
At any rate, we'll have to go by
our intuition from here on out...
Hey, losers! You're really scared witless!
I doubt these zombies will tell us
the truth if we threaten them.
Then let's take this pig as our tour guide.
What?!
Go! Go!
H-Hey, you!
Go and learn just how
terrifying our master truly is!
Our real boss is one of the Seven
Warlords of the Sea, Gecko Mori--
Ah! I can't say his name!
It's too terrifying!
Merely saying his name
sends chills down my spine!
Your missing crewmates
won't come back unscathed...
You'll lose one pal after the next...!
You will regret coming here!
Before the Seven Warlord's Gecko--
no, before my master's true power,
all of you will taste fear!
You sure love to ramble on and on!
Then pass this message on to that jerk Moria!
"If anything happens to my crew...
...I'll send you and this
entire island flying!"
Anyway, it won't kill
Sanji to fend for himself.
C'mon, let's go!
Hey! You're seriously taking me with you?!
Say something!
Dear Master,
it looks like some fearsome
people have entered the mansion.
They surprised all of the Surprise Zombies.
♪ Surround the mansion ♪
♪ Let's Fiesta Night! ♪
♪ We won't let a single pirate... ♪
♪ ...get away ♪
♪ Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!) ♪
♪ Round and round and turn and die
♪ Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!) ♪
♪ Round and round and turn and die
♪ Zombie Night! ♪
♪ Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!) ♪
♪ Round and round and turn and die
♪ Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!) ♪
♪ Round and round and turn and die
♪ Everybody, Zombie Night!
(Fuuwa! Fuuwa!) ♪
♪ Round and round and turn and die
♪ Zombie Night! ♪
It's time! All of our prey have
entered the mansion grounds!
You may fight to your heart's
content for this one night!
Awaken, General Zombies!
Arise, ancient warriors!
The pirates...
The Straw Hats
are a small crew of eight.
Wipe them out and present
them to our master!
Now go, my courageous General Zombies!
Hey, Chopper! According to the newspaper,
aren't a bunch of zoos popping up?
I've always been against
throwing animals in cages!
This is a reindeer talking here!
I'm against cages, too!
Caging animals is barbaric! But still...
I'll make an exception today...
Please put the animal zombies in cages!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Bunch of Animals?
Perona's Wonder Garden!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!