Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
That's Hogback's laugh.
What is this room?
His laboratory!
It's almost done!
What a glorious mario!
Behold, Cindry-chan!
The work of a genius... is truly art!
He's clearly trying to
turn that into a zombie.
Hogback revived all of
the zombies on the island.
That's the only possible explanation!
"Evil Be Gone"
Good day to you!
If you're curious about
what's inside, you should go in.
"Yo ho ho"?!
B-Brook...?!
A severely injured old man?
He's obviously a zombie!
How dare you make fun of zombies?!
Don't underestimate us!
Are zombies supposed to be this full of life?
Teach them just how
dangerous zombies can be!
What, you wanna fight?
We can teach you a thing or two
about how dangerous we are!
600 Million Berry Jackpot!
"His Name is Moria! The Great
Shadow-Seizing Pirate's Trap!"
So... what were you guys doing here?
Well... We are zombies,
so we were kinda buried...
And we were kinda rotting...
Right, right. I was rotting.
Yeah, so was I.
Are you trying to be funny?
No, no! Not by any means!
We're sorry! Honest!
That right? Then I have a question for you.
Did a man with a long nose,
a woman with orange hair,
and a raccoon dog that resembles
a reindeer pass through here?
Huh?! Uh, y-yeah... Yes, yes, and yes.
Maybe I saw them, maybe I didn't...
But our lips are sealed!
We aren't allowed to share information
on that topic with outsiders.
It's the rule.
Right, right!
Yeah?
It's the rule! It's the rule!
It's the rule! It's the rule!...
So you absolutely refuse to talk, huh?
All three of them passed through!
They squealed like pigs!
That was fast...
They're my crewmates.
You didn't go after them, did you?
Huh?!
Th-They're your crewmates?
I-I didn't attack them! Right?
Y-Yeah. S-Same goes for me.
I didn't attack them!
We didn't attack them! We didn't
attack them! We didn't attack them!
You'd better tell me the truth.
He attacked them!
What?! Hey, you don't sell friends out!
You nibbled on him a bit, remember?
We all attacked them together.
Stupid! Don't tell him that!
Nami and the other two
apparently raced for that mansion.
I'm glad they're okay!
But they didn't know anything about Brook.
Do we really need him? Forget that weirdo!
Yeah, really.
But man, those were some spineless zombies!
Yeah! That didn't even count as a warm-up!
But don't let your guard down.
We have no idea what could be
lurking around the next corner.
What's this? Starting to
chicken out, Swordswuss?
Shut up, you stupid cook!
Don't lump me together with you!
What was that, Disoriented Moss Head?!
Wanna fight, Curly Eyebrow?!
P-Please hold up!
I saw what you just did!
You're terribly strong, aren't you?
Could you please hear me out?
A severely injured old man?
We've told you before, that's a zombie!
No, I'm a severely injured old man.
That's confusing! Just pass
yourself off as a zombie!
So what did you wanna discuss?
There is a man I would like you to defeat.
I'm sure you could take him down!
He has created countless victims,
all of whom could be saved
if you defeated him!
If I get my shadow back,
I'll do anything I can to thank you!
Your shadow?
So what? Are you another
person who lost his shadow?
Your shadow...?
It's true!
Gramps, you don't have a shadow!
You're just like Brook.
So who the heck stole it?
Who is on this island?
M-Moria...
The man's name is Moria.
He is truly terrifying.
Moria?
By any chance...
Are you referring to Gecko Moria?
Yeah, that's him. That's the Moria I meant.
Robin, do you know him?
I know his name well.
That man's bounty used to
surpass even yours, Luffy.
It used to? So that means...
Right... Gecko Moria
is one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea.
One of the Seven Warlords?!
Are you sure, Robin?
Yes... Gecko Moria is a man
shrouded in mystery.
But what is that man doing
in a place like this?
I'm afraid I don't know. But there
are more than a few victims
left to wander this forest
after he stole their shadows.
There are other people here?
Yeah. You would be wise to remember
that Moria has had his eye on you
ever since he invited you here.
He invited us...?
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
So that's the deal?
Those who stayed must creep around
the forest in fear of the zombies.
Those who took to the sea must
spend their lives in fear of the sun.
Either way, it hardly feels
like we're even alive anymore.
At the very least, I wish that
just once--once is all I ask for--
I could walk under the light of the sun!
That's your story? Dude, that sounds killer!
All right! I'll help ya out!
Don't worry about a thing, stupid!
You idiot, I'm not crying!
You're way too easy to read.
Don't be so quick to take on
someone else's problems.
You heard him!
Hey, geezer! Only ladies can
use tears to win people over!
You can't make my heart throb!
That's just so...
But, hey, I was searching
for the shadow thief.
If he's after us, we're gonna
have to kick his butt anyway.
So wouldn't we wind up
helping you on the side?
Get it?
I'm happy to hear you say that!
Even if we're on the side,
it still gives us hope!
We're counting on you, Mister!
Best of luck!
Kick Moria's stinky butt!
What the heck?! The other victims
were listening in on us?!
Yeah! Excuse us for not making
your heart throb, Curly Eyebrow!
Shut up! Leave me alone!
Who's there?!
"Evil Be Gone"
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
What are you doing here?!
"Evil Be Gone"
What was with that "yo ho ho"?!
Was that Brook just now?
But he wasn't a skeleton!
He had skin and muscle.
Plus he was wearing sandals
and carrying a katana.
How dare they blow me off?!
You're right! He was wearing
a completely different outfit.
What's that mean?
Infidels!
He found us!
What did you see?
I made it perfectly clear to
keep your noses out of my lab!
I-I-I didn't see a thing!
N-Neither did I!
Uh-huh! I didn't see anything either.
Honest?
C-Cross my heart! I swear I didn't
see a zombie in the works!
Don't say that!
Well, it's all good.
It doesn't matter what secrets
you uncover. It's too late anyway.
In a couple of minutes...
...the "night raid" will begin!
"Night raid"?
We round up the unsuspecting guests
who wander onto this island.
Then the night raid begins!
They just had to rebury the zombies
right before the night raid!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
You couldn't feel something
even if it was itchy, hot, or painful!
You're all dead!
Right...
Now get up, Soldier Zombies!
No matter how many times you're defeated,
you can rise and attack again!
That is what makes zombies truly terrifying!
Yeah!
What a pain...
Hey, get your act together!
Give me a break, zombies!
I dare you to say who I am!
You're our leader!
You're our leader, Absalom!
Leader! Leader! Leader! Leader!
Leader! Leader! Leader! Leader!...
Peeping Tom!
Erotic Leader! Erosalom! Erosalom! Eros!
--Pervert! Pervert! Pervert!...
--Shut up!
W-W-Welcome back, Perona-sama... in bulk!
Gah! Don't talk, Kumacy!
Why must you have such a deep voice
when you're so cute?! It's annoying!
I-I'm sorry.
If you aren't cute, you have
no right to serve me!
Hurry! Hurry!
It's starting! It's starting!
It's time for the night raid!
It's almost midnight!
Master!
Moria-sama!
Time to wake up!
Nin, do it!
Okay, sure thing!
Master!
I was having a nightmare!
How dreadfully wonderful, Master!
It's been roughly four days
since our last night raid.
You've been asleep that
entire time, Moria-sama.
As such, we have prepared
four days' worth of food for you.
We have some impressive prey this time!
After toppling Enies Lobby,
they've become a hot topic!
They're Straw Hat Luffy and his gang!
I'm sure you will find
use for them, Moria-sama.
Rain?
It's coming down pretty heavy.
All right! Let's run for the mansion.
Just a sec!
I can see somethin' huge behind the mansion.
It's like some kinda massive mark.
A mark?
The fog has cleared up a bit, hasn't it?
What is that? A flag?
No! Isn't that a sail?
A sail?!
It sure is!
You're still following us?!
What did you mean?
Just as that man said, it's a sail.
But it's so large that you
can't see the whole thing.
Thriller Bark is carrying an entire village,
making it the largest
pirate ship in the world!
It's a pirate ship that
hauls around a village?!
It's the largest in the world...
Awesome!
Makes sense. "Bark" is definitely a word
used to define a type of sailing ship.
But I never thought I'd see a
ship carry an entire village...
You can see how the main mast
connects to the back of the mansion.
That is where you will find Gecko Moria.
Now then, my Soldier Zombie Corps!
The General Zombies will
take those pirates down!
No matter how many times they defeat you,
stand back up and renew your attack!
Drive them into a corner with
your terrifying immortality!
Well, the clock has struck midnight.
It's time for us to go all out.
Don't count on escaping us, foolish pirates!
Are you ready, zombies?
Yeah!
This is the land of the
deceased, Thriller Bark!
May you have unpleasant nightmares!
Well, shall we go?
It's a haunted mansion!
It has finally begun, Absalom!
Right! It's time for the night raid!
The night raid!
Go on a rampage, General Zombies!
A-A night raid!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Feast of the Zombie Song! The Night
Raid's Bell is the Sound of Darkness!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!