Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy was ejected from
the Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma, a Warlord of the Sea.
Separated from his friends,
he arrived alone at the
female-only empire of Amazon Lily!
Don't let him escape!
There she is! That's her!
Luffy fled the village with Margaret,
a Kuja warrior, in tow, but...
If we keep this up,
I'll only grow attached to you!
Whoa, now! Stop!
I am Vice-Admiral Momonga
of Navy Headquarters!
Warlord of the Sea and
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Show yourself! I've come for you!
I like the title of Warlord.
I don't want it taken away.
But I hate the World Government.
I don't want to obey its orders.
Love-Love Beam!
If you do not reappear in two days' time...
...the agreement is off!
Do as you wish.
"The Secret Hidden on the Backs--
Luffy and the Snake Princess Meet"
Open the gate!
The Snake Princess has returned!
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Kuja Pirates!
Snake Princess!
Ran-sama!
Daisy-sama!
We had a big haul!
They're so cool!
I'm gonna join the pirates someday too!
It's the Gorgon Sisters!
Snake Princess! Snake Princess!
Ran-sama!
Daisy-sama!
Rindo-sama!
Blue Fan-sama!
Cosmos-sama!
Marigold-sama!
Sandersonia-sama!
They're always like this.
It was a long trip.
They must've really missed our big sister.
She looked at me!
No, she looked at me!
Welcome back. Your Monkey Carriage is ready.
Has anything happened?
No. Nothing at all...
Carry it slowly and carefully!
Iron ore, gunpowder, alcohol,
and crops from the north...
What a tremendous haul!
We plundered two merchant
ships and one pirate ship.
The center sea people just offshore
also gave us their cargo.
The Kuja Pirates truly are elite!
I suppose so!
Where's the Snake Princess's present?
Don't worry. It's been sent to the castle.
Ran. Any books at all?
Down here.
Granny Nyon!
Let me think.
Oh, those center sea people
did give us a newspaper.
Here you are!
What?!
Welcome back!
Welcome back, Snake Princess.
Thank you for holding down the fort.
I've prepared the finest, most exquisite
jewel from your spoils of war.
Even the jewel pales in
comparison to her smile!
Snake Princess!
A decoration of that quality
would only spoil my beauty.
Enishida. What is this?
Oh, it's a clay model that
children from the village
worked hard to make for you!
They must have worked hard to paint it, too.
Oh!
We made this for the
Snake Princess to look at!
The way they carefully carried it to
the castle to prevent it from breaking
was truly tender and innocent!
Oh, I see.
So they made me...
...out of mud and clay...
Snake Princess!
Don't bring such filthy
things into the castle!
Throw it away at once and clean the floor.
Anyway, Enishida...
Y-Yes?
I didn't see any of our defense warriors
there to greet us on our arrival...
Oh, well, actually...
A rather violent monkey
appeared in the jungle, and...
It was such a savage and crude beast
that they all had to go after it...
A monkey?
Yahoo!
There he is!
Take this!
Did you get him?!
L-Look!
Men certainly are stubborn...
Don't think you can get away from us.
Don't worry. They'll be back shortly.
I'm truly sorry they
weren't there to greet you.
Well, no matter.
Would you like something to drink?
White sake.
I think I'll have some, too.
Granny Nyon.
This is my room. Why are you here?
G-Granny Nyon!
How did you get in?!
I can get in any way I want.
Throw her out.
Wait, Snake Princess!
You forgot "please"...
"Please."
Pardon me. Please wait, Snake Princess.
The center sea people's ship
is anchored off shore.
They've come here to get you, have they not?
They've ordered you into
active duty, have they not?
That's right. An invitation to war.
Why aren't you going?! You must go!
If you go, the agreement will be upheld!
Certainly someone with your abilities
won't meet an untimely fate!
But...
...I'm scared!
She's almost like a puppy!
Wait, this is no time for that!
Granny Nyon...
This land is currently protected by
your title of Warlord of the Sea!
Up until recently, this island was
protected from outside enemies
by the great defense network
that is the Calm Belt!
However, now the center sea people
are using new ship-crafting techniques
to come and go through
these waters as they please.
The fact that you're a Warlord of the Sea
is the only reason they
won't set foot on this island
to put a stop to the Kuja's pirate ways.
The island is also home to the
very young and the very old.
If you lose the title
and we return to being
a regular pirate nation,
only tragedy will await us!
Are you sure you're not just afraid?
My life could end at any time now.
Look closely at this crystal ball!
That's Granny Nyon's fortunetelling
ball that's right 200% of the time!
Let us shed light on your future...
I see your future!
"Go!"
Detestable!
Throw her out!
This instant!
Y-Yes! Right away!
Wait! Snake Princess!
Stop! What are you doing?!
I watched quietly,
only for you to put on a pathetic act.
What are you trying to pull here?
Your era is long over...
...Gloriosa, ex-empress of Amazon
Lily from three generations ago!
Even if this land should be
destroyed by one of my whims,
everyone will forgive me.
The reason for that is,
yes...
...because I'm beautiful!
There it is!
The Snake Princess's
"excessively looking down on others" pose!
Long ago, despite your status of empress,
you deserted this land
and left for outside waters!
You Kuja traitor!
That's why I live quietly on
the edge of the village now!
Then you should continue
to live there quietly.
I will not have you interfering with me,
the current empress!
Snake Princess!
Hey! Let go!
That said, I can't help but admire your zeal.
You win.
You agree to what I said, Snake Princess?
It really does pay to talk things through!
Thank you!
You'll go, then?!
I lied. Don't get cocky!
Get out of my sight!
Curse you, Snake Princess!
S-Snake Princess...
What have you done?! She's an old woman!
I don't know what came over me...
Yes! Yes! That sort of thing
happens to all of us!
Clean up the broken window too!
Yes, ma'am!
Annoying woman!
Granny Nyon!
Aged as I may be, I am still a Kuja warrior.
I have not grown decrepit!
My hands are dirty.
Is the bathwater ready?
Yes, ma'am! I will issue
the advisory at once!
The Snake Princess is about to bathe!
Okay! Stay still now!
Oh! Sorry!
Leave the castle premises immediately!
Come on! Let's hurry!
I-I just started eating!
Hurry outside!
Everyone who's on duty today, to your posts!
It's time for their bath!
Get ready!
The people in the castle are coming,
so it's about to get packed in here!
"Bath"
For the next several hours,
entrance into the castle
is strictly forbidden!
What are you doing?
You're not allowed past here, you know.
Say...
Why does everyone make such a big deal
when the Snake Princess takes a bath?
How old are you now?
Eight.
Then I'll tell you.
The Gorgon Sisters' secret?!
That's right.
You're in charge of keeping watch.
Yes, Big Sis.
Please take your time.
Gorgon was the name of a monster
that once lived in the center ocean.
Anyone who looked at this terrifying
monster would instantly turn to stone.
At the end of an adventure,
the Snake Princess and her sisters
managed to slay the Gorgon monster.
But when the monster uttered its death howls,
it placed a horrible curse
on the three warriors.
The monster's large eyes
were etched onto their backs,
and everyone nearby who's lured in
by their charm and looks at them
is turned to stone and killed.
The Gorgon Sisters never remove
their clothes in front of people.
And when they bathe,
they always post guards
like this to keep people away.
Oww...
Ouch!
That's the man's voice!
Have the snakes found him?!
Ouch! Ouch!
Let go, you!
Where did he run to?!
He went up the craggy mountain!
Don't tell me he went back into the village?!
He wanted a ship!
What?!
That hurt...
Hmm, what do I do now?
I'll get spotted again if I just sit here...
She did mention this island
has a pirate ship...
If I can just borrow it somehow...
No, wait. Nami's not here.
I'll end up drifting around
if I go all by myself.
Oh, I know!
Asking for a ride on the
ship is the best way!
I'll ask if they'll take me to
Sabaody Archipelago!
Which means...
I'll have to talk to someone important,
and since important people
live in tall buildings...
I'm thinking so hard I might get a fever!
Okay! I'll just go into
a tall building first!
I'll try that one!
Hurry to the village!
The Snake Princess has
probably already returned!
If she finds the man,
things will turn serious!
It's brittle!
What was that?!
The castle tower's roof collapsed!
What's happening?!
The Snake Princess is taking a bath in there!
More water?!
Ouch, it's hot! Wait, this is bathwater!
I'm gonna die! I'm gonna drown!
My feet are on the ground. I'm safe!
Is this a bath?
A man!
Hey...
That thing on your back...
It seems familiar somehow...
You saw it, didn't you?!
Luffy is captured by the women again
after seeing the Snake Princess's secret.
Margaret and two other
Kuja warriors defend him,
but the enraged Hancock turns them to stone.
Seeing his saviors petrified
infuriates Luffy,
but a terrifying executioner
approaches from behind him...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Heartless Judgment!
Margaret is Turned to Stone!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!