Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
During their voyage in
search of Fishman Island,
Luffy and friends met the mermaid, Camie.
To save Camie's friend Hatchin,
who had been captured by
a kidnapping gang, the Flying Fish Riders,
the crew headed to the Flying
Fish Riders' hideout.
Whether it's from the sea
or the sky, bring it on!
I'll go nuts on 'em!
Boys!
It's battle time!
Yeah!
"Tragedy! The Truth Hidden
Behind Duval's Mask!"
Well, now, which one's
got the most fight in it?
Hey, hey, hey!
That's the one!
Gotcha!
Wha?
I'm takin' over!
H-Hey!
Whoo! This is awesome!
Yeah!
I'm flying!
Luffy's flying one of them!
Leave him be.
Eat this!
Bombs!
Damn!
Nami-san! Robin-chan! Are you okay?
That was close! They almost got us!
Damn them. If they'd hit the ladies,
I would've had to kill them.
Hoist the sails! They're in the way!
Right!
We're gonna dive!
Roger!
Luffy!
Luffy-san!
Wait! You idiots!
What do you think you were doing
in the middle of a fight?!
Sorry...
And why did you guys try to save him?
You've got powers!
Sorry...
I... I'm sorry for causing trouble...
Think of how we felt, having to save
you three lumps who can't swim!
Idiot! Don't make more work for us!
The Macro Pirates!
Now's our chance! Get Camie!
Right!
Hey, Straw Hats! Pay attention to us!
Luffy-chin!
Camie! Pappug!
I'm free from the cage and the binds!
Thanks, Roronoa! You're a good guy!
Just following captain's orders, idiot.
Hachi!
Hatchin!
You guys took advantage of
the fact that I couldn't move
to beat me up, didn't you?!
Yeah, yeah! I didn't get
to do enough beating!
I'll use my Fishman Karate to finish you!
You really have no luck!
Since you kept mouthing off at us,
we're gonna pound you even more!
Let's go! I'll stain the sea red with
the new Goldfish Fencing techniques
I developed just for you!
Hatchin!
Here we come!
Takoyaki Punch!
We'll let you off the hook for today!
Hatchin!
Camie! Pappug!
I'm so glad you're safe, Hatchin!
I'm sorry, Camie, Pappug!
I meant to come save you!
Don't worry about that, Hachi!
Look out!
Don't forget, this is our hideout!
The ones who are gonna sell you all are us,
the Flying Fish Riders!
Roronoa!
Zoro-chin!
You left the fight too soon.
Leave the rest to us and go hide.
Thank you for everything, Roronoa!
I'm really sorry for what I did back then!
Back then?
I caused you so much pain
with my Six Swords Style.
Not one of those swords even hit me!
Really? They didn't?
Here they come, Chopper!
Take this, scum!
Fire!
Bullseye! Did you see that?!
My condolences, suckers!
You're awesome, Usopp!
Would anyone like to try the Zero Fight?
Zero Fight?
Sounds fun! But if I'm gonna do
it, I'm giving it all I've got!
You'll give us plenty of
medical coverage, right?
How about a million?
It's a deal, Head! I'm going!
Outta my way!
Some huge guy is coming this way!
He's swinging an iron rod!
He isn't holding the handlebars.
He's not planning to
charge us head-on, is he?
What?!
The ship won't withstand
a crash from that monster.
Luffy, you go after the fish.
All right!
You're about to find out
that a crash at this speed
is like being hit by a meteorite!
Sanji's right! He's charging right at us!
But the impact of that crash
is gonna be just as hard...
...on you!
Gum-Gum...
Balloon!
This'll be dinner tonight!
You were both so cool!
Seeing it up close, it really is big.
Damn! The usual methods aren't
working on these guys!
Usopp!
There are more of them flying
around than I realized!
How many do we have to
bring down to finish this?
Damn! I wanna ride one!
Don't think I've given up after last time!
Give up! I'm not saving you again!
How can this be?
What's wrong, Brook?
My first battle as one of the Straw Hats,
and I nearly drowned...
If I can't be of use now,
I'm a failure as a man!
How many of those flying
fish can I bring down?
I cannot say, but I can show you...
what I can do!
He can really jump!
What's that skeleton guy doing?!
I'll skewer him!
Lullaby Song.
Wow! They all fell... asleep...
You guys, too?!
Music is
power!
Pardon me!
Whoa! I fell asleep!
Damn that guy! What was that?
He must've used some kind of dirty trick!
It was no trick.
It was music!
Wait!
That Brook's pretty good!
It's getting fun now!
I'm going, too!
Wait, Luffy! Not again!
All right, gotcha!
If you try to go under, you'll pay!
Hey!
He's asleep!
Hey, you! Wake up!
That jerk! He dove in to the Head's room!
You saw, didn't you?
Hey! You're—
You know me, don't you?
Roronoa!
Zoro-chin!
I can't run any longer!
My legs are about to cramp up!
Uh, not that I have any muscles to cramp...
You really went all out, Brook.
You took out a lot of the flying fish.
I had to do something useful...
But... I need a break...
Zoro-san, you're still suffering from
the damage you took at Thriller Bark...
It's not enough to let
these fish bring me down.
Don't worry.
You let your guard down, Roronoa!
Six Swords Style!
Tentacle Sword Overload!
Huh... You saved me?
That's right. 'Cause you
weren't paying attention.
Hatchin! You were so cool!
That's my boy, Hachi!
Really?
Die, fishman!
Pardon me!
I thought I was a goner! Thanks!
You're welcome.
I told you, you left the fight too soon.
Don't rush in individually! Formation!
Formation (Hentai)
Pervert?
Pervert (Hentai)
You talking to me?
Attack in flight formation!
Formation (Hentai)  Flight (Hikou)
Perverted misbehavior?
Perverted (Hentai)  Misbehavior (Hikou)
You mean me?
Not you!
Here they come!
Here! Over here!
Come on down!
A woman?!
Seems like a waste, but our
orders were to kill you all!
You think you can kill me?
What?!
Too bad! That's Mirage Tempo!
Watch for thunder clouds ahead!
Dos Mano!
Clutch!
Carving Hoof Diamond!
Don't break formation!
You talking to me?
No, he's not!
Now!
Oh, they didn't mean me?
What the heck?! Guns don't work on him!
Strong Hammer!
Amazing!
They really are strong, Pappug!
I never would've thought
they could do all this.
I thought we'd just get
Hachi and hightail it home.
Take this!
Damn!
Franky, dock the ship!
They have the advantage as long
as we're drifting on open seas!
I know that. That's why I'm doing this.
These guys aren't giving
us time to move the ship!
Luffy!
Run! There's a big one coming!
The Iron Mask?!
A guy in a mask, and a cow!
A cow?
That's Motobalo's voice!
The Head's here!
You just let them shoot
you down left and right?
What is that?! Something just burst out!
You're not mosquitoes or flies!
You're Flying Fish Riders!
He trampled his own house down
to make his appearance...
I don't need this hideout anymore.
Not if I get to kill the Straw Hats!
We're sorry, Head.
We'll sink all of these guys to
the bottom of the sea right—
Move!
I have no need for fishmen,
mermaids, or gloves!
If you want to run, then get out of here!
I'm a starfish!
I'm not in the human trade
because I want to be.
You all know that very well, don't you?
Of course, Head!
Today is a joyous day.
The man I have wanted to kill
so badly that I dreamed about it
is right in front of me!
I'm so grateful! There truly is a God!
The man who showed up that day and
plunged me into the depths of Hell...
Hey, does it look like he's
talking in our direction?
On this day, here and now,
even if I go down as well,
I will kill you!
The pirate, "Black Foot" Sanji!
I have so longed to see you.
Crap! The Head's really mad now!
Huh? He wants to kill me?
Sanji, who's that guy?
Does he have some kind of grudge against you?
Maybe it's from when you
worked at the restaurant?
Try to remember!
That was three years ago...
All I ever did back then
was piss people off...
Just get shot! You'd get what you deserve!
Don't you play dumb, Black Foot!
It was just recently!
Watch it! Get down! They're harpoons!
But if it was recent, I'm even more stumped.
What is that? Something's
weird about these harpoons...
These are Scorpion's Poison harpoons.
If one pierces you, you'll
be dead in three minutes.
Feel my wrath!
Nami-san, look out!
Damn that bastard! I can't remember!
Who are you?!
I'll murder you and your whole crew!
I saw him without his mask.
You did? Who is he?
Don't be too surprised.
It's a face you know, too.
Me?
That fool!
Duval-sama's iron mask!
That's fine. Take a good
look at my scarred face.
Wha— Huh?!
No way...
What?!
He's...
Wow.
Oh, my...
I could cry!
I have waited for this day.
After I decided to kill
you, I took to the seas.
But searching for you was not easy.
You look nothing like your
wanted flyers, after all.
Even if the Navy or bounty hunters saw
you, they might totally overlook you!
No, that's not true.
They do find you!
Head...
They find you, and they say...
"I found you,
Black Foot Sanji!"
And then I tell them...
"I don't know who that is!"
"I'm not even a pirate!"
Stop screwing around!
The Sunny's in trouble!
We're gonna get sunk!
Hey, relax! This week, I'm the
most super I've ever been!
I'll show you the Sunny's true power!
Wow! The Sunny is amazing!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Unleash the Sunny's Super Secret
Weapon, the Gaon Cannon!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!