Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that's what it takes
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It's important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We go...to where the dream is
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can't stand still, I can't stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler
of the island and the
puppet master of Shinokuni
- Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate
ally - the Warlord - Law,
were drawn into a climactic battle
which ended with Caesar's
defeat and capture.
Pirate brothers and sisters!
Thank you for helping us!
When we grow up, we will become...
...Pirates!
Don't!
Let's sail out!
Let's negotiate.
Your most important business partner is
one of the Four Emperors.
The big-time pirate - Kaido,
the King of the Beasts.
What would happen if he finds out
you can't produce SMILE anymore?
He'll destroy you.
What do you want in exchange for Caesar?
Name your price.
Resign from the Seven Warlords.
Damn squirt!
"The G-5 Wiped Out!
Doflamingo's Sudden Attack!"
How were you doing, Sunny?
I can't see the island anymore.
The fire, the ice, and the deadly gas.
The centaurs, the G-5, and the Warlord.
It was like hell.
Well, we're in the New World.
I'm sure it's not gonna get any easier.
Ow, ow, ow... Easy!
Be quiet!
To be honest, I wanna kick your ass!
Ouch!
But I'm a doctor.
So I won't!
Please don't hurt me!
Ouch! Ow, ow, ow!
No, Brook! It's not a "little lamb"!
It's the Mini-Merry!
MINI-MERRY
I see.
You're the eighth person to ask me that.
Like I told the rest,
after I broke out the cage
parting ways with Luffy and the others...
There you are, Sunny!
So they hid you here, huh?
Let's go, Sunny!
I got out to the sea through
a channel in the lab
and retrieved the Mini-Merry...
...which had been docked
at the entrance to the island.
And then, in order to join you guys,
I used the General Franky
which is impervious to toxic gas
and went back to the lab.
Super!
I see, I see.
So that little lamb
was okay. That's good!
Can we have a cup of tea?
Sure.
Here you go.
It was very delicious!
I'm glad that you liked it.
By the way, why are
you two on this ship?
Oh yeah, I haven't thought about that
but the kids had gone with the Navy.
We're in the midst of
our important trip.
So we didn't want to get
involved with the Navy
and waste our time.
You can drop us off on
some island with a harbor.
Until then, please let us stay on board.
Please!
Okay, no problem!
Yeah!
You can pay us later.
Are you gonna charge us?!
Nami, where are we going next?
Hold on.
The next destination is already set.
It's Dressrosa.
The gas didn't work at all?!
This protective suit is made by Vegapunk
and in fact...
...it's way beyond Caesar's ability.
Caesar knew that, so that's why he said
that to my colleagues who
were his test subjects.
You all, just run!
The protective suit won't help!
Take it off and run to the lab now!
What? O-Okay!
Master!
And that's how they all got petrified.
--Let's get going!
--Yeah!
Those who got petrified are still alive!
If Caesar is telling the truth,
they're just in a state of apparent death
paralyzed in the shell.
Yeah, but the poison will damage
their body and kill
them in twelve hours!
We have to find them
and break the shell before that!
Let's save them all at any cost!
Yeah!
Thank you...
...for allowing us to enter the island.
I'll never forget your name.
I can save my people's lives!
I promise I'll come
back to turn myself in!
This is the only exit anyway.
Just go!
Okay!
What should we do with these?
Are they pirates?
I don't know. It's just creepy.
Something's flying toward us.
What?!
Isn't that somebody's head?!
Huh? Don't be ridiculous!
Y-You were right!
Heads are...
...Flying toward us!
What?!
That guy is...
N-No way!
Y-You're...
D-Doflamingo!
The Warlord?!
W-Why is he here?!
Conqueror's Haki!
Why did you do that?!
They're not here.
The ship is gone.
You're a Warlord!
Why are you attacking the Navy?!
I know some pirates were
here a little while ago.
Where did they go?
How dare you do that to our colleagues!
Don't do it!
I can't move my fingers.
What happened?!
Wh-What are you doing?!
W-What about you?!
No, I can't... control my body!
Law is different
but Straw Hat is just an ordinary pirate.
Don't!
Where did they go, you bastards?!
Wh-What are you gonna do to me?!
Answer my question.
Ouch!
Which direction did those shitheads go?!
I don't know what you're talking about!
Then go to hell.
Stop messing with my soldiers!
S-Smo-yan...
Smoker.
Tell me where those shitheads went.
I'm thinking about going to Green Bit.
Well, I don't know,
"Joker."
We could've caught them
but we let them get away.
I don't know what to say
to our base commander - Vergo.
He died, didn't he?!
I think you know too much.
Smoker!
Take this!
It's no use!
It's no good!
He keeps suffering that guy's strange attacks!
He has to defend himself!
Why doesn't he use his jitte
with the Sea Prism Stone tip?!
It'll cancel out Devil Fruit powers!
Demon Bamboo!
You're no match for me.
Stop resisting and just
accept your death.
--Smo-yan!
--We'll fight, too!
Do you guys wanna die first?
Stay away!
Smo-yan!
Vice Admiral Smo!!
Dressrosa?!
Yes, there is something
we have to do there.
D-Dressrosa?!
What? Do you know the place?
Th-That's exactly where we...
I mean, I want to go!
You need to go there, too?!
Uh-huh, I think so!
You have no idea what's
going on, do you?
Nope!
The current is shifting?!
What's going on here?!
A slope?!
Yee-ha!
It's fast! The ship's going fast!
Look out for rock reefs!
What's going on around here?!
It's a sea slope. It's not uncommon.
It is uncommon!
We don't have to go against the current.
The needle in the middle
on your Log Pose must be
pointing toward Dressrosa.
But don't try to go straight.
Take a detour.
Why?
Because it'll work out better for us.
He's being such a know-it-all smart-ass.
Come to think of it,
you were talking on the Transponder Snail earlier.
Who were you talking to?
That was Doflamingo.
Doflamingo?! The Warlord?!
I've heard he's the most evil one!
The plan is already in action.
What plan?
Yeah, tell us about the plan!
Get together, everybody!
We formed an alliance
to kill one of the Four Emperors?!
The Four Emperors, huh?
It's great!
No, it's not!
That's a super big deal!
Wait, wait! Let's calm down, everybody!
Luffy, tell them about the alliance.
Okay! We and Tra-guy's pirate group
formed an alliance!
Let's be nice to each other!
Does anybody wanna oppose this?!
--I do!
I do!
Does it make any difference?
Luffy's mind is already set, isn't it?
Thank you.
But I have to warn you.
There may be a slight difference between
how you define "alliance" and how Luffy defines it.
Be careful.
That's why Luffy kept saying "kidnap"
which was so out of character for him.
If he had just come to me
with that strange sheep
and ask me to cook it, I
wouldn't know what to do.
You bastards.
You're not gonna get away with this.
Extraordinarily big names
will hunt you down!
Idiots!
Realize how stupid you are! Go to hell!
Hey, Sanji! I was in the
middle of his treatment!
Wait until I finish it.
Really?!
I asked you guys to kidnap
Caesar at Punk Hazard.
Meanwhile, I destroyed
the machine which was
manufacturing a substance called SAD.
The great pirates in the New World
often have their own territory.
They lead countless numbers of people
and reign like a syndicate.
It's nothing like what
you've seen before.
One pirate group is never strong enough
even to see their captain's face.
But since it's an underground community,
they have to do their businesses secretly
to avoid the Navy.
And Doflamingo is the most trusted
and powerful man among them.
His underground alias is Joker.
And Joker's most important
business partner now is...
...one of the Four Emperor -
Kaido, the King of the Beasts.
Our target.
--Stop!
--Smo-yan's gonna die!
If you kill him,
who would lead misfits like us!?
Don't worry.
There is no way to find
out who knows what.
That's why, Law, Straw
Hat, and you soldiers,
I'm gonna kill you all!
No!
Whoa-whoa.
Excuse me, young man.
Could you step aside?
What?!
He is my...
...friend.