Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy has snuck into Impel Down
to rescue his brother, Ace,
who has been captured by the Navy.
Now at level 4 the Burning Heat Floor,
Warden Magellan has ambushed him!
I'll find out all about when
and how you broke in...
...after I pass down your sentence!
I'm not gonna tell you
even if it means death!
No!
Straw-chan!
Bon-chan!
Why did you do that?!
I told you that you can't fight!
The poison will harm you
if you get it all over you
but even one touch will be lethal!
Venom Road!
No matter how hard you try...
...you can't get away from me!
Magellan guards the worst prisoners
in the worst prison in the world!
He's the master of hell!
Make up your mind, Bon Clay!
There's no way to beat Magellan!
I'm sorry!
We have no chance to win!
I'm sorry but I gotta run!
I'm sorry, Straw-chan!
I'm sorry!
Don't you wanna give up now?
I'm not gonna let you execute Ace!
I don't wanna lose to you by not
touching you because you're poisonous!
I'd rather touch you and...
...give you my arms!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazooka!
"The Showdown Has Come!
Luffy's Desperate Last Attack!"
How thoughtless you guys are!
If you'd have just shut up and gotten away,
I could have laid the blame on Warden!
I'm at the staircase to level 3!
We have some casualties
caused by the escapees' raid!
Yes, we have Buggy the Clown
and Mr. 3 in custody!
I told you to just be on your way
but you just had to fight me!
You stupid bastards!
H-H-He's strong!
Surprisingly strong!
Damn Hannyabal!
I don't wanna be tortured!
If I'm going to get tortured, I will...
...bite off my tongue right here!
Okay... I'm gonna bite... now!
I'm really gonna do it!
H-He's coming!
Hey! Get out of my way!
Outta my way, you fools!
If you don't wanna get hurt,
just let me go through!
Let's get Mr. 2!
Damn! Don't stand in my way!
Drunken Swan Soiree!
There's no way we can beat him!
I'm not gonna dream an impossible dream!
If I'd stayed there any longer,
I'm 200% sure that I'd be killed!
I've gotta run!
Don't look back!
All I can do is run!
Straw-chan!
You seem to have brought me to my knees!
We never know what a cornered rat will do!
But now you got enough poison on your hand...
...to affect your whole body!
It must really hurt, poor boy!
You still don't give up?!
Gum-Gum...
...Twin Jet Pistol!
Venom Blowfish!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet...
Hydra!
...Pistol!
It didn't hurt him at all?!
Fog?
Venom Cloud!
Damn it!
It's no use!
That poison fog is a part of me!
It's alive!
Your vision's blurry?
Your ears are ringing?
Gum-Gum...
...Balloon!
I said "it's no use!"
Why can't you see that?!
No matter how hard you try,
there's no way out for you!
I assume that you can't use your hands now!
My poison will take...
...everything from you in time!
LEVEL 4--IN FRONT OF THE STAIRCASE
I'm going to bite off my tongue now!
I am really doing it!
You can't stop me!
I can't do it!
Dammit!
Take them away!
Yes, sir!
Fools!
Wait... D-D-Don't do this to me!
Please don't!
I-I don't want gomon (torture)!
Komon (anus) stinks!
Yes, it does!
Wait right there!
W-Who is it?!
He sounds familiar!
Isn't he...?!
Swan Arabesque!
W-Who are you?!
You!
Mr. 2!
The third escapee?!
Damn!
That's enough!
Take this! And this! And this!...
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux, trois!
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux...
Take this 'n this 'n this!...
Un, deux, trois! Un, deux, trois! Un...
You're quite a fighter!
But you can't get away!
Ack?
Who are you?
So cute!
W-W-What are you doing?
You really don't know when to give up!
You want to rescue your brother that much?
It'd be easier if you just stop fighting.
Just close your eyes!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Hey, jailer!
Tell me the truth!
Is there something going on the upper levels?
No, there isn't.
Are you out of your mind?
Why are you so determined?
Portgaz D. Ace is a major criminal
who is soon to be executed!
And you're an intruder who
wants to help a criminal like him!
I won't forgive any of those offenses!
Ace's execution in Marineford is...
...the absolutely final decision
provided for under the law!
There is nothing you can do about it!
Shut up!
Stay away...
Stay away!
Luffy!
This is pathetic.
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
Have you had enough now?
Second Gear!
Hydra!
Give me...
...Ace!
This is your punishment.
There is no way to neutralize the
amount of poison you have absorbed!
You will agonize for 24 hours
and then pass...
...to the real hell!
A... A...
Ace!
After being defeated by Magellan,
Luffy is tossed into level 5.
Despite knowing there's no antidote for the poison,
Bon Clay makes a stand to save his friend.
However, standing in his way
is a pack of Army Wolves!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"For his friend!
Bon Clay Goes to the Deadly Rescue!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!