Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Luffy and the gang have arrived in Enies Lobby.
If we can't recover Nico Robin
and Franky on this straight path
"Iron Fence" "Main Gate"
from the main gate to the Gates of Justice,
"Courthouse" "Main Island Front Gate"
"Gates of Justice" "Tower of Law"
we will have lost.
Why?! No matter where Robin is taken to,
we can just keep going after
them until we get her back!
I explained this before we
left Water Seven, didn't I?!
The only destinations beyond those gates
are Navy Headquarters and the deep-sea prison.
So we have to settle this matter
before that at any cost.
She's right.
That being said, even if we all rush in,
if we encounter CP9, you guys are
the only ones who can defeat them.
After the train ride together, I now
know well how strong you guys are.
So, you guys stay and wait
on the sea for five minutes
and charge in to the main island in
Rocketman through the main gate.
We'll go in first and break open the
main gate and the main island front gate
so that the train can pass through.
After that, we'd like you to keep on
moving no matter how many of us fall.
We're only a little over 60 people,
but our enemy's forces are
probably well above 2,000 to 3,000.
We'd like you guys to go after only CP9,
avoiding unnecessary battles.
Okay, got it.
Okay, guys! We're now
at the front of the island!
Take a good look at the sky behind Enies Lobby.
Those are the Gates of Justice.
Whoooa! That's huge!
Now, there's no time to lose!
Well then, as we planned,
we're gonna go in first!
Leave the backup to us!
Hey, you two! Aren't you
supposed to be with us?!
All fired up to get back Robin, Luffy has...
Hm? Where's Luffy?
What? He was right here up until now.
Hmph!
Is that Straw Hat?
What?!
Oof!
Why the hell is he doing things on his own?!
That man doesn't have a
clue about the plan at all!
That was a waste.
He said he got it, didn't he?
He's not the type who can wait five minutes.
We should've known.
...infiltrated Enies Lobby by himself.
Gum-Gum...!
Meanwhile, Spandam,
the chief who leads CP9, was...
Well...
Today is a joyous day when all
eight members of CP9, including me,
are to gather together in one place
for the first time in five years.
And yet, what's up with this article?!
The orders to assassinate
the heads of the local branches
of the revolutionary army only
required you to kill three of them,
but twenty-three of them are dead!
If you have an excuse, I'd really like to hear it!
Yoyoi!
...waiting for Lucci and the
others in the Tower of Law,
the back room of Enies Lobby,
with other members of CP9.
...my fault!
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Jabra"
Stop it, Kumadori!
A man shouldn't apologize so easily!
I'll explain what happened
to Chief, so just sit tight!
"CP9 [Six Powers Master]
Fukurou"
Iron Body.
How regrettable...! I can't die.
Just die already, you jerk!
You guys, that's enough...
Ouch! I spilt my coffee! Dammit!
Also, they said that Nero was useless.
Oh, well...
Whoa! What the heck is this place?!
What a huge hole! It looks
like the island is floating.
I see a town there, too. I wonder
if Robin is around there...
There's someone up there!
It's an intruder! Shoot him down!
Oops, they found me.
He went inside the gate!
Luffy passed through the
main gate in one shot and...
This is the main gate! This is the main gate!
This is a report to Chief and
the main island front gate!
What is it? What's going on?
An intruder went over the main gate
and is currently dashing towards
the main island front gate!
Oh... It's just an intruder.
Calm down and take care of him.
Yes, but...
This is the main island front gate.
We confirmed the intruder.
...was approaching the main island
front gate by charging straight ahead.
Hey, hey. Stop.
Do you know what this place is?
Deal with him carefully. If my eyes
didn't deceive me, that man is...
...Straw Hat Luffy!
What?! What did you just say?!
I think that's Straw Hat...
A pirate with a 100 million-Berry
bounty on his head!
Robin...
Where is Robin?!
A-Another report from the main gate!
What is it this time?!
A suspicious group on a monster carriage
has just passed over the front iron fence!
Please send reinforcements!
Please send...
What happened?!
Gatekeeper!
Come in!
What is going on?!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Luffy Cuts Through!
Big Showdown on the Judicial Island!!"
What's the matter, Nico Robin?
Don't stop.
"Courthouse" "Tower of Law"
"Main Gate"
Are you guys ready?
Are you hurt?
I'm fine, because...
...I'm Sogeking!
In four minutes... the sea train
Rocketman will charge in!
"Main Island Front Gate"
"Main Gate"
Excuse me, but... please let me pass.
Even if you ask nicely...
...no means... no!
Okay. Then...
...be prepared, okay?!
How dare you, pirate?!
Gum-Gum...
...Ally Robot!
Whoa! That's dirty!
We can't attack him like that!
Such an obvious trick! Don't flinch!
Ally Robot... Punch!
Ahh! Sorry!
Ally Robot... Kick!
Ahhh! I'm so sorry, sir!
That's enough! Your back is wide open!
You bastard!
Bring him down! It's just one unarmed man!
What's with his agility?!
I'm in a hurry.
More people are coming later, so... See ya!
What?
Hey... stop!
He went inside! Hurry inside!
He entered the main island!
Let Chief know!
This is main island front gate,
reporting to Chief!
S-Straw Hat Luffy has entered the main island!
What?! You let him enter the main island?!
What the hell is going on?!
What are Oimo and Kashii doing?!
Did those two get taken out, too?!
No, sir! Since it's currently
in the middle of the night...
...they're probably sleeping.
This is no time for sleeping!
Get them out of bed!
All the guards sleeping on the main island, too!
Y-Yes, sir!
It's just an intruder.
You don't have to make
such a ruckus, right, Chief?
You've got us.
Don't be ridiculous! This is the judicial island,
which acts as a sacred symbol of the
entrance to the World Government.
Any idiot should know what
it means to invade this place!
And yet, he entered even the main
island just to get a crew member back.
It's shameful! How dare they mock us?!
Damn those Straw Hats and their subordinates!
Gatekeeper! Explain what's
going on at the main gate!
Hey, gatekeeper!
How many enemies are we looking at?!
What's their current location?!
Come in, main gate!
Hey, what's the matter?!
Come in, gatekeeper!
Rope Action! Figure-of-Eight Knot!
Bazooka Bat!
I don't wanna waste bullets on this!
Go inside through the side
doors and open the gate!
Don't let them open it!
Get out of our way!
Mozu! Go to the left!
Got it!
I won't let you!
Whoa! Bed-head is coming out of my nose!
You should pay attention!
Hurry up!
Thanks!
Keel Breaker!
Aren't they unlocked yet, Mozu, Kiwi?!
Ship demolition is the Franky Family's job.
Picking locks like this is...
This side is unlocked!
This side, too!
Okay, then! Open the gate,
Herculean Destroyers!
Don't let them open it! Defend it at all costs!
Move! You're in our way!
Rush in!
We broke through the first gate, the main gate!
Whoa! What the hell is this hole?!
We don't have time! Ignore that! Move forward!
Just keep moving and run towards
the main island front gate!
It's a waterfall!
We did it!
Hey, guys! This way!
Give me a hand right away!
Kashii-san! Oimo-san! Get up right away!
Th-The main gate has been forced
open by suspicious people!
Hm?
Hey, he said the main gate
was forced open, Oimo.
Yeah, that's not good, Kashii.
I hate having to get up.
But it's work. Let's go.
Oof!
What?!
"Kashii
'Main Island Front Gate'
Gatekeeper, Enies Lobby"
I didn't get enough sleep.
I'm gonna get rid of them
quickly and go back to bed.
Me, too.
G-G-Giants!
I don't know what you guys
came all the way here for,
but I suggest you go home before we crush you.
Right, Oimo?
Yeah, Kashii. I think so, too.
We're gonna squash you to your bones.
Giant gatekeepers?! This isn't fair!
They're huge! Our Herculean
Destroyers look small.
Now, go back!
I'm not gonna let you go through this gate!
Me neither!
They're coming!
No matter who we're up against,
don't flinch, Franky Family!
This is for Bro!
Yeah!
Hey, you get it, right?
Yeah.
All right!
If we don't go, who will?!
The Herculean powers we
gained working in ship demolitions
are a match for those Giants!
Destroyers!
O-Our Herculean Destroyers are...!
In an instant...!
We're born warriors!
The blood in our veins is different
from that of small humans who
happen to be a bit bigger than others.
I'm not gonna let even a single person pass!
Me, neither!
D... D-D-Don't get cold feet! Don't give up!
That's right! Big Bro Franky is
on the other side of that gate!
Show them a fight worthy
of Bro's name, Franky Family!
"Main Gate"
Two more minutes...
Ribbit!
"Main Island Front Gate"
"Main Gate"
"Courthouse"
"Main Island Front Gate"
Hey, Straw Hat Luffy.
How many friends did you bring?
There are 10,000 soldiers in Enies Lobby!
Yeah, I'm by myself.
Get out of my way!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We're not gonna let even
an ant pass through this gate!
If you don't give up and go back,
we're gonna stomp on you!
Dammit! We can't afford to be delayed here!
Don't flinch! Open the path for Rocketman!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Battle Against Giants! Open the Second Gate!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!