Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit, he decided to enter.
Meanwhile, Robin and Usopp arrived at Green Bit
to hand Caesar over
and came across little people in the forest.
Mil Fleurs! Campo de Flores!
I caught one!
Huh?! What did you catch?!
I think it's a little person!
At the same time,
to grant the girl
that he met on the street, Violet's, wish,
Sanji made a raid on an
unknown villain's hide-out
and got caught in a trap.
You're a good-for-nothing,
"Black Foot" Sanji!
Did you really think that
a guy like you could win my heart?
How funny.
You're lying, Violet-chan...
I'm thinking about you.
The way you looked at me
at that moment...
I knew you were telling the truth!
It doesn't matter
if a million people accuse you, I...
I believe in women's tears!
"The Unknown World!
The Tontatta Kingdom!"
"Believe in women's tears"? How absurd!
He must've gone crazy in fear of death!
Face reality!
You were completely fooled by Sis' act!
What a shithead!
Sis, if this pervert is useless to us now,
let's just kill him already!
We got her permission!
He's worth 77 million berries!
A member of the Straw Hats! "Black Foot" Sanji!
Let's cut his head off!
Hierro Lágrima!
Whoa! Sis, what're you doing?!
Eye Whale!
Help!
Violet-chan?
Eye Whale!
Violet-chan, you were working for
Doflamingo against your will, weren't you?!
Run, Black Foot.
Violet-chan, what about you?!
Forget about me!
Why?!
We know
what you people have
been doing all along.
What?
I was your enemy
but you kept believing in me!
You sure are a good-for-nothing!
Thank you for what you've said.
It made me happy!
I don't know why but
you don't wanna work for Doflamingo, do you?!
You even fought your own men!
Let's escape from this island together on our ship!
Look at me, Black Foot!
From the moment
you all arrived here with Caesar,
you were walking into that man's trap!
Trap?
Yes. Look inside my head.
How can I do that?
What you see is Dressrosa this morning.
What does this mean?
What?
What the...
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
So the winner of Block A was Burgess!
The winner of Block B was Bartolomeo!
And the match of Block C is about to start!
Who is going to win this one?!
All competitors seem eager to start!
Alright! It's time finally!
What is it?
A bull?!
Are you gonna fight, too?!
How funny! You're all fired up!
Hey, who's forcing his way in?!
Stop pushing, idiot!
It's not me, shithead!
Whoa!
Isn't it starting yet?!
Hey, an old geezer like you should stay back!
What did you say?
Say it again!
I said "Your grandpa is an old geezer"!
Whoa-whoa, brother, relax.
That's enough, squirt.
We will show you
what we are capable of in the match!
What did you say?!
Don't mess with us Funk Brothers!
Thank you for waiting!
The time has come!
The competitors of Block C are...
...entering!
The competitors are coming
in one after another!
Just like Block B,
Block C has many formidable contenders!
The battle will start soon!
Who is going to win...
...Portgas D. Ace's Flare-Flare Fruit?!
Until the day you are filled with happiness,
I will always be by your side!
Was it a dream?
Wait! Monkey-san!
I got you!
Again! What kind of place
is the Flower Field?!
Be quiet and keep running.
I'll tell you later.
Watch out for the police!
Aren't you a soldier?!
Don't be scared of the police!
Soldier-san!
What the hell? Do you know her?
Rebecca.
I saw the list in the Colosseum.
You entered the competition as I thought.
I told you not to!
I...
I'll do it! I'll win it!
Soldier-san!
So...
So... Hey, can we live together?!
A warrior who cries easily can't win
a competition!
Hey, let's go!
Is it okay?
Yes.
Just go!
Is it really okay?! That girl was crying!
That's why we got to hurry!
I'm just a toy but I have something
that I want to protect!
But I can't even shed
tears from these tin eyes.
THE FOREST OF GREEN BIT
Hey, Robin, what's going on?!
You said there was a little person!
Yes, I have him here.
Huh? That's not even funny!
Nobody's out there, right? It's all safe?
Did you rob those Navy soldiers?
This is no good!
We have to do something!
There is no little person...
Wow, there is one!
I think his friends are still around here.
What?!
I heard someone talking.
Anesthetic flowers!
What's this smoke?
Hey, are you alright? Robi... n...
Tired...
Usopp...
She's gonna fall asleep soon.
What should we do with these people?
Since they saw us,
we must get rid of them!
What's in her bag?
A book, a notebook, and clothes.
--A candy.
--A Transponder Snail.
Make sure to take all weapons.
There must be something on her!
We are searching her clothes!
--Nothing around Point C.
--Roger.
--Nothing around Point A.
She's not hiding anything
around Point B, either.
The Big Human is waking up!
Go on the alert!
Okay!
W-Wait a minute! Ouch!
Don't try to run! Stay calm!
My body is pinned to the ground!
It's no use trying to move!
I sewed your body onto the ground
with my magical Stitch-Stitch power!
Stitch-Stitch power?
Yes! I sewed you up with this needle!
You're a villainous Big Human, aren't you?
I'm sorry but I think there
is a misunderstanding.
Are you a Devil Fruit eater?
I'm a Tontatta Tribe warrior - Leo!
A WARRIOR - LEO
THE TONTATTA TRIBE
(A TRIBE OF LITTLE PEOPLE)
Leo-san. Where am I?
Where is Usopp?
I mean, the other human - he's not here?
Is he okay?
We also captured that long-nosed Big Human
in accordance with our kingdom's rules.
So this is you Little People's kingdom.
Indeed, you're in the Tontatta Kingdom
underneath the great forest that we created.
The forest? You mean Green Bit?
Did you people grow all those giant plants?!
Yes! There is no plant that we can't grow!
Watch out, everybody!
Kabu-san!
This Big Human can sprout flower-like hands
on the ground!
Flower-like hands?!
We've never grown such things!
Yes, it must be a magic!
The strangest thing I've ever seen!
There was no time to run
before she caught me!
That's right!
I got hypnotized by something
and they must've carried me here!
I can maybe get away from here with my power
but it can create a stir.
You Big Human! What are you up to?!
Are you here to destroy the Tontatta Kingdom?!
No! I'm sorry!
I just caught him out of curiosity!
Whatever the reason is,
we can't let anybody who
saw us Tontatta Tribe go alive.
Why?! I wasn't going to hurt any
of you people in the first place
and I'll never tell anyone that I saw you!
Don't lie!
I don't wanna hear your excuses!
I mean it!
What?
Then, I'll let you go!
What?!
--Oh, what a relief!
I thought she was a bad person.
Great!
They believed me!
Why are they so credulous?
You're free now!
Here are your glasses.
Thank you.
Hey, Leo!
Tonta-chief-sama!
What are you doing?
Tonta-chief-sama, she is a good person!
No way!
But she said so herself.
What?!
Okay, then.
Again?!
Everybody here is so credulous?!
Hmmm, we don't often have a chance to
stare at a Big Human like this.
Who are you?
My name is Gancho.
I'm the Tonta-chief, the king
GANCHO
THE TONTA-CHIEF (THE KING)
OF THE TONTATTA KINGDOM
of the Tontatta Kingdom.
You can stay as long as you like.
Hey! Hello!
Do you want to eat some simmered pumpkins?
Ah!
Thank you! But I don't have time.
Here, here!
Our tree sap cookies are delicious!
Why don't you have tea with us?
I'm sorry. I have to go.
Do you want some grilled mushrooms?
Where is my Transponder Snail?
Oh!
I released it into the wild!
Oh no! There is not much time until three!
I have to call Law!
Where can I get out?
I must go!
Wait! Are you leaving?
I thought that you were a good person!
If you're a good person, give us your weapon!
That's the rule!
But I...
If you don't give it to us,
we're gonna strip you of all you have!
But I don't have any weapon!
Then we have no choice.
We're gonna strip you of all you have!
Take everything she has!
My sunglasses!
They're gone!
Go!
No! Wait a minute!
What's the matter?
That Big Human is...
...the hero's partner!
What?!
Th-The hero?!
Usopp?
Who is the hero that you're talking about?
I'm talking about the other Big Human
that we captured earlier.
He came to save us!
He's the legendary... legendary...
He's the legendary hero!
That's good!
--Awesome!
--I wanna see him!
Usopp... What did he tell them?
It's two fifty-seven.
We don't have time!
The appointed time for Caesar's hand-over
from Law to Doflamingo is...
...in...
...two minutes.
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring... Ring,
ring, ring... Clank!
Hey, Law! This is Sanji!
Black Foot-ya! Did you find the factory?
That's not important now!
What's wrong?
Listen carefully!
You've got to get out of there!