Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
This country will soon be destroyed.
And it will be rebuilt under a new king.
Namely, me!
Citizens of Fish-Man Island!
It's time to say goodbye...
...to the old Ryugu Kingdom!
Three hours from now, at Conchcorde Plaza,
I'm going to cut this
incompetent King's head off!
Straw Hat Pirates!
I'll show you something good.
I know you are somewhere on
the island watching this.
You people shattered Arlong's dream
- he was a symbol of Fish-Men's anger.
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
--What fools...
--I can't believe they got caught!
--It's water!
That room will be filled with water by
the time we finish executing the King.
You lowly creatures can't
survive that, can you?
Shark! Take me to the Ryugu Palace!
I said "Wait," Luffy-kun!
Huh?
You people shouldn't fight Hordy!
Jimbei! They have my crew!
And I got to do something about Hordy
before my friends get into real trouble!
You're impossible!
Just shut up!
Stop me if you can!
I shouldn't let my guard down
just because we fought together.
I almost forgot that
you're that man's brother.
You ready to do this?
Kid?
"A Rift Opens Up!
Luffy vs. Jimbei!"
People called me The Submarine
of the East Blue when I was a kid.
I can easily swim even an 82-foot pool!
I can run that far!
I can't swim but I can run!
Hey, Brook! Let's see which one
of us is faster sometime soon!
You can't beat me! I'm going
to run beyond the horizon!
Anyway, it doesn't look good, does it?!
No, it doesn't! The surface of
the water is getting closer!
--Look, look! The water is...
--It's coming! It's coming!
Shut up!
What's your problem?!
How can you be so calm?!
Yeah! Do you have any ideas?!
Nope.
--Don't be so honest!
--That's so clear, I like it. Yeah...
If only I had my sword.
Sword? But...
I have no choice.
I have to do it in front of you two...
What is "it"?
Dorororororo...
Bone, bone, bone, bone...
Hey Brook, what are you doing?
Hey! Brook!
Bang!
Boom!
I'm out!
What?!
Okay, see you!
Hey, w-wait, wait, wait!
You got some explaining to do!
You can do something like that now?
Yes, I can make my soul leave my body.
That's just like a real dead person.
Yes, you're right.
It happened when I was on
my world tour as Soul King...
I was in quite a slump
at that time for a while.
TDS SALES PLUMMET----
CONCERT TICKETS REMAIN UNSOLD
Sales of TDs and concert
tickets were dropping.
And I didn't know what to do.
Today's concert was not so great.
He's not making great music lately.
I couldn't feel his soul!
What happened to you, Brook?
Write a new song that will sell!
It's not that easy to make a hit song...
Music is something much more sublime.
Maybe... Maybe, the God of Music
doesn't love me anymore.
One more time... Just one more song is fine!
God! God of Music!
Bless me with a melody that will
shake everybody to their soul! God!
Boom!
What?! What is going on?!
Since I got this ability,
I noticed what's missing in my songs.
I found a way out of my slump!
--What was it?
--Well...
If you had the ability to pass
undetected through walls...
Any able-bodied male
understands the potential, right?
I'm jealous, Zoro! I wish I were him!
Shut up!
Oh, the water got that high!
Do something already!
Luffy-chin! Boss Jimbei!
Luffy! Jimbei! Hold on a second!
What are you guys doing?!
I'm gonna go to the Ryugu Palace to save
my crew and kick that Hordy guy's ass!
I said "Don't do it"!
Hey hey, why do you have to fight now?
Cut it out, guys!
Luffy-sama! Boss Jimbei-sama!
Shark! Take me! To the Ryugu Place!
I said "Wait"!
Outta my way!
Fish-Man Karate--Shark Brick Fist!
--What?!
--Luffy-chin!
Huh?!
Luffy-sama!
Ow... Ouch!
It worked?! He's supposed to be immune
to blows like that as a rubber man!
The Fish-Man Karate is all about
manipulating the water around you!
The shock wave can travel
through water vapor in the air
and through to the water
within your target's body!
Every living thing is made up of water.
So even a rubber man can't escape the impact!
Damn you!
I won't let you go, Luffy!
Second gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Stamp!
Is this all you learned from your training?
Don't bet on it!
Enough.
Robin!
Robin-chan!
Hey, move aside, Robin!
Who are you?! Move!
Robin-chan's in danger!
Don't fight.
I don't know the reason but
you two are friends, right?
Huh?! Why did Robin come out of the forest?!
WATERWHEEL TOWN
Take this!
J-Just give up! You guys can't win!
No way. Didn't you see
Boss Hordy's broadcast?
This country will be destroyed.
And Neptune is gonna die!
What did you say?!
No!
Don't kill them.
If you do so, you'll be no better than them!
B-But...
Ryuboshi, Manboshi, take them into custody.
--I got it-so-la-ti-do!
--Count on it!
You're as indulgent as before-dosun.
Does indulgence run in the
Neptune family's blood?
You are not just getting back at
humans but hurting your fellow beings.
Doesn't it pain your heart?!
Any Fish-Man who sides with
humans deserves death-dosun!
Lead the way for your
father--towards death! Fukaboshi!
Screw you!
Shit!
Dammit!
They did it!
They got the New Fish-Man Pirates!
Only the 3 great royal brothers could do it!
Prince Fukaboshi-sama!
Leave the rest up to us.
Thank you.
Let's get to Conchcorde
Plaza to save our father!
All right. Let's go!
Okay, let's go to the execution ground.
Do you want some of us to
stay here at the palace,
Boss Hordy?
No, I don't think so.
This Ryugu Palace is impregnable.
Leave some men to open the
gate when we come back.
We don't want the new
king getting locked out!
We sure don't!
That'd be nonsense-jamon!
You can't win citizens'
hearts with violence!
You have only a little
life left. Say what you want.
This hurts.
That stupid swordsman cut me there.
The drug is wearing off.
Hey, give me the Energy Steroid.
Y-Yes.
The pain is gone!
Is it okay to take that much at once?
I-I don't know.
Boss, what should we do
about those 3 Straw Hats?
They're just humans.
They'll drown if we leave them like that.
No matter who is coming to save them,
no one can break into the palace.
That aside, how are the new residents
from the Fish-Man District doing?
They're doing fine.
They're already moving.
That's good.
There'll be empty houses for them.
Some will leave the country
and the others will die.
They can just move into those houses.
We'll make a great country in which
all citizens can look down on humans.
I found it! The ray of hope!
Those Fish-Men that we saw earlier are
all gone and nobody is here in the palace
but they left Pappagu-san behind.
All right then, Brook,
ask Pappagu to find the key to unchain us.
--And the keys to this cage and this room...
--Wait a minute, fool!
Huh?
One of my swords is enough.
Just bring my sword.
I'll cut them all!
Wow, you're so reliable!
All right, I'll go ask Pappagu-san!
I-I'm scared!
What the hell? I thought we
were just invited to a banquet.
I wonder if those Straw Hats are doing okay.
Pappagu-san...
Huh? Huh?
--Pappagu-san...
--What? What?
I found you!
Boom!
I'm here!
A ghost!
Wait!
It's a ghost--I'm scared!
Pappagu-san! It's me!
I don't have much time! I need the
key... I mean, the sword! Hey, wait!
No, stay away!
--No!!
--What do you mean "No"? Listen to me! Wait!
Are you okay, you two? And Sanji?
Think about it, Luffy!
What will happen if you guys resort to
violence now on the Fish-Man Island?
Everytime Fish-Men tried to open their
hearts to humans, humans disappointed them.
"Humans are very violent."
"Humans hate and look down on Fish-Men."
What happened in the past planted those
twisted ideas in Fish-Men's minds.
In the case of Arlong,
many Fish-Men believe that humans
hunted him because he was a Fish-Man.
If you, the people who beat
Arlong, fight Hordy now,
what do you think will happen?
Even if it helps the island
overcome this crisis,
witnessing you people knocking down
Hordy who is standing against humans...
...would make the islanders to think
that things will never change.
But, Jimbei,
we have to rescue our crew.
And if nothing is done,
Hordy will rule the Fish-Man Island.
We have so many friends on the island.
Hey, Hachi.
You've been trying so hard
to hide who did that to you
but you said a while ago...
...that Hordy attacks those Fish-Men
who are sympathetic to humans.
Did you get beaten by them
because you spoke up for us?
Hachi!
Hatchin, is that true?
Hordy and his crew did that to you?
I can't...
Jimbei!
I think part of the reason Luffy wants
to fight is because this is your home.
I heard that you helped our captain
when he had his back against the wall.
We can't thank you enough for that.
And if Luffy wants to fight,
we will go along with him!
We can't just leave the island like this.
We have reason to fight!
The reason is...
Camie-chan's here!
And Shirahoshi-chan's here!
Yes! This country is the
Mermaid paradise of my dreams!
Get out of my way, Jimbei!
You gotta let me go!
No, I won't! Leave it up to me!
You bastard!
Then I'll just beat my way past you!
I'll fight you as many times as
I have to till you understand!
What did you say?!
Cut it out, guys!
Neptune's execution draws ever closer.
Hordy's powerful allies are mobilizing.
The New Fish-Man Pirates are overrunning
every part of Fish-Man Island.
But then, just as his ambition
is coming to fruition,
an terrifying change befalls Hordy!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Something Has Happened to Hordy!
The True Power of the Evil Drug!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!