Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
It's show time! I'm like a lightning arrow!
Lightning Bone Sword...
Gavotte Bond en Avant!
Mission: Complete...
Gum-Gum...
H-He wouldn't...!
...Battle Axe!
Brook!
Robin-chan!
Gum-Gum...
Now we're in for it.
Shoot!
...Gatling!
Sanji! Chopper!
"The Incredible Battle Starts! Luffy vs. Luffy!"
Still standing: three!
Go on! Stomp all over them, Oars!
Gah! Here he comes!
It's impossible! There is no way
we can take this monster down.
I'm fresh out of ideas!
Wh-What should we do?!
--Usopp!
--Huh?
I'll create an opening.
Eh?
So do your thing!
Eh? What? Zoro, what's that
supposed to mean?
Oh, I get it! That's what you meant!
You've got it!
Huh? What's going on? Usopp!
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
--Gum-Gum...
--What?!
108-Pound--
...Bell!
I'm out of the game if I take any direct hits.
What's taking Usopp so long?!
This is the battle of the century
for the great man, Usopp!
You'd better not move!
Hey, monster!
Yeah?
I'd love to play with you some more,
but the sun is rising soon.
Why don't we finish this up?
Poopy!
Of all the things to say!
Do you seriously hope to defeat us
when you're gasping for breath?
Yeah!
What?! You're getting under my skin!
I don't know how to give up!
Now bring it on, monster!
Let's settle the score!
Of all the nerve!
Oars, crush the idiot already!
Yeah! Master, let me land the finishing blow!
You keep out of this!
Gum-Gum...
Zoro!
One Gorilla!
Two Gorilla!
Three-Sword Style...
...Pistol!
...Two Gorilla... Slash!
Jerk!
Crap!
I'm stuck.
Aw, man! This bites!
Three-Sword Style...
...Yaksha Crow!
H-He did it! That worked!
--Usopp, now!
--Not my right arm again! Quit going after it!
I said that doesn't hurt me!
You're bouncing every which way!
He vanished!
Zoro!
I win.
Hey, Oars!
Look over here!
I did it.
What was that? I swallowed something.
No... You didn't!
Usopp, what was that...?
I did it... I did it!
I got Oars to eat salt!
Woot! Yay! Yay!
Salt? What's so great about salt?
Oh, yeah! You don't know.
Zombies are weak against salt.
Look! Oars is finished!
Luffy's shadow is gonna come out!
It's purification time, you zombie monster!
We've won!
Go!
That was a close one!
What is Moria's shadow doing there...?
I was internally guarding against that!
What a blissful dolt!
You were living in a fool's paradise if you
thought I was going to knowingly leave
his weakness wide open, stupid!
Damn it!
You dropped this, Long Nose!
Usopp!
Oh, no! He spilt the salt!
Brook got this salt for us!
Crap! Shoot! This is our last reserve!
Dang it! Shoot! Shoot!
How dare he make fun of us?!
Damn it! Curse him! Screw that--
Gum-Gum...
...Stamp!
Crush him!
Usopp!
Stop! Stop it!
Usopp! Usopp!!
Stop it!!
Keep it up! Turn him into dust!
Same goes for that woman.
Crush her! Smash her!
Trample everyone here!
That includes the people who are out cold!
They still have a little bit
of breath in their bodies.
Squash them till they
aren't recognizably human!
Hey, giant!
What do you think you're crushing?
There isn't a single soul under your feet.
Huh? I...
I'm alive?
I have no idea who you are, but thank
you for saving me from--what?!
No way!
Who're you?
My name is...
...Monkey D. Luffy!
--L-L...
--L...
Luffy?!
Luffy?! How do you figure?!
I guess I can see the resemblance,
but are you sure?
Is it really you?
It's really me.
But even the way you talk is different...
What happened to you?
Does he have the power to transform?
Or did he catch on...?
Did he defeat everyone?
Uh, y-yeah...
Aside from us, that monster took everyone out.
I see. Get back.
"Get back"?! Luffy, do you
realize what that is?!
That's the zombie with your shadow!
To top it off, it can stretch out
and use your attacks!
How are you going to fight it...?
What are they talking about?
Don't worry about it! Just crush them, Oars!
Of course! Gum-Gum...
--Here it comes!
--...Rifle!
What?!
I am the one and only Luffy!
Hey, something is flying straight for us!
--What is it?!
--Is it a bird?
No way!
It's Oars!
Dude!
Is that really Luffy? I can't believe my eyes!
D-Damn it!
What?!
What's going on?
He's doing it! He's actually fighting!
He's kicking Oars' butt!
Now's our chance! Find them!
Huh? Who are all those people?
Any luck? Have you found them?
Nope! You?
Oh, hey!
--Zoro!
--I found one! He's a member
of the Star of Hope's crew!
Here's another!
He's severely injured.
Everyone's hurt bad!
One of them has even turned into a skeleton!
It isn't safe to leave them unconscious here.
Hurry and get them somewhere safe!
What are they doing?
And in such large numbers?
Think they're zombies?
What if they're after Zoro and the others?
Let's hurry down!
Okay!
Gum-Gum Stamp!
Oh, dang! What's going on?!
Oars is getting his butt kicked!
I can't believe someone is flinging
him around when he's so big.
What's going on?!
Hey, Oars!
Hey, did you hear? Moria-sama is
currently inside of Oars' stomach!
What?!
That means the ruler over all
of the Thriller Bark zombies
is getting defeated along with
the ultimate Special Zombie?!
What type of sick joke is this?!
Oars is a legendary villain that was
called the "Devil" 500 years ago!
We're ruled by one of the Seven Warlords
of the Sea, Gecko Moria-sama!
Say what?!
Nightmare Luffy?
So, bluntly put, you did that to Luffy
by stuffing the shadows of
a hundred people into him?
Exactly, members of the Star of Hope's crew!
Honestly, the strength
of his power terrified us!
But he'll only retain that power
for two or three minutes.
Before long, the shadows that we
crammed into him will fly back out.
We feel bad about what we did to your captain,
but we want to walk under the sun once more!
We want to be human again!
He is our hope!
The sun will be rising soon.
These few minutes will determine
the fate of everyone who has fallen victim to this island!
We're counting on you, Nightmare Luffy!
He destroyed the mansion!
Hurry away from the mansion!
He really is amazing!
Sweet! Keep it up, Nightmare Luffy!
Jerk-face! You're just a shrimp!
Gum-Gum Bullet!
Ow, ow, ow...
Oars, this is pathetic!
How did Straw Hat come by all of this power?
Damn! If I stay in here,
I'll keep taking collateral damage.
I should leave the cockpit for...
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
...Battle Axe!
Gum-Gum...
...Storm!
Oars...!
Moria-sama!
Watch out! He's collapsing!
I don't believe it...
Oh, yeah! Where's Luffy?
The shadows... are leaving his body.
Hey, is Luffy gonna be okay?
Luffy!
Dude, are you okay?
This isn't a dream, is it?
He won, didn't he?
He did! The Star of Hope won!
He defeated Oars and Moria!
Everyone will get their shadows back!
Thriller Bark has fallen!
Three-Sword Style Secret Technique!
Three Thousand Worlds!
Armée de l'Air Power Shoot!
We're up against your shadow.
Settle the score yourself, Luffy!
Yeah! Here I go!
Third Gear!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The End of the Battle Is Nigh!
Pound in the Finishing Move!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!