Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
Gold bells and a bird...
Do you suppose they
were symbols of old Jaya?
Dunno, but I think they were
part of some sort of model.
This here's called a South Bird,
and they still exist on this island!
Oh! Do they have weird calls?
Yep. Just like the logbook says!
Sailors have long used South Birds to...
Oh, crap!
What is it?! What's wrong?!
Go catch this bird! Right now!
Why?! What for?!
Why do we need a bird?
Listen closely! The Knock-Up Stream
you're heading for tomorrow
is located directly south of this cape.
How are you going to get there?!
Once you're on the open sea,
there's no way to get your bearings!
That's right!
We're heading for ocean, not an island,
so we have no guide to rely on!
So you'll use the bird's behavior for that!
I heard the sad tale of your
Montblanc family at the pub.
It moved me, Cricket.
Treasure someone else struggled to
get has a special flavor all its own!
Wanna know what people call me?
The Hyena!
"Dreams Don't Come True?!
Bellamy versus the Saruyama Alliance"
Here they come! Dodge!
These praying mantises aren't normal!
Our net!
What's with this forest?!
It's him!
What do you mean?!
The South Bird is the bugs' control tower!
Why is a bird controlling bugs?!
They're here! Where's it coming from?!
What's that? I hear something different...
Up ahead!
Huh? Boulders?
They're rolling this way!
Is it dung beetle dung?!
No! They're bugs!
Ladybugs!
They're huge! Oww!
Damn things!
There's no end to 'em!
Why is your mole cricket army attacking me?!
You're in the way! Do you
think you can beat me?! Huh?!
I can hear it, but I can't see it...
S-Slug!
Salt! Throw salt!
Sanji! Your Somersault Kick!
Alright! Not that kind of "salt"!
I'm sick of running! Bring it on!
No, Luffy! Bear-bees are really poisonous!
Fireflies!
So pretty!
Cockroaches!
Pigs!
We gladly accept fights people pick with us!
Don't underestimate the Saruyama Alliance!
Get 'em!
Hand over your gold quietly,
or else you're gonna pay dearly!
How do you figure?
O-Old man!
Monkey Punch!
You know it's dangerous for kids
to swing stuff like that around!
Well then, I guess we should
get this midnight show started!
Spring...
...Snipe!
Way to go, Bellamy! Yay!
What do you think of our captain's
"Spring-Spring Fruit" powers?
Speechless, huh?
Clean up the trash! Take care of 'em!
So much for your Saruyama Alliance!
You're just an old man and
a couple of overgrown apes!
Jackpot, Bellamy!
This is definitely it!
Oh! Would you look at that?
Wonderful gold bullion!
There's more! Wow!
This's a big haul!
You guys... aren't qualified to have that gold...!
Qualified?
Is this qualified enough for ya?!
Big Chop!
You fool...
We're way stronger than you are!
How much more qualified do we
need to be to steal treasure?!
Well, old man?!
Watch out, old-timer!
Havoc Sonar!
Bastard!
Wait, Sarquiss!
I'll end his life.
Not that again... The power
of the Spring-Spring Fruit...!
Run, Shojo!
Spring...
...Snipe!
Shojo!
Old-timer! We found gold! A bell-shaped ingot!
Look! It matches what's listed
in the logbook! It mentions bells!
Alright, let's go. Load the gold on board.
Grow up, old man!
This "city of gold" is just a
product of Noland's imagination!
If you wanna be a pirate
in the coming new era,
then you need to realize
that dreams never come true!
The city of gold does exist!
Hey, now! Don't go wild! It's a small house!
Wait, kiddo...
A hatchling who doesn't have the
guts to pick fights with dreams...
...is in no position to talk about pirates!
What was that?
No luck. We couldn't even see a single one...
We saw one, but there was no time
for the bird, with all those bugs...
All we did was run...
Yeesh! Seven people, and you get zilch?!
Get it together, you guys!
That includes you!
I can't run any more!
"You really think you can catch us? Idiots!"
What?! He came here to tell us that?!
Dammit! I'll shoot you good!
All I needed was to see one.
Old guy! We caught a bird!
Old diamond-head!
Masira!
Shojo!
What in the world happened?!
Damn! Who did this?!
Hey! Gimme a hand!
Right!
Look! The Going Merry...!
What the hell?! Who did this?!
Dammit! Who was it?!
Sorry...
Old guy!
Hey, old guy! Are you awake?!
I'm truly sorry!
There's nothing we could do! We're pathetic!
But... there's still time to
strengthen the ship before sunup...!
Wait, old guy! Tell us what happened first!
No... It's okay. Don't worry about it.
Doesn't matter now...
More importantly, you need to...
Ah! Great! You caught yourselves a South Bird!
Perfect!
Luffy!
The gold... It's been stolen!
Nah, it's alright... Forget about that junk...
You need to focus on...
What do you mean, "junk"?!
It took you ten long years
of diving into the ocean
and torturing your body
until you found that gold!
You can't just...
Quiet!
It's alright... This's our problem...
Listen!
If they all work on it, the Saruyama Alliance
can fix and reinforce that ship, no problem.
I'll have 'em finish in time for morning!
There won't be any trouble
with your departure tomorrow!
Listen! We will send you
into the sky, without fail!
Old-timer...
Hey, Luffy.
Bellamy's mark...
Want help?
No, I can do it alone.
No, Luffy! Don't be stupid!
We set sail in only three hours!
If I run along the coast, will I reach
the town from this afternoon?
Yes, you will.
Hey, kid! Where're you going?!
Don't be a fool! Do you
know who you're dealing--
If you wanna stop him, use this.
K-Kid...
I'll be back by morning!
I'm empty now! That's every
last drop of water in my body!
Now I won't sweat a single drop!
This ol' drunk is broke and dry!
O, God of Alcohol, thank you for today!
But I guess there's no such thing...
A newspaper?
Let's see! What bad news is there today?
Oh, this isn't a newspaper.
It's a stack of wanted posters...
Honestly, this is a lawless town!
I'm sick of meeting new bad guys!
This is that spineless kid from this afternoon!
Boy, that sky island talk was a real hoot!
Thirty million, I believe he was worth...
Crap! I had a little too much to drink!
Let's see...
1, 10, 100, 1,000, 10,000,
100,000, 1,000,000, 10,000,000...
Yikes! I really did drink too much!
1, 10, 100, 1,000, 10,000,
100,000, 1,000,000, 10,000,000...
...100,000,000!
Three hours, Luffy!
If we delay our departure any more than that...
...you'll lose your chance to go to the sky island!
He must've done reckless diving day after day
without letting those bubbles
disappear from his body!
This is a duel with the man
who screwed up my life.
Sorry! I'm truly sorry!
There's nothing we could do! We're pathetic!
Damn him!
Those big apes were hilarious!
They had huge gashes all over
and had tears and snot dripping down
as they cried, "Old-timer!"
If he's that important,
they should've protected him better!
Right?!
Talk about lame!
Don't be like that.
They couldn't help it; they were
up against you and Bellamy!
After all, our captain is a major
rookie worth 55 million berries!
Bad news!
What's the deal?! It's the middle of the night!
This afternoon! Those guys in here, they--!
Oh! Bellamy! You're still here?!
You gotta get out of here!
You're in the most danger!
What're you talking about? Me, in danger?
100 million...?!
60 million?!
That's right! Those two from this afternoon!
Their bounties are higher than yours, Bellamy!
You're dead meat!
Are you serious?! Crap!
We laughed at the wrong people!
Think they remember what we look like?!
It's dangerous to stay here!
I never met anyone with a 100 million bounty!
Hey, hey, hey! You fools!
Scared of a few scraps of paper!
Do you have knotholes for eyes?!
You saw their leader!
Made it!
Did you know that there were once pirates
who faked their own wanted posters
to make names for themselves?
People'd see their bounties
and just curl up and surrender,
even though they could've won in a fight...
Just like you guys now!
You saw how weak they are,
but look at you now! You're pathetic!
You're right! Boy, those
bastards had me scared!
Bellamy's right-- someone
with a bounty of 100 million
has gotta be involved
with some pretty bad stuff,
but then why hasn't he been in the papers?!
Definitely! I ain't heard of any straw hat kid!
Whew! Had me scared for a minute there!
Alright! Back to drinking! Cheers!
Bellamy! Where are you?!
To think he'd call me out...
Hey!
I just heard the rumors about you...
You got business with me?
Yeah! Give back old diamond-head's gold!
Ah, beyond the never-ending sky
The future that I once saw
is now starting to take shape
There are days where I almost lose to myself
When that happened, there was
someplace warm I could go
The friends I took pride in
always, without fail,
pushed me onwards, didn't they?
Ah, the stars are pouring
down underneath the sky
This unique moment...
You said you were goin' to
a sky island. How'd it go?
I'm about to head into the sky...
after I beat you up!
All you ever say is dream-like crap...
If you want, I can make you
dream forever... in the afterlife!
So long, Straw Hat!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"100 Million Man! World's Greatest
Power and Pirate Blackbeard!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!