Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Boss!
"The Sun Pirates Split! Jimbei vs. Arlong!"
And so that was how the captain of
the Sun Pirates - Fisher Tiger died.
The captain's death.
I think you all must know
how painful it was...
...for the crew who were left behind.
What are you going?!
"Don't kill humans"?!
See what happens when
you show mercy to them?!
Brother Tai was a fool!
Arlong-san!
Arlong-san!!
I won't forgive them at any cost!
Get ready, you bastards!
You're the Fish-Man...
So noisy!
You're Arlong, aren't you?
What brought you here?
Why did you come back so...
THE NAVY HQ VICE ADMIRAL
BORSALINO (FUTURE ADMIRAL KIZARU)
...nonchalantly?
I'm gonna kill all the people
who betrayed Big Brother Tai!
I'm gonna go to that island too!
So you're seeking revenge?
That's right! Fisher Tiger is dead!
You lowly creatures killed him!
Oh I see, he's dead.
But you need to come with me now.
Enraged by Fisher Tiger's death,
Arlong lashed out against
humans and he was imprisoned.
He could've survived if he hadn't
been refused a transfusion.
Fisher Tiger didn't have to die
if there was Fish-Man's blood.
You humans killed him!
"Fisher Tiger,
the Captain of the Sun Pirates,
Dies After Being Denied a
Transfusion of Human Blood."
Not too far from the truth.
The cause of his death was related to humans.
Arlong told the Navy a lie...
The truth was far more tragic.
Tiger was betrayed by humans so he
refused their blood because he had
hard feelings against them.
Plus, he was a slave.
If that became public,
it would have stained Boss' honor.
That's why Arlong told a lie.
Captain Jimbei! There is an enemy ship!
Even without the Boss,
there is no turning back now!
Prepare for action!
Don't kill anybody!
Yeah!
I start identifying myself as
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
and as the captain of the Sun Pirates,
I did nothing but fight, day in and day out.
THE FISHMAN ISLAND - THE RYUGU PALACE
"I am writing this because..."
"...I thought that you two deserved
to know the whole truth."
"The Sun Pirates captain - Jimbei."
My mind is set.
I guess Tiger had no choice but
to live the way he did-jamon.
Now I understand what was going
through his mind that day.
I'll be alright! I will not give in!
We shall live under the sun!
The day that humans and we
understand each other will come!
Sign here to show that you want to relocate!
That's impossible, Otohime-sama!
We just can't!
Humans refused to help
Tiger-san who saved slaves
of all races without discrimination!
How could we understand them?!
Another day without any signature.
Mother-sama!
My sweet babies!
Mother-sama, are you okay?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
You look very tired.
You're my consolation!
But I'm fine!
Mother-sama!
I promise you...
...a great future!
Queen Otohime was working
so hard day after day.
Rescuing humans from shipwrecks...
--Are you alright?!
--It was pirates again.
--Help me...
--Of course, we will help you.
Let's take them to the island!
Teaching the island children
about the world above...
Like I taught you yesterday, this is
an area with many trees called forest.
Forest? The Sea Forest?
Collecting signatures...
Wait!
It'll only take a minute!
However...
Queen Otohime!
Oh, you folk are the ones
who signed it, aren't you?
We need to ask you a favor.
How many signatures have you got so far?
I have been doing this for 5 years
but on about 100 sheets of paper
there are 10 signatures each.
Which means there are 1000 supporters.
The population of the Fish-Man Island is
5 million so, to be honest, I'd prefer more...
Now, here is what we have to ask you.
We're afraid we want to withdraw
our signatures - which amount to
about half of what you have.
What?
You haven't heard yet?
The pirates who arrived the other day...
...committed a robbery in this
town and got away from the island.
Queen Otohime...
Queen Otohime!
Oh kids! Do you want to hear
about the world above?
Um... My mom wants the paper
that I signed the other day!
My mom wants it!
What do you want?
I listened to you because you're the Queen...
But we have problems with humans...
We don't wanna...
...Hear your speech anymore.
We are tired of it.
Welcome home, Mother-sama!
I worked so hard today! I'm home, my angels!
I think I overdid it...
Could you leave me alone for today?
You are all liars!!
Otohime-sama! You're on the air
- the whole country heard it!
Shurrup!
Minister of the Left!
A-Are you drunk?!
I'm alright!
Shurrup! I'm not... I'm not drunk!
Yes, you are!
--What is that?
--Is that Otohime-sama?
Everybody, listen!
We... We are capable of staying
in the water forever if we want!
But in the ocean so broad,
and on the seafloor so dark,
we chose to live in this
limited area... Do you know why?!
Otohime-sama...
Isn't it because there is some light and air?
But there is more light above ground,
and the sky is higher!
Why do our children sneak
out to see the Sabaody Park?
There are more beautiful places
than we can imagine in the world!
There is no place that we should not go...
You are just making convenient
excuses to convince yourself
and giving everything up!
Have courage!
And go for what you truly want!
Your Majesty...
If humans stand in your way,
let's face them together!
Then maybe we can make a difference for
the future of the children on this island,
even just a small one!
I left my family behind
on the Fish-Man Island.
My kid and wife... I wonder
how they are doing.
But you can go home someday.
We former slaves will get
killed if they find us.
So whether we want it or not, we have to
keep sailing for the rest of our lives.
I'm sorry! I didn't mean it.
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
Are you alright now?
It was awful.
I can't believe that you got beaten so bad.
Arlong, who was locked up in Impel
down the other day, is nothing.
The most violent one is Jimbei!
He was unbelievably strong.
It's too dangerous to have him at large.
Hmm...
UNCLEAR JUSTICE
They want me to join the Seven Warlords?!
Your bounty was raised
to 250 million berries!
They figured that you're gonna be an
even bigger threat to the Government.
They finally got it!
Let's turn them down and gain
more notoriety, Captain Jimbei!
No, I think I'm gonna take the offer.
What?!
Welcome back, Jimbei!
I heard about the Seven Warlords.
If I join the Warlords, Aladdin and the
others who don't want to be pirates...
...can live in this country without being
chased under the amnesty of the Government.
More importantly, if I become a Warlord,
the Fish-Man can get closer
to the World Government.
For the good of the Queen who
we've caused so much trouble.
Thank you.
She's not feeling well now.
And it could make the late
Tiger's dream come true -
liberation and freedom for the Fish-Man!
But at the same time, I think the amnesty
would cause us some trouble too...
IMPEL DOWN
--Arlong-san!
--Arlong!
Arlong-san!
--Arlong-san!
--Arlong-san is back! He's back!
Arlong-san!
If you've got something to say, just say it!
You're gonna join the Warlords,
huh? Brother Jimbei.
You're gonna be the
Government's dog, aren't you?!
Don't you remember what Brother Tai said?
Don't let resentment and
anger get the better of you!
You've gotten soft, Brother.
I know I'd be safe if I just
followed you, but I refuse!
Big Brother is dead!
I'll lead the Arlong Pirates again!
I'll take my men with me.
So this is it.
Arlong, you fool...
If you really wanna stop
me, you better kill me...
...right now!
A-Arlong-san!
If you can't do it, I'm free to go.
I represent the anger of the Fish-Man!
How arrogant you are!
Jimbei-san!
That's great!
Stop it!
Just take him away now!
Arlong-san!
Don't worry, Jimbei.
You two grew up together and
he's like a brother to you.
No wonder you couldn't just kill
him even though you were justified.
Why can't that fool understand...
...what Brother Tai truly meant?!
Wherever he goes, as long as he engages
in violence, the Navy won't leave him alone.
Or if that doesn't work,
let's go and stop him ourselves...
...at any cost!
Well, well, we'll go our own way,
just like we used to, Captain Jimbei!
Macro, you...
Let them go!
Bye!
Damn, he's like a monster...
Hachi, let's go.
The Sun Pirates split into three groups
and went separate ways.
Because of Jimbei's status
as one of the Seven Warlords,
he is able to safely bring the
former slave Fish-Men home.
Just as Otohime's ideal future
had seemed one step closer,
a drifting ship arrived.
On board is a Celestial Dragon
who thinks of Fish-Men as
nothing more than slaves!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Shaking Fish-Man Island!
A Celestial Dragon Drifts In!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!