Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
The Arctic Path is enshrouded by ice.
After getting split up,
the Straw Hat Crew are attacked
by a group of bounty hunters
known as the Accino Family.
It's show time!
Love Throw!
The lady is flying into my chest!
Today is his birthday, so everyone
came to pick up a birthday present!
Was the flag the present?
Boo! Bad guess!
These are the presents.
You have a 80-million-Berry bounty, right?
Luffy and the men on Puzzle's ship
catch the second oldest son
in the Accino Family, Blend.
Ah, crap!
Luffy!
As for you ex-pirates!
You'd better prepare yourselves!
Puzzle-san?
Puzzle!
You still haven't caught them?
How is the Straw Hat's flag coming?
It should be here soon, Papa.
Please calm down.
Where am I?
Meanwhile, Nami and Franky got caught
by the Accino Family's third son, Hockera.
Damn it!
I'll break your nose!
Scary!
Usopp, how dare you harm a lady?!
Hey! Are you turning against me?!
How dare you hurt my sweet honey, Arbell?!
Wait!
Hey, Arbell-chan!
Take this, you punk!
Eat this! Flame Star!
Whoa! Move!
Youch, that smarts! I whacked my head!
The great Usopp-sama
Headbutt worked! Just as planned!
Arbell-chan, are you all right?
Salchow...
Who're you?!
"Stifling to the Max!
The Twins' Magnetic Power Looms"
I'm freezing!
I heard you're the one
who saved me. Thank you!
How do you feel? Does it hurt?
It seems okay.
Hey! You've got some nerve,
making us serve you!
How dare you underestimate
the Phoenix Pirates?!
Say your prayers!
Are you sure about this?
My siblings won't keep quiet
if something happens to me.
Shut up! We're done taking garbage from you!
You've got spunk, brat!
You're a...! You're nothing more than a...!
Stop right there!
Puzzle-san?
Don't get the wrong idea. I didn't
capture him so we could get payback.
Huh?
I want to... cut a deal with you.
A deal?
Yeah. I want you to let them off the hook.
In exchange...
In exchange, you can have my head.
What?!
P-Puzzle-san, you're...?!
How could you say that?!
This is great! You're quite the captain!
If you do that, what'll happen
to the Phoenix Pirates?!
Jiro...
The captain has made up his mind.
But...!
Jiro!
I...
How dare you bastards try to trick us?!
I should teach you a lesson!
Stansen!
Captain, what are you doing?
Let that creep have it!
Go on, Captain!
Captain, why? Go back to
the way you used to be!
Please! Come back to us!
Damn it...!
We aren't pirates anymore!
Puzzle-san...!
You've got a clever captain.
Very well. I'll spare your whole
crew in exchange for your head!
No! I... I'm a member of the Phoenix Pirates!
Hey!
I'm gonna take this jerk down!
Jiro, stop. It's all over...
Kid, I dare you to so much as touch me!
I'll get back at you and all of your crewmates!
Damn it!
Straw Hat...?
Weren't you listening, punk?
Hurt me and they'll all pay the--
Give back my flag.
Luffy...
Your flag?! Take a look around you.
Now isn't the time!
This has nothing to do with them.
Give back my Jolly Roger right now!
I-I don't have it right this second, so I can't!
Then take me to it!
C-Calm down! Someone is on
his way for me as we speak.
Your flag is in the Arctic Path's last stop,
my family's base of operations, Lovely Land!
But you're finished once you reach Lovely Land!
I'll send the whole lot of you to the
afterlife before you ever see that flag!
Isn't the flag here yet?
Campaccino!
Papa, Lil's kite is currently flying it over!
It will be here any second now!
And what happened to my birthday party?
It will resume as soon as everyone returns.
Campaccino, how long must I wait?!
P-Papa, don't get so upset!
We're almost to my house.
This person and this person are also
headed over to your house, right?
Yup!
My big brother, Hockera, is taking them!
I see...
Papa is going to love this!
Hey! Can't you do something about the cold?
I could have if I'd known we'd
get turned into popsicles!
I know! Wanna try melting the ice
from the inside with my Fresh Fire?
Don't even! What if you started a fire in here?!
Then what do you suggest?
I want you to come up with
something that isn't dangerous!
You're one picky chick!
You're not picky enough!
Dang, this doting couple is annoying!
Arbell-chan, what do you see in that monkey?
They really pulled a number
on us earlier, Arbell!
Salchow, now that it's come to this,
let's show them our ultimate move!
Hey! They're about to do something.
All right! I'd better show
Arbell-chan how cool I am.
Oh, crud! This looks bad!
They're spinning around a lot more than usual.
I will save Arbell-chan from that ugly man!
Okay! We'll go with that plan!
You're up!
We're looking really great! Arbell, here we go!
Right, Salchow!
Death Spiral High Jump Ultra Love Throw!
Whoops!
Youch!
Damn it! I can't dig my heels
into the ground without slipping!
Sanji, I'm not confident I'll survive
if I get hit by that again.
I swear, you always make such
a big deal out of everything!
This is clearly a fatal injury! Isn't it obvious?!
Salchow, we're the best!
We're looking really great, Arbell!
Let's give it another go!
Yeah!
Usopp.
It's time we hit them with
a combo attack of our own.
What is it? Did you come up with a sweet idea?!
Hey! What's with this situation?!
Now I won't slip!
Ow, ow, ow! Ow, ow! That hurts!
Collier Frit!
Nice!
Arbell-chan...
Did I earn a high score for artistry this time?
Shut up, you wanted man!
Get off of me already!
Salchow! Hang in there, Salchow!
Ar-Arbell...
Have you learned your lesson?
Your measly attacks will never work on us!
Ar-Arbell-chan...
Sanji, how long are you gonna lay there? Get up!
If you're gonna give up, now is your chance.
I still haven't hit you with
a full 10% of my power.
Did you think we were randomly
skating on top of the ice?
Eh? Huh? What? What do you mean by that?
This is what we mean!
C-C-Cold!
Surrender now!
What?!
Let us catch you and we'd be willing
to save you. If you don't hurry...
Wh-What're those?
Ouch!
You'll die from hypothermia
if you don't surrender soon.
Sh-Sh-Shuddup! Hey, Sanji! Wake up!
Ushopp, I'm sharting to get sweepy...
Stupid! That's really bad!
I'm sweepy...
Fine! Fine! Just save us!
Look, Salchow! I caught something!
So did I, Arbell!
D-Damn it...!
Kissy-poo!
Hey, when is he gonna get here?
Click.
What's that?
Hey, kiddo! I've got a portable
transponder snail in my butt pocket.
Could you get it?
Blend, what's keeping you? You're late!
Papa is angry. Hurry back home.
Hey! Can you hear me, Blend?
Answer me!
The Phoenix Pirates have Blend!
If you mess with us, he's dead!
Jiro, you...!
I take back what I said!
What?!
Big Brother is coming.
Your brother?
You've taken your tough act too far!
You've just bought everyone
tickets to the afterlife!
What do you mean we're going to the afterlife?!
Wha--?!
I-I won't tolerate any funny business.
Hey, dude! Why'd you start glowing?
Wow! What's he doing?
Just wait and see!
What is that?
Huh? When'd you break free?
He's really fast!
That can't be right!
What's going on?
Did you use a clone technique?
How dare you capture my darling little brother?
Little Brother!
Big Brother!
It's been a while, but...
...let's show them our combination plays!
Awesome! How did you do that just now?!
We have the ability to manipulate magnetism!
We can pull ourselves together or apart at will!
And the magnetic powers that link us
can instantly separate us by the
distance of our measurable feelings.
Such is our...
...brotherly love!
Hey! Did you eat a Devil Fruit?
Why are we drawn to each other?
Because we are...
...twins!
Wow! Twins are awesome!
No, there is definitely
something fishy about them!
Blend, which one is our prey for today?
For starters, that guy is Puzzle the Phoenix.
He has a 100-million-Berry bounty.
And that is Straw Hat Luffy
with a 300-million-Berry bounty.
Oh, so that's him.
And that's his cotton-candy-loving pet,
Chopper. He's worth 50 Berries.
Fifty?!
What is with that 50-Berry bounty?
What indeed, Big Brother?
Don't say that! 50 Berries says a whole lot!
Whatever. Moving on.
Do you think you can
escape our combination plays?
Hey!
Straw Hat!
Look over here!
Don't, Luffy! Behind you!
Behind me?
Repulsion!
Did he fall into the ocean?
He was nothing before us brothers!
Luffy!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
Big Brother!
Luffy!
Awesome!
Straw Hat...
Done already?
Campaccino!
What was that?
Is someone in here?
How long are you going to keep me waiting?
What happened to my birthday party?
Where's the flag?
Dang, it's hot in here! What's with this room?
Who're you?
What's this? You aren't Campaccino!
I have a special bottle I've been saving...
Would you like to join me?
What? Sure...
Hey, just make yourself at home!
Thanks!
The Family was sweet enough
to throw me a birthday party,
but then they took off mid-party
and haven't come back!
Yeah? Talk about a coincidence!
My friends vanished before I knew it.
I'm still looking for them.
You too, eh?
Oh, thanks!
Who knows where they went
or what they're doing?!
Seriously! Where'd they decide to go goof off?
Gum-Gum...
...Bell!
Doctor!
I'm fine!
Guys, if you don't give back our flag,
I'm gonna kick your butts for real!
Blend, Papa is getting hot with rage!
We need to finish this up fast.
He's a Devil Fruit power holder!
If we can drop him in the ocean, he's finished!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Leap!
Fusion!
Luffy!
Captain!
It's no good! He's too far!
There is no way I'm gonna fall in!
Magnetic Repulsion!
Phew, that was close!
Straw Hat!
You cannot hope to escape from us!
You really are persistent!
Gum-Gum... Twin Pistol!
Repulsion!
I'm on my way, Luffy!
Wh-What was that?
Jiro, look out!
Jiro!
Are you all right?
Captain...!
Hey, take the ship back! Please go after Luffy!
We can't do that!
You can't tell a ship where
to go here in the Arctic Path.
Luffy...
We should just ignore anyone
who doesn't come back!
Knowing them, I bet they're having fun
slipping and sliding on the ice. Sheesh!
Well? What do you think?
That collection is my pride and joy.
Your collection?
Right! They're the flags of all
the pirates I've hunted down.
Impressive, isn't it?
You've got a disgusting hobby.
Hey, don't be so harsh!
Oh, it's here! It's here!
I'm sure you'll understand
once you feast your eyes on this.
Their total bounty exceeds 600 million Berries.
This Jolly Roger belongs to the Straw Hat Crew.
What do you think with your
120 million bounty, Roronoa Zoro?
Bastard...!
How the hell did you get that Jolly Roger?!
Wouldn't you agree it's
a rather nice Jolly Roger?
Jeez, it's cold!
So you're gonna lock us in here, huh?
All of the walls are made outta ice!
And it's so cold that I'm starting to get sleepy...
Don't fall asleep!
If you do, you'll turn into an ice cube!
Where did Robin and Zoro go?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Mansion in Chaos! An Enraged
Don and an Imprisoned Crew"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!