Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter and fight fierce
battles against other tough
contenders from the New World.
Come after me, Doflamingo!
What? Is he gonna go across the bridge?
No! Idiots!
I get it.
Wait, Doflamingo!
They have nothing to do with this!
It's over, Law!
--Doflamingo is flying towards us!
--What?!
Young Master-sama!
What is this?! A nightmare?!
Are we gonna get killed?!
No!
Watch this, Law!
I'll viciously slay your allies
right before your eyes!
Don't!
Tra-guy, help...
Hey!
My friends are crying in fear!
Leave them alone!
Sanji!
Here comes quite a tough one.
"A Big Clash!
Sanji vs. Doflamingo!"
You're the "Black Foot" of
the Straw Hats, aren't you?
Diable Jambe...
...Premiere Hachis Hash!
Pentachromatic Strings!
--Sanji-san!
--What did Doflamingo do?!
Save your friends if you can.
--Doflamingo is coming this way!
--You've got to be kidding!
Young Master-sama!
--Stay away from us!
--Go away!
No!
Diable Jambe...
...Poele a Frire...
...Spectre!
It's powerful! He's quite strong!
All right, Sanji!
Go!
Wh-What happened? I can't move!
Oh? Sanji-san got frozen in mid air!
He's been grappled
by the Young Master's power!
Doflamingo's power?!
Black Foot is like a bug caught
in a spider's web now!
All he can do is wait for death!
What?!
Look!
--What is it?!
--A whip?!
Don't do anything! Just run!
Use Coup de Burst to get out of here!
We can't do that!
Overheat!
Sanji!
Get away, Sanji-kun!
Shambles!
Room!
Law, eh?
DRESSROSA
Run!
It's Tra-guy! He saved Sanji!
Sorry. I made a mistake!
Let's get on the ship!
Tra-guy-san!
Sanji!
Damn! I'm on the ship again!
Caesar!
Oh, Giolla! Help me!
I'm being held captive, too!
I dropped my guard.
Sanji-kun!
Nami-san!
No! Doflamingo's coming again!
Damn!
Black Foot-ya!
How's the plan to destroy
the factory going?
We found out where it is
but Franky said it's gonna
be harder than we thought.
How's my father?! And Kanjuro?!
San-goro!
How are they doing?!
Momonosuke.
The samurai is heading to the factory.
He'll be alright once everything is over.
So we need more time.
Hey, you!
Is that my heart?!
Were you keeping it in the cabin?!
This is mine.
I had your heart with me.
Damn!
Y-You had it in your body the whole time!
Everyone!
I want you to take him
and head for Zou!
Zou?
I gave you the Vivre Card
that leads you to the island.
Is this a Vivre Card?
Yes. It'll point toward an island called Zou
that I talked about earlier.
Here it is.
Head for the island?!
What about Luffy-san and the others?!
The only thing left to do on this island is
destroy the factory.
We'll catch up with you guys soon.
No! We'll wait!
We can't set sail without our captain!
We're the Straw Hats!
What?!
The Navy ship is flying towards us!
How is that possible?!
It must be Fujitora.
Doflamingo is coming from that way!
The Navy ship is getting closer!
No!
You can wait here if you want
but don't let them take Caesar!
Fire!
Something's falling from the sky!
Meteorites?!
Room!
Tra-guy-kun, we "Spiral Hats" are
gonna leave now!
I agree!
Just go!
Hey, Law!
I realize we have
to carry Caesar as far as possible.
It's clear we have to leave here now.
But I thought Dressrosa was just a waypoint.
Our main purpose was killing Kaido
of the Four Emperors, wasn't it?
Aren't you getting too hung up
on Doflamingo?
Meteorites! Meteorites!
Takt!
Issho-san, they hit the bottom of our ship!
Oops, I hadn't thought about that.
Law-san is there, isn't he?
Why don't you stop eating?!
What's the matter?
Let's get back to Dressrosa now.
What?!
The tide of the war...
...will turn, it seems.
Tell them to turn around!
Yes, sir!
Everybody, ready?!
I'm ready!
I'm ready, Nami-san!
I won't let you get away!
The whip, again!
Joker! Help me!
Excess Whip String!
Nami-ya! Listen.
You have to sail where there are no clouds!
What?! Why?!
Doflamingo is a String-String Fruit eater!
He moves through the air
by attaching strings to clouds!
He can't follow you if there are no clouds!
Strings? I see!
Just go now!
Get ready for Coup de Burst!
Doflamingo, look!
Law, what do you think you're doing?!
Young Master-sama, don't worry about me!
Hey you!
I want to ask you something!
Hey, you on the second floor!
I'm talking to you! Say something!
Hey, can't you hear me?!
You, right there!
Hey!
I just met my hero - Luffy-senpai today
but now, Zoro-senpai is talking to me!
I can't stop crying from happiness!
He's acting strange.
I wonder who he is.
Hey, I don't know who you are
but can you tell us how to enter the Colosseum?
All the doors are closed!
Z-Zoro-senpai is asking me a question!
I'm so glad that I sailed out to the sea!
What is he talking about?
Seems like he got very excited.
Hey, calm down and listen. We're...
I wish you were there to see it, Zoro-senpai!
Luffy-senpai was awesome as hell!
I just heard him say Luffy-dono
and Zoro-dono's names now!
Why does he know who you two are?
I don't know.
Now, the battle royal here
in the Corrida Colosseum!
Only one winner from Block D can
move to the finals!
They are all fighting intensely
to get that one spot!
The way she moves...
I don't think she's just another gladiator.
But why?
Why doesn't she make an
attack even passing up
some critical chances?
What is she doing?!
She's at the edge of the ring!
You'd better worry about yourself
before you worry about someone else!
Rebecca will be fine.
Go get them!
Hey, stop backing up!
You're at the edge now!
All right! Stay at it!
It's not all right!
Well, you'll see.
Prepare for death, you little tramp!
Go to hell, Rebecca!
Just finish her off!
Drop dead!
See?
That's my girl, Rebecca!
What?
What did she just do?
Yeah, we barely outran
the Navy and Doflamingo.
We're gonna head for Zou.
Huh? No, wait, Sanji!
Are you gonna leave us?!
Sorry.
Get through somehow and meet us there.
What?!
I'm ready to get away
as soon as I have a chance!
You can't do that to me!
Sorry.
Sanji, we'll be alright!
You can go to Zou (elephant)
or Giraffe or wherever!
I'm gonna destroy the factory for sure!
What are Luffy and Law doing?
Zoro and Kin'emon went
to tell Luffy what's going on.
Law is...
What's the point in letting half
of the Straw Hats get away?
The other half is in Dressrosa.
If I take them as hostages,
they'll come back
right away to return Caesar to me.
I thought that you knew
there are quite a few people...
...who underestimated them like that
and got burned.
I'm afraid that I have to break up my alliance
with the Straw Hats now.
When I joined forces with them,
my only purpose was to use them
to stop the manufacture of SMILEs.
Even if I can't kill you right now,
Kaido will kill you sooner or later
once you lose all the SMILEs.
I see.
So you're gonna sacrifice
yourself to kill me.
I want to see how the world
falls into a mess after you die,
but more importantly, I want to make
you pay for what you did 13 years ago.
Joker!