Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Luffy was ejected from
the Sabaody Archipelago
by Bartholomew Kuma, a Warlord of the Sea.
He landed in the female-only
empire of Amazon Lily!
"Everyone Falls in Love!
Pirate Empress Hancock"
Sorry I can't pay you back for
everything you've done for me.
Well, I should be going now!
Men are so mysterious.
Their arms stretch, they suddenly grow fat,
their chests are flat,
and between their legs they have...
Hate to ask for help again,
but could you take these off?
Your family jewels?!
No! I mean these!
I'm going to look for my friends now!
But they'll laugh if they
see me dressed like this!
I think it looks very nice on you...
There.
Thanks!
Hating frills...
Men really are strange creatures.
Well, yeah, I guess so.
Thanks for taking it off!
Well, bye!
I'll never feel relaxed
until I find my friends!
You certainly are hasty...
As long as the others are still alive
like I am, that's all that matters.
As long as they're alive,
I can keep fighting again and again!
I'm gonna surpass all of those guys!
Alright! I'm gonna walk on my hands
all the way to Sabaody Archipelago!
That'll make me stronger!
Could you give me a ship?
You really are hasty...
You don't have any ships?!
This is a Calm Belt?!
Yes. This maiden island is surrounded
by a giant Sea King den known as a Calm Belt.
Which is why sailors never dare come near.
Castaways will sometimes
miraculously drift here,
but most of the time only as corpses.
But you said there's a pirate group here!
The Snake Princess's pirate ship, the Yuda,
is pulled by vicious, poisonous sea snakes,
so Sea Kings can't attack it.
It's the only ship on Amazon Lily!
Now what do I do?
There's no wind...
Should I build a raft and
paddle all the way there?
That's ridiculous!
Okay! I'm gonna build a raft
and paddle all the way there!
That's what you just thought up!
It's done!
That's terrible! It's already about to break!
No way! I thought he was a pirate!
I had no obligation to save you!
Are all men unable to swim,
even if they're pirates?
That was close!
Darn it!
If only Franky were here!
I dunno what to do!
I'm the one who doesn't know what to do!
You could've at least escaped
to somewhere far away...
If we keep this up,
I'll only grow attached to you!
Whoa, now! Stop!
What're you doing?!
Oh, yeah! These arrows!
They were strong enough
to destroy stone walls
when I was being chased earlier!
They don't seem like
special arrows, though...
What are you talking about?
The arrows possess "Haki"!
Their strength is only natural!
Haki? What's that?!
There she is!
Margaret is all right!
Everyone!
The man is with her! Kill him!
Uh oh!
Halt!
Stop!
Margaret! Are you alright?!
We need to hurry and finish the man off!
The Snake Princess has returned!
You have real guts to lay anchor in
the middle of monster-infested waters.
Yes. We were attacked
only moments ago, in fact!
The Sea Prism Stone in this warship
may conceal our presence,
but staying anchored here for so long
is bound to attract attention visually.
It's not easy,
but the agreement between
the Kuja and the government
forbids us from getting any closer
than three kilometers from your island.
Consequently, we're forced to wait
in the middle of the monsters' den.
Have you heard?
They say the Kuja are specters
that turn people to stone!
Get real!
Did you kill that Sea King?
Sea Kings are hardly rare in the Grand Line,
but in the Calm Belts,
they're certainly larger...
no, monstrous.
Any sign of the Kuja ship?!
Not yet, Vice-Admiral!
There are no approaching ships at all!
How long is she going to keep us waiting?!
Or has the Kuja empress decided to...?!
S-Sea King!
Fire! Fire!
Impossible! Not even cannons have an effect?!
The ship'll be smashed to pieces
if we don't do something!
What do we do?!
There's no way to defend against it!
Is it planning to eat the entire ship?!
To think the very first to greet us
is this beast and not the Kuja...!
That's...
...the vice-admiral!
Allowing an entire warship
to be food for a Sea King
would belittle the name of justice!
Those cuts...
Did you slice it from inside its stomach?
I have not come to hunt Sea Kings.
I would like to finish my business here
and leave these waters quickly.
It looks like you have some skill.
I was growing tired of waiting!
At last you've returned, Kuja Pirates!
I am Vice-Admiral Momonga
of Navy Headquarters!
Warlord of the Sea and
Pirate Empress Boa Hancock!
Show yourself! I've come for you!
So sorry, but the
Snake Princess isn't coming out.
She's sent many replies now!
That's men for you!
Such unsophisticated creatures!
I haven't seen a live man in a long time!
Pirates and merchants always escape
by boat when they see the Kuja flag!
Stop. That's a crude laugh.
We have received her replies of,
"I will follow your orders
to convene at once."
But she shows no indication
of coming whatsoever!
This morning's newspaper.
A place and date has been decided
for the public execution
of Portgas D. Ace, 2nd Division
Commander of the Whitebeard Pirates!
There is no turning back now!
The World Government has issued strict orders
forcing the Seven Warlords
of the Sea to assemble!
Refuse and the agreement is off!
Your title of Warlord of
the Sea will be revoked!
Think about what that would mean!
Until now, the World Government
has allowed you to do as you wish,
but without the title, you would be
nothing more than ordinary pirates,
and therefore adversaries of the
World Government and the navy!
Do you hear that, Boa Hancock?!
Who placed a kitten...
...in my path?!
M-My deepest apologies!
I'm the one responsible!
Be more careful.
Y-Yes!
S-Stop that!
So you've come out, Boa Hancock!
Don't let your guard down, men!
He's right!
We're dealing with the boss
of a bunch of specters!
There's no telling how terrifying she is!
Don't let your guard--!
Th-That's the Pirate Empress?!
She's the definition of the most
beautiful woman in the world!
Halt, man!
These girls are terrifying!
Nami's much better by far!
Or not...!
One direct hit from these
arrows and I'm a goner!
Alright!
Is that man a gibbon?!
Damn! We lost him!
We cannot have a living man
in this land whatsoever!
We have to find him and kill him
as quickly as possible!
Let's split up and search!
All right! Find him and
kill him, without fail!
Understood!
Is it a good idea to be here?
This is where I ran from earlier...
No other choice!
This is no time for that!
There he is!
Uh oh!
I won't miss this time!
Did you get him?!
Not yet! He fell into the jungle!
"Amazon Lily Empress,
Captain of the Kuja Pirates Warlord of the Sea –
‘Empress’ Boa Hancock"
So you've finally come for me...
What meddlesome people.
"Youngest of the Gorgon Sisters –
Boa Marigold"
My recent replies were lies.
"Second of the Gorgon Sisters –
Boa Sandersonia"
I will not go to war!
But...
I want you to let me keep
my title of Warlord of the Sea.
And...
I also want all of
the cargo on your ship.
What nonsense is this?!
You're not a selfish little child!
Do you honestly think we'll accept
such outrageous demands?!
Hurry and haul it over!
What a beautiful woman!
I'll give her anything!
Why are you hauling our cargo?!
Come to your senses!
Oh no! I blindly listened to what she said!
Portgas D. Ace's public execution
is in exactly one week from today!
Fire Fist Ace's life will be ended
in the town square of Marineford,
where Navy Headquarters stands!
In other words, Whitebeard will
make a move within the next week
to rescue Ace!
Navy Headquarters, led by three admirals,
is prepared to counter Whitebeard
with full military force!
Will you lose the title of Warlord,
or accept the orders to assemble?!
Decide now!
Time is nearly up!
I like the title of Warlord.
I don't want it taken away.
But I hate the World Government.
I don't want to obey its orders.
How does this sound?
The marines who came to get me
had a mysterious accident on the sea
and were wiped out when
they all turned to stone?
She's planning to do something!
Don't let your guard down!
I've heard about this before!
A ship was attacked by the Kuja pirate ship,
and when it was discovered later,
only strange statues were found onboard!
H-Hey! Look at that!
Wh-What are those?!
S-Strange statues?!
I already told you!
Your childish selfishness
will not be allowed!
Big Sis has a terrible personality.
But she gets everything she wants.
Yes. There is a reason for that.
Do you know why that is?
Because no matter what I do...
...even if I kick a kitten...
...even if I pull your ears off...
...or even if I kill someone,
everyone in the world would forgive me.
The reason for that is, yes...
...because I'm beautiful!
Because I'm beautiful!
Snake Princess!
We'll let you do anything!
After all, you're beautiful!
Stop that, all of you!
For being charmed by me,
your guilty consciences...
...will turn your bodies solid!
Love-Love Beam!
Hanco--!
I'd expect no less from
a navy vice-admiral...
I see.
You used pain to block out the evil thoughts.
You've much experience, indeed.
However...
I wish I could say the same about your men.
Fools...!
It looks like you're the only one left now.
One and zero are not the same!
We will now return to the
peaceful Amazon Lily!
Yes, Snake Princess!
Boa Hancock!
I will wait here as long as I can!
I will not return empty-handed!
If you do not reappear in two days' time...
...the agreement is off!
Do as you wish.
Hoping to borrow a ship,
Luffy makes his way into the Kuja Castle,
but in his rush, he bursts in on
Hancock as she's taking a bath.
As he sees Hancock's form through the steam,
something on her back catches Luffy's eye...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Secret Hidden on the Backs --
Luffy and the Snake Princess Meet"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!