Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
gooru mada tooku
We're still far from our goal
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
And while each member of the Straw Hats is
fighting the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law are heading for the Royal Palace
to take down Doflamingo.
I see no end to this.
I'm gonna take out all of them!
Stop messing with Straw Hat Luffy!
You dumbshits!
Rah-Rah-Rah-Rampage!
I found a shortcut to
reach the higher levels.
What? Really?!
See? There's a shortcut!
Now, go ahead, Straw Hat.
We'll guard the entrance!
Alright, thanks!
Moocy, let's go!
What?!
Ring, ring, ring...
--Luffy. It's me.
--Robin!
Viola found the key to Tra-guy-kun's cuffs!
Oh yeah?!
Let's meet up at the Sunflower Field
on the fourth level!
Stop! He's soaking in the water!
What?! It's a dead end!
Go back! Hurry!
Moocy! Don't panic!
This is just a slanted water well.
There is no such shortcut in here.
You!
Doflamingo!
"A Great Escape!
Luffy's Tide-turning Elephant Gun!"
Doflamingo!
You weaklings are working together...
Looks like you're gonna get those
handcuffs off soon, aren't you, Law?
Why the hell are you here?!
I came to save you.
How could you fall into such a stupid trap?
That crap about a shortcut!
Straw Hat!
Bullet String!
Moocy!
Give him up! Straw Hat-ya!
Moocy...
You have no sense of crisis...
Stay... with me... Moocy...
So cheesy!
Anyone could kill you guys like this.
There are some idiots who
are saying they'll kill me,
rampaging out there...
It's amazing how you found
people who side with you
under these circumstances.
I've been giving you due respect for
that special quality of yours
since the War of the Best.
But...
...you're actually this dumb!
Why did you choose him, Law?
You used to be a more promising man.
Even when you were a kid,
you were more ruthless
and more cunning!
Am I right?!
Who made you... into such a coward?
Shut up!
I'm not willing to become like you!
I've been... saved!
By my brother Corazon, you mean?
If you haven't become a coward,
why do you want to die in vain...
...alongside this dumbshit?
Stop! Don't hurt Straw Hat-san!
Get your hands off of him!
--What the hell is this?!
--What's wrong with his body?!
It's his clone as I thought.
Clone?
That's a string puppet.
You guys...
--Straw Hat-san!
--Glad that you're safe!
In any case, pull out Straw Hat-san!
Yeah!
Are you okay?! Straw Hat-san?!
Don't do it!
Doflamingo!
The guy with a hundred-million berry prize...
I found him!
If I can kill him, I'd be invited
to join the Doflamingo Family...
That's...!
D-Damn!
What're you doing, old man?!
Let go of it!
You're gonna kill Kyros...
I'm not gonna let a foreign pirate
do such a thing!
You fool!
You stupid old geezer!
How dare you bother me!
I'm sorry. You saved my life, elderly man.
Thank you!
I-I beg you!
S-Stay still, don't resist and...
...let me capture you!
I'm sorry but I can't do that!
Stay away!
You people are peaceful in nature
and don't wish to fight...
But Doflamingo forced you to do such a thing!
And I have to take him down for it!
I'm sorry!
You saved me... Thank you!
No, no, no, no...
Now, is that his lower body?!
What's going on with that?!
All in all, we brought down
the big game, didn't we?!
Idiot!
I told you before. That's a fake!
He took the trouble to
send the string puppet...
To tease us?
He said he came to save us.
Oh yeah!
Actually, that Kelly Funk guy from earlier...
That bastard was fooling us!
What a simple-minded fool...
He fell into our trap completely.
We learned that and
when we tried to stop him...
We gotta do something!
Abdullah, can you get up?
What?!
That infamous assassin Kelly got
taken out in a split second...
If it's true,
it's like we were really saved by that jerk!
He's mocking us!
What's going on out there?!
How are Cabbage and the others?!
We're totally falling behind...
I bet everybody else reached the second level
by now!
Damn! I thought we could take a shorter route
to the Sunflower Field!
We gotta go back! Hurry up!
No...
Let's go for it... A shorter route!
What're you...
If there's no shortcut here,
I'll have to make one!
What?!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 1
What the...?!
I guess everybody else is heading to
the second level already.
Gotta hurry up.
W-Wait a minute!
What are you up to, Straw Hat-san?!
Straw Hat?
Gum-Gum...
Ah! There's not a single
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 2
dropout on the first level!
It's impossible!
Our subordinates can't match them-in!
Straw Hat and his group aren't here yet.
Let's take them out one by one.
Sounds like fun!
What's wrong, Farul?!
What the...
What's going on?!
Something's coming!
Elephant Gun!!
What's that?!
A fist?
Oh my...!
I see. That's smart!
Only Garp's grandson could do it!
Straw Hat did it, didn't he?
Look out!
Straw Hat!
I like this confusion!
Chin Jao and the others are
heading to the third level!
Stop them!
What was that explosion?!
--Oh no!
--There'll be another one!
They don't even know what it is!
How could they be freaked out by it!
Guys! Don't lose sight of the enemies!
I need to rush!
Alright! Let's go, Tra-guy!
He really made a shortcut!
You're too reckless!
Guys!
Take care of Moocy, okay?!
Yes, sir!
Alright! Let's go!
This big hole...
What the... hell is going on...
What's this?!
Gum-Gum...
...Rocket!
It's Straw Hat!
Alright! I caught up with
them on the second level!
Straw Hat!
Trafalgar Law!
--Let's get going! Straw Hat-ya!
--Yeah!
Wait for me, Mingo!
Oh damn!
Dragon Claw Fist! Dragon...
...Claw!
What a fight!
Oh yeah. This smoke doesn't
slow you down at all!
I guess not.
That's what I'd expect from
No.2 of the Revolutionary Army,
leader of the next generation.
Your attacks are quite sharp.
You don't mean that.
IN FRONT OF THE SMILE FACTORY
Fraland!
Tontattas?!
Listen to me, Fraland!
We have an idea to unlock the door
to the Factory!
What?! Really?!
Yes!
So please keep Señor busy like that!
I got it!
Count on me!
IN THE TOWN
Look! There are two people with a prize
of a hundred-million!
Shoot!
Oh no! They found us!
You bastards!
What are you gonna do if
you hit Robin-senpai?!
Don't worry!
I'm gonna put up a barrier now!
Barrier it is!
Dammit!
I can't cross my fingers like this!
Shoot them down!
Whoa! Watch out!
You assholes! Don't push your luck!
When it comes to this,
I'm gonna do the same thing
that I did at the Colosseum!
Hey, wait! What is he doing?!
What?! Don't tell me...
he's gonna do it!
Take this, fools!
Humph! What a bunch of cowards!
THE PLATEAU - LOCATION OF
THE ROYAL PALACE - LEVEL 4
THE SUNFLOWER FIELD
You'll promote me to executive of the Family
if I win the competition?!
Yeah.
You can do it.
He told me to finish you off here.
That's Young Master-sama's order.
I can't go on... like this!
Hey hey, Doffy!
Did you send String-Joker off somewhere?
Yes...
I wanted to deliver something
but I guess he doesn't need it.
Deliver something?
You guys...
Do you remember the day we met Law
for the first time?
He was nuts!
Even his eyes were crazy...
Yeah, yeah!
He looked like me when I was a kid.
I sensed he would become my
right-hand man in 10 years or so.
It's a shame that I will have to kill him
with my own hands.
We have an intruder!
Don't touch him!
He has explosives strapped to his body!
Hey! Who the hell is this kid?!
Who lets him in?!
Let me join your pirate group.
I wanna destroy everything that I see!
Towns, houses, people...
I wanna destroy them all!
I...
...grew up in the White Town - Flevance.
It's not so long...
...before I die.
Mingo!
The Executives of the Doflamingo
Family show themselves
before Luffy and the others
and a back-and-forth, full-scale
fierce fight begins!
When it seems their way to
the Royal Palace has been blocked up,
the disorganized group of debtors finally
proves their real worth!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A United Front! Luffy's
Breakthrough to the Victory!”
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!