Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
go-in Go
Force it and go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a
pirate alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will get the
Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize
- and won the first round.
Meanwhile, Lightning Soldier and the
Tontatta Tribe are having a rally underneath Dressrosa.
"Operation Dressrosa SOP"!
One of Doflamingo's subordinates
turned us into toys.
We have to knock out
this Hobby-Hobby Fruit eater!
--Hobby-Hobby Fruit?
--You can imagine what will happen then.
Oh! It will break the spell?!
That's right!
All the toys in Dressrosa will change back into
their human forms at once!
So if we can knock her out,
all the toys can change back?!
That's right!
We'll frighten her out of her wits
and make her pass out!
And that's Operation...
Sugar!
Oversurprised!
Panic!
Y-You are...
It's been a while!
I thought he died!
"Operation SOP Starts!
Usoland Charges Forth!"
Ouch!
Are you still crying?!
Because...
I've never seen Luffy-dono crying like that.
He must be very happy to see that person alive.
Uh-huh, uh-huh!
I'm asking you! Who is that person?!
M-My brother!
Brother?!
What?! Luffy-dono has a brother?!
I thought your brother was "Fire Fist" Ace!
Are you saying he is alive?!
It brings back memories!
Answer my question!
When we become pirates,
we might not be on the same ship
but our brotherhood will always
be with us!
Wherever you are, whatever you do,
we'll always be bonded together!
So from now on,
we're brothers!
Ace was right!
We were always bonded together as brothers!
I said "Who is that"?!
THE KING RIKU ARMY HEADQUARTERS
Everybody! Are you ready?!
Yeah!
THE FLOWER FIELD
(THEIR PRESENT LOCATION)
We'll sneak into the port through the underground passage!
THE TRADE PORT
Our target is just one girl!
Sugar!
She's just a girl
but it's not gonna be easy!
We're gonna knock Sugar out
so all the toys in the country will change back to humans!
Yeah!
Free our captive Tontatta friends
and take Dressrosa back for King Riku!
Yeah!
We, Yellow Cub Squad, and...
We, Pink Bee Squad, will lead the way!
Let's go!
We're gonna go at high speed!
--It's finally starting.
--Yeah!
But this passage to the trade port is too...
...narrow!
Robiland and I can barely fit in.
What about me, then?
Fraland, why don't you take off your shoulders and arms?
Okay, let me take them off... I can't!
Hey, me-land can't go in there!
We weren't expecting big humans to use it when we made it.
You have to enter from the Toy House!
The Toy House is
located at the base of the plateau that the palace is on.
That's where the toys go back every night.
Humans aren't allowed to go in.
You call it a "house" because the toys live?
No, they just call it a "house."
There are no beds to sleep in, or anything.
Inside, there is only a passage into the ground.
A passage?
Every night, the toys go down underground
through the passage and work all night.
What?!
Doesn't that mean the toys in the town
are always exhausted?
Yes, indeed.
As are, the Tontatta people...
...who are forced to work!
I can't believe it! It's horrible!
A-Anyway, through that place,
Fraland can go down to the SMILE factory, right?
Yes. There are four entrances in four directions.
However, all the entrances are tightly guarded!
It's more exciting that way!
If I have to go there anyway,
I'll create havoc!
--What?
--Wh-Why do you wanna do that?
--Because it's better for you.
--What do you mean?
While I'm drawing their attention,
finish your business with Sugar.
Hm? Who is that?
Swim briefs?!
What's wrong with his head?!
--Is it a weapon?
--Or is he just an idiot?
Oh! He's got two dimples on his chin!
There's no mistaking it!
He is Cyborg Franky of the Straw Hats!
--What?!
--You sure?!
Senor!
Oh, Senor! If you jam a tomato in your mouth  like that,
it's gonna be messy around there!
H-He's so...
...hard-boiled!
Stop climbing all over me, you little tramps!
SENOR PINK - AN EXECUTIVE
THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY (THE DIAMANTE ARMY)
Go hang out with younger guys!
Don't say that, Senor!
Don't give me the cold shoulder, Senor!
I'm not into...
...fledglings.
Oh! Senor!
--Don't leave me, Senor!
--Senor!
Senor!
Who is that pervert?
You have no right to say that!
This is the east entrance of the Toy House!
The enemy's here!
You have to let me in!
Weapons Left!
S-Shoot him!
He's one of the Straw Hats -
Cyborg Franky!
Coup de...
...Vent!
See?
Those idiots are causing trouble.
I thought it's the Navy's duty to
save countries affiliated
with the World Government.
Excuse me for a while.
They've started, huh?
They're attacking the Toy House.
Don't worry!
The Straw Hats are going
for the SMILE factory.
If they make it this far, then...
Then?
Let's turn them all into toys, okay?
Uh-huh.
Nobody knows.
Nobody knows your existence, right?
I guess.
THE UNDERGROUND PASSAGE
We're almost there at the trade port!
I feel bad.
You don't need to.
Helping our hero - Usoland is...
Our Honor!
Well...
Commander! Fraland started wreaking havoc at the Toy House!
Okay!
If I have to go there anyway,
I'll create havoc!
Is he gonna be okay?
Don't worry! He's a super cyborg!
But I just received notice that four of the executives
of the Family, are on guard of the Toy House!
E-Executives?!
They're the formidable Diamante Army!
A group of fighters!
Are they... pretty strong?
Their winning percentage in fighting events is 100%.
They're the big stars of the Colosseum!
100%?
That means they've never lost!
That's right! Which means...
...nobody knows
how strong they really are!
Good! Formidable as he is, Franky is unaware
that Senor is coming from behind!
What?!
Are you blind?
Huh?! How did you emerge
from the ground like that?!
Strong Right!
Why did he show up in front of the enemy voluntarily?!
Senor!
Why did I show up in front of the enemy?
The only thing that a man does
behind someone's back is...
...undress a woman.
Ah, Senor! So hard-boiled!
However,
a man stands in front of someone...
...only when he steals a kiss
from a woman.
Oh, I'm fainting...
Senor! You're the man!
You guys are super stupid, aren't you? Huh?
What kind of ability is that?!
How many key figures are there
in the Family, Leo?
10 executives currently lead 2000 subordinates
all over the country now.
And 3 top executives lead them,
each with their own unique army.
First, the Trebol Army
THE TREBOL ARMY
(A TEAM OF MEMBERS WITH SPECIAL ABILITIES)
has members with special abilities.
Sugar!
SUGAR
Violet!
VIOLET
Giolla!
GIOLLA
Next, the Diamante Army!
THE DIAMANTE ARMY (A GROUP OF FIGHTERS)
A group of fighters!
Lao G.!
LAO G.
Machvise!
MACHVISE
Senor Pink!
SENOR PINK
Dellinger!
DELLINGER
The last one is the Pica Army!
THE PICA ARMY (A COMMANDO UNIT)
A commando unit!
Gladius!
GLADIUS
Buffalo! Baby 5!
BUFFALO
BABY 5
We've seen Buffalo and Baby 5!
We know there are two others overseas.
VERGO - A TOP EXECUTIVE
A top executive - Vergo!
And an executive - Monet!
MONET - AN EXECUTIVE
Our target is Sugar, right?
Of the team of members with special abilities?
Uh-huh! That's right.
Then, we don't have to face the group of fighters!
Good luck, Franky!
But they're all pretty strong!
What?!
Give me a break!
Meadows is defeated!
Rebecca is taking down Block D's potential winners one by one!
She, and Agilia who is backing her up,
are really pissing off the crowd!
Now, who's gonna knock out Rebecca?!
Oh?! Can he stop her?!
Suleiman the Beheader!
Or are we gonna see Rebecca's Back-to-the-Water Dance again?!
Rebecca!
Whoa! He fended off
her Back-to-the-Water Dance!
Here we are!
I'm sorry, Usoland!
--Thank you.
--No, no, no.
We're here! This is the underground world
where the trade port and the factory are.
Yeah?
It's kind of noisy here.
We're gonna head for the palace!
I'm gonna leave the other task up to you!
Yes, I got it!
Wait for me, Doflamingo!
I'll take you down even if it means death!
Is it from above ground?
Hey, who dropped the box?!
A toy's been buried under it.
I-I'm sorry!
I'll keep working,
just let me see my family!
Idiot! Those who can't meet their quota will get scrapped!
Take him!
W-Wait! I can still work!
Help!
Usopp.
Robin, I just...
Look.
What are you doing?!
If you don't like it, the deal is off!
You jerk! You're taking advantage of my weakness!
If only Joker weren't on your side...
What the hell is this?!
It's a massive port town!