Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hey, is it true that a Navy ship came?
What? A Navy ship did?
Yeah, I heard that it was
anchored here when day broke.
Why would the Navy come...
...to such a remote island?
But no one has seen any marines on it.
What the heck?
Not even a single person can be found.
It's like a ghost ship.
That's ridiculous.
--Professor!
--Professor Clover!
Did something happen?
I hope it's nothing to worry about,
but a Navy ship is anchored at the seashore!
They might be here for an investigation.
We should be cautious, just in case!
Let the scholars know.
The raft is finished!
Then... you're leaving already?
What's wrong? You've got
"I'm lonely" written all over your face.
Come to think of it, I was thinking
of attaching a flag or something.
So I'll stay here a little longer.
To sea? So you wanna set out to sea, too?
Yep.
My mom has been busy with her
archaeological research all this time.
But when she comes back
to this island next time,
I'm going to ask her to take me with her to sea.
So I studied hard and I was finally
able to become an archaeologist.
An archaeologist? When you're still so small?
Yep.
But... you don't even remember
your mom's face, right?
Right... but she's still my mom.
I wanna see her.
--Say, Saul...
--Hm?
Do you know that the world has a blank history
of 100 years that no one knows about?
Yeah. It's called the "Blank Century."
I'm curious about it, but the Government
prohibits people from investigating, so...
Yeah. I heard that my mom is traveling
around the world investigating it.
But don't tell anyone about it,
since it's actually a crime.
What?!
C-Could it mean that she's traveling in
search of those stones called Poneglyphs?
So you know about Poneglyphs?
Of course I do! But don't talk
about it in front of people, okay?!
Not to mention, about your
mom traveling in search of... Ah!
What's wrong?
Robin... Do you know your mom's name?
Olvia.
It's Nico Olvia.
Saul?!
Robin is Olvia's daughter...!
Then... could this place be...
an island called Ohara?!
--Yeah.
--Ahh! This is terrible! Oh, no!
So I drifted to Ohara?!
This is no time to be sitting around talking!
--Robin!
--What is it?
This might shock you, but listen to me carefully!
Navy battleships should be
headed to Ohara right now.
Navy? Why?
In order to eliminate the scholars on this island!
Eliminate them?
Don't tell...
--That's a lie...
--Don't tell the Government you're a scholar!
--That's a lie...!
--Got that?!
That's a lie!
It's true! I'd never lie to you!
Go to town now and see if anything
strange has been happening!
It's possible your mom might be back, too!
What?!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Fated Mother and Daughter!
The Mother's Name Is Olvia!"
It's been a while, everyone.
--Olvia...
--Olvia-san...!
So it was you who came on that Navy ship!
We thought you had been caught by the Navy...
I'm sorry that I came back bearing bad news.
But what I just said is true.
So the government has finally
set its sights on Ohara?
Did you read the newspaper?
The Poneglyph search team that set off
from Ohara six years ago was annihilated.
All of them except for me...
A total of 33 members...
I was also temporarily captured.
The government evaluated
my fellow scholars' belongings
and figured out that we came from Ohara.
This is inexcusable! To think that this
island is now in danger because of us!
Stop it! It's no one's fault!
Those who set out to sea and those
who stayed here--we're all one team!
It was you guys who experienced a terrible time.
We put you through a terrible ordeal.
Professor...
Ohara is a place where talented
scholars from all around the world
gather and continue to study history.
The Government has been
considering us a threat.
They must be thinking that they
finally found something on us.
They're not gonna pass up this opportunity.
Yes, but we were able to get
that information without delay!
In the end, everyone in Ohara who
claims to be a scholar will be eliminated!
So, everyone, get out of Ohara immediately!
Yeah... This time, we probably won't
be able to slip past their investigation
like we usually do...
...if they are trying to kill us.
Then, hurry up and...
But you know, Olvia...
I can't run away leaving this
treasure of mankind behind.
You should know that.
We feel the same way, Olvia.
You guys...
We don't know what the Government is up to.
But if we run, the precious history
that exists here won't be protected.
We'll try whatever we can,
just like we always have.
More importantly...
...there must be something
weighing on your mind.
But I can't see her.
Make up your mind, Olvia! Are you
gonna come aboard the ship or not?
If you have a lingering attachment
to your child, don't come with us.
If this is about your husband's
unfinished business, we will...
No! I'll come with you!
I'm a scholar from Ohara. I can't
abandon our predecessors' will!
I'm sorry, Robin.
I'll solve all the mysteries
and come back for sure!
Mommy... Where's Mommy?
Where did Mommy go?
Your mom set out to sea for work.
You'll stay here with us for a while.
You're noisy! Be quiet or I'll hit you!
Hey, stop it. She's only two.
Our daughter is two, too.
I don't care whether she's your
big sister's child or whatever--
how dare you take in such a burden?!
Wow...
Who's there?! Don't move!
U-Um... I... Um...
I'm sorry!
When you wanna read books, just let me know.
But I don't have money, so...
You don't have to pay.
You can read them all for free.
--Free?
--Yeah, since this is the best library in the world.
--The best one in the world?
--That's right.
By the way, you're Olvia's daughter, right?
Do you like books?
Yeah.
She looks just like you did
when you were a child.
And like you were at that age,
she's a rare genius, too.
So long as I know she's okay...
I've stepped into this line of work.
So I have to give up my attachment to her,
since I can't make her a "criminal's daughter."
Professor Clover! This time, a ship flying
the World Government's flag has come!
A Government ship has come
all the way to the West Blue...
It indeed seems quite serious.
Everyone, listen.
You guys and I are neither fellow
scholars nor acquaintances.
Keep that in mind... no matter what happens!
Wait, Olvia! What're you going to do?!
Hey, let the headquarters know
that we arrived at our destination.
Now, go, go, go! Keep on moving!
Geez... What a pain.
In any case, this work'd
better get me a promotion.
Hey, go get all the scholars and restrain them.
Yes, sir!
--What's going on?!
--A woman with a gun is running around!
For Heaven's sake! I'm sorry, Robin!
Vice Admiral Kuzan!
Hm? What is it?
We've been notified that CP9's
Chief Spandine has arrived in Ohara.
What? Is that something so important
that you had to wake me up to tell me?!
I-I'm sorry!
What's the matter, Robin?
Did my mom come here?
What're you saying? There's no way
that your mother is in Ohara, right?
I have to give up my attachment to her,
since I can't make her a "criminal's daughter."
What's this about all of a sudden?
Y-Yeah...
Oh, that's right! There's trouble!
I heard that Navy battleships
are coming to this island
in order to capture all
the scholars on this island.
Is there a disturbance or
something happening in town?
What?
It's not a battleship.
We heard that a Government
ship just came to this island.
It'll probably be a more
rigorous investigation than ever.
Listen, Robin. Even if the
Government people come,
don't tell them you're an
archaeologist no matter what.
Since you're small, no one will think
that you're a scholar. Got that?
Out of our way!
Stop what you're doing!
Get outside with your hands in the air!
You're being quite violent!
This Ohara lab is suspected of a
serious crime--deciphering Poneglyphs!
It requires a thorough search,
so all of you, go outside immediately!
Treat this place with care.
The value of everything in here
is beyond your imagination.
We don't have to listen to what you say!
Take them outside!
Yes, sir!
To all the townspeople!
We now suspect that this island's scholars
are devils who wish to destroy the world!
What?! Why?!
They're world-class scholars
and the pride of this island!
Consequently, we'll conduct a
large-scale search of the entire island!
During that time, those who have
nothing to do with archaeology
are expected to take an ID with them
and temporarily take refuge on the
evacuation ship at the west seashore!
An evacuation ship?!
Why are you going that far?
If it's the scholars' problem,
we have nothing to do with it.
So there should be no need
for us to leave the island.
It's our duty to pass that message to you.
No matter what happens later
to those who ignore our advice,
it's none of our concern.
--Leave town!
--Evacuate to the west seashore!
The World Government is up to something!
Ahhh! I got shot!
Th-This is it for me! I'm a goner, dammit!
Tell the top... that I want my son
to take over the position of chief!
Chief, please take a close look.
The bullet just went through
the sleeve of your jacket.
Oh, I see.
I won't miss next time.
Well, well... To think that a heinous
criminal who splendidly escaped
the Navy's prison is coincidentally
visiting this island... Nico Olvia.
You kept denying your connection to
the Ohara scholars, and yet, here you are.
It seems as if you're declaring
that this is your hometown...
That the scholars here are committing
the same crime that you guys were.
My being here alone isn't proof of those things.
I'm sure you have all sorts of
excuses ready. You're a smart woman.
But it doesn't matter anymore.
Your connection to Ohara
doesn't need to be proved.
If we dig through every nook and corner,
evidence of your research on
Poneglyphs will turn up in no time.
The Government thinks that
the probability of this is 100%.
Being able to capture you guys,
who were on the run for six long years,
just gave the Government a small push.
There are plenty of Poneglyph
researchers around the world.
Each time we captured one, we always
searched for their connection to Ohara.
Do you know why that is?
Don't tell me... In order to
use Ohara as a warning...?!
Exactly! If Ohara, the holy land
of archaeology, is crushed,
it'll send shockwaves throughout academia.
We can make the world realize
what happens to those who
research the "Blank Century."
Then the battleships from Headquarters
under standby order are...
Whoa... Just how much do you know?
That's right.
They're used to ensure that not
even a single criminal escapes.
But as a matter of form,
we need to verify the crime.
After all, we're not pirates.
So I came all the way here to conduct
a compulsory investigation on the island
and to send off those who have
nothing to do with the matter.
Yeah, I came all this way.
Take her down.
Hey, stop it! The books
here are a world treasure!
There's still someone here? Take him outside!
--Come!
--Dammit, you bastards!
There's gotta be a hidden room!
Make sure we find it!
This is terrible...
The battleships are already within sight!
Is this all of them?!
Now, gather all the scholars here!
Look. The scholars have been captured.
What on earth did they do?
They said that the goal of the scholars'
research is to destroy the world!
That can't be right.
Where's the evacuation ship?!
It's at the west seashore! Hurry!
Hurry up and go! Hurry to the west seashore!
Robin... It seems that
there's an evacuation ship.
We can no longer tell what
the Government will do.
You hurry up and go there, too.
No! Even if I get on that ship,
there won't be nice people!
I'll stay here with you guys!
--Robin...
--Just like you guys, I'm a--
Just go already!
Are you guys working hard?!
Thank you for taking the
trouble to come here, Chief!
Anyway, I didn't expect that a ferocious
animal would appear on this island.
I was nearly killed.
Olvia...!
Olvia-san...!
All right, listen carefully.
This woman is an escaped prisoner.
The group she belonged to
was recently eliminated for the crime
of deciphering the ancient texts.
However, we still don't know the ringleader.
Well, if you guys are connected to this woman,
it'll make matters quite simple.
How terrible of them to hurt a woman like that.
Robin, go to the evacuation ship. Hurry!
Robin...
Robin...!
You've...
...grown so much!
Olvia...
Wh-What have they done?!
Have they no respect for the library?!
To think that they'd take
such drastic measures...!
Whoa... They've made a big show.
--Click.
--Hello? Is this the Chief?!
Yeah, it's me.
We've found it!
There's a secret room in the basement,
and in there, we found a huge stone
that's probably a Poneglyph
and research documents clearly
discussing the ancient texts!
All right, well done!
Click.
Well, scholars of Ohara!
Your death sentence has now been decided!
It's indeed regrettable...
...that the world's best archaeologists
lose their lives together today.
See? What a letdown. That was all I had to do!
The only thing I have left to do is
report this to the Five Elder Stars.
Roger.
Professor! Are they really gonna
kill all of you?! That's a lie, right?
Why would they do that just because
you read the ancient texts...?!
Idiot! You brat! The purpose of their
research is to revive a powerful weapon
and commit mass murder!
That's not true! They aren't
thinking about anything like that!
Robin, stop it. It's pointless to discuss
the matter with an errand boy like him.
What'd you say?!
Is it really the weapon itself that
the Government is afraid of?
--Professor!
--Professor Clover!
It's connected, Chief.
Okay.
--This is good timing.
--Huh?!
Let me speak to the Five Elder Stars,
the world's leaders, before I die.
We, the scholars at Ohara, have continued
our research for a long time,
and although the research isn't completed yet,
we formed a hypothesis
about the "Blank Century."
So I'd like to report it to them.
What rubbish...
--Hey.
--Yes, sir.
Robin, get out of here immediately.
Listening to what I'm about to say is a crime.
Professor...
Hey, it seems like the scholars
have been found guilty.
Is that true?!
Hey! Navy battleships are moving
toward here from the eastern sea!
They're gonna do something!
Let's hurry to the evacuation ship!
Wh-What the...?!
It's a giant!
Where are you, Robin?!
Escape from this island right away!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Saul, please take care of Robin!
Please let my daughter
escape from here at any cost!
What?! What about you, Mom?!
Aren't you gonna come with me?!
There's still something
that I have to do here, so...
No! I don't wanna be separated!
I was finally able to meet you!
Mom!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Tragedy of Ohara!
The Terror of Buster Call"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!