Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass, We are best friends
We will keep making our own route
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
Running at full speed everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai koto subete kuria shite
We keep finding the things we want to do and doing them all
asa ga machikirenakute uzukidasu (I can't wait)
We can't wait until the morning (I can't wait)
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
sore nara isso taiyou sora e to hikizuridashite
go-in Go
Force it and go
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
and if that makes you feel something - that's the treasure
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
Tomorrow and the day after,
asu mo asatte mo
there will be a chain of burning, intense excitement!
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
koukishin ni makasete
Go along with your curiosity
omoi no mama mezasu basho e sore ga adobenchaa
and go wherever you want to go - that's the adventure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
kokoro no chizu hirogete
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
The bond with potential power will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in which a winner will
get the Flare-Flare Fruit as the prize - and won the first round.
And while the last match of the first round is on,
the losers are...
You're...
I mean, you, sir, are...
...King Riku-sama, aren't you?
Since I'm deep underground now,
I no longer need to disguise myself.
"A Horrible Past!
The Secret of Dressrosa!"
THE CORRIDA COLOSSEUM
Luffy-senpai!
Oh?! You must be...
Oh, wait! No! My name is Lucy!
That's not important now...
Oh, I can't!
I'm too nervous to even speak.
If you've got nothing to say, I'm gonna go now.
I wanna go support Rebecca.
Don't go!
I was asked by Z-Z-Zoro-senpai!
What?! By Zoro?!
Yes!
He asked me to bring Luffy-senpai to him!
I see! Where is he?
H-He's outside of the Colosseum.
I-I'm gonna show you! This way!
Okay!
I'm counting on you, Crest Head!
"Counting on you, Crest Head"?!
Luffy-senpai's counting on me and...
I'm counting on you, Crest Head!
...he gave me a nickname!
That means...
I'm counting on you, Crest Head!
...I'm Luffy-senpai's friend now?!
Hey, what's wrong?
Heated fights are going on
in the battle royal of Block D!
She's so persistent! Very tenacious!
The contender - Rebecca!
Watching her not-unbeautiful fighting style
makes me...
...wanna not unsupport her!
I'm Rebecca's real father!
THE KING RIKU ARMY HEADQUARTERS
A-Are you?!
Drop dead already, Rebecca!
--You kin of King Riku!
--Part of that evil family!
Granddaughter of the pyromaniac!
Go to hell!
If you're her father...
If you're telling the truth,
since she's King Riku's granddaughter...
When you were a human,
don't tell me you were...
Everything started that night.
Hey, answer my question!
Were you King Riku's...
No, it might
have started long before.
Since the day a woman named Monet
started to work at the palace...
What?
Monet?!
The bird woman that we encountered
in Punk Hazard?
This country has changed
in a big way last decade.
Both the scenery and the people!
DRESSROSA - 10 YEARS AGO
Hey, what happened?
Some pirates did this.
But the King Riku Army fought for us
so we got away with this little damage.
Oh, the King Riku Army!
I have a message from King Riku-sama.
What? From King-sama?!
"I'm sorry that I couldn't protect
my dear citizen's house from the pirates."
"The King Riku Army will handle
the repair of your house."
--That's more than we deserve!
--Don't worry. Guys, get to work!
Alright! Let's help them!
Yeah! We help each another when someone's in trouble.
That's what King Riku-sama always says!
Okay! Let's do it together!
It's been two weeks without rain.
Yeah but even during this drought,
the flowers don't die.
Why is that?
It's thanks to the fairies.
They are protecting the flowers.
I wanna eat more!
--If you have energy to shout, you're fine.
--What?
Although we're very poor,
we don't have to fight in a war in this country.
That's the best thing. Don't you think so?
Uh-huh!
For 800 years
under the reign of the Riku Family,
this country had never been involved
in a war.
That's amazing.
Yeah.
It's miraculous for a country.
Even though the country was poor,
the people and fairies all helped each other
and were rich in spirit.
Dressrosa was a very peaceful country.
However...
A "nightmare" came flying to the palace
out of the blue!
Who are you?
Don't try to scream or call for help.
Y-You are...
My name is Don Quixote Doflamingo.
I guess you know what my name suggests,
don't you?
I've been troubled by hearing
about a pirate named Don Quixote these days.
Yes, you were right to be troubled.
I'm a descendent of the Don Quixote Family
that once governed this country.
I am the rightful king of this country!
And now, I'm...
...back!
But you robbed a transport ship
of the Heavenly Tribute
of money for the Celestial Dragons
from various countries
and became a Warlord by blackmailing
the World Government, I heard.
They don't know what to do with me.
They can't handle me
because I'm not afraid of the Celestial Dragons.
Since you know my status and what I'm capable of,
I'm just gonna cut to the chase.
I want my country back!
If you refuse,
there's gonna be bloody mess in Dressrosa.
But I'm not a devil.
I know you don't like to fight.
So...
I'm going to sell you this country
for 10 billion berries.
You're gonna sell this country for money?!
I can just...
...take it back from you
without giving you such an opportunity.
If we can avoid a war by paying money,
I'd like to do so.
But 10 billion berries is a lot of money!
We don't have that much...
Yes, you do!
Scrape it up from your dear citizens.
What?!
I'm expecting to have it
by the break of dawn tomorrow.
You can't get aid from other countries.
Prove your worth as a king.
And you can't tell your citizens about me.
You only have two choices.
Collect money to avoid a war or...
...fight me and see
your citizens bathed in blood.
Pick the one that you want.
Can't we fight Doflamingo, King-sama?!
No! Fighting may sound good
but humans should not kill each other!
But it's hard to collect that much money!
There aren't that many rich people in this country!
We shouldn't have to pay the family
that once abandoned this country in the first place!
If it means war, we're gonna fight...
For 800 years, Dressrosa has never fought a war.
It proves we're not beasts!
Don't become a brute! Be a human!
I won't let you kill anybody!
--But...
--Captain Tank!
I know you have a lot to say.
But what we value the most is
the citizens' lives.
I know you feel the same way.
I beg you!
We soldiers of the King Riku Army
truly believe in you
and do as you tell us to.
And we take pride in it!
Tank, thank you for saying that.
No.
Please forgive me for being disrespectful.
Listen! We don't have much time!
Split up in units and go to different towns!
Collect 10 billion from all over the country.
If we can't do it,
this country will be taken over by the pirate.
We're going to lose the trust of the citizens
by collecting their money.
But it's just for several hours!
When everything is over,
we'll make it up for them sincerely!
That's the only way!
There's no fooling anyone to get out of this!
Collect as much as you can!
The country is on the line!
Yeah!
Let's go! Follow my lead!
--It's the Army.
--What are they doing this late?
That's Captain Tank!
Stop!
Listen, everyone!
Bring all the money you have
in this town here!
--Whoa-whoa, what's the matter?
--What's going on?
--Just bring it!
--Hurry up!
King-sama will be furious with you
if he hears about this!
This is...
...the king's order!
King-sama will be furious with you
if he hears about this!
This is the king's order!
Hurry up! We can't tell you what's going on
and we don't have time!
Just believe in King-sama
and bring all the money you have here!
That's too sudden.
It's impossible!
No one's gonna accept such a request!
The Video Transponder Snail?
Nation of Dressrosa!
King Riku-sama!
It's King Riku-sama!
I know it's too sudden
and an unreasonable request.
But please let me borrow all of your money
from all of you people...
...without asking me for a reason!
The king is bowing his head!
King Riku-sama!
But why is he doing this?
It's really too sudden!
King-sama, stop bowing your head!
You shouldn't be doing that!
You're the king!
--Please stop!
--Lift your head!
The successive kings will be ashamed of you
for doing such a thing!
--King-sama!
--Why do you have to do that!
You're humiliating yourself in front of the whole world!
Just stop!
King-sama!
Please! This is not some kind of joke!
I don't mind cutting
my arm or leg off to prove it!
Listen, Tank.
If things go wrong,
I will kill even just Doflamingo.
King Riku-sama, is that...
I'll leave the rest up to you.
To live up to his expectations,
I'll collect the money at any cost!
Even if I lose...
...the trust of the people in me
as a military captain!
I am begging you!
Hurry up, everyone!
Let's bring all the money we got as the king says!
Yeah! King Riku is such a kind-hearted man!
He wouldn't do this out of ill intent!
That's right!
There must be a reason for this!
--Bring all your money!
--All right!
The king's virtue made it possible!
Here!
Thank you!
I'm sorry!
They're doing it out of their trust
in the eight centuries of the Riku Family's reign.
How wonderful this country is!
It will be saved for sure!
Thank you!
King Riku-sama!
Long live King Riku-sama!
Thank you all.
Take all the money to the palace!
--Hurry up!
--Yes, sir!
--Captain Tank!
--What's wrong?!
--King-sama is in the town of Sevio!
--It's on the screen!
What?!
THE TOWN IN THE SOUTH - SEVIO
King-sama!
You didn't have to come all the way! We're gonna...
Get away!
What?!
It's King-sama!
King Riku-sama! We don't know what the deal is
but we trust you so...
Get away!
What?
Get away from me!
What?!
King Riku-sama, what are you...
Don't! There is a magazine!
King Riku-sama!
King Riku-sama?
Stop! Don't make me do this!
--King Riku-sama, please stop!
--What are you doing?!
Back off! Stay away from me!
Get away from me!
He cut the soldiers, too!
My body is moving on its own!
What are you doing?
King Riku-sama!
Boy... What kind of king he is!
Well, the night has just begun, soldiers.
You should dance, too!
Parasite String!
Wh-What the hell? What's going on?!
M-My arm is moving on its own!
What?
The soldiers are rampaging now, too!
Stop it!
Help me...
C-Captain!
It's not me!
I-I can't control my body!
I know!
That's what's happening to me!
Why does it move on its own?!
Is it what's happening to King-sama?!
King Riku-sama, why are you doing this?!
He's never done anything wrong up
til now!
Did we do something?!
There's no way to justify myself!
This country is finished!
Doflamingo set us up!
--What happened to the king?!
--Please stop!
Hey, hey!
Can we do it already, Doffy?
Idiot. Don't rush.
I have to make the people tremble
with fear more
and get them hate King Riku
with all their heart!
And then, the heroes will appear!