Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Now, what're you gonna do?
Take me to the shore already
so that I can knock you out!
You don't have to tell me!
I'll shut you up right here, right now!
Super Cartwheel, Iron Ball!
I'll slam you into the corner of
the tower using this momentum!
I see. It indeed looks like
I'll get smashed into pieces.
Franky Centaur!
--Chapa!
--I've got both your legs!
Now you can't move around at will in the air!
So what?! Even if you do that,
you can't stop this momentum!
That's not totally true.
70 mm 0.2 Cola Cannon!
A bit of Coup de Vent!
Ahh! The momentum has died down!
The rotation stopped! Damn you!
But this is enough!
We're already above the shore!
Now, take this!
70 mm 1.5 Max Cola Power!
Coup de...
What're you doing?!
Give up already, you bastard!
Coup de...
...Vent!
Super!
Yoyoi!
That voice... Don't tell me
he broke the fridge door...
I... I... I... I...
I... I... I... I... I...
I had a feast!
He got a little fatter!
Just how much stuff in that fridge did you eat?!
--Hm?
--That's...
Snap!
Listen, Sogeking. Don't lose your posture.
You are a sword!
Someone get me a lawyer! I'll sue you for sure!
Suit yourself.
I'm gonna try this out first, okay?
What? What?
Ahh! This is a dream! This is a dream!
Morning, come already!
Those guys sure do some weird stuff.
This is interesting!
Oni...
Hey! Wait! Hey! Are you really gonna do it?!
You're the demon here!
...Giri!
Ow, ow, ow... Stars are coming out of my eyes.
Just don't move!
Tiger....
Huh? Tiger? Tiger?
I'm in trouble! I'm in trouble!
Dammit!
That hit me good. Stars are
coming out of my nose, too.
I said don't move!
Don't be unreasonable!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Are they idiots?
Are they going to fight us seriously?
After all, it seems like we have no
choice but to play rock-paper-scissors.
And I'll cut off the hand of the loser.
Wait! Like I said, don't you
have any better ideas?!
No, I don't.
You don't have to be so blunt!
This is no time for stupid arguments.
Just give it up, nose.
"Just give it up, nose"?
Chopper! Please hurry up!
"Uncontrollable! Chopper's Forbidden Rumble"
Yoyoi!
I've never seen anyone with
so little self-discipline as him.
To think that he gained weight in the
few minutes I took my eyes off of him...
You don't... need to be...
need to be... need to be...
I'm not concerned! Just speak normally!
That's "need to be concerned," right?!
Well...
Thank you!
That's exactly what I was... I was... I was...
I got it, so you can cut that out!
Anyway, there's no need
to be concerned, then?
Come back here!
I was... I was... That's right!
As for why...
...just look! Life Return!
Wh-What the heck?!
Digest!
Absorb!
Now, I'm back to normal!
Ahhh! What?! What are you?!
What did you just do?!
Do it again.
If you wish...
Life Return!
Digest!
Absorb!
Amazing! One more time!
O-One more time?
Life Return!
Digest!
Absorb!
You're amazing! How does that work?!
Glad you asked!
A thousand years at sea, and a
thousand years in the mountains...
Breathing in the wind and drinking dewdrops,
I trained myself, living as a hermit!
After all that, I've... I've... I've...
I've acquired this "Life Return"!
Essentially, if you extend
your consciousness everywhere,
from your hair to your internal organs,
toes, even the tip of your downy hair,
there's no part of your body
that you can't manipulate.
Extending your consciousness
even to the tip of your hair?
I've read about that kind
of ability in a book before.
It's called something like biofeedback...
Then your hair moves around like
an octopus because of that ability?!
Yoyoyoi! An octopus?! How terribly rude!
Call me... a valiant...
...lion... will... will you?!
Why does it matter which one?
Life Return!
Hair Bind!
Yoyoi!
Yoyoyoi!
Dammit!
If I get caught by that, it'll be all over for me!
Shave!
Where did he go?!
Finger Pistol! Q!
When that stick doesn't
even have a pointed tip...
Q! Q! Q!
Heavy Gong!
Iron Body!
Yoi!
Ow, ow, ow...
What's the matter?!
Dammit!
As I thought, he won't budge unless
I attack with Arm Point or Horn Point.
But rumble balls are potent drugs.
One in six hours is a proper dosage.
If I take more than that,
it'll be a huge strain on my body.
On top of that... the second one will
alter the transformation wavelength,
and so it'll be hard to
control my transformations.
With the third one, I'll lose consciousness
and hardly be able to fight.
What do I do? I can take just
one more and get strengthened.
I'll roast you on a skewer!
Shishi Kabob!
Yoi! Yoi!
Yoi!
If I don't do anything, I'm just wasting time!
Rumble!
This is high-risk, but it'll give me a chance!
--Yoyoi!
--This is all or nothing!
I'll somehow settle this within three minutes!
Take this! Horn Point!
--What?!
--Yoyoi!
Wrong one!
Ow, ow, ow...!
Kabob!
Jumping Point!
Ah! Wrong one!
Yoyoi! Yoyoi!
As I was afraid, I can't control
my transformations. Dammit!
If only I could somehow use Arm Point,
I could give him a cloven
attack with all my might!
This room is dangerous with the fire spreading.
This is no time for me to be stuck
with a guy with no key on him!
I'd better hurry up and get the #2 key...
...and free Zoro and Sogeking!
Or we can't rescue Robin!
That's right... Robin...
That's right! I'm...
I'm...
I'm fighting in order to save our friend!
What a tough animal!
Life Return!
His hair changed into the shape of hands!
I have to do it! I can't be
defeated in a place like this!
I'm their only hope!
Shishi Finger Pistol!
Yoyoi!
Showing mercy is never... part of a lion's fury!
Ouch...
Taking the second rumble ball is like gambling.
There are seven transformations in total.
In other words, the probability of
getting Arm Point is one in seven.
If I could get it, I could hammer
my strongest attack into him.
That's my only chance!
Arm Point!
Shishi Kabob!
For my friends... Arm Point!
Yoyoi!
Arm Point!
Wrong one!
Wrong one! Why doesn't it come out?!
My body is at the end of its rope.
I somehow have to get Arm Point out!
Yoyoi!
Hm?
--Yoyoi!
--Whoa!
It's out! I didn't notice it!
Be prepared!
I'll put everything I have
into this... into this attack!
Cloven...
Shishi Finger Pistol!
If I back off now, I won't get another chance!
Cloven...
Iron Body! Strength!
...Roseo Metel!
Go down!
That was my best attack!
Ahh...
Ahh... Splendid...!
It was indeed a beautiful blizzard of...
cherry blossom petals.
I can't...
Did I do it?
I can't bear it anymore!
I will give you hell! Yoyoyoi yoi!
Tempest Kick! Lotus!
This is it... I no longer have
energy left to fight back.
Chopper!
Chopper, what in the world did you do?
I don't remember.
"I don't remember" doesn't cut it.
It was good that no one died, at least.
Even while you were sleeping,
the entire country was making
a big fuss about that night.
How are we going to settle that?
So I did something that terrible?
You almost destroyed an entire village.
It's fine that you love experiments,
just like your old man did,
but for something like that, you have
to do it only after thorough planning.
Thorough planning...
You were not doing it for
fun at all. I know that much.
But that's exactly why you
need to be even more careful.
Doctors are always
entrusted with people's lives.
Small mistakes can become irreversible.
We're always walking on
the edge of a cliff like that.
If you can't even imagine what kind of result
careless actions can cause, then you
should give up on becoming a doctor.
Seriously, you inherited
everything from that quack,
including his predisposition for causing a fuss.
The world always has its
troublesome seeds, huh?
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
I won't do it again.
I'll never do it again,
so please don't kick me out.
You're such a fool. Hurry up and get better.
Or I can't even go out shopping.
Life Return!
Hair Bind!
Don't cry. Don't cry.
If you do, it'll be a disgrace to your manhood.
He's gonna kill me...
This isn't an evening in a mountain
village where you can hear the cicadas.
This is a journey to hell
that you knew could come.
The leaves I broke off of a willow tree
branch to give to you as a parting gift,
hoping for your return someday,
are colored crimson!
Take it! Now, now, now, now!
Crimson... Song of Willow!
I'm gonna die...
Robin... That's right. I can't give up!
He slipped away from my Hair Bind!
Rumble...
I'm sorry, Doctorine.
Just like Doctor put his life on the
line in order to save the country...
...I want to put my life on the
line in order to save my friend.
If I'm gonna die anyway, I'll do it!
Just please, nobody come into this room.
I used three Rumble Balls.
Then I lost consciousness and after that...
You could say that your Devil Fruit
powers went out of control.
Don't ever go down that path, okay?
It's an excessive power that destroys
foes, friends, and even your own body.
What you turned into was just like a real...
...monster.
Boss! Big news! Big news! Big news!
Oh, what's the big news today, Usopp?
We're going to appear again after a long while!
And that Buggy guy and his men will go
wild noisily, messily, tiredly, disorderly...
Now, now, now... Why don't you
eat and calm yourself down? Here.
Okay. Ahh! Anyway, this is big news, Boss!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Boss Luffy Returns! Is it a Dream
or Reality? Lottery Ruckus!"
I'm gonna be a policeman!!