Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
After being separated from his friends,
Luffy comes to rescue his brother Ace
who has been captured by the Navy
by sneaking into Impel Down - the
greatest prison in the world!
Luffy is now at level 2 - Wild
Beast Hell with Buggy the Clown.
It is a wild beast of hell!
Damn it!
Gum-Gum...
...Giant Pistol!
What?! Someone's broken in to Impel Down?!
That's impossible! No one has ever
broken in all the prison's history!
Did they notice our plan?!
Transfer the video!
Warden!
Can I see the prisoner now?
Okay, let's go! I'm ready to go!
W-Warden! Don't you realize
how serious this is?!
If you're having trouble on
this floor, I can help you.
Who is that guy?
Long time no see, Straw Hat Luffy!
You helped me out without noticing.
I always pay back my debts.
Who are you?
Oh, that's 3! That means...
You were on the island with
the Giants! You are San!
No, I'm Mr.Three!
"A Warlord in Prison! Jimbei
the First Son of the Sea!"
To be honest, when I was assigned
to this floor I thought I was dead,
but it's surprisingly peaceful.
It couldn't be any other way.
What kind of floor did you think it would be?
This lowest floor holds the
worst villains with more
than a 100 million berry price...
...or other infamous menaces.
That's why the security here is so tight
and that's why it's called Eternal
Hell -the worst floor for
prisoners to be held on.
Well, the only chance for them
to get out from the deep sea...
and get sunshine is when
they go to their execution.
Death is maybe easier...
...than spending the rest
of your life in this hell.
Maybe!
Hey! The Warden and Vice Warden
are on their way with Boa Hancock.
I wonder why the pirate empress
wants to see "Fire Fist" Ace.
Yeah, he is the most dangerous
prisoner in Impel Down,
I mean, maybe in the whole world now.
I don't want any trouble.
Speaking of dangerous men, that
guy who is a Warlord like Hancock
who rebelled against Navy Headquarters
is also pretty dangerous.
I am...
...not going to run!
I can't even move to scratch an itch.
They beat you up, huh?
Captain.
It doesn't hurt me, Ace-san.
What hurts me is...
....the fact that I can't take a stand...
...for my beliefs about humanity and justice!
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei
A Warlord of the Sea
(A Whale Shark Fish-man Formerly
With a Bounty of 250 Million Berries)
Jimbei.
I can't die without doing something about it!
I don't give a damn about the title of
Warlord of the Sea! I don't want it!
If it means I can stop this war...
I'd be happy to sacrifice my life!
No wonder we can't reach them!
The jailors' room on level
2 was crushed by a Basilisk!
A Basilisk was beaten?!
Where are those two?!
What's happening on level 2 now?!
I see them!
--Really?--But...
...there's three now.
What?!
"Level 2
Floor of Wild Beasts from Hell"
It seems like all the wild beasts
on this floor are after us now!
We can't just run forever!
You're right! As soon as we stop
running, we're gonna become dinner!
And while we're busy running,
jailors from other floors are on
their way here to catch us, too.
I'm tired already...
I don't have time for this!
Gum-Gum...
Chop-Chop...
Candle...
--...Pistol!
--...Cannon!
--...Lock!
Augh! That big centipede just exploded!
It was just made of a bunch of Puzzle
Scorpions! They are extremely poisonous!
They're multiplying!
I told you!
They sure were fooled by my footsteps trick!
They found us, stupid!
Damn it!
By the way, I heard that the boss of
beasts on level 2 looks like a lion.
Is this them?
No! These are man-eating lions with
human-like faces called Manticores!
"Prison Guard on Level 2
MANTICORE"
Once they catch us, they'll
eat us to the bone!
To the bone!
--Key!--What?
Give me the key!
Don't pay attention!
Since they look like humans
they do impressions of people!
--Help me!--It's too painful!
They just learn what prisoners say!
They don't even know the meaning!
I-It's creepy!
--Loincloth! Loincloth!--Strawberry-print
panties!
Who taught them those dumb words?!
Beef Steak!
--What?!--Don't react to it!
Hey you!
You said that you're gonna help us, right?
Of course! Let's join forces
to break out of this prison!
Where can we get down to level 3?!
Huh? Don't you wanna break out?!
I thought that you wanna go up to level 1!
Straw Hat came here to
rescue his brother Ace!
Brother?! "Fire Fist" Ace
is Straw Hat's brother?!
And you came here to rescue him?!
I've no time!
If Ace is being held here, I'm
sure that they put him in level 5!
And he wants to go there?!
No way! That's crazy! I'm not going!
Wait! Tell me where the stairs
to go down are, at least!
The stairs to go down? Oh yeah!
The stairs are connected
between level 1 to 3.
Why don't I use Straw Hat as a bait--to
the beast guarding the stairs!
And then, I can just take off!
All right, Straw Hat! Let's go together!
Count on me, Straw Hat!
Follow me...
Oh no. There's something
here. And what the...
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
It's a guardian of the
stairs called the Sphinx!
"Prison Guard on Level 2
SPHINX
(A Lion with a Human-like Face and Feathers)"
Is it a lion?! Or a grandpa?
--Omelet rice!--Steak!
--Underpants!--Strawberry-print panties!
Thin noodle.
T-Thin noodle?!
Chinese Noodle!
Vegetable noodle!
They taught him mainly names of noodles?!
BBQ pork noodle!
Spicy Szechuan noodle!
Cool dude!
--Who, me?!--Who, me?!
He's very tough!
T-That's gotta be...
The Sphinx is going nuts somewhere!
I knew it! We'll be stuck here forever!
Ground pork noodle!
Hot-pot noodle!
Canton noodle!
I wanna eat Sanji's food! I
haven't had it for long time!
Wonton noodle!
Damn! He's pretty strong!
You know, I don't wanna go
down to the lower levels!
I'm totally with you!
All right! Now, let's form
an alliance to breakout!
I'm so glad that you are a real escapee!
Alright, let's execute the
"Straw Hat for dinner" plan!
Oh yeah!
Miso flavored noodle!
Salt flavored noodle!
Soy sauce flavored noodle!
Hey, what're you guys doing?
Oops!
H-Here he comes, Straw Hat!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
Why did you want to make him angry?!
Oh no!
It's not fair! I wanna go
up higher like you two!
Cold noodle!
I got you, naive animal!
That's just a wax figure that
I made with my Wax-Wax power!
Hot thin noodle.
It's better with Miss Goldenweek's coloring,
but it's enough to fool an animal like you!
Here we go!
Can you tell which is the real me?
Noodle!
You missed it!
Wow, that's fun! It's like Whack-A-Mole!
--Noodle!--Missed it!
That's him!
Oh, it's not! This one?!
--Noodle!--Missed it!
--Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
Noodle! Noodle!--Go get him!
He's playing with Sphinx!
How simple-minded are you, Straw Hat?!
Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
Noodle!
You're starting to enjoy this!
They're having more fun than I
expected. I gotta make a break now!
Hey, what are these unusual tremors?!
They must be making Sphinx mad!
Noodle! Noodle! Noodle!
Noodle!
What?! What happened?!
Is it safe to be on this floor?!
Level 3 to monitoring room!
We're hearing big noises from upstairs!
Mr. 3! This is our chance!
The plan is a success!
This wasn't our plan! But let's just run!
Oh?! That must be the door to the stairs!
I'll make a key out of wax!
This is the monitoring room!
We can't get in touch with level 2 yet!
So we don't know what's going on!
Noodle!
Oh no! You stupid beast! You
battered down the floor!
This is level 3! Augh! The ceiling is
crumbling and the beast is about to...
This is not good!
No no! This is the way to level 3!
Sorry, noodles!
I'm known by the government
as a pirate who hates pirates
except for you people.
You hates pirates?
Must be surprising for you, Ace-san.
I visited Whitebeard's ship frequently
but because of my status, I always
traveled under the sea to get there.
Because I like you people.
Ho-hum.
I remember that you almost killed me once.
I can say the same for you.
I just wanted to do something for him.
Fish-Man Island is peaceful now and it's
all because of the old man Whitebeard.
When pirates go along the Grand Line,
they always pass Fish-Man Island.
Right after the dawn of Great Pirate
Era, Fish-Man Island was in trouble.
Countless human pirates and Navy
who were chasing after them...
...were wreaking havoc.
A large number of Fish-men and mermaids
were kidnapped and sold as slaves.
And just when everyone gave
themselves up to despair,
Whitebeard came.
"I declare that this island
is my territory now!"
With just those few words, no one
bothers Fish-Man Island anymore.
What power!
How could I ever forget that day?
And he's protecting other islands
with his name in the same way, too.
It's not right to knock somebody down
just because he's the head pirate!
If he ever got killed, what
will happen to the sea?!
It's clear to everyone that that
time of confusion would come again!
The government must know it, too!
I wanted to stop the war even if it kills me.
I wanted to rescue you, Ace-san.
Jimbei, that's enough.
It's too painful.
I haven't given up hope yet.
I believe that a miracle will
happen and a chance will come.
It looks like there's a lot of fun
going on in the outside world!
It's a now-or-never chance
to defeat Whitebeard.
I can't help getting excited.
You bastard!
You think that you can fell my old man?!
It's not just me.
Kill Whitebeard!
That guy's gonna die? Yee-ha!
That'll be great!
Get me out to the sea!
I'm the one who will kill him!
Let me have a chance, too! I'm
gonna put an end to his era!
Shut up, you assholes!
Jimbei, "Fire Fist," just so you know,
there are dozens and dozens
of silver medalists
in the world who in the end didn't win...
...against Whitebeard and Roger
all holding back their tears.
Straw Hat! You're the worst
troublemaker in the world!
Sorry, noodles!
Level 3!
This is Starvation Hell, where
prisoners are given no food or water
and are tormented by extreme heat.
As Luffy and the others roam
this desert-like floor,
they fall into a trap set by a chief guard.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Chief Guard Saldeath's Trap!
Level 3 - Starvation Hell!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!