Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
Say... This ground...
It's dirt.
Eh? Oh, right!
Sky islands are made out of island cloud...
Why is this island different?
Looks like checking into it
might be worth a lot...
This is the Illusion Forest Ball Ordeal,
with a 10% survival rate!
You'd better hurry before the boat
goes deeper into the Illusion Forest!
Hey! We gotta go after the boat
before we lose sight of it!
I'm gonna take care of the ball guy!
Don't do anything reckless!
He's got some weird powers!
We'll come back once we stop the boat!
Right! Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!
Again!
Dammit! Can't see from down here!
Watch yourself, Luffy!
These priests are no ordinary people!
Let's find the boat ASAP
and get the hell outta here!
"The Ordeal of Spheres!
Desperate Struggle in the Lost Forest"
Don't be in such a rush! Stay for a while!
Now then, where are the other two?
I won't let a single one escape!
Here we are!
Hey! You see it, Usopp?!
Found it!
Gimme directions!
Straight ahead! Climb up
the tree after the next one!
You can jump onto it from the branches!
Got it!
Yikes! It's him! What's he up to?!
Go!
Look out, Sanji! There's a ball headed your way!
What?! What's Luffy doing?!
Surprise Billiard!
Usopp!
He was aiming for me!
It's gonna explode!
"Pop"?!
A dud...
Idiot!
Why, you...!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Stop, Luffy! Don't hit those balls randomly!
What the--?! What the--?! What the--?!
Oh, no! Too late!
Look out! They're coming from all directions!
You people are fun!
Spears! Crab!
Four at once!
What the--? Another dud?
Or should I say, I hit the jackpot?
I freaked out for nothing!
Huh? You want me to sing, too?
Okay! Listen in awe to the one
known as the Singing Pirate!
Here goes!
Hey! I haven't sung yet!
Oww! Hot! Oww!
Water! Water! Water!
Oww! Hot! Oww! Oww!
River!
Oww!
I went through!
Luffy! Don't fall into the river below!
There might not be a bottom!
Eh?!
Yikes!
Are you stupid?!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Hammer!
Usopp Hammer!
Rubber Band! Usopp Hammer!
Yahoo!
Oh! I didn't think of that!
Now I can finally try it out!
Got any ideas, Usopp?!
I sure do! I'm known as
the greatest pirate inventor!
I'll show ya my latest weapon!
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
Uhh, what?
Just watch!
There it is! On the river straight ahead!
I can make it! Set up!
What is he up to?
Alright! Now it's just a
straight line to the Crow!
If it goes any further in,
we won't be able to get it!
I can't let this chance go!
Wow, not too shabby! Watch out for the balls!
I ain't gonna screw up!
You can call me King of the Jungle!
Here goes!
Usopp Aa-aa-aa!
Alright! Go!
Yes! Perfect! Get on board and stop the boat!
What're you doing?! Get on already!
Yeah... about that...
I forgot that the rope is attached
to the belt, so I can't get down...!
Crap! Crap! Crap!
Yahoo! Hey, Usopp!
You seem to be havin' fun, too!
I need a word with you two.
Got it? I'll forget what just
happened, so do as I say!
Yes! I'm sorry!
I'm sorry...
Forget about the boat for right now.
All three of us are gonna attack him at once!
I don't care if he is a priest;
if we all attack at once,
we should be able to find a way to beat him!
Beat me?!
Where'd he go?!
Impact!
Sanji!
Life is suffering...
Now, for the other two!
Thanks!
Hey, did something move over there?
Dunno.
Say, did you see anything, Robin?
No, nothing at all...
You sure it wasn't just a monkey?
A monkey? I guess so...
Say. Do you think we should
check out the other shore after all?
No way! What if we get
attacked by sharks again?!
Geez! You're hopeless...
I can't get near it like this...
I promised Zoro I would fix the ship...
Alright! I'll do my best, too!
Just don't let them notice you!
Gently... Gently...
I did it! Now I can fix the ship!
The whistle...!
One blow of this One Whistle...
...and I shall come to your aid!
Normally, I charge five million Extol,
but I will give you the
One Whistle as a present!
Wait! We still don't know your name!
I am Gan Fall, the Sky Knight!
And this is my partner, Pierre!
May luck be with you, warriors!
So how do we get up there?
I know! Let's call that old man and ask!
H-H-Hold on, Luffy! This is only
supposed to be used in emergencies!
What if that weird masked
guy shows up again?!
Here! I'll hold on to this whistle!
Any objections?!
Yes!
Yes! Yes! Yes!
How can you say that?!
I'm the weakest girl here!
It's only natural that I hold onto this whistle!
I wanna blow it!
You just wanna try it out, Luffy! Forget it!
I wanna call the old man here!
Let me hold on to it! I'm the weakest!
You wish! I'm the weakest!
What?! Quit screwin' around!
I'm clearly the weakest!
No, I am!
Don't downplay my hopelessness!
What a strange argument...
'Kay, let's do this! Center of the ship!
I'll put it on the main mast,
so if anyone's in trouble,
they can get the whistle from here and blow it!
Now it's fair!
Alright.
Got it.
Oh, and none of you are allowed to blow it!
Huh? But I wanna call the old man...
Blow it and I'll kick you
to the ends of the earth!
Yes, we'll be careful.
A-All right! Good thing this was here!
Now if anything happens,
the Sky Knight will come save me!
But the whistle is a last resort!
All right! I'm going to work hard
and watch over the ship!
What's that?
Huh? You're the only sacrifice I get to kill?
Cobblestones...
We might find more clues if we follow these...
Say, what do you think that sound was?
Dunno. Stay right there.
I'm sick of you things!
What an unlucky day.
You gotta be careful.
T-Thanks...
Usopp!
Even if we're far apart
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
You have a friend here to share the pain
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
I won't let it just be a dream
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
We're in huge trouble, aren't we?
Yeah, it's one thing after another!
So we can't save you yet, Chopper!
Eh?! I'm in big trouble!
You already got a strong ally on your side!
Eh?! O-Oh, right! Sky Knight!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Chopper in Danger!
Former God vs. Priest Shura"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!