Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew each
completed individual training.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level.
But they have yet to gather and are
stirring things up as a fragmented crew!
"Hordy's Onslaught! The Retaliatory
Plan Set Into Motion!"
Look at that, Luffy-sama!
That cloud looks like an animal called a
"racoon" that I've seen before in a book!
Ah, that looks like Chopper!
Chopper?
Uh-huh! Chopper is my friend!
Friend?
Something is flying...
I can't see clearly, it's too far.
Luffy-sama, what's wrong?
THE RYUGU KINGDOM
THE PORT TOWN--CORAL HILL
Mom, what is that?!
Hey, look at that!
What is it?
Ryugu Palace! Ryugu Palace! Come in!
THE MAIN ENTRANCE
BORDER CONTROL HEADQUARTERS
Ryugu Palace! This is Border Control!
Hello? Hello?
--That's weird.
--Clank.
Why can't we reach them?
Is the Transponder Snail sick?
Why are they coming in flocks
to the Fish-Man Island?
I have no idea.
I know those dangerous people
from the Fish-Man District
don't just come here for the shopping.
Listen, guys!
Today will be remembered as the day
that everyone on the Fish-Man
Island united under one flag!
All Fish-Men, including the Merfolk,
have to be like-minded!
We must dominate the humans
since they're such lowly creatures
who can't even breathe in the water!
Let's correct the mistakes of history now!
Today will be the anniversary
of our engagement, Shirahoshi!
No need to hurry. Let's get married tomorrow!
That annoying faction from the Sun Pirates
- Jimbei's group--is not here-dosun!
Neptune, the God of the Sea, and the
brothers; Fukaboshi, Ryuboshi, Manboshi!
Much! If we can bring those 4 under control,
Neptune's army can't stand against us-ch!
Let's bite all the soldiers' flesh off!
I'll just cut them--whatever
you tell me to do.
Let's begin.
Go ahead and begin conquering
major towns on your own!
The Ryugu Kingdom falls today!
And then we will dominate the sea floor!
Just in time.
The Sea Forest...
I wonder what this place is like.
There's no mistaking her!
Nico Robin of the Straw Hats!
Woman! You and your friends are
suspects in 2 ongoing investigations!
First, for multiple counts of
Mermaid kidnapping! Second,
you people are suspected of being
a potential risk to the Fish-Man Island
based on Madam Sharley's prevision!
So we're taking all of the
Straw Hats into custody!
I don't know what you're talking about.
And did you say "prevision"?
You people need to get your brains checked...
...if you unashamedly believe
in such unscientific things.
Madam Sharley's previsions
are accurate! Come with us!
No thank you. I don't want to miss my bus.
Get her!
Mil Fleurs!
W-We have to report... She... got... away...
SEA FOREST
They had information as I thought.
There is a Poneglyph somewhere here.
I think this kingdom holds the
important key to the 100-Year Void!
THE RYUGU PALACE
--What's wrong with these guys?
--One after another...
Why do we always get involved in trouble?
Stop whining, Nami! The battle is on already!
They keep attacking us so we have no choice.
Shut up, Zoro! We don't wanna get ourselves
into more trouble than we already have!
What's wrong with pirates
fighting pirates? There's no crime.
Boy, he never learns!
Guys, you're barely clinging to life
- why do you wanna fight so badly?
Let's settle this peacefully...
Do you think they'll give up that easily?
The switch for the gateway...
If we can't open it, they'll kill us!
Kill them!
Let me do it too!
You little...!
They leave me no choice.
Die!
Why don't they get it?
Outta my way!
Oops!
I wonder what that was.
Luffy-sama.
Why are you so strong?
I've been training myself since I was a kid.
But there were people stronger than me.
Oh, there are people even stronger than you?
What's wrong, Shark? You don't feel well?
Megalo?
Do you have a stomach ache, Shark?
That was close! Be careful, Shark!
Don't accuse me of cutting
them just because I like it!
But you looked like you were enjoying it.
You're a natural born manslayer!
Well then, if you were attacked by pirates,
what would you do? Serve tea?!
Well, serving tea and
talking is one way to solve...
They wouldn't let you!
In any case, if you beat them all,
you won't be able to find
out what they wanted!
Stop worrying so much about them.
Something is wrong with this picture...
Why do most of our crewmembers
tend to act like this?
--Well, look at our captain.
--Yeah, there's no point in even questioning it.
I wonder if Luffy-san has met the Mermaid
Princess already. I wanna see her too!
More importantly, untie me!
Give me back Shirahoshi-jamon!
Why do you think that we want to
kidnap the Mermaid Princess?!
I know Straw Hat Luffy did
it-jamon! Shirahoshi!
I saw Luffy-san and Shark-san
coming out of the room for sure,
but I didn't see the Mermaid
Princess with them.
But she is not the kind of girl who
just sneaks out on her own-jamon.
Shirahoshi is as big as myself-jamon.
Someone will notice her if she gets out.
What?! The Mermaid Princess is big?!
I'm a princess-jamon!
No way...
Oh yeah-jamon! Maybe, he hid Shirahoshi
in Megalo's mouth and took her out!
Stop making us laugh under
these circumstances, King.
Who would do such a thing?
Even if he had the idea...
My nose is itching too.
Luffy-sama, did you catch cold?
I don't often catch cold.
I wonder what it is.
Shirahoshi!
In any event, our captain wouldn't kidnap anybody!
You better look for somebody else!
No, I can't think of anybody else!
If Shirahoshi doesn't come back safely,
you can't have your ship
or friends back-jamon!
No! You can't do that to us!
I... I did it!
Looks like those human
pirates pulled it off.
Sunny, are you alright?! You're a super
miracle ship just as I thought!
This place is like a graveyard of ships.
The tide brings sunken ships here.
Isn't it ironic?
Although that's what this place is,
it receives the blessings of the Sun Tree Eve -
corals have grown beautifully
drawing fish and whales here.
That's amazing! There are a lot of whales
and they are so much bigger than the Sunny.
Whales only come to fertile seas.
This place is wonderful!
I've been studying this magical
Sea Forest in the deep sea.
Yeah, it's hard to believe that
this place is in the deep sea.
Just like the Fish-Man Island.
Treasure Tree Adam--it is so valuable.
But you built a hell of a ship out of it.
You think so?
It's made with the same material as the
King of the Pirates' ship that Tom-san made.
It's my greatest design of all!
I'll do the coating. Count on me, completely!
Oh, thank you... Um... Can I ask your name?
I'm Den.
Den-san. You don't look like him.
You're a Merman--not a cowfish.
I thought you'd look like him
since you're his brother.
DEN (TOM'S YOUNGER BROTHER)
SHIPWRIGHT/RESEARCHER OF THE SEA FOREST
That's how a human would think.
Races on earth--family members often
look like one another, don't they?
Fish-Men are a little different.
Fish-Men and Merfolk each have different,
ancient genes from their ancestors.
A MOTHER AND SON
When an octopus Mermaid
gives birth to a shark Merman,
that means one of her
ancestors was a shark Merfolk.
It's not so strange when kids don't look
like their parents on the Fish-Man Island.
That's why we can't understand why you
humans want to discriminate against...
...those who don't look like yourselves.
Hmm...
By the way, one of your
ancestors was a robot?
I'm a human.
Human? Oh, one of your ancestors
was a humanoid robot.
No, a normal human!
It's okay.
It's not okay!
Oh yeah, she mentioned you and
Iceberg-kun in her letter.
Oh, that old bag Kokoro wrote to you?
What a thoughtful old woman.
So I know everything about what happened.
My brother lived his life completely
like he always did, to the very end!
And you traveled all the way to tell me that.
He had a good pupil.
Stop it!
Oh, so you're a robot!
No... Well, let's just
say that I'm a pervert.
Oh, by the way, somebody has been
sitting there for quite a while.
Oh, that's Boss Jimbei!
Boss?
He said he's expecting somebody.
He doesn't wanna enter the
island since he's a wanted man.
THE ENTRANCE OF THE RYUGU PALACE
THE GATEWAY
THE MAIN GATE
THE PALACE GATE
We have intruders!
How did you guys get this far?!
I can't believe this! I was ready
to start a fight right away
but Neptune and all the soldiers are tied up!
I didn't expect to see a present like this.
What a surprise.
That guy!
Why is he here?!
The hateful Vander Decken!
You've shown up at last!
And that's...
...Hordy Jones from the Fish-Man District!
Why did he come back here?
Hordy? That guy is...
He was once a decorated soldier in our army.
Is this some kind of trap?
It's too good to be true.
We've had visitors one after another.
What a lively palace.
Ah-ha! You guys are their accomplices!
You let them in, didn't you?!
You know what, we wouldn't be
here if you guys didn't invite us!
They look formidable! Who are those people?!
--Hey, let us have our arms at least!
--Please, let us fight!
Vander Decken!
Since you've shown up, there is no doubt!
You're the one who did it!
Give me back my daughter!
We haven't even got married yet.
It's too soon for you to say that, Father-sama.
Don't call me Father-sama!
Where did you take Shirahoshi?!
You'd better tell me she's unharmed!
What are you talking about?
You're talking like the Princess is missing.
Quit acting dumb!
Why else would Shirahoshi have
disappeared from her room all of the sudden?!
My Shirahoshi disappeared?!
She's my... My daughter-jamon!
Neptune-sama, don't lose
your temper over his nonsense!
Calm down, Decken.
Look. All of the humans that you threw,
aimed at the Mermaid Princess, are here.
That means that Princess Shirahoshi
was here at least during that time.
Help me...
Plus, it doesn't matter
if they're lying or not
because you know how to
check where she is now.
Check where she is?
You're right! Hordy,
you're a very smart guy! I suspect!
Huh? Is he leaving?
What is he gonna do?
Alright, you coral, fly to Shirahoshi!
It's not heading towards the tower!
We've been in love for a decade!
Nothing will tear us apart...
...except for death!
...And I had a very big fart!
Luffy-sama, that is so
inappropriate to talk about.
Is it?
Before you become somebody else's,
I'd rather see you dead with
your blood splattered all over!
Shirahoshi!
A wall of the royal palace is destroyed
and seawater begins to rush in.
Hordy attacks Neptune's
army with his full might.
The soldiers risk their lives to
protect Neptune, the God of the Sea
when Zoro stands to face Hordy.
With the seawater is rising, Zoro will
battle in dramatically unfavorable conditions.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Battle in the Ryugu Palace!
Zoro vs. Hordy!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!