Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
To rescue his brother Ace who
has been captured by the navy,
Luffy stowed away on a navy ship with
the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock's help
and headed to the Great
Prison - Impel Down!
Meanwhile, the rest
of the Straw Hats
had been sent to separate
islands by Bartholomew Kuma.
As time ticks down for the
public execution of Ace,
tensions at Navy
Headquarters are rising
and preparations for
war are underway.
Nobody can stop it now.
We made the
king of the sea...
...angry!
"A Deadly Infiltration! The
Underwater Prison Impel Down!"
I wanted you and Luffy to
become good marines.
But instead, both of you brothers
have become notorious hoodlums.
I'm sure that you
heard about Luffy.
He picked a fight with the World
Government at Water Seven
and destroyed the Judgement
Island - Enies Lobby!
I rushed there and gave him
some tough-love with this fist
but he didn't
learn even a little.
So he went and made a big
mess at Sabaody Archipelago.
I'm so proud of
my grandson!
Oh yeah. I told Luffy
about his father.
A father? Do I have a father?
Your father's name is
Monkey D. Dragon!
He's a revolutionary!
Luffy was surprised to
know about his father.
It doesn't matter to us at all.
Because Luffy and
I unfortunately
have the blood of the world's most
infamous criminals in our veins anyway.
There was no way for
us to become marines.
I took over the name "Portgaz" from
my mother to whom I owe so much
but I never wanted to have my
good-for-nothing father's blood.
Because I don't have any memory of
him and I don't owe anything to him.
Ah yeah, I understand
but he tried...
What I want to say is...
Old man,
You are too valuable
to let die now, boy.
Run as wild as you want
on the sea under my name.
You are my son from now!
My only father is...
Whitebeard!
Vice Admiral Momonga!
I see a pirate ship!
Whose ship is that?
That mark... I've
seen it before...
I'll look into it!
If you don't remember, they
must not be a big deal.
Let them go! There is no
time to waste on this trip.
Yes, sir!
Ahh! Look over there!
It's a big Sea King!
If he targets us, he can eat
this whole ship with one bite.
Please don't notice us!
He's gone.
W-We came all this way but
there is nothing
we can do now.
What should we do
now, Sister Alvida?!
Don't ask me what to do!
It's you guys who
wanted to come here
and who spent a fortune
on an Eternal Pose.
B-Because we really wanted to save Captain
Buggy who has been taken to Impel Down!
Look at the sea!
We're about to enter the Calm Belt
where monsters have their nests.
You think this ship
can sail there?
But there is only one other course
and that's exclusively for the Navy.
They're not gonna open the
Gate of Justice for a pirate ship.
No way! We can't
even get there?!
If nothing is done, Captain
Buggy will be executed!
...Along with his
friend Ace-kun!
Richie! Look at how sad he is
thinking about the Captain!
Impel Down is the greatest
prison in the world
and it's impossible to
break in or break out.
You better just give up.
Buggy the Clown's luck
as a pirate has run out.
That can't be true!
This is not the way
Captain Buggy will die!
Yeah! Until the day he finds
Captain John's treasure island
which he has been searching
for with all his heart,
we're gonna stand
by Captain Buggy!
Captain Buggy!
What a compassionate
lion you are!
Richie!
Alright, have fun!
I'll take this Big Top so
you guys take a boat.
What?!
No way! This is
Captain Buggy's ship!
But Buggy is not here!
Oh, that's true.
I'm not going to march
up to death's doorstep -
and I won't let you
waste this ship.
You guys can chase after
Buggy to your heart's content.
We'll never stop
following our Captain!
Whether it's to the great
prison or the end of the world!
Yeah!
I have a feeling that you're gonna
die before you even see Impel Down.
Captain Buggy! Thank
you for everything!
We won't forget what
you've done for us!
Have a peaceful
execution! Goodbye!
See you in next life!
I can feel your grief, Richie!
This is Momonga,
marine code G100660.
We are about to sail on the current
so prepare to open the Gate!
The navy ship that Luffy
and Hancock are on
is approaching
the Tub Current
which is exclusively
used by the Navy
and connects three of the
government's central facilities.
"The Great Underwater Prison
Impel Down"
Just kill me!
Hey, new guy!
How come you're eating without first
paying respect to our cell leader?
Should I say hello every
time I eat something?
Don't be ridiculous!
There's a rule that a newcomer
should give his food to the boss!
That will learn ya!
H-Hey, wait a minute! That
was just a little disagreement!
We're not on death
row! Get us out of here!
It has been four and half days since they
left the Maiden Island - Amazon Lily.
Vice Admiral Momonga! We
are arriving at Impel Down!
Hurry and open the Gate!
Aye-aye, sir!
This is the world's
greatest prison!
We were delayed a bit
because of head winds
but we have arrived
at Impel Down!
Oh boy! We have to hurry!
Get Hancock now!
Yes, sir!
Hancock-dono! We are here!
I'll be right out.
What the hell?! They have more navy ships
here than when they did the Buster Call!
This is the most dangerous
place in the world
so this is necessary.
But - you saw
the Buster Call?
I know it only by
what I've heard.
It was an all-out attack by five vice
admirals with a fleet of ten ships,
and the strongest military
operation by the Navy.
Is this where Ace is?
I think he is being
held deep underwater.
Now, get into my cloak.
Thank you for coming,
Vice Admiral Momonga!
W-Wow! L-L-Look at her!
That's the pirate empress! She's the
most beautiful woman in the world!
Her beauty has no limit!
How many volts is the power of
her beauty?! 10,000? 1,000,000?
What's that noise?
It hurts my ears.
Can I turn them to stone?
Please don't.
The Navy can't take
any more humiliation.
Are we already inside?
Not yet.
Don't rush, Luffy.
The condition
you named was
to see the key figure of this whole
mess, Portgaz D. Ace, wasn't it?
Like I told you the other day,
pirates are not welcomed here
even though you're a Warlord.
So we'll put handcuffs made
of Sea Prism Stone on you
and we'll conduct a strict
body search before you go in.
Because we don't want any ploys
to free any of our prisoners.
Luffy, they'll
search my body.
I'll figure out a
way. Just go on.
I don't mind.
What?! Buggy the Clown
has vanished from his cell?
He ate a Devil Fruit?
Vice Warden! Vice Admiral Momonga and
Hancock-dono of the Seven Warlords arrived.
Alright, I'll be there.
Wow, c-c-cute! Open
the gate please!
Open it fully! Give her space!
Here we go, Luffy!
Take care!
Hancock-sama!
Have a nice visit!
Shut up, you idiots!
Don't be so mean!
And take care!
Help me!
S-S-Somebody!
Get me out!
What a dark atmosphere!
This must be hell.
Finally, we got in! But
we're not in the clear yet.
Welcome to my Impel Down!
Oh, I got it wrong! I said
"my" - jumping the gun!
I'm still the vice warden,
Hannyabal. Nice to meet you!
I'm Momonga.
I knew that you were coming.
And you're Empress
Hancock-dono?
You're my Empress
Oh no, I'm sorry! That
was over-ambitious!
The dumb-ass-warden...
Oh, sorry!
The Warden Magellan is in his office on
level 4 and I would like you to meet him.
Vice Jail Manager Domino
and I will guide you.
It seems like you are in a rush so
let me ask you to come this way.
Vice Admiral-dono, you can go that way.
I'm afraid I have to conduct a body search.
If you were a prisoner, we'd ask you to go inside
of this cell and take off all of your clothes,
then we'd push you into an iron pot filled with
"the warm water of hell" boiling at 200 degrees
to receive your baptism and get sterilized at
the same time and you would be ready to enter.
There are different
classes of prisoners.
Among all recent
newcomers, "Fire Fist" Ace,
Jimbei of the Seven Warlords
and the former Warlord Crocodile
didn't turn a hair while receiving baptism
and entered prison very smoothly.
Please come in. We search guests
in a private room so don't worry.
I'd like you to take
off your cloak.
Those are well-suited for hide
something inside so I'll take it here.
It's not like I don't trust you but you
better not do anything suspicious.
Surveillance Transponder Snails are
everywhere inside of Impel Down
and they keep sending video
to the surveillance monitors.
Wow! This is the
pirate empress!
She's as beautiful
as they say!
Snails! Let me see
Hancock-sama more clearly!
Close-up! Zoom
in for a close-up!
Wow! Cute!
Now, let's just start.
Let me put these Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs on you.
I'm not a prisoner but
you put handcuffs on me.
You couldn't be more careful.
Public execution of Ace...
...is in 33 hours!
Luffy parts ways with Hancock and
infiltrates the prison alone.
He slips through the guard
to search for Ace's floor,
but he finds it harder than he
thought to penetrate Impel Down's
iron-tight security.
Just then, that man with
the red nose appears!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Reunion in Hell?! The Man
Who Ate the Chop-Chop Fruit!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!