Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
If you want to continue traveling with us,
that moment is the only
chance to come aboard.
Say... Karoo...
What would you like to do?
"It All Started on That Day!
Vivi Tells the Story of Her Adventure!"
Igaram! I will...
I will be Queen of the Pirates!
Vivi-sama!
Oh, Igaram, good morning.
What's wrong? You're all sweaty.
Hey! You can't just barge in like that!
Vivi-sama is changing right now!
Ah... well, uhm... Good morning.
Yes, do you want something?
--Ah, no...
--I told you to get out!
Ow, ow... I guess it was just my imagination...
Oh, King. You were there...
Good morning.
Ah... good morning.
At any rate, Terracotta-san is scary.
What were you doing?!
Isn't this too tight, Terracotta-san?
This is how a princess' formal attire is.
I heard that the Square
is already full of people.
Really?
It was announced that
your speech starts at 10:00...
They're being really impatient.
Well, I do understand how they feel, though.
After all, this is your coming-of-age
ceremony that we've waited 2 years for.
Under normal circumstances, this would
have been held when you were 14.
But I don't have anything
impressive to talk about...
It's okay, you don't have to.
All you have to do is show everyone
how much you've grown. That's all.
The coming-of-age ceremony is held
to celebrate you becoming an adult.
Please consider the King's feelings
in taking the trouble to hold it now.
Oh, yes... I heard that your speech today
will be broadcast throughout Alabasta
using transponder snails and amplifiers.
I'm looking forward to it.
I received a report that a
battle started at the harbor.
I see...
Now that it's come to this,
we can no longer get involved...
Fire! Fire! Fire!
Dammit! Shoot cannonballs!
Then I could repel them!
Seriously... Gimme a break!
If we keep taking these iron
spears on the ship's bottom,
it'll be just a matter of time before we sink!
Here come more!
Hey! I can't keep plugging
the holes any more!
Do something, you guys!
It takes all our effort
just to protect one side!
One ship against eight isn't a fair fight!
If this was close combat,
we'd have a better chance...
Whether we chase them or run away,
they'll never change this formation!
This is the Black Cage Unit's specialty,
the "Black Spear Formation"!
You're not good enough
to break it! Idiots! You idiots!
Hey, hypnotist! You're a pirate, aren't you?!
Shut up! I have my reasons!
The one on the left...
Where do I know him from?
I've finally found them!
That annoying violent cook and his gang...!
I'll sink them here today! I've powered up!
Now, stare at this ring.
I'll finally prove today that I'm not a weirdo.
Busy, busy!
One...! Two...!
Jan...
Huh?
Brother!
Whoa...
Usopp! Did you do that?! Amazing!
O... Okay! It was just as I calculated!
That's what happens to
ships once I'm on the job!
Nosie, that was amazing! Good job!
The ships in the south sank! Now we
can break through there in one shot!
Bon Clay-sama! There's trouble!
What is it?!
The "Black Cage" is here!
Oh, no!
What's going on?
It's Black Cage Hina!
She's a captain at Navy Headquarters
and this area is under her jurisdiction!
She's a real pain.
We'll hurry up and fly the coop!
Yes, sir! Bon Clay-sama!
It looks like we've
weakened them quite a bit.
There's no ship that we can't take down
using our Black Cage Formation.
Don't get carried away.
When dealing with guys like that,
if you take them lightly,
you'll end up getting hurt.
Once we pull up, you guys stay back,
or you'll be in my way. That'd annoy me.
Yes, ma'am!
What're you guys doing?! We have to run!
If we pass through that point in the south,
we'll be able to escape
with minimum damage!
If we don't change course,
they'll take us down for sure!
If you wanna go, then go. We can't.
You can't?! Why?!
Bon Clay-sama! Please hurry!
Let's get out of here ourselves!
Noon at the eastern harbor...
...we have an appointment.
We don't have time to go around,
so we have to dash through.
Ahh... that's ludicrous!
Is there some treasure worth
your lives there or something?!
Just go ahead and die, then!
We're going there to pick up our friend.
S... So it's for your pal...
I'm coming in, okay, Vivi?
Sure, come in.
Vivi, what did you want to talk...
Wow...
How amazing...
I mistook you for the Queen
when she was young, Vivi-sama.
Yes, indeed...
Please have a seat, Daddy--
no, Father... Igaram...
I have something important
to talk with you about.
Bon Clay-sama!
Running now wouldn't be like Bon Clay...
--Huh?!
--If we abandon pals who would
risk their lives to pick up their pal,
will we... be able to enjoy
our food tomorrow?!
Listen, guys... Straw Hats, too!
Listen to what I have to say carefully!
Miss Hina! They're dividing their forces!
The duck ship is going south!
The duck is probably a decoy in any case.
Well... Actually, all the
Straw Hats are on the duck ship!
The sheep ship is the decoy!
Follow them! Return to
the formation immediately!
Three minutes!
Prepare to attack!
Ready? Full speed ahead!
Am I the Straw Hat you guys're looking for?!
Just kidding!
Miss Hina! The sheep ship
is heading to the east!
What?!
You were tricked, weren't you?! We're
experts at disguising ourselves! And...
...we're the Straw Hats' friends...!
Even if I go astray as a man...
Even if I go astray as a woman...
...I can't go astray as a person!
If we are to fall, we'll fall
together into the true sky.
I'll make it bloom... Oh, come my way!
By... Bon Clay...
Bring it on!
I'm humiliated...!
B-Bon-chan!
Bon-chan... We'll...
We'll never forget you!
If we are to fall, let it be in the sea...
The flower of friendship... is rejoicing...
We don't know the ringleader?!
Right... It's a so-called
underground organization.
As for their boss, even its members
know nothing about him.
So that's... the enemy of this country...
It's already impossible for us to gain
information on them from outside.
Rather, further investigation
will only put the country at risk.
But we've got a lead, right?
--Yes...
--Hm?
What?!
Igaram, do you know what I'm thinking?
N-No! I don't! I-I have to go back to my work!
--Igaram!
--No! This isn't a game!
Then that's all the more reason to, Igaram!
I can't just sit around and do nothing!
Ahh! They're after us again!
Get out of our way, you bastards!
Look! It's Vivi-sama!
Oh, Vivi-sama!
--Princess Vivi!
--It's Vivi-sama!
Princess!
She's grown up!
Then, Vivi-sama. Let me
ask you just one question.
It all started on that day...
Are you prepared not to lay down your life?
I had... a little adventure...
Hey! The princess's speech has started!
--I've been waiting!
--So she was really okay. I'm glad!
The ceremony in Alubarna has started!
It was delayed by two hours. What happened?
Well... I hope it won't cause a commotion...
Koza! Hey, Koza! Come out!
Vivi-chan's speech has started!
The amplifier is cranked all the way up.
She can be heard anywhere in town.
It was a journey... to cross the
dark sea in search of "despair."
After I left the country,
I saw such a vast sea.
And on that sea, I found
unbelievable, thriving islands...
Creatures I had never seen before...
Sceneries I could barely consider real...
At times, the melody
of the waves was quiet...
...swaying gently, as if
easing my small worries...
Other times, the melody was violent...
...laughing at me, as if it would
tear apart my weak heart...
In that dark, dark storm,
I encountered a single, small, ship.
The ship said to me,
while pushing me onwards...
"Can't you see that light?"
This wondrous ship, which never
lost its way even in darkness,
danced its way across the huge waves.
The ship didn't fight the sea, but its
stem was pointed straight ahead,
even during a headwind.
And the ship pointed and said,
"Look! There's a light!"
History will soon call this an illusion,
but to me, it is the only truth.
What's she talking about?
It's about the Navy that she secretly fought.
And...
Vivi...
You heard the speech, right?
It was Vivi's voice without doubt.
They're just broadcasting the
ceremony being held in Alubarna.
She's already decided that
she wouldn't come here.
No, that voice just resembled
Vivi's voice. That's all.
This is the Tamarisk place, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Let's go. It's past noon.
There's no way that she didn't come!
Let's get out and look for her!
She's definitely here!
Hey, this is bad! The Navy is after us again!
Just how many ships are there?!
Dammit! We're gonna sail out now!
Starboard!
Give up, Luffy. Her case
is different from ours.
What's going on?
What the hell is going on?!
Hey, show your face, fake princess!
No, Squad Captain Igaram!
Where's the real Vivi-sama?!
Where is the princess speaking from?
Vivi-sama is now...
They can throw pretty far...
Everyone!
Vivi!
Karoo!
--Vivi!
--See?! She came!
Vivi-chan!
Let's go back! Better hurry!
The Navy is right there, too!
I came to say goodbye!
What did she just...?
Karoo, give me the handset.
I can't... go with you!
Thank you so much for everything!
Who's she talking to?
No way... Is that the princess of this country?
She should be at the ceremony in Alubarna...
I'd like to go on more adventures,
but there's no ignoring...
that I love this country!
Where is Vivi-sama?!
Beat it, Squad Captain Igaram!
We don't wanna see you!
Nice dancing, Squad Captain Igaram!
--Keep it up!
--We came here to see Vivi-sama!
So I can't go!
I see!
I...
If we're to put a sign,
I'd want it to be an "X."
--Why?
--We're pirates, right?
But it actually means "death"
to your opponents, you know.
That's fine! I want it to be an "X"!
Right, Vivi? It looks cool, right?
Yes, I like it, too!
It doesn't matter what it is.
Just write it. That's not the point!
I...
This will do!
I will remain here...
It's a sign of our friendship!
...but if we ever meet again some day...
...will you call me your friend again?!
Did you hear that? That princess
is connected with the Straw Hats...!
The princess is a friend
of pirates?! Can't be...!
--You'll forever be our...
--Idiot!
Don't reply! The Navy has noticed Vivi.
If we prove she's connected with us,
she'll become a criminal.
Let's part without saying anything.
No matter what happens, this thing on
our left arm is the sign of our friendship!
We're going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
Set sail!
One Piece!
Which direction should I run towards
to see a more wonderful tomorrow?
I took the helm and opened the
miraculous map that I stored in my heart
I aimed for the sky and sought out
my dreams, though at times I got lost
It wasn't a dream; when I met you,
I discovered the wonderful person in me
With just a bit of courage,
I gained something grand
Now's the time for my "wish"
to become my "pledge"
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
Let's sketch out the tale of the future
I'll put all my feelings
in a brand new wind now
Shining ray! Find your brand new way
A never-ending journey to be together
I'll chase after you
wherever you go, Shining ray
Luffy-san and the others are gone now...
I will never forget the important
things I learned on that ship.
We have to work hard for the future
of this country. Okay, Karoo?
I'm sure they'll find wonderful new friends.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Scent Of Danger!
The Seventh Member is Nico Robin!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!