Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
We got to carry on Hard knock days
susumubeki Hard knock days
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
do I have to get up to make my dream come true
tachiagareba My dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
put to the test everyday
tamesareteru youna Everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
karaburi no sukima ni sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air, off-guard, reality countered me
Mercilessly, beat me, hit me, and even if I fall again
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Oh
Only those who get back on their feet and look forward
mou ichido tachiagari mae wo mita mono dake ga
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
will have the last laugh, only winner
(We gotta go, till we make it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted by the mighty winds
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
We're still far from our goal, we got to carry on the way
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
A safe bet? There's no such thing
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance with
Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices on the heads of
Luffy and 11 others, and now they're being hunted by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law finally clash with Doflamingo
at the Royal Palace!
We are birds of a feather.
We Navy and Doflamingo are both out of place.
The Navy will never be a hero
in this country.
If somebody notices that's what you're thinking...
No.
I was just being blocked by you...
It's like a gamble.
I'm sort of a lucky man.
King Riku-sama!
What are we supposed to do?!
If you tell us to fight, we'll take up arms!
--King Riku-sama!
--We'll follow you!
Shall we wait... for a while?
What? Wait?
It won't be too late to choose death.
Did you think you could take me down?
The fact that shitty brats like you guys got conceited
and thought even for a second, that you could defeat me is...
...an unbearable humiliation to me!
Listen.
I'm a descendent of the noblest bloodlines in the world...
The Celestial Dragon!
We're admirable just by the fact of our birth.
I used to possess the most unobtainable power
in the world.
Father! Where are the slaves-eh?!
Let's go buy some-eh!
Father, why don't they fall down on their knees-eh?
Father! Why do they come after us-eh?!
They're a Celestial Dragon family! Don't kill them...
Make them suffer for the rest of their lives!
By the age of ten,
I'd seen heaven and hell on earth.
Then, I killed my father
who caused all that
and returned to Mariejois with his head!
But...
...the Celestial Dragons in heaven
would never accept a renegade family!
I knew there was no way to get out of this hell.
I swore to myself at that moment.
That I will destroy...
...every single thing in the world
that they dominate!
The life I've lived was
on a very different level from yours!
I have no time to play around...
...with you brats!
"The Ultimate Power!
The Secret of the Op-Op Fruit!"
A town located in
the Northwest part of Dressrosa - Primula.
PRIMULA - THE NORTHWESTERN TOWN
W-W-Wait a minute!
Honey...!
P-Please!
D-Don't do it! I'm begging you!
Please!
I don't wanna do this!
But I can't... I can't control my body!
Sorry! I'm so sorry! Forgive me!
With this much stuff,
we can rebuild our ship-yashi!
Deshi, deshi!
Wait, damn pirates!
What're you guys doing
under the cover of fire?!
--Oh no!
--Deshi!
Don't just stand there! Let's run!
I won't let you get away!
You can't catch us!
Stop!
--No-way-poo!
--Puppuku-poo!
Shoot tranquilizer bullets!
They got excited by the fire?
Or do they sense something?
Damn! We're already short-handed!
It's gonna die if we don't stop it!
Tranquilizer bullets!
Do we still have any?!
What's going on?!
You people are the Navy, aren't you?!
Do something about this situation!
Isn't there any way?!
We're short of tranquilizer bullets
as well as soldiers.
What should we do?
If nothing is done...
Vice Admiral Maynard!
What's wrong?!
The fight between Sabo of the Revolutionary Army and Issho-san in Acacia,
winded up in a draw due to injury!
What?! Don't be silly!
The admirals from HQ are
the Navy's greatest military powers!
Why, Issho-san?!
Doflamingo can't keep his position as a Warlord after this!
We have to capture him now!
The Navy has been doing the same thing over and over again just like that!
You have been in the Navy for a long time
haven't you, Vice Admiral-san?
Weren't you even listening all this time?
To these screams filled with anger?
They are not crying! They are angry!
Does the World Government...
...pretend to be God or something?!
Those words... hang over my head...
What should we do?!
But now isn't the time to think about it!
We'll deal with the pirates that
headed for Doflamingo later!
In any event, we'll keep trying to bring
the nationwide confusion under control!
Do your best not to harm
any citizens or animals!
Sedate those who are out of control
with tranquilizer bullets!
That's all we can do now...
I see no end! Can we bring them under control?!
Dad!
Mom!
Are you okay?
Damn! So annoying! Can't take it off!
It's no use!
Dodge, Straw Hat!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Gum-Gum...
...Octopus Stamp!
That was close!
Behind you!
You guys have no idea...
Can you imagine what people would do
to a fallen Celestial Dragon?
People are all...
...cruel.
What are you talking about,
Fake-mingo?!
All right then,
let's begin with the executions.
You're the first, Law...
Hey!
Chop him up into bits and pieces,
like he did to me!
I'm really... disappointed by you...
There's something not quite clear to me.
You're a former Celestial Dragon, expelled from Mariejois.
Why do you still have power?!
CP-0 works directly under the command of the World Gov't
but you brought them into action this morning!
Do you still wish to know that
even though you're going to die soon?
It's because I know about
the important national treasure...
...that they have inside
The Holyland of Mariejois!
The national treasure in Mariejois?
Yes. It's something that could shake the world
by its very existence.
Kill Doflamingo-eh!
We can't keep that kid alive-eh!
To them, I'm an escapee who has the most dangerous card to play.
They tried to kill me but I didn't die
so the Celestial Dragons became very cooperative.
Plus, if I could have had your Op-Op Fruit power
in my hands that day,
I would have taken the helm of the world
utilizing the national treasure in Mariejois!
Your power has such value.
As well as the "Personality Transplant Surgery,"
there's another usage!
Do you know about it?
If a wise man utilizes the Op-Op Fruit, even the dream
people have had since ancient times could come true.
That's why quite a lot of people call it
the ultimate Devil Fruit.
Yeah, I know...
Even though I have no interest in it.
The greatest power of this fruit is
to grant another person eternal life...
...via the "Perpetual Youth Surgery"!
The greatest power of this fruit is
to grant another person eternal life...
...via the "Perpetual Youth Surgery"!
But once it's performed,
the surgeon himself will die.
Indeed!
That's why I wasn't gonna let you eat it!
How dare you repay kindness with ingratitude!
Oh, I'm sorry!
Diamante's swordplay!
Bullet String!
Lao G's martial art!
Room! Injection Shot!
Gladius's gunnery!
You got all your fighting skills from us!
Yeah!
And I'm still here thanks to Cora-san!
I'm grateful!
Because I can take you all down with this power!
TRAFALGAR LAW (10 YEARS OLD)
A BOY FROM THE WHITE TOWN
Damn!
SPIDER MILES - A PORT TOWN IN THE NORTH BLUE
16 YEARS AGO
Don't kill him, Diamante.
This is just a try-out before we take him into our Family as an apprentice.
--You jerk!
--I know, Doffy.
If I beat him,
will you make me an Executive?
DIAMANTE AND TREBOL
♦ ♣ EXECUTIVES OF THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
Can't help my nose from running!
Damn!
Are you serious?
Stop laughing! I'm serious!
You can't kill a person
just with your spirit!
I told you! I have explosives!
I'm gonna die soon anyway
so I'm not afraid of anything!
Don't mess with pirates!
He was just a big talker-dasuyan.
It's over! It's over! Let's play tag!
Okay-dasuyan!
Dammit...
Wait! Wait, wait!
THE WASTE PROCESSING PLANT
No-dasuyan!
Where's the captain?
Our captain Doffy doesn't have time
for a kid like you.
Uh-huh, uh-huh! We understand
you can't live long and you'll die soon.
When? Hey, hey!
When are you gonna die?
Three years and two months from now.
A doctor said so?
My dead father was a doctor.
I found out by seeing my medical data.
What a smart brat.
I wanna kill as many as I can
in these three years
and destroy everything!
He must have a screw loose!
Can't help my nose running!
Well, we accept kids, too.
We had about hundred kids come until now
but most of them escaped crying within two days.
Are you gonna be okay?
Nin! Trebol-sama!
Diamante-sama!
They're the only kids remaining.
What is it? Buffalo? Baby 5?
Cora-san came back!
--He tripped!
--We knew he was gonna trip-dasuyan!
--You tripped! You tripped! You tripped!
--Dasuyan! Dasuyan! Dasuyan!
--You tripped! You tripped!
--Dasuyan! Dasuyan!
Dasuyan....
Doffy won't care if you're a kid or not.
If you do it right, you can get promoted quickly
but if you're useless, that's it.
Well, good luck.
Cora-san, I brought you a cup of tea.
It's hot.
Corazon, did you finish your work
without any trouble?
Then, give me the earnings.
We have to be faithful when it comes to money.
Your name is Law, isn't it?
This guy who just returned is an Executive like us.
His name is Corazon.
CORAZON - A ♥ EXECUTIVE OF THE DON QUIXOTE FAMILY
He's an absent-minded idiot but...
...he's strong, maybe because of his blood.
Captain Doffy's brother by blood.
He can't speak because of a traumatic event
in his past, I heard.
In addition...
He doesn't like kids. Be careful.
What the...?!
Oh, he's dead!
He crashed into the mountain of scrap metal-dasuyan!
What's wrong with him?! He must be nuts!
Damn! Damn!
Damn! Damn! Damn!!
I'm gonna kill him!!
Cora-san caught fire!
Flevance, the country Law was from,
was white and beautiful like a country of snow.
People used to call it the dream country.
His beautiful homeland, however, became a
warzone suddenly and perished from the face of the earth!
The extreme hardships that Law went through as a boy are now revealed!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sad Memories! Law the Boy from the White Town!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!