Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
To rescue his brother Ace who
has been captured by the navy,
Luffy stowed away on a navy ship with
the Pirate Empress Boa Hancock's help.
I'm sure that you
heard about Luffy.
He picked a fight with the World
Government at Water Seven
and destroyed the Judgement
Island - Enies Lobby!
Oh yeah. I told Luffy
about his father.
Luffy was surprised to
know about his father.
It doesn't matter to us at all.
Because Luffy and
I unfortunately
have the blood of the world's most
infamous criminal in our veins anyway.
There was no way for
us to become marines.
I took over the name "Portgaz" from
my mother to whom I owe so much
but I never wanted to have my
good-for-nothing father's blood.
Because I don't have any memory of
him and I don't owe anything to him.
Ah yeah, I understand
but he tried...
What I want to say is...
Old man...
Run as wild as you want
on the sea under my name.
You are my son from now!
My only father is...
Whitebeard!
You better just give up.
Buggy the Clown's luck
as a pirate has run out.
That can't be true!
This is not the way
Captain Buggy will die!
This is the world's
greatest prison!
Welcome to my Impel Down!
Oh, I got it wrong! I said
"my" - jumping the gun!
I'm still the vice warden,
Hannyabal. Nice to meet you!
Now, let's just start.
Let me put these Sea Prism
Stone handcuffs on you.
I'm not a prisoner but you put handcuffs
on me. You couldn't be more careful.
Public execution of Ace...
...is in 33 hours!
"A Reunion in Hell?! The Man
Who Ate the Chop-Chop Fruit!"
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs...
Put out your hands.
Please don't hurt me!
W-What's wrong?!
Come out, Luffy!
That was close!
I was thinking of taking a risk
and sneaking out very quick but
you can turn
anything to stone!
It looks like I can't go
any farther with you.
I can't use my power while
wearing those Sea Prism cuffs.
And they'll take my cloak
away so I can't hide you.
I wish I could do more but...
What're you talking about? I wouldn't
have made it this far without your help!
I was able to get in even though the
building is surrounded. I'll be fine!
Luffy.
They built this place as a
fort that locks people in.
Don't get in any trouble.
Once they catch you, you'll
never be able to get out.
I know that you're strong
but promise me that you
won't get in any trouble.
Alright! I promise!
Thank you so
much, Hancock!
I won't forget what you've
done for me. I owe you!
Did you just call
me Hancock?!
Alright, I got you, Hammock!
Can I have more,
Hammock?!
What're you
doing, Hammock?
Hancock!
Now I can die happily!
Hey! You can revert
them now! I'll be fine!
Finally, he loves me back!
Hey!
It's taking too long.
I think she's being careful about doing it
because Hancock is an important figure.
A thorough body search...
Wow! Do you think that's
what they're doing?!
What are you imagining?!
Beep! Beep!
Vice Warden Hannyabal!
We're not getting any visuals from the snail in
that room! Is something going on in there?!
Domino! Something wrong?
She's not answering.
On the pretext of checking what's
going on in the room as a vice warden,
this is a chance for me to
see Hancock's body search!
Hey!
The body search is done!
Beep! Beep!
We're getting visuals
again! Everything is fine!
I'm sorry. Did I take
too much time?
What? No no!
Everything is fine here, too!
I'm not happy with
this. I'm not a prisoner.
Who do you think I am?
I'm sorry. But that's the
rule here at Impel Down.
It's strange. Feels like I've
lost a part of my memory...
Lead the way now!
Alright then, let's
take the big elevator.
We're gonna go
down to level 4,
the Burning Heat Floor
where Warden Magellan is.
It's hot there so be prepared.
Luffy!
Good luck!
Thank you!
W-What's the matter?!
"Thank You"
"I...
...love...
...you"!
He said "I love you"!
--Hey!
--Hancock-dono! What's wrong?!
Are you alright?!
What happened to
her all of sudden?
Now, where should I go?
He said that the elevator was
going down to the basement.
And Hancock said that Ace
might be held underwater.
Oh yeah!
This Vivre Card would
help at a time like this!
It's this way!
Blugoris are returning!
They got food!
Open the hatch!
--Good job!
--Take the meat to the refrigeration room!
Are you awake? We'll pass
through level 1 shortly.
Help me!
It's worse than I expected.
You can't be serious.
This floor only contains
prisoners with light sentences.
--What?
--She's right.
Level 1 of Impel Down
is the Crimson Floor.
Why is it "Crimson"?
That's a secret!
Next up, level 2 is the Floor
of Wild Beasts from Hell.
Level 3 in the basement
is the Starvation Floor.
And level 4 that we're heading
to is the Burning Heat Floor.
It's gonna take a
while to get to level 4.
In the meantime, you'll hear the
pleasant screams of prisoners
so please enjoy it.
Is "Fire Fist" Ace in level 4?
No, he isn't. We have more levels
than that and "Fire Fist" Ace is...
Luffy...
Ace should be
down these stairs!
Hey, you cheater!
You didn't tell us that you
had that kind of ability!
Shut up!
Being tortured every day and night
here is like dying a thousand deaths!
Are you gonna just
run out on us?!
Huh?! I don't remember
making friends with you.
I'm like a free, wild eagle! If you don't
like it, why don't you do what I did!
Oh, you can't! Then you
have to die like a dog!
--Kiss my ass!
--I'll get you someday!
Buggy!
I already forgot about you!
A Surveillance
Transponder Snail?!
Good evening!
We found him!
Buggy the Clown who escaped
from community cell #4 of level 1...
...is in the hallway in
front of solitary cell #22!
Get him now!
Damn! They found me!
You bastard!
Shit!
Surveillance Transponder
Snail #71 has been shut off!
Did you hear
that? It's Buggy!
That's what happens when you try to
escape alone! That serves him right!
He's gonna get the
worst punishment!
Here comes Blugoris!
Go for it!
Get him!
This Vivre Card keeps
leading me down but...
...it's a dead end.
It's prisoner #8200!
Don't let him get away!
He was hiding the fact that he ate Devil
Fruit! Don't forget a Sea Prism Stone!
Hurry up!
Split into two and get
him from both sides!
Yes! Made it!
Hurry up!
What happened?
"Level 1: Crimson Floor"
Are these all cells?
A scream? Forget it
- I gotta get going!
Go away! Jerks!
Help me!
This way!
They're gone!
"DANGER"? It's not like
anyone is gonna touch it...
What the...?!
Wait!
That was close!
I didn't see that coming!
Hey! The traps over
here have gone off!
Oh no! Somebody's coming!
Stop!
Let's go!
Oh? Looks like they
aren't coming. Oh, well!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Young man!
What?!
Wait a minute! How
did you get out?
What's the matter?
Get out? I got
in from outside!
Okay, bye!
Wait, wait! Quit lying, you!
It's true!
Who are you? You don't look
like a jailer or something.
Why aren't you behind bars?
Man, you guys are irritating!
Oh yeah! Do you
know where Ace is?
Ace?
This Ace that you're
talking about is...
"Fire Fist" Ace?!
Yeah! I'm here to rescue him!
That's impossible!
Yeah, I heard that
he just got in.
They must have put him on level
5. You can't get anywhere near it!
Impossible!
That floor holds all the criminals with
bounties of hundreds of millions or more!
Level 5?
By the way, young man,
can you run to the jailers'
room and bring us some keys?
Yeah! Please, young man!
It must be fate that brought
us together in this big world!
Right?
W-What's that?
That's Blugori!
Blugori?
Run, young man!
They're gonna get you!
Augh! What're those?!
Right side!
Left side!
Unite!
You fools! Don't mess with
a Chop-Chop Fruit eater!
Wow! Straw Hat!
What're you doing here?!
Oh, it's just Buggy.
Right! Shut up! You asshole!
You're as annoying as ever!
I didn't know that
they also got you!
I came here on my own
will! No one got me!
Nobody comes to a
prison on his own will!
Ah? Don't tell me that you
heard that I was captured
and that you came
here to rescue me...
No way! Stupid!
That's gross!
Cut it out! Bastard!
I promised Hancock that I
wouldn't get into any trouble
but you got me involved!
It's not like I'm
enjoying this situation!
Let me go!
Buggy's Peaceful Escape
Plan is officially ruined!
Who gives a shit?
They're ahead of us, too!
Damn it all!
Hey! Should we just fight?!
What're you
thinking, stupid?!
You don't know how painful
all the torture's been!
They're so cold-blooded!
--Doesn't matter if we don't get caught!
--What're you talking about?
I gotta hurry! My cover's
already been blown!
That's what I don't like
about you and Red-Haired!
You guys always stay
positive in a bad sense!
Alright! I'll do it!
I have no choice!
I'll change my plan!
Now for some chaos!
I'm with you!
Luffy joins up with Buggy,
and they use Buggy's Chop-Chop
Fruit power to get through
the prison and find Ace's floor.
But level 1 of the prison, the Crimson Hell,
shows its terrifying true
form and impedes their path.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Break through the Crimson Hell!
Buggy's Chaos-Inducing Plan!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!