Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Thanks, Merry.
Thanks to you, we were able to escape.
I never thought that you'd come, Merry...
But when I think about it,
you've always protected us.
I'm so glad that you're our friend.
Thanks, Merry!
At any rate...
...you guys sure did pull one
outrageous stunt back there.
To start with, to think that you shot
through the World Government's flag...
Well... it's not a big deal.
All we did was take back a friend
who was taken away from us.
"Thank You, Merry!
Snow Falls over the Parting Sea"
Hey! Hey, hey, hey! Usopp!
Where are you, Usopp?!
Hey!
Usopp!
Oh? He isn't here?
Usopp! Usopp!
Usopp!
Where are you, Usopp?!
Hey, he's calling for you.
O-Oh, this isn't good. Without thinking, I...
That's enough! Come out already!
If you don't, I'm gonna beat the crap outta you!
We're gonna beat the crap outta you!
Hey, do you know where Usopp is,
Sogeking? I can't find him anywhere!
D-Don't worry. He went back
ahead of us on a small boat earlier.
What?!
Why?!
But this ship actually belongs to him now...
Just what is it they need
in order to recognize Usopp?
Not here, either.
What's going on?
As we suspected, I can't find
anyone anywhere on this ship.
That's strange.
I wonder who on earth sailed this ship to us...
But we definitely heard
that voice calling out to us.
Is that right?
Yes, someone most certainly called to us.
Like I said all this time...
it was the Merry's voice!
What?! Really?!
Right, Merry?! Say something!
You idiot. There's no way a ship would talk.
I kinda felt that way too, though...
But there's no way something
like that... could happen, huh?
Everything was a mystery to us, but...
...for some reason, these words
remained in my heart.
I don't even know if this person actually
said it or I was imagining things...
Don't worry.
I'll carry you guys for a little bit longer.
This may sound stupid, but...
...I feel that it might've been
an incarnation of the Merry.
You think I'm crazy, don't you?
You don't have to believe me.
Believe you?
This person looked like a sailor
holding a wooden hammer, right?
What...? Why...?
Do you know?
Brother...
You saw a Klabautermann.
K-Klabau...?
Klabautermann.
It's one of the legends known among sailors.
The more care the ship receives,
the more it appreciates the sailors.
This ship probably wanted to somehow
carry you across to the other shore.
She was able to encounter a crew
that she wanted to carry so badly
that she'd borrow a human form to appear...
I bet she's been very happy.
I see...
Then, the one...
...who talked to me then...
...was really you, huh?
Merry...
Hm?
I see a ship coming towards us!
Wh-What?! Who's that?!
It's the Straw Hats!
They're alive!
So you guys're okay!
The Galley-La Company's ship...
This is amazing!
They rushed out in Aqua Laguna and
still made it okay! I can't believe it!
They came back from Enies Lobby!
Ahoy! Ice pops!
Stupid-berg...
Nico Robin...
What a crazy lot.
They took on the World Government...
...and they really took everything back.
Merry!
Look! Their ship is...!
Hey, what's going on?!
What happened all of a sudden?!
All of a sudden? Isn't this just natural?
What?
It was declared that Merry could no longer sail.
But...!
The Merry is...!
Pops! This is bad! Merry is in trouble!
Please do something!
You guys... This is good timing!
You guys're all shipwrights, right?!
I'm begging you! Please do something!
She's our friend who has been
traveling with us all this time!
And just a bit ago she saved us!
So please, pops!
Then let her...
...rest now.
I've already done everything I could.
What's this sound?
Is someone on the scrap heap island?
Isn't this... the Straw Hats' ship?
The damage must've been caused by
Aqua Laguna. It's in a terrible state.
Well, I guess it's beyond just damage...
I want to set sail.
What was that?
I want to set sail one last time!
What am I doing?
There's no hope left for this ship...
Iceberg-san!
What are you doing there?!
Another big wave is coming!
Thank you.
What?! You want to set sail?!
The sea is still stormy!
I'll go alone if I have to.
What?!
We can't let you go out there all by yourself!
I'm watching a miracle right now...
A miracle of a ship that
has long passed its limits...
I've been a shipwright for many years,
but I've never seen a pirate ship this incredible.
It's lived a splendid life.
Let's go back, everyone!
Back to the seas of adventure!
Merry!
I came to get you.
Okay...
Well, then... are you guys ready?
--Yeah.
Merry... The seabed is dark and lonesome,
so we'll watch you to the end.
Maybe it was good that Usopp wasn't here.
There's no way... that he could bear this.
What do you think?
I disagree.
Everyone must someday say farewell.
This is a man's parting.
Not even a single tear should be shed.
He, too... is prepared.
Thank you for carrying us
for such a long time, Merry.
Snow...
Whoa...
A caravel!
Every day we'd play
covered in mud until the sun set
Yahoo!
Now the Going Merry pirate ship is all set!
It's hard to abandon
those innocent days we spent
Cheers to our new ship and crewmate!
Even if I'm a dreamer, I'm still me
Look at this! The Merry
got damaged quite a bit!
When navigating a sailboat,
everyone has to participate!
So things don't all have to fit
together like a jigsaw puzzle
Learn it appropriately!
--Aw...
--Yes, ma'am.
I'm sorry.
What are you doing?!
Cannon practice!
Just as someone's "Yes"
could be a "No" to you,
They sure don't fly good!
I'm telling you, let me try!
Awesome! You hit it on your first try!
you'll surely always be free
Whoa...! I really hit it on my first try!
Even if tomorrow a wind passes
through and breaks the puzzle
No one would blame you for that
Zoro! Hey! That's my seat!
The entrance to the Grand Line
lies ahead of that light.
We had a dream that day
In order to find the All Blue!
In order to be King of the Pirates!
Our belief in ourselves
In order to become a master swordsman!
In order to draw a world map!
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
I-In order... to become a
brave warrior of the sea!
We're going... to the Grand Line!!
We know the pain that
you hold in your heart, so...
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
The entrance to the Grand Line is a mountain!
A mountain?
In the end, we can all surely smile
We made it!
This is the greatest sea in the world!
Go!
Whoa! We're flying out of it!
Don't look back! We're going straight ahead!
Let me... join your crew.
There's no place for me to go or go back to.
So let me stay on this ship.
Oh, I see... Then I guess
we have no choice... Okay.
We continue to dream even today
Luffy!
Who's this ship's navigator?!
We're flying!
Carrying the feelings you
entrusted with us as well
Awesome! The ship is flying!
It's a sky island!
We once again cross these
rough seas and fight the pain
So that our promise won't become a lie
And someday, to you who departed
our ship and live in a different world,
we'll deliver the completed puzzle
I'm sorry...
I wanted to carry you even further.
I wanted to continue going on
adventures with you forever.
Merry!
A voice...
But I--
It's us who have to apologize, Merry!
I'm not good at steering...
...so I ran you into icebergs at times...
There was a time I tore the sails, too.
Zoro and Sanji are stupid,
so they broke all sorts of things!
Usopp would fix them each time,
but he isn't good at it!
So it's us who have to...
But I've been happy.
Thank you very much... for taking
good care of me all this time.
I really have been happy...
...because I had you.
Merry!
It was quite an ordeal, but we're back.
We're back!
The restoration of Water Seven starts now!
Hm... There seems to be a ruckus outside.
Grandma! The Navy is here!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Peace Interrupted! A Navy
Vice Admiral with a Fist of Love"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!