Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Seeking a ship coating craftsman
to help them reach Fishman Island,
the Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
where they met Rayleigh, a craftsman
and the former vice-captain
of the Roger Pirates.
Luffy and company had decided to
hide while Rayleigh coats the Sunny,
when Bartholomew Kuma,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea,
appeared before them.
Three-Sword Style...
...Gum-Gum...
...Diable...
...Mouton...
...Jet...
...600 Pound...
...Cannon!
However, Zoro had doubts about this Kuma...
If this is a fake, then
that's the real problem.
That'd mean there are two
guys who're this strong.
Meanwhile, the rookies
took on Admiral Kizaru,
an assassin sent by Navy Headquarters, but...
This is Borsalino.
What the hell, Uncle! You do
have a Baby Transponder Snail!
Why didn't you contact me?!
Oh?
Oh, Sentomaru-kun!
Don't give me, "Oh!" What are you doing?!
You're on the island now, right?!
Oh, I wasn't able to get
a hold of you, you see...
Whatever! Just get to work now!
The culprits have split up!
Straw Hat Luffy,
Captain Kid, Trafalgar Law...
Which do we start with?
Oh, you don't say? In that case...
Bastard...
If you ain't Bartholomew Kuma,
then who are you?!
You look exactly like
the Warlord of the Sea...
What the hell's goin' on here?!
"An Even Stronger Enemy Appears!
The Battle Axe-Carrying Sentomaru"
You're in the way!
Get the hell outta here, Trafalgar!
I'm taking this guy down!
You're the one who's in the way, Eustass-ya!
Room!
You're a Warlord of the Sea,
yet all you can do is shoot beams?!
There they are! Trafalgar Law,
captain of the Heart Pirates
and Eustass Captain Kid,
captain of the Kid Pirates!
Don't let them escape!
Damn! Now there's a whole load of marines!
This is no time for us to get stuck here!
Bepo!
We're bustin' straight through! Let's do it!
Hold on, Jean Bart!
You're the new guy! Don't give me orders!
Take this!
That bastard took all the fun!
Repel!
That's Bartholomew Kuma,
one of the Seven Warlords of the Sea?
Damn! There's not even time to strike back!
Hey, Zoro!
Th-Three-Sword Style...
--Zoro!
--That idiot!
Hoofprint...
...Blizzard Rose!
Chopper!
Strong Hammer!
Franky Boxing!
Spider Net!
His hand-to-hand combat
abilities are insane, too!
All right! Get ready, now!
Here I come!
Swallow Bon en Avant!
H-Huh?
I'm stuck!
W-Wait! That's dangerous!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Oh, I'm already dead, though...
But this is no time to be saying that!
Special Attack: Atlas Comet!
Now's our chance! Run!
Th-Th-That was scary! Th-Thank you!
H-Huh? He's acting strange!
What?! Now explosives work on him?!
One went in his mouth!
Something shorted out inside his body!
His body's hard, but he still bleeds.
He's just like me, a regular living person
whose body has been modified with weapons!
Nami-san! Look out! He's spotted you!
Oh no!
Ochenta Fleurs!
Cuatro Mano
Shock!
Yes! The beam went off inside his mouth!
He blew himself up!
Sorry to interrupt your little break, mister,
but there's a lightning advisory
right where you're standing!
From the dark clouds to the Climate Baton!
Thunder Lance Tempo!
That had quite an effect! Spectacular!
That didn't affect him at all!
He's still in tip-top shape!
But what is he aiming at?!
Is he acting out of desperation?!
The freak's starting to go berserk!
Give in to despair and the fight's all over!
Hey! Knock him this way!
I'll teach you to be stubborn!
Diable Jambe!
Flambé Shot!
Alright! He's finally starting to fall apart!
Demon Aura Kyutôryu...!
Asura!
Wh-What is that?!
Zoro multiplied!
Nine Lightening Slashes!
Gear Third!
Here goes!
Go, Luffy!
Just one last push!
Gum-Gum...
Crush him, Luffy!
...Giant Rifle!
I'm shrinking!
That stopped the bastard, right?
Yeah, it had to have...
It's creepy...
It looks like it could still start moving...
If it does, we're done for...
I'm so worn out I can't move...
Maybe we should've run away
instead of fighting it...
No, it's best to defeat
whoever we can ahead of time.
We are being chased, after all.
Still, after all is said and done,
what was this guy?!
Given that he's a cyborg,
he must've originally been a person
who looked just like Bartholomew Kuma.
The most natural possibility
is that he was a twin brother
or a super look-alike who was modified.
There's definitely no way to
create a live person from scratch.
PX-4...?
Let's rest a little...
I didn't expect it to turn into
such an all-out fight so suddenly...
I'd love to rest,
but we really should hide first...
If we get spotted again now,
we'll all be caught in one fell swoop!
That's true...
But... wait just a tiny bit longer...
You guys got some nerve!
What?! Another enemy?!
Where's that voice coming from?!
Above! Above!
Hoisa!
Who are you?!
Hey, now! You're a real disgrace, PX-4!
It costs as much as an entire warship
to build one Pacifista like you!
Geez, now what am I supposed to
tell that lousy punk in my report?!
"Captain of Navy Headquarters Science Unit"
"Sentomaru"
The Warlord of the Sea is still here!
I-Is that the real one?!
Real or not, we don't got enough
strength left to fight that thing!
Did you just say "Pacifista"?!
Pacifista? That's like a pacifist, right?
Is that the name of the guy we just beat?
Who the hell are you, Battle Axe?!
How dare you call people
by their weapons' names...
It's no use asking me questions!
I ain't gonna tell you anything!
I got the toughest defense in the world!
As such, my mouth is sealed just as tight!
You can at least tell us your name!
I have no reason to answer anything!
I already told you!
I'm Sentomaru, the most
tight-lipped guy in the world!
Oh, okay. So you're Sentomaru?
Just so you know, I
voluntarily told you that.
I wasn't answering your question.
Let's begin, PX-1!
He shoots beams from his palms too! Not paws!
I don't wanna think about it,
but that means this is a third one!
What's going on?!
Our safety is more important
than that mystery right now!
O-One more fight,
and we will be critically injured...
...before we even run into the admiral!
Yeah...
Let's get away from here!
But not all together!
We'll split up in groups!
Running sounds good to us!
The three of us should split up!
Alright! You gonna be okay?!
Shut up!
I'll protect you, Nami-swan!
Even if it costs me my life!
Okay, thanks! Now let's get going!
Mellorine!
If you're ready to give up your life,
then you can act as a decoy for all of us!
Offer's for ladies only, you damn bastard!
You can protect your own
damn self, Panty-Man!
Zoro-kun! Do everything you can
to protect me, okay?! Please?!
Hold on, Usopp! I'm hurt enough as it is...!
Fear not! I shall cover you!
I would imagine you're still quite damaged!
I was witness to the entire
incident on Thriller Bark
when you stepped in for him!
Oh...
Thanks!
Let's run there!
Yes!
I'm so scared of beams now!
Guys! Meet on the Sunny in three days!
They're splitting up! After them, PX-1!
Don't let 'em leave Grove #12!
Things'll get ugly if they do!
Special Attack: Super Smoke Star!
Now's our chance!
You certainly are dependable!
Crap! The bridge!
Here he comes!
No! Why's he coming after us?!
Whoa, hey, you! Stop it!
Quit pushing!
He went that way! You guys alright?!
This is no time to be
worried about other people!
Not that pirates mean anything to me, though!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Hoisa!
Wh-What the...?!
What did he just do?!
Your attack power is quite nice,
but I have the greatest defense in the world!
Ashigara Dokkoi Shove!
Luffy!
What the...?! This guy is strong, too!
Just so you know, I don't have powers.
Oww...
There's something weird about his moves!
What's the big idea?!
And you call yourself a friend, you brute?!
Get back!
Zoro!
Wh-What?! Who are you?!
Get away! Get away from Zoro, you dumbass!
Z-Z-Zoro-san!
Zoro-san's been hit by a beam!
Hey, Zoro! Hang in there!
Geez, took you long enough!
About time you got here, Uncle Kizaru!
Kizaru?!
Be careful! That man is a navy admiral!
Admiral?!
It's too late for you now...
A 120 million bounty...
Pirate Hunter Zoro...
I'd heard that you're quite the swordsman,
but a one-hit knockout?
Your exhaustion must have really built up...
D-Damn...
The admiral...?
Now you can have a nice, long rest...
Zoro!
We've got a Warlord of the Sea,
a weirdo with a battle axe,
and now a navy admiral?!
If we let you guys escape,
we'll end up losing face.
As we are now, we can't beat these guys!
Everyone focus on escaping!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Admiral Kizaru's Fierce Assault
The Straw Hats Face Certain Death!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!