Edited at https://subtitletools.com
A world... Yes!
A world for you who seek freedom
stretches out right before your eyes.
If your endless dreams are your guide,
surpass them, under the flag of your beliefs!
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
When the summer sun
sways the sails of my heart
It's the cue to open the door to a new world
Sailing through the rocky waves of despair
We head beyond the horizon
Making a splash,
I've just started on my search
Heading towards a world without end
My heart bursting with enthusiasm,
I'll go to the ends of the earth
In search of light yet unseen
"Upper Yard" "Lovely Street"
"Angel Beach"
In pursuit of Nami and the others,
Luffy's group entered the Illusion Forest,
and were greeted with a rigorous
Ball Ordeal by the Priest Satori.
You're still alive? Impressive indeed!
Well, then, as a reward, I'll give
you my prized finishing blow!
Meanwhile, Chopper, who was looking
after the ship alone on the sacrificial altar,
was attacked by Shura, one of the four priests.
No!
Offer your life... to God!
N-No!!
Die!
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
Sky Knight!!
You probably came here knowing this, but...
...you're already a criminal!
Ahh, I'll show you what I do
to aggravating fools like you!!
String Ordeal!
"Profound Mystery!
Ordeal of String and Ordeal of Love?!"
Ah! That's...!
Come out! Ball Dragon!
Oh, it's just a bunch of
surprise clouds put together.
Are we supposed to be surprised by that?
I'll have you know, it's made up of surprise
clouds containing explosives or sharp objects.
What?! Then that means...!
You touch the fire-bomb ball
somewhere on its body and it's over.
One explosion will cause another,
and its gigantic body will
instantly cause a huge explosion!
Surprise Balls! Go, Ball Dragon!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!!
No! Wait, Luffy!!
Whatever you do, don't touch that thing!!
If you lay even one finger on it,
we'll be blown to bits!
How are we gonna fight it if we can't touch it?!
Exactly! Forget about fighting that thing!
Our only option is to run!
So we just keep running?!
How should I know?!
Here it comes!! Jump!!
Why'd we hafta land here?!
You're quite the stubborn ones.
It's the same result either way!
But if you died before you
experienced the power of Ball Dragon...
...it wouldn't be fun!
Aisa!
Where have you been?
Ah! Kamakiri!
Upper Yard again? That's
Vearth in your bag, isn't it?
Don't go there too often...
...or you'll lose your life.
Bahhhh! Don't tell me what to do!
You haven't even been able to beat Eneru yet!
That damn brat!
A chance?
That's right.
For some reason, Gan Fall entered Upper Yard.
That old geezer thinks that he can
settle everything in Skypiea peacefully.
He's got it all wrong.
Win or lose... Those are the
only two outcomes in a battle.
"Wyper Shandian
(a warrior of Shandora)"
The Great Warrior Calgara said,
"Light the fire of Shandora."
We'll follow those words.
It doesn't matter who we have to fight--
the former God Gan Fall, or Eneru.
So long as they reign as "God,"
no matter what their differences are,
to us they're the same!
They all have to be eliminated!
Wyper.
Hm?
A rebel against Eneru
appeared on Angel Island.
I heard it's a young woman.
It's been six years since Eneru started reigning,
and this is the first time.
So what?
Since Gan Fall saved her from judgment,
Eneru now has a reason to
judge even the former God.
Gan Fall has never harmed any of us,
not only as the Sky Knight,
but also as the former God...
...nor has he tried to directly
confront Eneru, either.
That very man finally stepped into Upper Yard.
And if he and one of the priests
kill each other, that'd be great.
Or do you mean to say that
Gan Fall is no longer our enemy?
When men have a common enemy,
they get deluded into thinking
that the one next to them is an ally.
If you have doubts,
then stay out of the fight, Laki!
You'll only be in our way!
Aisa!
What?! I didn't go to Upper Yard!
Don't go into the tent yet.
Wyper, or rather, the man descended
from the Great Warrior Calgara, is angry.
Yeah, that's scary.
He's scarier than God.
Help... them?
Us?
Yes, that's right.
Let's try to create a way for
them to escape somehow.
I can't tell what they're doing... Amazing!
I no longer think that I can
negotiate with your group!
Ha! You're as soft as ever!
What is this fight?
Heaven's Judgment...
That young woman did something foolish.
We are never to... anger God Eneru.
Please come back...
...God!
I got you.
Is something wrong, Gan Fall?!
What did you do?!
Why...?! Why can't we move?!
You won't need the answer...
...when you're dead!
Profound mystery... String Ordeal!
You can enter Upper Yard, but you have to
face difficult ordeals from us, the four priests!
Don't think they can be beaten so easily!
God Eneru is...
...someone who is glorious and distant.
That's right. The sacred
ground will sing again...
...someday, for sure...
Sky...
Sky Knight!!
I've gotta save him. I've gotta save him!
There're skysharks here!
The Sky Knight'll be eaten by them!
Ha! Think of it as Eneru-sama's anger!
B-But how can I save him?
I can't swim... and I'll be
eaten by the skysharks, too.
He says not to harm his friends.
He says not to damage the ship.
He says he doesn't want to die.
What a dilemma.
Such a damned selfish animal!
He really irks me!
If you want to live so much,
then why are you so weak?!
Damn you!
Sky Knight?! Hah! You were forced out
from your position as God, you old fool!
In the end, you were no
match for us, the priests.
Ahhhhh!
Sky Knight!!
Ha! You're a Zoan, aren't you?!
Are you stupid? You can't even swim!
Oh, yeah, you're a Zoan, too.
How inconvenient...
Why don't you follow your master?!
Ahh, how absurd!
I can't stand how weak they all are.
If this was a bottomless river,
there'd still have been some hope.
But unfortunately,
this river does have a bottom.
Let's see... I wonder if those three
escapees have already been hunted.
Is that well that strange?
Yes. It's unbelievable that a well
would be stuck underneath a tree.
The balance between civilization
and nature here is off.
Well, in any case, unless we come up
with a way to cross this cloud river,
we can't walk around this forest.
We're far from meeting God.
The civilization couldn't
estimate the growth of this tree.
I've never seen a case like this before.
Hey, Nami! Can you see
anything from up there?!
The island where God lives... Upper Yard...
Hey! Say something! Did you find God?!
I wonder if she saw something.
This island... Can't be...!
You're pretty much dead.
Hurry up and rest in peace.
I'm a priest. There's no way you can win.
I-I can't go on anymore!
My heart can't take any more surprises.
Soon, you'll be out of options.
Your boat has nearly reached this forest's exit.
When that happens, it's all over!
So long as you can't fly like birds,
you won't be able to get out of here.
You'll wander around in this
forest and die of exhaustion!
That won't...
...happen!!
It will!
Surprise Balls!
Ball Dragon!
Now, it's show time!
Which one is the fire-bomb ball?
Touch it, and there'll be an
astonishingly huge explosion!
Good, now's the time. We can still make it!
I'll leave things here to you, Luffy!
Hm?
Oh? You're gonna climb up that tree to escape?
Why can he read my mind?!
Don't follow me!!
Wh-What?!
Oh, I see!
It was controlled by this string.
I'll take care...
...of this thing!
I can't control Ball Dragon anymore!
What impudence!
Just hang on and come to me!!
Hey, don't hang on with the other hand, too!
There it is!!
So I was right! There's no doubt! That's the exit!
Of course! Why didn't I think of this sooner?
We fell from such a high place.
It's natural that the exit is at the same height!
Now that I know where the exit is,
the boat rule doesn't matter!
I have to hurry. I'm worried about
that huge explosion earlier.
They'd better be okay!
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
That was close! What an unbelievable idiot!
No, he might've been
determined to take me with him.
This isn't good. I'm still insufficiently trained!
He took control of the pace for a second!
If I can't stay calm over a little thing like this,
it'll hinder my Mantra!
You're right!
That was close!
Ah! You're still alive?!
Ahhh! Get off of me! You idiot!
Don't stick to me, you weirdo!
I said get off of me, now! You idiot! Idiot!
Don't let him go, Luffy!
Get off of me!
Don't ever let go of that doughboy!
You...!
Oh, Sanji! You're alive?!
I almost died because of you!!
Pay more attention to others!
Well, in any case, doughboy...
You keep saying "ordeal this," "ordeal that,"
but frankly, it's got nothing to do with us.
However, we accept that stupid sky ordeal...
...because two helpless ladies are
waiting for me to come to their rescue.
In other words, yes...
...this is... a love ordeal!
Is this guy an idiot, too?!
Ahh! I said get off of me!!
Y-You! You! Dammit! Let me go!
You guys play dirty, attacking two on one!
You creeps kidnapped our friends.
You made a cute angel cry and tried to kill her.
You have no right to say we play dirty.
He's right.
It's amazing that you can
predict our movements.
But even if you can predict them,
it doesn't mean anything if
you can't avoid them, does it?
I-Idiots! Stop it! I'm one of
the priests that serve God!
Let me go! Hey, are you listening?!
Not being judged by a priest is
a 1st degree crime in Skypiea!
Now listen here! Attacking me means you
declare war on the Almighty God Eneru!
Shut your mouth! Or the flavor will escape.
For example, when you want to produce
the supreme mignonnette from pepper...
...the important thing is to, strongly, roughly
and without hesitation, beat it to a pulp.
Then, the wonderful flavor
confined inside will be...
Ahhh! Ahhh! Stop it!
Ahhh! Stop it! Stop it!
It's gonna hurt! So stop it!
Concasser!
Even if we're far apart
I don't want you to forget
That on those days when
you're brought to tears
You have a friend here to share the pain
That far-off feeling we refuse to concede
I won't let it just be a dream
The eternal brilliance that
everyone is searching for
We will surely embrace it with our own hands
Phew, it's finally quiet. What's the next ordeal?
After a love ordeal is,
of course, a romance ordeal!
Follow me! We have to
somehow get to the seashore.
It looks like things're gonna get crazy!
This is our chance!
Today we'll definitely crush the
priests and take Upper Yard back!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Light the Fire of Shandora! Wyper, the Warrior"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!