Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people
seek the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future --
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright,
but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really
need everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
Three years have passed since
a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
Seeing hope beyond turmoil,
the people took up weapons.
The burning land is now
enveloped by a sad bellowing
and a mighty swell.
To stop the fighting,
Luffy and company travel
to the green city of Erumalu
and then head for the Yuba oasis,
where the rebel army is.
"Rebel Warrior Koza!
The Dream Vowed to Vivi!"
Hey, quit it!
Look at how much
you spilled! You big waster!
What's the big deal?!
Ace brought a whole bunch with him!
There's a limit to everything!
You've been guzzling away for a while now!
He's tryin' to drink, too.
This is so when Nami-san says,
"Oh, I'm so thirsty!"
I can take it right to her!
Nami-san! Vivi-chan!
Would you like some water?!
Don't be dumb! I'll drink it!
We're fine for now.
Gimme that!
You're gonna spill it! Quit it!
You want some, too?
Thanks. But I'm fine.
Say, Vivi. Could you tell
me about the rebel army?
Yes, I probably should tell
you about it in advance.
It was 11 years ago...
Vivi! Grow up to be a great princess!
"Alabasta Kingdom, 11 Years Ago"
Our village... Our village dried up!
Why didn't you help us?!
But the weather is the doing of the gods.
I may be king, but I cannot
control the forces of nature.
But my dad said the king
could do anything!
I can only do what can be done by man--
Your Majesty! This boy's
father has come to the palace!
My deepest apologizes, Your Majesty!
Forgive my spoiled son!
I take full responsibility!
I'll accept any punishment!
I will do better! Please, I beg of you!
I can't believe what a fool you are!
You fool! You fool! You fool!
Toto, was it?
Yes, Sire!
The kingdom will temporarily
guarantee the livelihoods
of those villagers affected by the drought.
You may live here, in Alubarna,
and make plans for your future!
Oh, what thoughtfulness!
Thank you! Thank you!
Whatever! As if you'd understand
the feelings of the villagers!
Wait! Koza! Get back here!
Toto.
Yes, Sire!
He's a good boy. He spoke
of the villagers' feelings.
He stormed in here for
the sake of the villagers.
Hmph. Crybaby.
What did you say, runt?!
Runt?
Cobra-sama.
What is it, Igaram?
With all due respect,
the kingdom doesn't have enough
money to support all of them.
You fool!
We can just trim down our own
living expenses or whatever need be!
Understood. As you wish.
It's terrible, Your Majesty! It's Vivi-sama!
I had a fight. I lost.
--Vivi!
--Vivi-sama!
That little punk!
How dare he harm a princess!
--I'll pulverize him!
--Wait! Wait! Igaram!
My deepest apologies!
I'll die to make amends!
Enough, both of you!
Fools! It was a children's quarrel!
Welcome! Come on over!
Come on over! Low prices!
It's yummy! Here you go!
It's a showdown!
--Come on over!
--Fight! Fight!
Don't go easy on her
'cause she's a princess!
Teach that sassy princess a lesson!
You can do it, Vivi-chan!
Hey, you! Koza's our leader, you know!
If I win, I get to be your leader!
Like I'd ever lose to you, pipsqueak!
I've always been our leader in the village!
Here goes!
Listen, guys!
As of today, Vivi is the
vice-leader of our Sand-Sand Clan!
Anyone got a problem with that?!
No!
Look, Igaram.
Vivi has made friends.
Yes.
That is the most important thing to have
if she's to carry Alabasta
on her shoulders someday.
Toto-ojisan! Ma'am! Good morning!
Where's Leader?
Oh, good morning! If you're
looking for Koza, he already left!
I assume he's at the usual spot.
See you later!
Oh, Vivi-chan!
What will you do about lunch?
I'll eat with you! Thanks!
What a strange country this is!
The princess of a kingdom,
mingling with commoners like us!
It's proof of peace!
Igaram-san. Will you join us for lunch?
No, no, that's quite all right!
I brought rice balls!
Well, I must be going!
Your Majesty! What are you doing here?!
Urgh! Sire!
You're following me again?!
B-But I'm worried about Vivi-chan...
Go home! You'll only cause me more work!
What?!
Don't give me, "What?!"
--Sounds like it was a nice country.
--Yes.
--Gimme that water!
--You wish!
But a lot happened...
Heya, girly!
Headed out? Want us to come with ya?
Attack, Sand-Sand Clan!
What's with these guys?!
They still haven't kicked the bucket?!
Leader! Everyone!
Run, Vivi! These guys are out to get you!
--Get going, Vivi!
--They're gonna kill you!
But... Leader!
We ain't gonna kill ya!
We want ransom money,
so we're just gonna kidnap ya!
Damn you!
Now come here, Princess Vivi!
I won't let you have her!
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
What is that?!
What is this thing?!
Huh? What is this?
Poke, poke, pokey, poke.
It's huge!
Wow!
Say. Tell me more about what happened!
Yes. Our leader, Koza,
was a very strong-hearted boy...
But I was worried for that heart once...
I won't let you have her!
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
What pathetic excuses for bodyguards!
There are more of 'em?!
Oww! Oww!
Damn! She got away!
The ruins are that way! Catch her!
Don't let 'em go!
Move!
What on earth?!
Hey! What happened to you?!
What happened here?!
Some bad guys came to get Vivi...
What?!
Grownups, with blades...
They just went into the ruins!
Koza went after them, too!
What?!
Oh, Princess! Where are you, Princess?
Where the hell are you hiding?
Find her! Find her!
Don't let her get away!
Princess Vivi! Come on out!
Oh, there ya are!
Please, just let us catch
you like a good little girl!
Not so fast!
Leader!
You alright, Vivi?!
Oww...
Don't underestimate the
Sand-Sand Clan, villain!
Leave this city at once!
Listen, boy. Shut up and
give the princess here.
It's not smart to make grownups mad.
A blade! Let's run away, Leader!
--That doesn't scare me!
--Huh?!
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
Leader! Don't do this!
You wanna fight, huh?
Leader!
Bastard knocked our boss out!
What the hell?! Let's give him a thrashing!
Alright! Come here!
Hey, you!
You dimwits!
Daddy! Igaram!
Vivi-sama! Are you all right?!
Curse you! Thought you could
kidnap my daughter, did you?!
You lousy vagabonds!
Take this! And this! And this!
These appear to be their friends.
Chaka! Pell! What are you doing here?
Why? That's what we'd like to ask you.
What is the king doing in a place
like this, away from the palace?
You should refrain from
acting so recklessly.
Igaram! Koza's been hurt!
Yes! Let's get him to a doctor immediately!
The Sand-Sand Clan members
atop the hill, as well!
Chaka! Pell! Make arrangements at once!
Yes, sir!
What brave children!
What's wrong, Vivi? Why so glum?
I was so scared...
Yeah, I was scared too.
They had blades with them and all...
No!
You told them to protect
me to the death, Leader...
Protect her to the death, Sand-Sand Clan!
Don't talk about dying, Leader...
Oh, more than anything,
she was afraid of losing her friends...
Vivi is still little, but a princess, Koza.
Your deed today was an immense one.
You have my gratitude. Thank you.
Vivi's a friend. It was only natural.
I see.
I can tell the next generation of
Alabasta will be in good hands.
Do you like this country?
Yeah! I was born here!
I'm the same way!
I'm...
I'm also a bit concerned.
How so?
Standing above others requires
difficult decisions in no small measure.
Vivi-sama is too kindhearted for that.
Igaram.
Yes, Sire?
This is fine. Alabasta is
fine just as it is now.
Allow me to accompany you,
for as long as I live!
Yuba?
Yeah! Your dad talked
to my dad about it!
Old man Toto?
He asked if he'd want to start a
town at the empty oasis of Yuba!
That area's like the
crossroads of Alabasta,
where all kinds of travelers
and merchants pass through!
Just wait until a town is built there!
So many citizens will be happy!
Awesome, huh?!
And my dad was asked
to be its representative!
Are you going too, Leader?
Of course!
My dad says to stay here...
...and starting a city is no easy matter...
...but I'm gonna do it!
I'm gonna build a new city
with my own two hands!
This country needs the city of Yuba!
We're counting on you, Toto.
Yes, Your Majesty!
We will build a wonderful city!
Well, Vivi-chan.
This is goodbye for a while.
Come visit sometime,
once the city's taken shape!
Okay, Toto-ojisan!
We're gonna make an awesome city
and make this kingdom even lusher!
Time to go!
Bye, Vivi! Grow up to be a great princess!
Yeah!
Koza! Don't act so high and mighty!
Oww!
Koza is right.
Yuba will surely make
this country lusher.
I see. This Koza friend of
yours was a really nice boy.
But that has something
to do with the rebel army?
Yes. It does.
We're going to the city of Yuba,
where the rebel army is stationed.
And the name of the rebel army's leader...
...is Koza.
You don't mean--!
The boy I just told you about.
Nami-san! Would you
like some too, Nami-san?!
This desert shrimp is yummy!
It's not a shrimp! It's a scorpion!
C-Can't eat any more!
Knock that off, you guys!
Let's go, Lashes!
What's she so mad about?
Beats me.
Like the adventurers
I dreamed of when I was a child
I continue on to the ends of emotion
I scoop up my hands,
and the sand and time
that spills from them
show me that this is
what I was born to do
Let's continue swimming
at a near-tumbling speed
Until we wash up someday
on a white sandy beach
no one knows about
Ace hardly seems like
a wanted criminal, huh?
Yet, pirates all over the world
fear the name "Fire Fist Ace."
What kind of pirate is this
Blackbeard he's chasing?
I hear there's someone who beat Blackbeard.
--Yeah, a bounty hunter named Scorpion.
--There's someone that awesome?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Showdown in a Heat Haze!
Ace vs. the Gallant Scorpion"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!