Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil
and involved in an all-out war!
Now, set off the fireworks!
Okay, I cut you already.
Quinto Tierce Fantasia!
Mil Fleurs...
...Gigantesco Mano...
...Stomp!
The Soldier Dock System!
Channel 4!
FR-U 4!
I'll take care of it!
The new number! Channel 5!
Brachio-Tank 5 is here!
Come on out, Kraken!
There are only 10 of them!
Just crush them all!
Then it'll finally be over!
Oh, hey, Surume!
It's me! Surume!
The Kraken betrayed us!
Listen, Surume! Stay here
and protect Yowahoshi!
Um, thank you for doing this, Surume-sama!
"Iron Pirate!
Here Comes General Franky!"
They're pushing their luck too far!
I'll make them pay for this!
Where am I?
You're in Conchcorde Plaza.
Don't you remember?
Looks like they have some good swordsmen!
Get out of my way!
Don't cut me! Hyouzou-san!
Get away!
Run!
Oh? What's going on?
They're trying to escape from us!
I guess they're scared of us!
Let's take out their
officers while they're gone!
Yeah! Advance!
There is one of them right in front of us!
Prepare to fire!
Roger! Preparing to fire!
Oh? He's gone!
Cookie Cutter!
There he is! Prepare to fire!
I'll get him this time...
Oh, he's gone again!
There! Fire!
What?! Oh, he's gone again!
No, there he is!
Damn! He moves so quickly!
Hey, Commander Chopper!
It's rattling! Is there something wrong?!
What? What?! What?!
It's a sink hole!
That serves you right!
Special Attack - Daruma Drop!
Ouch!
I just dug a web of tunnels
underground with my fangs!
Hey! What happened?!
Usopp! Chopper!
Now, I'm gonna take care
of that stupid biker too...
Oh no!
A sink hole!
What?! Is he dumb?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Hey! Are you okay, guys?!
Bastard! Super I won't forgive him!
You guys, get out!
Why?!
Are they splitting up?!
Hey, what are you doing, Franky?!
How dare you kick the commander out!
Because it's gonna turn
into a single-seater!
Let's get perverted!
You're already a pervert!
Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Stand by!
Oh, it perverted!
That's not it!
Brachio-Tank 5!
Head change!
Black Rhino FR-U 4!
Docking!
What?! Docking?!
Iron Pirate!
General Franky!
Awesome!
What the hell is that?!
Cool!!
Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
The transforming robot of our dream!
The mad genius Vegapunk
who I haven't met yet.
I realized his old dream...
...after trial and error
for the last 2 years.
By using the shape-memory
alloy called Wapometal,
I finally did it!
D-Don't be intimidated by its looks!
Oh, so strong!!
There is more to come!
Look at this! This is
the "plunderer's sword"!
Franken!
He has a sword!
General...
...Watch-Your-Step!
Striking below the belt!
It's unmanly but effective!
The cannons in these shoulders
will get you while you're jumping!
What?!
What?! Cannons in its shoulders?!
Franky Cannon!
Oh, the cannons are in your shoulders!
--But...
--...you're so cool!
--Oh yeah!
Oh, how awesome!
Dammit!
He's so tricky!
I've got more new weapons!
Watch out!
Come on! New weapons!
General...
...Weight!
It's so heavy!
--You're so cool, General!
--Weight! Weight!
What's so cool about that?
Oh!
Here is a weak one!
How dare you say I'm
weak! I'm just a chicken!
Sorcery Climate Baton!
Watch out for a gust of wind.
Gust Sword!
Do you understand now?
It's Weatheria's science of weather!
Don't underestimate it!
Oh? Huh?
Where did Chopper go?
Let's get that guy!
Damn! I got kicked out of the tank after all!
I have no other choice but to fight.
But I'm not scared!
Because I'm not the same
person that I used to be!
Special Attack - Green Star!
Bamboo Javelin!
Master Heracles'n!
I'll never forget those 2 years that I
spent in the deadly Swindling Forest!
It begins now!
The second chapter of "The
Adventures of the Real Man Usopp"!
I'll make sink holes all over the plaza!
Doesn't matter if it's a cool robot or
something else! Once it falls down, it's all over!
What is that?!
Somebody else is digging too!
Daruma-san got blown out!
Wh-Who is it?!
It's me!
Horn Boost!
I'm good at digging too!
Chopper!
Cool! You can turn into a stag beetle now?!
It's not a stag beetle!
I strengthened 7 of my transformation
boosts in the last 2 years!
I only need the Rumble
Ball for just one boost now!
So I can turn into any other
forms whenever I want!
What a pain-in-the-ass coral guy!
I'll bite your flesh off!
These are not coral - they're horns!
And I'm a pain-in-the-ass monster for you!
They all seem so full of
life when they're fighting!
Like they've been waiting
to fight for so long!
How many of them have we killed?
N-None, sir.
Kraken!
Good job, considering it was you.
You gained their favor so
slickly and caught Shirahoshi!
Now, squeeze her to death!
Your brother at the North Pole...
I know exactly where he is.
We can just go there and
kill him whenever we want.
You brothers are mythical creatures.
Even dead, I can sell you for a good price.
Don't tell me that's what you want.
Kraken?
I can't believe this.
He was obeying Hordy because his
brother was taken as a hostage!
I'll tell you one last time!
Squeeze Shirahoshi to death!
Huh?
Surume-sama, y-you're hurting me!
Surume!
So you were doing everything he says
in order to save your brother's life?
I know how you feel.
Is it your younger brother or older brother?
Let me try to save his life too!
Did you forget?
I'm your friend!
Surume-sama!
Straw Hat is coming this way!
Kill him!
You guys are no match for him-dogon!
Let us take care of him-ch!
Straw Hat!
We won't let you come any
closer to our captain-ch!
Drop dead!
We won't let you guys...
...Get in his way!
Stop Straw Hat!
Second Gear!
Where did he go?!
What?!
I don't know why but I'm full of fight now!
Awesome!
How did he get there?! I couldn't see him!
That's...!
I can't believe it!
That's...
...the Ship of Promise!
"Noah"!
As Luffy and Hordy begin their battle,
suddenly, directly above
the Conchcorde Plaza,
the massive form of Noah appears
and terrifies the citizens.
As everyone begins to lose hope,
Shirahoshi places herself in front
of the Noah to save Fish-Man Island.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Noah Closing in! The Fish-Man
Island Facing Destruction!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!