Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
I don't know the answer yet
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
Oh
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Inside the bay, the Whitebeards
are trying to get to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their way.
And at the bay head,
the Pacifistas began to attack
the allies of the Whitebeards
to exterminate them!
Stop perpetrating this farce, Whitebeard!
I know about your deal with the Navy!
You have their assurance that the
Whitebeards and Ace will remain safe!
You have sold the 43 captains
of the allied pirates to the Navy...
...in exchange for Ace's life!
You know what you have done, right, Squard?
You thrust a sword into your father's body.
You're such a stupid son!
But I love you, son, even if you are a fool.
So, Squard, treat him kindly.
I don't love him any more than any other.
You are all family to me!
He has never changed at all, Sengoku.
He shook us up very well.
How ridiculous to say that I sold my sons!
He gave the pirates the way out.
I should never underestimate that guy.
If you are a pirate, you pick what
you want to believe on your own!
Those of you who'll follow me,
lay down your life for it!
Be ready! He's gonna run wild!
He's the strongest man in the world!
"The Encircling Walls Activated!
The Whitebeard Pirates backed into a corner!"
Whitebeard's on the move!
Follow Pops' lead!
Clear the way for Pops!
Don't let them come closer!
Fire!
Whitebeard!
Activating the encircling wall!
Do it faster!
Yes sir!
What's wrong?!
I-It seems like...
...the ice inside the bay is blocking it!
Figure out how to fix it!
Yes sir!
What's going on here?
I was told that Pops had
sold us, the allied pirates,
to the Navy in exchange for Ace
and that that was all there was to say.
Then why does Pops...
...save us and keep fighting?!
It doesn't make any sense!
That's not what I've been told!
Damn Squard, he's been fooled
by the Navy and stabbed Pops!
That's so preposterous!
How painful it is!
If this is the truth...
I...
I've done a horrible thing!
I'm sorry, Pops!
I'm sorry, Ace!
Squard!
Can you pay them back by crying?!
They played a dirty trick on us!
That old man is amazing!
He can fight even after being stabbed!
Anyway, I gotta focus on saving Ace!
Luffy-kun!
Jimbei!
Look at that!
They all went up to the plaza
while we weren't paying attention!
Hmmm! I have a bad feeling about this!
But the old man is in
the middle of the action now!
There is no time to think!
Yeah! Nothing will stop us!
Not ready yet?!
I'm sorry!
The ice is thicker than we thought!
Fire!
You alright?!
It's nothing! Keep moving!
Advance!
The wall isn't activated
yet! This is no good!
I'm gonna buy us some time!
Vice Admiral!
I'm not gonna let you get to
the plaza, Whitebeard Pirates!
I-It's Vice Admiral John Giant!
You're standing in my way. Move it.
I lost my balance!
Vice Admiral!
The ground is tilting!
Don't get close to Pops!
It's worse than an earthquake!
Whitebeard!
Ow, ow, ow...
The sea is...
I can't believe this!
Not just the island but the sea is...
...also tilting!
How outrageous that old bastard is!
Luffy-kun!
Jimbei!
I'm going to pull you up!
Thank you! I appreciate it!
Don't mention it!
Doesn't that old man care
about his own teammates?
His crew knew what to do, they evacuated.
Are you alright?
Ouch... Was that the end of the world?
I can't believe it!
So this is what the
strongest pirate is capable of!
What deadly power!
But in the name of absolute
justice of the Navy,
I can't let you pass through here!
It's coming!
It will reach the scaffold!
Keep going and destroy it!
Hey! Is the scaffold alright?!
Did it reach it?
It didn't hit the scaffold!
What made it veer off?!
Look at that!
3 admirals!
This happened because
the walls are not ready!
Your damn ice is blocking it!
Why couldn't you just melt it, Sakazuki?
Damn!
I can't believe that they've
repelled Pops' shock wave!
Don't be scared, guys!
Commander Jozu!
Let's charge them while they're off balance!
We cannot miss this chance provided by Pops!
Let's go, Whitebeard Pirates!
Advance!
Seems like they're all very angry.
How scary!
What's going on with the encircling walls?
I-I'm afraid...
Divert all power from the city!
Pass it on to the walls!
Yes, sir! Right away!
Ace!
Luffy!
I'm on my way!
Ace!
Full power!
Wh-What is that?!
Th-The walls!
We're enclosed!
What the hell is this?!
Take this!
Did it break?!
No, not even a scratch!
This steel wall must be very thick!
These steel protection barriers are what
they were calling the encircling walls?!
Damn! Aren't you gonna fight us, Navy?!
Hey, look at those!
They're all aiming towards us!
We gotta run!
We're enclosed! There's no place to...
There is a place!
Hey, what's wrong?!
It should be fully activated!
I-I'm afraid that the wall
can't lift the giant body of Oars!
It seems like his blood is
running down in the system
and making it less powerful!
Damn the Giant!
Oars! Y-You're...
What a guy!
He is still fighting, you know.
We have a chance to win!
We can't close it but...
...do it, Akainu!
Meteor Volcano!
He's firing lava fists into the air!
Wh-What's going on there?!
They vanished into the sky.
What's this noise?
What are they?!
They can't get away!
Melt the ice that they're standing on!
The Whitebeard Pirates
are trapped in the bay.
As the Navy's concentrated fire continues,
they try to reach the plaza
via the path Oars opened,
but the order to execute
Ace has finally been given.
What will Luffy do now?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Execution Order Issued!
Break Through the Encircling Walls!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!