Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
Zoro's coming down!
Cien Fleurs! Spider Net!
Eat this! You're still a zombie!
Special Attack! Salt Star!
How do you like that?
I-It wasn't enough!
Not for his massive body!
Heavy Gong!
D-Damn it, Luffy!
I don't know any of you losers!
I am Moria-sama's servant, Oars!
"You're Going Down, Absalom!!
Nami's Lightning Attack of Friendship!!"
One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven, eight...
Huh?
But some outsiders got thrown into the mix.
So that leaves the guy
I saw in the straw hat,
the orange-haired woman, and the cool hero.
I'm still missing three people.
Where could they be? Hmm?
No! I hate roaches! Gross!
Usopp 10 Ton...
No, no, no, no...
...Hammer!
She's awake!
--Not the hammer!
--Perona-sama!
--I hate cockroaches! Hurry and
get them off of me! Hurry!
--Perona-sama, please come to your senses!
--I hate roaches! Ew, yuck!
--There aren't any cockroaches.
We removed the sticky stuff
that was on your hand.
Where am I?
Your foe is long gone.
Perona-sama, you were
out cold when we found you.
What did he do to you?
I can't believe someone knocked you out!
Who trashed the mansion?
Was this the pirates' doing?
The pirates are certainly causing mayhem,
but this looks like Oars' handiwork.
Oars?!
What was he...?
As a matter of fact, word has it
Oars wiped out the General Zombies.
The ultimate corps?!
So we can't control Oars?!
Well, I couldn't say one way or--
--Guys!
--Brothers!
Woman!
O-Oars?
C-Come to think of it,
I heard he stepped on Hogback-sama.
What?!
Woman!
Is the woman around?
He's looking for a woman? Yikes!
I've gotta get away from here.
Between the pirates and Oars,
Thriller Bark is toast!
Hurry and gather up the treasure and food!
We're going to stuff it into their
pirate ship and make a break for it.
Whose ship?
The Straw Hats'! We're escaping
on their ship, so hurry it up!
Okay, we're on it!
Sheesh...
Woman!
Perona-sama!
Kiss the bride.
Yeah, let's speed through this.
I'm growing impatient!
Smooch...!
What?! W-Wait! What're you doing?!
No, stop it!
You've come to? Grah, give it up!
Once I give you this binding kiss,
you will become my lifelong companion!
I've already turned you down,
you perverted invisible beast!
I'm still at that age where
I want to go on adventures!
Shut up and rejoice! You will be
the King of the Grave's wife,
making you the Queen of the Grave!
Ew! What the hell?!
Heh, heh!
Curse you, Namizo!
--Lo...
--Lola!
Namizo...! Why, you...!
How dare you try to steal him from me?!
You said that you were shipping us!
That was a lie, wasn't it?
You were doing the opposite of shipping us,
and trying to steal Ab-sama.
You're a two-faced jerk!
W-Wait, Lola! Just a second.
I've been out cold this whole time.
I don't even know what's going on.
Oh, I'm in a wedding dress.
Why am I wearing this? Cool!
There's nothing "cool" about this, traitor!
Wait! You've got it all wrong!
Damn it, Lola! Not only
did you crash my wedding,
but now you have the gall
to attack my bride?!
Shut up and marry me!
Hell, no!
Ab-sama, I bet you don't know, do you?
A-About what?
This woman's real name is Namizo!
"She" is actually a "he"!
What?!
No, that can't be true... Seriously?!
Oh, yeah. That's what I told Lola.
So you're wasting your time!
Pursuing him will get you nowhere!
Do you get it now?
I've been chasing a man this whole time?
And I came within an inch of kissing him?
But I checked out his body in the bathroom...
I made it just in the nick of time.
I'm sure this is the place.
Usopp, Chopper! Wait out in the hallway.
Okay...
I must have imagined that...
Nami, you okay?
Everything's fine, so don't look in here!
Okay.
Th-That was close.
Boing! Boing!
Ba-boing!
All of the bouncy parts were there...
Make yourself scarce, Namizo!
Stop it, Lola!
Hey, hog! Stop it, Lola!
Beat it!
She isn't hitting me?
Namizo...
Lola?
Run for it, Namizo! I will hold him back!
I came to rescue you, my friend!
Lola!
Ab-sama!
Now, if that's sunk in, swear your
vows to me instead, Absalom!
Lola...
There goes the bride!
Your bride is right here!
I'm certain that she is a woman!
Lola, stay out of my way!
Lola!
Lowly zombie!
You've made me... waste my energy on you!
Oh, smart move!
Have you decided to stop running?
That's right. It's not like...
you could escape, anyway.
I'm an invisible man!
Thunder Charge!
How dare you?!
I think you and Beast Man
would make an awesome couple!
I was totally shipping you!
Really?
No one has ever encouraged me to
pursue my feelings for him before...
You're the first person to offer
such kind words of support.
I... I...!
Raise your head, my friend.
This is what you call "friendship."
I am Namizo. Please call me "Nami."
Friendship...? Nami!
Namizo...
Lola?
Run for it, Namizo! I will hold him back!
I came to rescue you, my friend!
How dare you hurt Lola?!
That's right! Dive into my arms!
Swing Arm!
It's not like that'll do anything!
That's why I'm going to...
Huh?
Ab-sama!
That's right! Dive into my arms!
Why? It didn't even faze him
on top of the bridge...
Sure enough, he had already reached
his limit after fighting that man.
It's no wonder.
Well, it's all cool.
I won! Yay!
I must have hit some vital organs!
Lola!
Are you okay? Hang in there.
Thank you for coming to save me.
Why are you thanking me?
We're friends, aren't we?
But I used to be so scared
of you that I told you a lie.
I'm sorry. I'm actually a woman.
Silly! I know that.
Lola...!
More importantly, isn't Ab-sama wide open?!
Be my groom, Absalom!
Huh?
Are they here? Nope.
Wait!
Wait, darn it! Giant Shallot!
Stop already!
Hold up!
Man!
Shoot! I lost sight of him.
Gum-Gum Whip!
I can't find Moria!
Whip!
There he is!
Wait!
Wh-What was that all about?
Wasn't that Straw Hat just now?
But didn't Straw Hat say that
he would "kick Moria's butt"
and race off to the castle?
What was he chasing after?
I wonder what he's hunting down, don't you?
M-Moria!
He said he was going to kick my butt?
Do you seriously think
Straw Hat can pull that off?
Sorry to burst your bubble,
but that's impossible.
The most losers like you who hide in the
forest can do is spend your time praying.
Are they in here? Come on out,
Straw Hat! Woman! Cool hero!
Damn, that's one nasty monster.
He's insanely powerful and fast.
What was his name again?
Uh...
I'm pretty sure it's Rose.
No, that's not right!
It ended with an... "s."
--Hughes?
--No, I think you're getting colder.
Orse?
Hm? No, I still don't
think it's quite right...
It's Oars.
That's it!
Uh, I'm sorry. I still can't...
Yeah, we know how it is.
Could you give us some space?
Sure...
Try to avoid his attacks.
Okay...
Hey, Oars!
If Luffy's shadow is inside of you...
...you shouldn't underestimate the
underlying strength of your crew!
I can't believe Oars is able to replicate
Luffy's moves with that massive body!
Now that it's come to this, we'll have
to do "that." Let's teach him a lesson!
We'll show him the strength
of our powers combined!
No way...! Do you want
to do "that" here and now?!
Let's do it, guys!
Tactics #15!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Knock Him Down!!
Special Attack: Straw Hat Docking?"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!