Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
I don't know the answer yet
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
The voice inside of me
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
Wicked rain will get in my way
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
shinjita sono saki e to...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
The historic War of the Best
in Marineford has ended.
10 years ago, in the East Blue,
Luffy met Ace for the
first time when he was 7.
I won't say it!
Then you die.
Don't!
"I Won't Run! Ace's Desperate
Rescue Operation!"
Outta my way!
--It's him, Porchemy-san!
--He stole the money from us! Damn you!
What?
A-Ace!
You made it easier for us
by coming here voluntarily!
We were having a hard time
making your friend talk.
Ace!
L-Let me go!
Sabo!
Porchemy-san!
Ace! Sabo!
It kind of hurts. Hey!
Do you know what happens
when you mess with adults?!
I'll fight you! Sabo, help him!
Ace!
He has a sword! Be careful!
Oh, he got the knife!
Porchemy-san, that kid...!
Let's go, Ace!
Go ahead!
You fool! Hurry up!
When I come to face someone, I won't run!
What'd you say?! You little shit!
Don't do it! He's not like
the thugs in the city!
You got that right!
Alright! Enough playing
around! That's our money.
Give it back to us peacefully, brat!
You must been possessed by
some evil spirit, right?
Give the money back so you won't regret it.
We have better plans for that money!
Wh...
What did you say?!
Wait here for a minute!
You're so reckless!
Why are you always like this?!
I won't run!
Stop talking crap!
If I'm beaten by kids, I may
as well quit being a pirate!
--We'll make sure you quit!
I'm gonna kill all of you!
I heard the whole story,
Porchemy. How pathetic.
Did you honestly get beaten by kids?
I'm sorry, Captain Bluejam... The money is...
Don't look at me! I don't
even want to see your face!
Now, who will get my money back?
Don't tell me we'll let
it go without a fight.
Of course not. We'll get it back right away.
You have a bad habit, Ace!
When faced with a real
pirate it's best to run!
Why do you have such a death wish?
This doesn't feel right.
I liked the one I had.
We made a stupid mistake.
The Bluejam clan won't forgive us.
They'll come after us!
Oh, that was scary!
I thought I was gonna die!
You're so annoying! Shut up!
Stop crying already!
I don't like cowards or people who cry a lot!
Th-Thank you!
You...
You helped me!
--You...!
--Whoa, he's just being thankful.
Why didn't you cough it
up in the first place?
They're kind of people who'd kill
women or kids without hesitation!
I thought if I said anything...
you wouldn't be my friend.
It's better than dying, isn't it?
Why do you wanna become my friend that much?
Because...
Didn't I give you a hard time until now?
How could you follow me this far?
Because...
Because I have nobody else to trust!
I can't go back to Windmill Village
and I don't like the mountain bandits!
If I didn't follow you, I'd be all alone!
Being lonely is more
painful than getting hurt!
Where are your parents?
Grandpa is all I have.
Is it easy for you when I'm around?
Uh-huh.
--It's hard without me?
--Uh-huh.
What if Gold Roger had a child?
I hope that there isn't such a child!
He must be some kind of devil
who'd be better off dead!
Do you want me to live?
Of course I do!
I see.
But I don't like spoiled kids like you.
I'm not spoiled! I'm strong!
Strong?! You're not strong
at all! You cry like a girl!
Have you ever gotten hit by
a spiky thing? I'm only 7!
When I become your age - 10, I'll
stop crying and become stronger!
I wouldn't cry even if I were
7, stupid! I'm not like you!
I'm gonna become stronger than anyone!
I promised Shanks that I'd
become a great pirate!
--You? Become a pirate?
--Yes!
--No way!
--Yes way!
Okay, that's enough!
Hey, by the way, I have a little problem.
--What? A problem?
--Uh-huh.
Bluejam and the others will try to kill the
three of us after this for sure, right?
Well, I think so.
This forest that I've been living is close
to where they are - the Cove of Pirates!
What if they attack me when
I fall asleep exhausted?
--You're gonna die.
--Yeah, you're gonna die.
Right?
That's why I need your help.
Guys, huddle up.
Why are they wounded? They're all bandaged!
Whoa! Boss! Boss! We have a problem!
Hmm? It's still early. What's wrong...
Whoa! What's going on here?!
1, 2...
Huh?
Ace, Luffy...
Ace, Luffy... Huh?
Ace, Luffy... Huh? Ace, Luffy... Huh?
Ace... Luffy... Huh?
Ace, Luffy, huh? Ace, Luffy,
huh? Ace, Luffy, huh?
Ace! Luffy! Who is that?!
Who is who?
It's still early - you're too loud!
How come there is one more kid?!
Who the hell are you?!
Are you talking about me?
I'm Sabo! Hey, you must be Dadan!
Sabo? I've heard your name before!
Oh yeah? That makes it easier! Thank
you for taking care of me from today!
"Taking care"? Don't tell me
that you're gonna stay here...
Don't answer me with a fart!
You must be kidding! I heard that
you're a worthless brat, too!
Oh yeah? I heard that you're
a worthless old bag, too!
That's unnecessary information!
I don't wanna look after one more brat!
But I heard that you're a good worthless
old bag because you can't refuse a request.
I heard that you're a truly
manly worthless old bag!
"Truly manly"? I'm a woman!
I'm not a gender bender!
Ace, Luffy, Sabo!
I'm giving you a place to stay!
You gotta get to work already!
Thank you, Dadan!
--See ya!
Hey, Luffy! You stay here and do
some laundry and clean the house!
No way!
Oh, Ace, Sabo, wait!
Honestly! What annoying brats!
Oh yeah!
I forget to tell them.
Hey, Dadan!
While we're gone, the Bluejam
clan might come by so be careful!
The Bluejam clan might come by? Why?
Because we beat some of his crew up! Bye!
What?!
Dadan sure is an understanding
worthless old bag!
She's still a worthless old bag!
Plus she's a mountain bandit
and her face is scary!
What are we gonna do now?
First...
Eat something!
Okay, let's eat!
Luffy, so you ate the Devil Fruit?
Uh-huh!
No wonder you can't swim.
Here, you can have this, too.
Thanks!
You're too kind, Sabo.
Well, what's wrong with that?
So, what fruit did you eat?
Gum-Gum!
Gum-Gum? Gum?!
That's right!
In exchange for the ability to swim,
your body turned to rubber? So crappy!
It's not crappy! I can use
a lot of unbeatable attacks!
That's good. Good for you.
You have such a fat mouth even
though you can't catch a fish.
Your body really is rubber! Interesting!
Don't play with my body!
But rubber surely stretches
and shrinks and expands so...
...maybe it's useful when you're fighting!
Right?! Oh yeah, I came
up with another attack.
It's called "Gum-Gum Balloon"! I can
deflect cannonballs and everything!
Wow! Can you do it for me now?
Okay, I'll do it just for
you! Ace can't see it.
Don't look!
Here we go! Gum-Gum...
What?! What is it?! What the hell?!
Awesome! You're getting bigger and bigger!
...Balloon! See it?! It's cool, isn't it?!
Well, I don't think it's cool...
It's good for working off my meal!
What are you doing?!
Sabo, kick it back!
Ah, okay.
Stop it!
Is that the unbeatable attack
that will deflect cannonballs?!
Stop it!
Then, why don't you deflect my kick?!
--Wait! You can't just eat and run!
--You bastard!
--Take this!
Well, what can I say? Let it go.
I can't! I almost got eaten!
Calm down. You can have a lot
of crocodile meat for dinner.
Then I forgive you guys.
That easily?
I wanna eat the crocodile already.
I can't wait until dinner.
Ace! I wanna check something quickly.
Can you come with me?
--Did you find it?
--Look carefully!
I'm glad that we moved the "pirate savings".
Yeah.
Do you wanna check the Gray Terminal, too?
Yeah, okay. Why don't you go home now?
No!
He won't listen to anyone.
There are hooligans from the city
and Bluejam's people everywhere.
They're serious!
I bet that Bluejam got really frustrated.
Hey, guys! The kids that you're
looking for are all here!
There they are!
Stop! You can't run from us!
I can't believe that they bought
over pops at the Terminal.
We'd better lay low for a
while until things calm down.
Who cares? We'll just fight if they find us.
That's true but we don't have
to look for trouble ourselves.
I agree with Sabo!
You just shut up!
Bluejam... The kids made quite an enemy!
I'm sure that they're gonna find
this place and come by pretty soon!
There is no way that we can defeat them...
Maybe this is the end of the Dadan family!
I have to say goodbye to the
humble-but-sweet mountain bandit's life?
It's better to quit the mountain bandit
business than to get exterminated!
"We can't defeat them"?
"Out of business"?
How pathetic you guys are!
Don't you take pride in
being a mountain bandit?!
It's easy!
If they come by,
we can just hand Ace and
the other two over to them!
But, boss, how do we explain it to Garp?!
Plus, Bluejam is not the kind of guy who
will be satisfied by just handing them over!
Th-Then...
Then?
Let's just pretend that
we don't know anything!
Now, try it! We gotta practice!
You guys, are Ace and Sabo
here? Just spit it out!
I-I don't know...
Terrible liars!
Boss! Boss! Ace and the other two are back!
Ace's close friend Sabo
started to live with them
after being forced to
leave the Gray Terminal.
Ace, Sabo, Luffy.
These three soon began spending their time
fighting with wild animals in
the mountain and in the jungle
and with hooligans from the
city and pirates at the cove.
In the end, the people at
the center of the kingdom
came to know their wrongdoing!
The names of Luffy, Ace, and Sabo
gradually gain fame among
the thugs in the town.
Then, one day, the three
of them meet a certain boy.
That meeting would change
their destinies in a big way!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"To The Sea Someday!
The Pledge of the Three Brats!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!