Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Hot-Hot powers, to the max!
Maximum Heat Level: 10,000 Degrees!
You can still heat up?
"We'll Be Waiting in the New World!
Parting with the Courageous Pirates"
I'm hot! Hot! Hot!!
What on earth...?
Wh-What's going on?!
Wh-Wha--?!
Straw Hat!
Unforgivable! I'll melt
the likes of you in a flash!
Sultry Hot Night!
What?!
Yow, hot! Hot, hot, hot!
Gum-Gum Pistol!
Rocket!
What?!
Second Gear!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
Nose Jet!
Hot-Hot Head!
Ow, hot...
Huh?
Straw Hat!
Die!
Naked Balloon!
Steam Iron!
10,000-Degree Press!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Gatling!
Jet Whip!
Ow, ow, ow!
What gives?
Lava! I had a feeling this island was...
Oh, yeah! That guy--
No way! That's impossible!
The water feels nice...
Actually, I wish it were warmer.
Doctor...
Tch! Hey, Robin. Think you could
work something out with your powers?
I can't tell which flag is ours.
Damn it! We're screwed!
We've hit the end of the line.
Huh? Up there... What's that?
Wh-What is it? What's up?
A bird...?
Wh-What is this?!
I-Isn't this...?!
This is it!
It's our Jolly Roger!
Thank goodness!
I was so worried--sheesh!
Isn't this great, Doctor?
Jiro!
Yeah, I'm so happy!
Yay! Hurray!
Hip-hip-hurray! Hurray!
Thank you.
Uh-huh!
Robin-chan, let's go!
We don't need to stick around
now that we've got our Jolly Roger!
--Right!
--All righty! To the Sunny!
Yeah!
Men, don't back down!
Put your backs into it!
It's hard to believe you were
licking those bounty hunters' boots!
Which is the real Commander Stansen?!
Beats me!
But this is the commander we all know.
Dammit, you guys! Quit your yakking and pull!
The captain and Jiro are risking their
lives to get our Jolly Roger back!
Protect our ship as if your lives depended on it!
Don't you dare let go!
Be proud of who you are!
We're the Phoenix Pirates!
Yeah!
--Sweet!
--Yay!
Take that!
We did it!
Okay, men! Let's take the ship back.
Roger!
Why those--! It's horrible! The penguins
are headed for Straw Hat's ship!
Those little...!
What now? They're coming back!
Yo, penguins! Long time no see.
This time, you get to face me.
It's hot!
There is nowhere left for you to run.
Soon that block of ice will sink into the lava.
Hah! I just have to kick your
butt before that happens.
Sounds simple enough!
Everything you say burns me up!
Hot-Hot...
Luffy...!
...Net Surfing!
Wh-What?!
Luffy!
C-C-Crap!
I won't let you escape!
Hot Omelet Shot!
I'm melting!
Uh... Huh?
I'm not melting?
What's going on?
Luffy!
Nami!
Looks like my Cool Ball made it in time.
But it won't last for long!
Luffy, finish this fight fast!
Yep. Thanks for your help, Nami!
You don't know when to give up...
Of course not! I'm gonna kick
your butt and go to the New World.
All of you pirates are nothing
but a bunch of idiots!
You go on about the "New World"
and that "King of the Pirates" nonsense.
You dream about things that'll never happen!
As a result, our business is flourishing!
I tell you, it's easy for bounty
hunters to earn a fortune--
it's the ultimate business!
And it's all thanks to idiots who're
willing to throw their lives away
for a meaningless scrap of
cloth called a "Jolly Roger."
Shut up!
What was that? You say something?
Don't... say another word.
Prepare yourself, Naked Balloon!
"Prepare yourself," huh?
You're better than most at
putting up the tough-guy act.
But look at your surroundings!
You might as well be in the burning pit of Hell!
For me, this feels like a cool breeze.
But for you, it must feel like you're
being cooked alive in a boiling pot!
It's no big deal.
What?
You aren't the least bit hot!
There is no way someone frozen over
like you could compete with my fire!
What?
Have you lost it? You think
you're hotter than me?
Open your eyes! Who could surpass the
heat emitted by my boiling hot body?
--Hey!
--Huh?
Quit arguing with me--bring it on!
I'm gonna send you flying!
What did you say?! That's bull!
I'm the 10,000-Degree Man!
What of it?!
My blood is boiling... at a million degrees!
What?
Gum-Gum...!
Bring it on! Take me down...
...if you can!
...Million-Degree Bazooka!
Watch out! Your hands are going to melt.
Not hot! It's not hot!
It's not hot! It's not hot!
What?! That's impossible!
Go flying!
Flag... Our flag...
What's this?
Whoa! What the heck?!
What's goin' on?
Ah! Over there!
--Luffy?!
--What's he doing down there?
Hey! Luffy! We got the Jolly Roger--
No!
Huh? Oh, it's the guys...
Hey, guys! What're you doing over there?
Crap! He found us!
Wh-What now?
Guys!
The ship! Hurry back to the ship!
Got it!
Hurry!
Huh? Those guys...
Hey, wait! What about the flag?
Hey!
Everyone, remember!
Pretend this never happened.
--Hey, wait up!
--Gah, he's coming!
Hey! I said to wait up!
What about the flag?! The flag!
Can't hear him! Can't hear him!
Hey, guys! Hurry!
Wait!
Crap! He's coming!
What should we do?
Sanji-kun! Zoro!
Roger! Let's do it.
Huh?
Fly!
That hurt!
--Here I go, Usopp.
--What?!
You'd better land on the ship.
Wait just a darn second!
Pound Phoenix!
You sent me flying!
--Franky!
--You can count on me!
Coup de Boo!
It smells like cola!
What are you guys doing?!
Didn't they steal the Jolly Roger?
We've gotta hurry and get it back!
Huh? The Jolly Roger?
What are you talking about?
You musta been having a nightmare? Right?
Huh? Y-Yeah!
Luffy, look over there.
What?
Huh? We've still got both of them.
Did that clone technique guy lie to me?
Guys, sorry I ever doubted you.
Don't sweat it, don't sweat it.
Phew, that was a close one.
W-We make it in time?
We did it!
You were great, Jiro!
You're a man among men!
Jiro!
I'm impressed that you managed
to get the Jolly Roger back.
I am very proud of you.
Thank you.
Captain!
Captain...?
Jiro, I want you to hoist the Jolly Roger!
The Phoenix Pirates are setting sail!
Okay, Captain!
Let's get ready, guys!
Yeah!
Pull us out of here!
--You got it!
--Yeah!
Let's beat it!
Stansen, sure enough, your decision was right.
I put you through a lot
while the "captain was gone."
Are you watching, Vigaro?
I swear we won't let your death be in vain!
Men, let's hit the ocean!
Yeah!
Hey! What the heck's going on?
It's that Hot-Hot man's fault.
He stirred up the magma
in the underwater volcano.
Let's hurry! It's only a matter of
time before the volcano erupts.
Got it! Pull out to sea ASAP!
Yeah!
The island vanished...
Phew, that was a close call!
Lil...
Hey, you! I heard what happened!
You returned a piece of Papa-san's
collection to the Straw Hats!
What the heck were--
Shut up for a second!
Okay...
Lil...
I'm sorry.
Big Sister?
I've made you feel lonesome, haven't I?
Let's apologize to Papa
about the flags together.
I'm sure he'll understand.
After all, we're family!
Arbell...!
Lil...
--La la-la la! La la-la la!
--Nice! That's nice, Arbell!
--La la-la la! La la-la la!...
--The way you care for your sister is really great!
St-Straw... Straw Hat...!
Papa, thanks for waiting! It's a bit late, but...
On a one, two...
Happy birthday, Papa!
Straw... Straw... Straw...
Straw Hat!!
Papa!
Where is Big Brother Campaccino
at a time like this?!
Straw Hat!
By the Accino Family name,
I swear I won't let you escape!
You're being a pest, Clone Technique Guy!
I will avenge Papa! Prepare yourself!
Campaccino!
What?! Puzzle?!
Your opponent is supposed to be me!
Straw Hat, he's my prey! Keep your hands off!
--Eh? What?
--You can go on ahead!
We'll deal with you in the New World.
Wait for us to finish you off there!
Sure! Bring it on!
You... greenhorn!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Jiro!
Luffy, why aren't we going to help them?
They're going to get killed!
Chopper, take a closer look.
Does anyone there look like he needs rescuing?
Huh?
Guys...
Hey, you guys! Don't just sit and
watch us! Hurry and get going!
Doctor, let's meet up in the New World!
Yeah! That's a promise!
Okay! Sunny, full speed ahead!
Let's go! To the New World!
Yeah!
Hey, guys! How're you doing?!
I'm Chopper Man!
I don't really know if it's been a while or not,
but next week's One Piece is my special!
You'll definitely have a good dream!
Here we go! Killer Cute Spark!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Go, Chopper Man!
Protect the TV Station on the Beach"
I'm gonna be... a huge robot?!