Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
saa yukou
So let's go
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is rushing to Navy HQ to rescue his brother,
Ace who will be executed in public!
Meanwhile, the Whitebeard
Pirates storming Marineford...
...begin an all-out war with the Navy!
Ace-kun...
Oars!
Climb Oars' body and advance!
What's that?
Heehaw!
"Straw Hat Team Arrives! Tension
Grows at the Battlefield"
I feel a chill in my heart!
Hey, partner! Can't you do something?!
Do you really think that
wax will help in any way?!
Why are Luffy and the others
falling from the sky?
We have to go back a little bit in
time to know what happened to them.
The ship that they were on was
hit by Whitebeard's seaquake.
It's speeding up!
H-Hey! Look at that!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
It's a tsunami!
--It's really big!
--We're gonna get caught!
The sea just suddenly drew back and now there's a big tsunami.
This must be...
Hey, Jimbei! We gotta do something or...
I don't want to be defeated
by a tsunami here!
I... I gotta save Ace!
Take in the sails!
Luffy-kun, let's ride on the tsunami!
Shouldn't we get away?!
What are saying, you ass?!
Turn around already!
Hey, stop it!
--We gotta hurry!
--Jump into the sea!
Help! Help!
How long have you been a pirate?
Are you a bunch of amateurs?
If we turn around now, we'll take the
wave on the side of the ship and capsize.
We don't have any option.
That's right!
Hang tight so you don't get
washed off by the big wave!
Damn!
Hurry up!
Just hang onto something!
My face is too big.
What happened?
--The wave stopped moving!
--What happened?!
What the hell?!
The ship has iced in and
we're completely trapped!
This must have done by...
Look down. You can see what's going on.
--Old man...
--The war has begun already.
Old man must have set that
tsunami as a declaration of war.
And this freezing is the
work of Admiral Aokiji.
Guys, listen!
I got an idea to get us through this!
We gotta hurry! There's less than 3
hours left before Ace's execution!
Uh-huh. And?
What?!
You want the ship to slide
down this frozen wave?!
That's the only way! First, we gotta
get this ship unstuck from the ice!
Are you nuts? It's a Navy
ship! We can't lift it up!
He's right, you idiot!
We can do it if we work together!
Oh, that makes me think that I can.
Yeah! We have the next King of the
Pirates - Captain Buggy on our side!
When Captain says that he can
do it, he will do it for sure!
Ring, ring, ring...
Attention, all ships and
soldiers! The target is TOTTZ.
Change the line and make
the shift to operation 3.
--It's a Navy operational message.
--Advance the preparation!
TOT... what was it?
Dunno. Must be some kind of code.
When you are all set,  we
move the schedule forward...
...and execute Ace immediately. That's all.
--Luffy-kun...
--Let's move!
This can't wait any longer.
We don't have time to argue!
Everyone, let's get on with Straw boy's idea!
Let's go!
H-Hey!
No! That's not the side!
And that was how Luffy and
the others started falling!
What just happened?! Did a
Navy ship fall from the sky?!
It's water, thank god. We fell into water.
I thought I was gonna die
by falling on the ice!
Why isn't it frozen around here?
Look! The ship landed in the area
where Jozu had cleared the ice!
Is it a surprise attack from the Navy?
No, they don't look like the Navy.
Climb! Climb up!
It's nothing comparing to
the water torture in hell.
It's inconvenient that Devil
Fruit eaters can't swim.
Where am I?
Oh yeah, I fell from there.
Ace!
Where are you? Where are you, Ace?!
Ace...
Get on the ship!
He's not on this side!
Where are you, Ace?!
Wait for me, Ace! I'll be there soon!
Don't get in my way!
Ace!
Ace...
Ace!!
Luffy!!
I can see you finally!
Luffy!
Ace! Hang on! I'll...
H-Hey, don't tell me that's...!
Crocodile!
That's not all! Who is in that lineup?!
All forces are here on both sides!
There are a lot of big names!
The world's got to be ready for it!
Ace, we're coming to rescue you!
We're here for you!
Garp! It's your family again!
Luffy!
Look! It's not only Straw Hat!
Jimbei and Ivankov of the
Revolutionaries army!
Behind them are many infamous pirates, too!
They must've escaped from Impel Down!
He always causes trouble... Straw Hat.
Straw Hat!
--What brought him here?
--And he's not with his crew.
Luffy! I'm glad that you're alive!
Look, Helmeppo-san!
What?! Nothing'll surprise me any more...
Straw Hat!
I heard that he was captured
at Impel Down! He's so tough!
He brought some big faces!
I didn't expect to see him again this soon.
He's the brother that Ace was talking about.
There's a former and an
active Warlord together!
And that supposed to be the big
troublemaker rookie--Straw Hat!
Smoker-san, look!
Die!
Straw Hat and Crocodile...
Why are they together?
So it is him.
The grandson of the hero--Garp and
the son of the revolutionary--Dragon.
I'll take care of him for good!
Of all things, you're working
alongside Straw Hat Luffy...
So that's your response, Jimbei?!
Yes, it is! I resign from The Seven Warlords!
It's odd that those people are teaming up.
Prisoners, a commander of
the Revolutionaries army,
some bizarre-looking people and...
...Crocodile.
I don't think that they have a common goal.
At least, in this battle.
Where's Croco boy?
Oh? I think he chickened out and...
There he is!
He went ahead of me!
--Crocodile is aiming for Whitebeard!
--Pops!
Long time no see, Whitebeard.
You never learn.
He knows too well how to fight against me.
You can't turn into sand
once you touch water.
Now that we are here, our
agreement has been fulfilled.
Why do you want to protect Whitebeard?!
As I thought--this old man is Whitebeard.
Then leave him alone!
Ace likes this old man!
Ace's brother is quite a fighter.
Don't let him come close to Pops!
Everybody was surprised
when a strong guy like you
came back after losing an arm
in the East Blue.
Who is this enemy that you
gave your left arm to?
I put it up for a new generation.
Hey, squirt, that straw hat you have...
...it looks like the one that
"Red-Haired" was once wearing.
Old man, you know Shanks?
Shanks left it to me.
Look, Pops! This is my brother!
You came here to rescue your brother?
Yeah.
Do you know who you're messing with?!
A squirt like you will be dead meat!
Shut up! That's not up to you to decide!
I know what you're up to!
You wanna become the King
of the Pirates, right?!
But I'm the one who'll become the King!
How saucy you are!
I won't forgive you if you
cause me trouble, spoiled brat!
I'm gonna do as I like!
I'm gonna rescue Ace!
--H-He's competing...
--...With Whitebeard!
It can't be!
We can punish all of them by
death, can't we, Sengoku-san?
Absolutely.
Luffy... Pops...
Hang on, Ace!
I'll get there...
I'll get there very soon!
At the Navy HQ, Luffy leads the charge
against the massive forces there.
As the men of the Navy attack Luffy in waves,
Ace shouts at him to stay away.
How will Luffy respond to his brother's wish?
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Even If It Means Death!
Luffy vs. the Navy; The Battle Starts!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!