Edited at https://subtitletools.com
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I think back to when I was a crybaby
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
Am I getting stronger?
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
I don't know the answer yet
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
But I won't walk away
nigedasanai kara
So let's go
saa yukou
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the
Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way
to the New World,
will speed along the
Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy is headed to the Navy Headquarters in order to rescue his brother, Ace!
Now, there are only 3 hours left before the public execution of Portgaz D. Ace...
"Ticking Down to the Time of Battle! The Navy's Strongest Lineup in Position!"
Stand up.
Climb.
"South Blue"
It's in 3 hours now! I wonder if Whitebeard has arrived yet.
I don't know. Do you think he's really gonna be there?
He's a big deal but isn't he too old?
You think so?
He was around before the Great Pirate Era. He must be senile by now.
We haven't heard his name in any big news for years.
How can you guys take this so lightly?
Because he's unignorable, the Navy HQ has called up its elites and...
...is expecting him with all their forces.
I'm almost certain that Whitebeard is going to appear.
And then what's gonna happen?
I don't know. How am I supposed to know?
"East Blue"
He's a pirate of a different era.
Is it possible for him to beat the Navy HQ?
It's not possible for any pirates to attack Marineford.
That's not true. I think it was 20 years ago,
a pirate called Shiki the Golden Lion invaded Marineford
and left the Navy HQ half destroyed.
This time it's going to be worse.
No matter who wins, a lot of people will die.
It'd be better if he didn't appear.
If nothing besides the execution happens, that'd be for the best.
"North Blue"
Hey, we want drinks, old guy!
Are you asking me to open the bar on a day like this? We're expecting a big war in any minute!
Go home! If the world's still here tomorrow, I'll open it!
Then just sell us some drinks! It feels like we're the ones who're on the scaffold!
We can't do without drinking!
He's not just another old man.
"West Blue"
He hasn't lost it at all!
It was just a year ago, when we saw him sitting right there...
...we thought we were dead.
"Grand Line"
Is Whitebeard that outrageous?
Even those kids know it. They're singing as they jump rope.
The pirate Whitebeard is scarier than a devil!
Oh, God!
Where is this world headed?
On the island of Marineford home of the Navy Headquarters,
lies a huge city mainly populated by families of the Navy.
An evacuation order has been issued to all residents at this time.
And at Sabaody Archipelago at the evacuation site,
residents are watching the proceedings of the execution on monitors.
Reporters and cameramen from various places are...
...standing by here to break the news quickly to the world.
That's really the best of Navy HQ.
I assume that Whitebeard knows about this.
But still, will he venture to be there?
Every look-out ship that the Navy sent has been swiftly sunk
and there has been no report of a sighting of Whitebeard.
So the tension at Marineford continues to rise.
And there is less than 3 hours left until the looming execution.
"Navy"
I have problem with that. Is that really necessary?
This public execution is not just an execution of a pirate.
It has great significance for the future of the world.
That's why it's necessary to...
You are responsible for this matter since you are one of the parties involved.
Don't forget that, Garp.
"Marineford Navy Headquarters"
Hurry and get ready!
Hey you, don't lag behind!
Don't slacken your pace!
No matter what happens, it'll last only 3 hours!
Then it's all finished!
Elite soldiers are summoned from all over the world--totaling almost one hundred thousand.
The crescent-shaped bay area and the whole island are surrounded by 50 Navy ships
and numerous cannons have been set at the bay area.
And in front of all the marshaled forces that can be seen from sea...
...stand 5 ruffians who hold the key to the war. Pirates--The Seven Warlords!
"Bartholomew Kuma"
"Gecko Moria"
"Don Quixote Doflamingo"
"Dracule Mihawk"
"Boa Hancock"
It's...
...the admirals!
I don't know why but I find them so intimidating!
Guarding closely below the scaffold are...
...the Navy's greatest powers...
...the three admirals!
"Navy Admiral
Aokiji Kuzan"
Akainu Sakazuki"
"Navy Admiral
Kizaru Borsalino"
Every force of justice imaginable is...
...now waiting for the Whitebeard Pirates to stop them from rescuing Ace!
Listen, Luffy.
We have to live without leaving any regrets.
Uh-huh.
We gotta go out to sea someday...
...and live as we like.
Freer than anyone else.
I see it!
Hey! Jimbei!
I see the Gate of Justice already! That was fast!
No, it wasn't! If the wind were right, we could have gotten here faster.
However...
I warn you.
As long as we don't open the Gate of Justice, you guys can't get to Marineford
or even get out of the Tub Current!
There is no sea for you all to get away to or to live on!
So now, how can we get through the gate?
You guys! It's almost time for...
Huh? What is it?
Time for Captain Buggy to conquer the world!
That's right!
The Navy HQ is nothing!
Whitebeard is nothing!
Who is the next King of the Pirates?
Captain Buggy!
That's right!
Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy! Buggy!
Ace!
Hey, look! "Fire Fist" Ace has come out!
This is the man...
...who may trigger a war that will shake the world!
And he is the one who holds the fate of the world now!
Okay, Garp? I'll tell them everything!
So be it. I'll be downstairs.
--Step aside for a minute.
--Yes, sir!
--Fleet Admiral Sengoku!
--What's going on?
--Give me a Transponder Snail.
--Yes, sir.
I have something to tell you all.
Portgaz D. Ace...
It's about the great significance of his death today.
It's not your fault.
Women are very sweet at times like this, Tsuru-chan.
Ace, tell them the name of your father.
Father? Why is that important now?
My father is Whitebeard.
No!
Yes, he is! Whitebeard is my only father!
We looked for you with our eyes wide open at that time.
Because we heard that there might be a child of that man on some island.
Based on a small amount of reliable information from Cipher Pol,
we checked all newborns...
...and preborn children...
...and their mothers but we couldn't find you.
No wonder.
Your mother risked her life to bear you.
She used a trick that can be called mother's pride.
That has misled us... Indeed, the whole world.
There is an island called Batelira in the South Blue.
Your mother's name is Portgaz D. Rouge.
She did something that completely defied natural law...
...for the love of her child.
She kept her baby inside her womb for 20 months!
No way.
And as soon as she gave birth to you,
she lost all of her strength and passed away right there.
A year and 3 months after the father's death,
the child was born with the blood of the world's most heinous man in his veins.
That was you!
You know it, surely?
They can't blame a child whose not born.
Garp!
Look after my child!
Your father is...
...the King of the Pirates -
Gold Roger!
"Fire Fist" Ace is a son of Gold Roger?!
This is huge news.
Call the head office! Let's issue an extra!
Does it continue?
Still?
The bloodline of the King of the Pirates?!
The secret of Ace's origin has been revealed.
His father Roger's feelings, and his mother
Rouge's strong resolve lay behind it all.
At Marineford, Whitebeard's fleet silently approaches.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Vast Fleet Appears! Here Come the Whitebeard Pirates!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!