Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing, let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Their total bounty exceeds 600 million Berries.
This Jolly Roger belongs to the Straw Hat Crew.
What do you think with your
120 million bounty, Roronoa Zoro?
How the hell did you get that Jolly Roger?!
"A Mansion in Chaos! An Enraged Don
and an Imprisoned Crew"
Luffy...
Luffy!
That was close! But I'm not
about to fall into the ocean!
How far can you run?
You may have a 300-million-Berry bounty,
but you're nothing before us!
I've had enough of your yapping!
Give back our Jolly Roger!
I'm willing to lead the way.
If you can defeat us brothers...
...we'll take you to that flag.
Jerks!
I nearly fell!
Having a hard time fighting on the ice?
It's just as tricky for you!
I wouldn't be so sure.
The Arctic Path falls under
the Accino Family's territory.
When we're in unison, no one here
stands a chance against us!
Furthermore, we have the power
of magnetism that strongly unites us!
Monkey D. Luffy, you're doomed
to succumb to our brotherly love!
I've heard enough of your boasting.
Just come at me already!
I'll kick your butts in no time flat!
What a brat!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Monkey D. Luffy, we siblings...
...will be taking your head!
I'm amazed you were able to dodge that!
Let's get him in one go,
Big Brother Campaccino!
Papa is growing anxious.
It's the end of--
You really are in perfect unison!
Don't laugh!
I should have expected as much
from a 300-million-Berry bounty.
You really did a number on us!
Nah, I haven't done anything yet.
Are you stupid or what?
The pirate scum...!
How dare he mock us?!
Curse you!
Die!
Jerk! How dare you get rough
with my Shark Submerge?!
I'm gonna make you pay
for that, you hockey freak!
It's only a matter of time before you turn to ice!
Keep the bravado up while you can!
Punk!
This sucks! Where the heck are we?!
Hey!
Sanji-kun! Usopp!
Please save us!
Nami-san, I'm sorry.
I let my guard down just a bit.
Hey, are you okay?
Yeah, thanks. You're a lifesaver.
Now we're down to four bounties left.
I just knew you were bounty hunters!
But, dang, this place is freezing!
This was carved from layers of ice that
have been forming for hundreds of years.
It quickly freezes anything that is inside.
You could say it's a natural freezer.
Make sense?
Arbell, that comparison was really great!
It was super easy to understand!
I can't wait to see whether
we'll catch the other four first
or you'll freeze first!
By now, my children should
have taken out your crewmates.
It's a pity! I hate to slice apart
the guy who treated me to a drink!
You, slice me apart? Are you up to the task?
You're a Devil Fruit power holder?!
I can melt anything I touch!
I could do this to your splendid
sword in mere seconds!
I gained this ability from my Hot-Hot Fruit!
In other words, I just can't touch you, right?
Thirty-six Pound Phoenix!
What?!
Bastard! Are you trying to
hurt my beloved collection?!
Wh-What was that?!
Troisième Haché!
Strong... Hammer!
Exploding Star! Exploding Star Star!
Usopp Hammer! Usopp Rubberband of Doom!
Exploding Star! Pound!
--Exploding Star! Exploding Star Star!
--You're wasting your time.
There is no way out. Give it up.
--Hammer! Exploding Star! Pound!
--It looks like that is the only way out.
--Exploding Star! Exploding Star!
--Franky!
Dammit! I wasn't even able to dent it!
I guess I'll call it a day.
Hey!
What's up?
C'mon! Do "that."
Sure! I should have enough for one last blast.
Let's go, guys! Everyone ready?!
Yeah!
1.0 Cola Cannon!
Coup de Boo!
Go!
Dammit! I'm outta cola!
No, you got us far enough!
Damn it!
Don't underestimate us!
Hurry and freeze over!
Click.
I-It's horrible, Arbell-sama!
D-Don Accino-sama is...!
Understood. I'm on my way!
Stay there and wait for the others to show up!
Hurry it up, Darling!
Coming, Honey!
Hey, we're seriously gonna
freeze if we stay here!
Papa-san!
Papa!
Yeah!
--This isn't good!
--It's like a sauna in here!
Honey, what should we do?
We can't let Papa's mood
get any worse! Put on a smile!
What's the matter, Papa?
You brats!
Didn't you make sure to gather
up my birthday presents?!
Listen to me, Papa! We've gathered them--gah!
R-Roronoa Zoro?!
What's he doing here?
I won't forgive you, bastard!
Don't ignore us!
Two-Sword Style!
--Uh, if I remember right...
--Hawk...
...Wave?!
I-I'm sorry, Papa!
We made a mistake that
allowed one to slip through.
P-Papa-san, don't worry! We'll be sure
to do a perfect job rounding up the rest!
And you got a new flag
to add to your collection!
See? So cheer up!
And my brothers-in-law will hunt
down the remaining members!
Okay, Papa?
It's not working. We can't
soothe his temper on our own.
Help us, Brother!
Damn it! You're tougher than
I expected, Clone Technique Guy!
We told you, we're twins!
Listen to what people tell you!
Now then, Papa is waiting for us.
We need to wrap this up.
Wha--?!
Blend!
Big Brother Campaccino!
Damn it!
Monkey D. Luffy!
Your head is ours!
Gum-Gum...
...Gatling!
Click.
What is it?
Yeah. Yeah...
--All right.
--Click.
Hey, you! Don't run from me!
You've escaped death
for now, Monkey D. Luffy.
We'll finish you off later.
Big Brother, what's the matter?
It sounds like Papa has gotten
even worse! We have to hurry back.
Wait, you two! Don't run away!
You jerks!
Give back our Jolly Roger!
Stop it! You'll die if you go to sleep!
Wake up, Usopp! Usopp!
Don't wake me up, Nami.
I'm in the middle of a pretty dream...
There's so many birdies and butterflies...
Merry, you've come for me, haven't you?
Wake up!
Are you trying to kill me?!
Where the heck is this?
Zoro?!
Where the hell have you guys been?
That's what we should be asking you!
More importantly, I saw our flag upstairs.
Guys, you didn't...
So it really is here, huh?
We've gotta get it back before Luffy notices!
Damn it! You can't even protect a
single flag, you lame excuse for a cook?
Back at you! How dare you come back
empty-handed, you shitty swordsman?!
--Jerk, take this!
--Hey, watch where you fling that sword!
Hey! This is no time for fighting!
It looks like everyone is doing well.
Huh?
Robin!
Robin-chan!
--Moron.
--What?!
Robin, save me!
Please! Pull us up!
Really, Miss, you're supposed
to go down there with them.
But see, you're special, Big Sister Robin!
I'll ask Papa to spare you.
And Papa does anything I ask!
My!
So let's go to the birthday party.
There's a birthday party?
Yup! It's for Papa!
We have a whole bunch of food!
C'mon! Say goodbye to everyone.
--Robin!
--Hey!
Darling!
--Hurry and rescue us!
--C'mon! Hurry and save us! Robin!
--Robin-chan! Darling!
Hey! Robin-chan! Come on!
Well, shall we head on up?
Really?
Let's go! Let's go!
I'll lead the way.
Hey! Why'd you leave us?
Wait, Robin!
Please don't abandon me!
Chopper!
I'm back!
Come back like a normal person!
Are you trying to destroy our ship?!
My bad.
What's the matter?
Isn't it a bit warm?
Huh? It couldn't be...
I knew it!
Papa's angry!
Let's call it off. It's best to stay away
from Papa when he gets like that.
Really?
At this rate, he'll melt everyone around here!
C'mon! Let's go play in my room.
Then let's take those snacks and drinks with us.
They're so warm, I doubt they'll be very yummy.
That's all right. Also, I'd like
to ask a favor of you.
Punks, you've got a delivery.
It's from Little Lady Lil's friend, Robin-sama.
From Robin?
A delivery...?
Robin-chan, I always believed in you!
Hey! Here's some cola, Franky!
Sweet! You can leave the rest to me!
Super! Cola replenished!
Here I go! Coup de...
...Vent!
Coup de Boo!
We wasted a bunch of time down there,
so let's get going, guys!
Yeah!
Let's go, Chopper!
Please take me with you.
I'm begging you!
Jiro...
Forget it!
Stay here, Jiro.
--Don't go!
--Captain...
There's no need to go.
I'm no longer...
It's okay! If we could raise
our Jolly Roger again,
I'm sure you'd return to your old self!
So I'm going to bring it back!
Don't be foolish!
I have already given up...
The words "given up" sound so lame...
They don't suit you, Captain!
You're the man who's supposed
to become the King of the Pirates!
Puzzle, I believe in you.
You are the man who will
become the King of the Pirates!
I'm still puny and a total weakling,
but just you wait!
I'll steal it back and--
--Wha--?!
--Eh?!
Why'd you whack him, Luffy?!
Don't exclude me from the conversation!
Are you a cold-hearted brute?!
That hurt! What was that for?!
Only someone who has fought till the
very end may use the words "given up."
You can't use them!
Listen to me!
There is no way a guy like this could
become the King of the Pirates!
I'm the one who'll become
the King of the Pirates!
Don't be stupid!
I've already decided that Puzzle-san
is going to become the King!
I don't care what you say!
I won't give up on my dream!
Hey!
Jiro, you aren't weak at all!
You've got an inner strength!
Luffy-san...
C'mon! Let's go get our flags back, Jiro!
Yeah!
I'll never forgive them for
stealing our Jolly Rogers!
Don't do it!
You don't stand a chance against them!
Don't go.
I'm not going to die.
I'm going to move forward.
After all, I'm a pirate!
The idiot...! All for me, everyone is...
Captain Puzzle...
Men, we're going after Jiro!
R-Right...
Hey, Nami! Aren't we in trouble
if Zoro is leading the way?
Shut your trap!
I'm sure we'll turn this into a
party you'll never forget, okay?
So cheer up, Papa!
Give our Jolly Roger back!
What was that?
Hey, don't drag your feet! Luffy's on his way!
At any rate, let's hurry!
See? I told you he'd come, Papa!
It's just a matter of time before we capture him.
I'm sorry I got mad at you.
Hey, you damn moss head!
I only followed you since you claimed
to know where the Jolly Roger was!
Back off! Be quiet for a second!
It's probably this way.
Why the heck do we have to follow this jerk?
We're here! This is it!
I'm sure of it...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Phoenix Returns! The Dream
Sworn to Friends on a Jolly Roger"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!