Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Has the Buster Call order been issued?
No, we still have to be on standby.
Hurry!
Run to the evacuation ship!
So this is a Poneglyph, huh?
Yeah. I heard that even if we tried to
blow it up, it wouldn't even get a scratch.
What a creepy stone... To think that
this stuff is scattered around the world...
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"The Tragedy of Ohara!
The Terror of Buster Call"
Is that right?
Yes, they deserve the death penalty.
Since we seized the evidence,
we'll carry out your orders.
It cannot be helped. This is quite unfortunate;
however, they violated the
world's laws. We cannot overlook it.
Stop the blatant superficial talk,
Five Elder Stars.
Wha...! Don't be rude! You're talking
to the leaders of the world!
Is this Ohara's Professor Clover,
the authority of archaeology?
I know your name well, since you've
contributed to the world's culture.
To think that someone of your
caliber would take the wrong path...
The past belongs to all mankind.
No one has the right to stop one from
wanting to know our unspoken history!
Professor...
Reading the Poneglyphs makes it
possible to revive the ancient weapon,
which puts the world in danger.
Even if your research has the best of intentions,
all it takes is for someone to
come along and use your research.
No matter what happened in the past,
if humans created that history,
we should accept it all.
If we don't succumb to fear
and learn all of history,
we can take countermeasures
no matter what happens.
That's an idealistic argument.
Is that so? Isn't that reasoning
just a convenient excuse for you?
Out of what is still left to us,
what interests us the most are the contents
of the Poneglyphs, along with their reason
for existing in the first place.
Why did the ancients take the trouble
to inscribe the text on hard stones
in order to pass it down to the future?
They inscribed history on unbreakable stones
and scattered them around the world.
Is it not because they thought that
their message would be eradicated
if they wrote it on paper or in books?
In other words, it is the proof that
those who left the Poneglyphs
clearly had an enemy.
What're you trying to say, Professor Clover?
If we assume that they were
defeated by some kind of enemy
and so ceased to exist,
this enemy must've remained
in history from that point on.
Coincidentally, just when the
"Blank Century" ended 800 years ago,
the World Government was founded.
If the current World Government was
the "enemy" of those that ceased to exist,
one could think that the "Blank Century"
is an inconvenient history
that was hushed up by the World Government.
By analyzing the ancient
documents and some Poneglyphs,
we eventually noticed
the existence of a country.
What the documents brought to light
was the existence of a grand kingdom.
Although it seems to have
boasted much power in the past,
the information on this country
has obsessively been erased.
They probably sensed they'd be
defeated by the allied countries,
later to become the World Government,
and so inscribed all the truth on
stones to pass it down to the future.
Indeed, those stones are the Poneglyphs
that remain to this very day.
I see. That's a bold hypothesis.
It's true that the ancient weapon
would threaten the world.
However, isn't it actually that the
World Government is more threatened
by people becoming aware of that
kingdom's existence and ideology?
We still have to analyze what this threat is,
but the name of this once-prosperous
kingdom that holds the key to everything is...
Eliminate him!
Professor!
Ohara has...
--You bastards!
--How dare you...!
Professor Clover!
...come to know too much.
Give the attack signal.
Don't move!
Don't let even a single person escape.
Well then, using this golden transponder snail
entrusted to me by Admiral Sengoku...
Professor!
Robin...
You fool! You shouldn't be here. Run!
...I'll initiate a Buster Call!
Take care of the rest.
He did something!
Hurry to the evacuation ship, Robin.
No! I don't wanna be alone!
Don't say such a foolish
thing at a time like this.
Robin...
That's the Buster Call request!
All battleships, to your positions!
Prepare to open fire!
Hey...
Look!
The Tree of Knowledge is on fire!
Hey, World Government! What're you doing?!
Taking our lives should be enough!
Don't look at me. It must've caught
fire from the explosions earlier.
This isn't a joke!
Do you realize how many important
documents there are in there?!
Hey! Don't move!
Ah... We don't need guns anymore.
Those from the Government, pull out.
Hurry up and get the books!
Put out the fire in the library!
Circulate water!
Take the books out of the library!
Bring that woman with us.
Come.
There's a piece of information
that only she knows.
It'll cause a problem if she dies here.
Mommy.
Robin...! Please... make sure you escape.
Don't die, no matter what!
Your nose!
Robin! Hurry!
Get out of here now!
--Robin-chan!
--Robin!
Are you... my mom?
Olvia! Are you gonna come
aboard the ship or not?
Mommy!
--I'll hold her, so go already!
--Mommy! Don't go! Mommy!
Mommy! Mommy!
I'm sorry, Robin.
I can never call myself your mother again.
I can't be allowed... to be your
mother after all these years.
--Monster!
Her mom abandoned her!
Robin! Those are my daughter's clothes!
I'm sorry, Aunt Roji! I wanted
to try them on just once!
You eat a lot for someone who lives here free.
Are you...
...my mom?!
Hmm? What? You have a kid?
No.
Olvia-san...
I'm sorry...
...but I think you're confusing
me with someone else.
Forgive me, Robin! I don't wanna
make you a "criminal's daughter"!
Olvia...
What a weird brat.
Hey, let's go!
I'm Robin!
I've grown, but don't you remember me?!
I've been waiting for you to return all this time!
Are you...
...really not...
...my mom?
I wanted you...
...to hold my hand...
...and walk with me someday...
So I studied hard and was able
to become an archaeologist!
I can read Poneglyphs, too!
That brat can?!
Stop it, Robin!
So...
...please let me stay... with you!
Mom!
Robin...!
Please...
...don't leave me...
...alone anymore!
What?! What the hell is this attack?!
I'm exercising a Buster Call.
Commence concerted fire!
We're targeting everything on Ohara,
the island of archaeology!
The research by the Ohara scholars
has reached a level we never imagined.
Knowledge can be transferred.
Don't let it out of that island.
Annihilate the devils living in Ohara!
In the name of justice!
Dammit! What's going on?!
We haven't gotten off of the island yet!
Are they trying to kill us?!
The Tree of Knowledge is directly
being hit by cannonballs, too!
There's no mistaking that this
is Headquarters' military power.
The government was probably going
to do this from the start. How foolish.
Chief. That brat said that she's an archaeologist.
Yeah, she did say that.
I don't know if it's true or not,
but when we don't know,
eliminating them solves the problem.
Remember her face well so that
you don't let her leave the island.
Retreat!
Then I'll take Olvia.
Forget her! No time for that now!
Just leave her here!
If we stay here, we'll get killed, too!
My life is the most important thing!
All, retreat! Go back to the ship!
Do something about the fire in the library!
Protect the Tree of Knowledge!
I wanted to do this...
...all this time!
Robin!
Mom!
It's my fault... Robin...
Is it true that you can read Poneglyphs?
If I had properly kept an eye on you...
I'm sorry. I wanted to be able
to read them at any cost, so--
I'm really surprised to know that you've
become able to do things like that.
You must've tried hard and studied a lot.
It's not something anyone can do.
That's amazing, Robin!
Fortunately, the officials from earlier
are the only ones who know about it.
This is no time to be sitting around here.
Olvia! Take Robin and run!
If you can somehow sneak
Robin onto the evacuation ship,
you can leave the island!
Robin! There you are! I looked all over for you!
Saul!
So you were able to see Olvia!
Saul! What are you doing on this island?!
By some twist of fate, I got shipwrecked
and saved by Robin on the beach.
More importantly, the situation is terrible!
You have to leave the island immediately!
Please take care of Robin!
Please let my daughter escape
from the island at any cost!
What?! No! What about you, Mom?!
Aren't you gonna come with me?!
Olvia... What are you gonna...
There's still something
that I have to do here, so...
Mom! I don't wanna be separated!
I was finally able to meet you!
I'll stay here, too!
Robin...
You're an Ohara scholar,
so you should know this very well.
History is the treasure of mankind.
It'll certainly light up the future
you young ones will live in.
But the history we received
from the past will disappear
unless we pass it on to the next era.
--Put out the fire!
--Protect the books!
Revealing the history isn't
what Ohara was trying to do.
We just wanted to accept the voices
of the past and protect them.
Our research will end now,
but even if Ohara is obliterated...
...we cannot give up the future
you young ones will live in!
I don't understand!
You will understand someday.
Now, go, Saul!
Are you sure about this?
Yes.
No! I'll stay here, too! Mom!
Mom!
I was happy to hear you call me that.
Thank you!
From now on, for you and me both...
Live, Robin!
What?! Vice Admiral! Vice Admiral Kuzan!
What?!
On the island... Yes, there's no doubt about it!
So what's the matter?! Just spit it out!
It's the deserter, Vice Admiral Saul!
Saul! Go back! Please!
No! I can't do that!
Robin! Be proud, Robin!
Your mom is honorable! Ohara is honorable!
Someday, pass down this island's history, Robin!
Ohara fought against the world!
Stop it! Capturing them is enough!
They're not even violent pirates! Are you
so weak that you can't suppress them?!
We've caught history
exploration ships many times,
but I don't understand why they had to die.
Vice Admiral Saul! We found one survivor!
How dare you kill my fellow scholars?!
Do you really want the weapon?
What pitiful people...
You don't have your own will
and yet you cast judgment on us...
Hey! He's a Vice Admiral!
...not doubting laws and saying it's
to prevent the revival of the weapon!
You're just frightened by the
history that you don't even know!
This is a top-secret mission.
Buster Call?
Five Vice Admirals command
ten battleships in a Buster Call.
I want you to be one of them.
They are just scholars.
Why do we have to go that far?
Those scholars that we've captured, too!
They look like they just really
want to know the history to me!
If their research is so dangerous,
the Government should help them, too!
We're the ones who actually have to kill people!
Give me the proof that they're completely evil!
Are you doubting the Government?
Don't fight! Just follow orders!
I'd like to ask you some questions.
This is an emergency! Vice Admiral
Saul took a criminal and deserted!
He knows everything about the operation.
After them! Capture Saul and Olvia without fail!
You can shoot them if needed!
Pursuers are coming! I'll deal with them!
You'll never be able to
go back to the Navy, Saul.
That's fine. I can't stay in the
Navy having this sense of distrust.
Even if they're obeying the law,
this operation is too tyrannical.
I'm just following my sense of justice.
Now, hurry to your hometown
to let people know.
I'm not gonna thank you for this.
Good luck.
Fire!
They're aiming at me!
Saul!
Ah! It hit him!
I'm sorry!
Don't apologize! He's already
those evil people's accomplice!
I'm sorry, Robin. That must've scared you.
Hold on a sec.
That must be it! Firing this close?
What if you had hurt Robin?!
Vice Admiral! Please stop! What're you doing?!
I don't know what justice is in this situation,
so I'll just protect my friend!
Stop it! Saul!
Be prepared!
If you make an enemy of me,
I'll make you pay for it!
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Robin! We still haven't heard you say it!
Say you want to live!
Robin!
Robin...
--Robin...
--Robin-chan!
Robin!
I... I...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Say You Want to Live! We Are Your Friends!!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!