Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
Put the pieces of our dreams together
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate
alliance with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition - in
which a winner will get the Flare-Flare Fruit
as the prize - and won the first round
but now, he's heading for the palace
to take back Law who's
been captured by Doflamingo.
Leo! Leo!
Stay with me! That was too reckless!
We must complete Operation SOP...
...as soon as...
...possible.
Then, the commander will...
...take down Doflamingo...
...for sure!
Rebecca, do you know
how your mother Scarlet died?
The Toy Soldier cried like a baby.
He was so pathetic.
You can't go after him!
Are you okay, Commander?!
Th-Thank you!
--Let's get going!
--Wait! They're gonna get beaten up!
Hey! Let go of me! You little bastards!
Stop looking back, Commander!
We were planning on
sacrificing ourselves from the beginning!
Don't be silly!
What will happen if you stop here?!
Even if
Leo and the others pulled off Operation SOP,
if we let Doflamingo walk away,
he'll turn everything back again!
You're the only one who can bring
down Doflamingo, Commander!
He's worth betting everything on!
Nobody remembers him now
but everybody knew him once!
When he was a Big Human, his name was...
...Kyros!
He was the strongest gladiator
in the history of the Colosseum!
That's who our commander is!
"The Rupture Human!
Gladius Blows Up Big Time!"
THE ROYAL PALACE B-1 - THE RAMPART TOWER
That didn't make a dent, did it?
I can't see an end to this!
How and where do I have to attack
to finish him off?!
THE ROYAL PALACE 1ST FLOOR
THE SOLDIER AND THE LITTLE PEOPLE
Break him down!
Don't get in my way!
Rampo!
--Are you okay, Rampo?!
--Commander!
You alright?!
No worries! It's nothing!
Once they pull off Operation SOP,
you can change back to being a great gladiator!
But we're responsible to help you
to reach Doflamingo before that!
You guys...
Don't tell me that's...
Commander!
There's another executive!
He's a member of the Pica Army!
Gladius!
You have no chance of winning now!
Rampo and I are gonna draw his attention!
So please run ahead!
No, don't!
Are you guys gonna try to
sacrifice yourselves again?!
Rampo!
Let's attack him from both sides, Cub-san!
Okay!
Wait!
Why should I fight these little rats?!
Take this!
Your buzzing around is annoying me!
Cub!
Rampo!
--Commander!
--Now is your chance!
Toys can't run that fast!
I ate the Pop-Pop Fruit
and became a rupture human!
I can detonate my own body.
And...
What?!
...Inorganic objects as well.
I can destroy a thing like
a tin toy completely!
L-Let go of me!
I have a...
...responsibility!
Rebecca!
Enjoy being blown to pieces!
Jet Stamp!
Who is it?!
--Soldier! Where are Franky and the others?
--You're...
Oh, you aren't with them?
Straw Hat! This is no time to talk!
Straw Hat Luffy!
Violet!
Gladius!
How could you...
How could you betray Young Master-sama!
--Alright! Bring it on!
--No! You have to run!
What're you doing?!
We don't have time!
And he's pretty strong, too!
Let's just go to the Suit Chamber now!
Viola-sama, why are you doing this?!
You know who I am?
I do! Even if you don't remember me!
I've been watching over you
with my Clairvoyance, too!
You and Rebecca!
What?
It must've been hard! Thank you!
Violet!
I will never let a traitor walk away...
...alive!
I didn't betray anybody!
Since that day a decade ago,
I've never trusted you guys,
not even once!
Either way, it's disrespectful
to the Young Master!
Helmet Pop!
Viola-sama!
Oh no!
It isn't a serious wound, is it?!
Sorry that I couldn't protect you!
It was just some shrapnel grazing by!
Let's make our way up!
How we go up doesn't matter, right?!
Wait a second!
The staircase is not that way...
--What?!
--What're you up to?!
That must be it!
Where did they go?!
Young Master?
Why're you here?
DON QUIXOTE DOFLAEMON
KIN'EMON IN DISGUISE
Hm? Young Master?
Who is Young Master? I'm Don Quixote...
That's how they address Doflamingo!
I am the Young Master.
There are some intruders in the palace.
Please wait upstairs until we wipe them out.
No, I can't do that...
I mean, I'll leave it up to you.
I'm gonna go down underground
to see how Kanjuro is doing.
Kanjuro?
The samurai who has disappeared
from the junkyard?
Indeed. I'm gonna go see Kanjuro
who has disappeared from the junkyard...
What?!
He disappeared?!
Boy! We made it straight to our destination!
THE SUIT CHAMBER
No, you'll have to wait!
Hey, why do we have to hide?!
Mingo is there!
Be quiet! Don't ruin their operation!
--What operation?
--The Tontattas' Operation SOP!
We can only make a move
after they pull it off.
So stay still for now!
I thought you guys wanted to destroy
the SMILE factory and that's it.
Then why are the Straw Hats working with
the Little People of Green Bit?
They're not acting on some casual whim.
The Little People?
How did they sneak into the basement?
Why do they wanna attack Sugar?
I don't know why but they keep doing things
that are causing me a lot of grief.
If it's not a coincidence, it means...
...they know what's behind
the darkness of this country!
Answer!
The Young Master is asking
you questions, Law!
Don't do it if it's gonna
make you cry-dasuyan!
You two never change!
I told you.
I have nothing to do with them anymore!
Our alliance ended.
I don't know what you're
talking about at all.
Are you trying to fool me?
Or do you really not know anything?
If Violet were with us,
she could tell what's in your mind easily.
Or...
...you didn't instigate them,
did you, King Riku?
The Tontattas once served you.
Father-sama?! Why is he here in the palace?!
Tra-guy seems alive.
King Riku!
I'm glad you're okay after a decade!
Your name is Kyros, huh? Come with me!
I will save you at any cost!
Hey, let's kick Mingo's ass already!
I said wait!
What are Leo and the others doing?!
The moment that all the toys in Dressrosa
change back to humans will be...
...the one and only chance
to take down Doflamingo!
I will finish him off at any price!
I won't let
Cub and the others' effort go to waste!
I'm counting on you, Leo! Usoland!
THE RUINS OF THE "EXECUTIVE TOWER"
IN THE UNDERGROUND TRADE PORT
Leo! You...
I'm not that hurt. It's nothing.
Everybody's trying their best!
To accomplish Operation SOP!
H-Hey!
Are you still going on with this?
Of course, I am!
If we can't knock Sugar out,
the commander and the Big Humans
who got turned into toys...
...can't change back!
Making Sugar eat this clump
of Tatababasco Sauce is...
...our responsibility!
These guys...!
Do you still want something?
How annoying.
Not just to rescue our captive friends
but also to save the whole of Dressrosa
and restore the King Riku dynasty, we must...
...accomplish Operation SOP first!
Charge!
Don't bother!
Stand up, little bears!
I don't wanna do this!
--I don't wanna fight our friends!
--Somebody, help!
Now, go ahead and kill each other!
What are they doing?!
They did their best already!
They are... helpless fools!
I agree.
But I like them.
Robin?!
You're barely alive!
Doce Fleurs!
What's this?! What's this?!
What's this?! It's so creepy!
--Leo!
--Robiland!
Do it now!
Put the Tatababasco grape in her mouth!
Thank you!
He can make it!
That's it!
Leo!
What?! What happened?!
I thought he was gonna make it!
Stop wasting your time!
There is no salvaging Operation SOP now!
Merciless Trebol torments and
squishes the Little People one after another!
But even though they hear their
friends screaming and crying,
the Tontattas keep their spirits high...
...believing in their last hope -
the legendary hero named Usoland!
On the next episode of One Piece!
A Liar! Usoland on the Run!
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!