Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and were drawn into a climactic
battle on Punk Hazard
which ended with Caesar's capture.
Then, they headed out
for their next destination - Dressrosa
along with their pirate
ally - the Warlord - Law.
In the course of their
trip, they were attacked by
the Breed Pirates who were
looking to get hold of Caesar
but they defeated them
after a great struggle.
"Don Quixote Doflamingo..."
"...Withdraws from..."
"...the Seven Warlords"!
"Startling!
The Big News Shakes Up the New World!"
"Withdraws from the Seven Warlords"?
What's going on?
How do I know? Don't ask me!
Dressrosa is finished!
All tall waves were originally...
...little waves, barely worthy of notice.
Hey! What's gonna happen to the arms deal
between Don Quixote family and us?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
I've been trying to reach them
but nobody picks up!
What should we do?!
I-I can't believe this!
We will lose the war without arms!
Hey, listen to this!
Those reckless rookies from two years ago
formed an alliance!
I'm sure they're up to something!
Doflamingo resigned from the Warlords!
Why did he do that?!
Isn't there anymore information?!
Alright! Get more information!
How did they find out about our alliance?!
Who is this freelance writer named Absa?!
He gets scoops very often these days!
I don't care about us.
I'm more concerned about the other news.
Straw Hat and Trafalgar!
I'm sure they're looking to take out
one of the Four Emperors like we are.
Which one is their target?!
Ring, ring, ring... Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring, ring...
Ring, ring... Clank.
It's me.
I resigned from the Warlords.
--He picked up!
--Picked up!
Finally!
Doflamingo?!
He will hear you!
Hello? I'm Monkey D. Luffy!
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
I told you to shut up!
Hey, Mingo!
Are you stupid, old Caesar's boss?!
He gave Brownbeard and the children hell!
We will give you back Caesar as we promised
but if you do that again,
I will beat the hell out of you!
Straw Hat Luffy.
You went away for two years
after your brother died.
Where were you
and what were you doing?
I shouldn't tell anyone about it!
I wanted to see you.
What?
I have something
that you'll want very badly now.
Something... that I'll want...
…very badly?
H-Hey!
How delicious is that meat
you're talking about?!
Straw Hat-ya!
Don't get drawn into his pace!
One chunk of meat! Two chunks of meat!
Luffy!
Keep yourself together!
This is a special attack called "His Pace"!
One hundred chunks of meat!
Two hundred chunks of meat!
Stop! Don't get drawn into it!
Joker! Cut the crap!
We'll hand Caesar over to you as we promised.
Well, that's for your own good.
If you try to run away with him,
you know what will happen to you guys.
Now, can I hear my precious
business partner's voice?
Joker! I'm sorry!
You resigned from the Warlords for me!
Did you hear him?
Yeah, he sounded fine.
Eight hours from now,
at the beach on the southeast
side of Green Bit,
the solitary island north of Dressrosa.
We will leave Caesar there
at three in the afternoon.
Go ahead and pick him up.
And this will all be finished.
That's too bad.
I wish I could have a drink with you...
Just hang up!
Clank.
That was close.
You almost got drawn into his pace.
Your eyes! Your eyes!
Hey, wait!
We didn't tell him how many men he can bring!
"How many men"?
That's right.
What are we gonna do
if he brings his entire crew?!
Damn!
It doesn't matter.
The handover of Caesar is a part of our plan.
It's just to lure them.
You mean, destroying a
SMILE manufacturing factory
while it's unguarded is our main purpose?!
Yes. But we don't know where it is.
You're joking.
Don't worry!
Factories are big. You can barely miss them.
Once we get there, we'll super find it!
I will destroy it with my laser beam!
Oh, brother!
I have intelligence on
everything but the factory.
No wonder.
It's an important asset for them, isn't it?
Maybe, there is a secret to it.
Law-dono!
You said you're gonna
go to Green Bit earlier!
Earlier!
We will dock this ship at Dressrosa.
Don't worry.
Is that so? Thank you!
Thank you!
Tra-guy, have you been to that island?
Dress-roba!
Dress-roba (old woman)?
It's "rosa"!
I've never been there.
It's that bastard's kingdom.
Then, let's figure everything out
once we get there!
It's gonna be an adventure!
Can't wait to see Dressrosa!
I wanna go to the Wano Kingdom soon, too!
Don't be ridiculous!
You can't just show up without a plan...
Sanji, I'm hungry!
What do we have for breakfast?
Sandwiches.
Yeah! I want a cotton-candy sandwich!
I'll just have a cup of tea.
I'm gonna have cola!
A glass of milk for me!
I think the best breakfast in the world is
Sanji-kun's sandwiches!
What is a sandwich?
I don't like bread!
I can't tell you why we were being chased.
But we set sail for the
place called Zou originally.
Zou?
Do you know it?
It's another coincidence.
After handing over Caesar
and destroying the SMILE factory,
I was gonna head for Zou.
Really?!
Yes, my crew is already there.
I-If so, can we go along with you there?
Yes, you can! Let's go there
and then the Wano Kingdom!
Hey!
Thank you!
W-Well...
Luffy-dono, thank you for everything!
Everything!
Don't mention it!
Right, Tra-guy?
Pardon me.
Three samurais including me, and Momonosuke -
four of us headed for Zou
but our ship wrecked
and two of us samurais and Momonosuke
drifted to Dressrosa.
But we had been chased by
Doflamingo and the others there
and I ran into an unknown ship.
There, I met the children
who were looking to get treated.
And unfortunately, the ship left the port
before I knew it and headed for that island.
--Father!
--Oh no! Momonosuke!
I was gonna go after the ship
and my fellow samurai Kanjuro tried
to cover me but got caught!
Go after Momonosuke! Don't worry about me!
He let me sail out to the sea!
I have to save him!
I have to go back!
What a man, Kanjuro!
Kanjuro!
Alright! I'm gonna go save him with you!
Guys! Don't forget our purpose!
Kanjuro!
Young Master-sama,
Trébol-sama is not here yet.
Okay.
Thank you for waiting.
NAVY
THE NAVY HEADQUARTERS
There are only seven Warlords in the world!
They are the pirates who
were chosen and given
the carte blanche for robbery
by the World Government
in exchange for their overwhelming strength
and notorious prestige!
Them taking sides with
the Government has to be
seen as a threat to all
other pirates in the world.
The greatest swordsman in the world!
"Hawk-Eye" Dracule Mihawk!
The king of Dressrosa
and a charismatic devil!
"Heavenly Demon" Don Quixote Doflamingo!
He is now the Navy's human weapon!
"Tyrant" Bartholomew Kuma!
The empress of Amazon Lily!
"Pirate Empress" Boa Hancock!
One of the Worst Generation
and the mastermind of the Rocky Port Incident!
"Surgeon of Death" Trafalgar Law!
And this man has become powerful rapidly
in last two years.
The leader of the Pirate Dispatch Organization
and a living legend.
"Star Clown" Buggy!
Are you surprised that I'm a Warlord?
You dummies!
It's not like I wanted to become one.
The World Government begged me in tears
so I accepted reluctantly!
But this is only the beginning.
No one can stop me from advancing!
I'm gonna join the Four
Emperors in a few years!
And I'm gonna become the King of...
And the man I told you about earlier.
They are the Seven Warlords.
But that all changed early this morning.
Doflamingo resigned out of the blue.
And we might need to expel Law
from the Warlords depending on his intention.
Together, they're one of the
Three Great Powers along with the
Navy HQ and the Four Emperors.
Things shouldn't be so unstable...
Yes, I know, Brandnew.
Fleet Admiral!
I'm not gonna let Law and Straw Hat
do whatever they want!
I got an annoying call from
Smoker of the G-5 yesterday.
Let's see how things go for today.
I sent Fujitora!
Your Majesty!
Please don't quit!
Doflamingo-sama!
Is it true what they say on the newspaper?!
Please tell us it's not true!
Trébol-sama!
Trébol-sama, where are you?!
Have you seen Trébol-sama?
No.
Okay.
I wonder what Young
Master-sama is going to do?!
If the Navy is gonna come to attack,
I want to fight-in!
We will just follow the Young Master.
Trébol-sama, where are you?
Oh, Baby 5!
What are you doing up there?!
Look! The whole kingdom is going crazy!
I'm sure the whole world is getting upset!
Hey, hey!
By the way, did you get
your fiancé killed again?
Too close!
Why do you keep asking me that?
You're so annoying!
Annoying but?
Annoying but what? Hmmm?
--Too close!
Annoying but you like me, maybe?
That's enough!
Young Master-sama was calling you!
Young Master-sama?
He wanted you to bring that thing!
Stay away! You make me sick!
Hey, hey, hey!
You just keep getting your fiancé killed! Baby 5!
Stop choosing guys that would
be killed by Doffy and marry me!
Hmm, just kidding!
Do you...
...need me?
Cut it out!
The Colosseum is always packed.
Thanks to you, Diamante.
What are you saying?
Doffy, that's because
you're a charismatic king.
No.
That's because you're strong.
Stop. You make it sound like
I'm the hero of the Colosseum.
You are the hero of the Colosseum.
Stop saying that.
Okay, I stop.
Alright, I admit it if you insist!
Yes, I am the hero of the Colosseum!
I brought it!
Doffy, it's that thing!
You're too close!
Too close but?
But I like it. Sit down.
If Straw Hat Luffy finds out about this,
I'm sure he will try to get hold of it.
An alliance can sometimes prove a hindrance.
Diamante. I want to entrust this to you.
Wait a second, Doffy! I can't take it.
No, I want to entrust this to you.
Stop. You make it sound like
I'm some kind of genius.
I can only entrust this to a genius like you.
Stop saying that.
Okay, I stop.
Alright, I admit that I'm
a genius if you insist!
Yes! I can take care of
that dumb-ass Straw Hat!
I'll be counting on you!
I know he will jump at it!
The source of his late brother's power.
The Flare-Flare Fruit.
I'm sure he wouldn't want
anybody else to have it!
I see an island!
I see it!
The Straw Hats see a shadow of an island.
What is that rocky island?!
We made it! It's Dressrosa!
You idiot! Don't shout!
Doflamingo will hear us!
No, he won't!
We'll save you soon, Kanjuro!
This is a kingdom of love
and passion - Dressrosa.
I can't wait!