Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
"The Worst Man in the Eastern Seas!
Fishman Pirate Arlong!"
The weather's so great!
Is the Grand Line far,
far away that way?!
Or is it maybe this way?!
That way?! This way?!
This is so exciting!
You're annoying. Sit still, will ya?
Sorry! Sorry!
But we finally have a cook,
so now we just need to get Nami back
and then we're finally
going into the Grand Line!
Nami-san, huh?
Just remembering her beautiful
visage makes me happy!
How I can't wait to see her again!
Hey, Yosaku. We're almost
to where Nami is, right?
You guys're soft-minded!
Too soft-minded!
Don't you get it?!
Minute by minute, we're heading
right for the infamous Arlong!
Big Sis's eyes were glued to
Arlong's picture when she saw it!
She wasn't her normal self!
Big Sis Nami plans to take down Arlong
and collect his
20 million-Berry bounty!
She may already be inside
his compound as we speak!
Well, let's have some food!
Yeah.
Gahh!
Don't tell me you guys've
never heard of Arlong?!
Arlong? Who's that?
Never heard of him.
Alright, listen up!
I guess I'll just have to
fill you in about everything!
Arlong is a fishman who used to
rampage throughout the Grand Line!
Fishman?
A fishman, huh? I haven't met one yet.
Say, I hear the mermaids on
Fishman Island in the Grand Line
are absolutely beautiful!
Are fishmen...
...like this?
--That's a masterpiece!
--Can't you guys stay focused?!
Alright, then. I'll explain
from the very beginning.
The reason the Grand Line's called
a pirate graveyard in the first place
is because of the three
powers that reign over it.
One of which is the
Seven Warlords of the Sea!
Seven Warlords?
Simply put, they're
government-authorized pirates.
What?
Why would pirates get
a government's approval?
By paying the government a cut
of the loot they take from pirates,
the Seven Warlords
are allowed to exist!
In other pirates' eyes, they're
no more than "government dogs,"
but they're strong!
Even Hawk-Eye Mihawk, the guy
Big Bro Zoro lost to, is a Warlord!
That's awesome!
There's seven of those guys?!
The Seven Warlords are awesome!
So, one of the Seven Warlords
is Jimbei, a fishman pirate boss.
And the fishman Arlong is
a pirate right on par with him
who used to commit atrocity
after atrocity in the Grand Line!
Like this?
That's just your last picture standing up!
Arlong has rule over 20 towns
since coming to the East Blue!
His strength is
far superior to Don Krieg's!
But why would Nami-san
go to this guy all by herself?
I told you, she's after
the bounty on his head!
No, who knows? Maybe Nami-san
is actually a mermaid!
Especially given how lovely she is!
"Nami"
Like this?!
I'll kill you!
Do you guys even understand
what I've told you?!
Yeah, there's a strong
fishman, right? We get it!
No, you don't get it!
You don't know how strong fishmen are!
We'll find out when we
get there. Quit worrying.
Anyways, let's have some food.
Yeah! Food!
Eh? Food?
What do you want?
Meat things with bones in it!
I want sautéed bean sprouts!
Alright! Leave it to me!
I'll be done in no time!
Meat and bean sprouts...
Having a cook really is great!
Y-Yeah!
Meat! A jumbo serving of meat!
And bean sprouts for me!
A jumbo serving!
I'm back here again...
My... hometown...
All right. Here is this
month's amount. Accept it.
Arlong-kun.
You're on a completely different level
of intellect than ordinary pirates.
You truly know how
to get ahead in the world.
Likewise!
Befriending me means you can
milk the East Blue all you want!
For a navy colonel,
you're wise to realize that!
Thanks as always.
Now you say that?
A good world is one in
which money flows well!
Money is good. You can
trust it more than anything.
Wouldn't you agree?
I-Indeed...
I hate humans, but good sports
like you are an exception.
Well, I should be going...
Come drink with us sometime!
Let's have fun!
It's not good for a navy ship on patrol
to be stopped at a pirate island.
I'll kill anyone for you
who tells headquarters.
No, I'll be leaving.
Hey! The colonel's heading back!
Take him to his ship!
Right!
Get in the octopus pot!
I'll take you there!
Right. Thanks.
But you always have such a funny face!
It looks just like a rat's!
Hey! Hachi! Watch your mouth!
The colonel is a valued guest!
Oh, right! Sorry!
No, it's all right.
Okay! Here we go!
You damn fishmen. You're creepy as hell.
But you're great as pay dirt!
Hey, you! Out of the way!
I'm here to kill Arlong!
Arlong killed my daddy!
Move, or I'll kill you, too!
Hey!
Arlong doesn't have time to
bother with little brats like you!
Now go home!
Use that to at least keep yourself safe.
Darn it!
Oh! You're back, Nami!
That was a long trip!
Well? How was your haul this time?
Couldn't have gone better!
I earned a ton!
I found so many suckers who are
fooled so easily! As you can see!
Betrayal is your forte!
I guess.
Hey! Brothers! Our friend has returned!
Prepare a party!
It's Nami!
Nami's back!
W-W-We're finally here! Arlong Park!
So this is the hideout
of the fishman Arlong,
who came from the Grand Line?!
Is Nami really here?!
Big Sis Nami was on the Going Merry,
so let's first see if it's
stopped on this island or not!
G-Good idea!
We're busting in.
W-Why are we suddenly doing that?!
Are you stupid?!
We haven't even found any clues yet!
We're dealing with
those fishmen, you know!
We gotta have a strategy first!
Forget that tedious stuff.
Luffy told me to bring her back.
I'm gonna do just that,
no matter who we're dealing with!
Not good...
Let's go!
There it is! I found it!
It's the Going Merry! It's over there!
So Big Sis Nami is here!
Hey, you! What's the big idea?!
Untie me!
We're farther east of Arlong Park...
Cocoyashi Village.
But it's strange.
Why's the ship stopped
so far from the village?
Untie me!
You've been hurt so bad
you're nearly dead!
Just take it easy!
Just leave this all to me!
I am so going to chop him up someday!
I'll bring the girl back!
You're in high spirits, now that
you know she's not in Arlong Park...
Right rudder, full!
Pull the boat up to the Going Merry!
Right!
All right! I hereby title
this brave image of me
about to tread unknown soil,
"Captain Usopp's Grand Adventure"!
Are you alright?!
There! There!
Fishmen!
Full speed ahead!
Right!
Why did you just pass by it?!
Did you see that?!
There were fishmen there!
They're Arlong's crew! They're scary!
Somethin' wrong with that?!
Don't you snap at me!
I guess this whole area is
seriously under Arlong's control!
What now?
Alright! We'll just say we
couldn't bring Nami back!
Untie me, you idiots!
Never seen that boat before.
It's suspicious.
Escape!
Agreed!
Hold it, you two!
Bye!
Hey! At least untie me!
Huh? It's just him?
Were you banished from
somewhere or somethin'?
I-I guess...
I'm gonna kill those guys!
Ah! So you got these injuries
from being tortured!
Alright! Let's take him
back to Arlong-san for now!
Forgive us, Zoro! I'll tell Luffy
you were a truly brave man!
What an unlucky person!
I'll never forget about you, Big Bro!
All right, then!
Let's get on dry land for now!
Right!
There should be a town
called Gosa up here!
W-What happened to this town?!
I heard Arlong ravaged it
a few weeks back, but...
A-All the houses have been flipped over!
I hear fishmen generally have
ten times the strength of humans!
In short, could this be how strong
people from the Grand Line are?!
But how'd even the street get like this?
That was the doing
of a monster called Momoo.
Monster?
This place even has monsters?
We brought him from the Grand Line.
From the Grand Line, huh?
"We"?
You're with that guy who
got banished, aren't you?!
Bye!
Get back here!
Escaped by a hair...
Please stay safe, Big Bro Usopp!
I'm going to wait here for
Yosaku and Big Bro Luffy!
As if a fishman can possibly
catch me on dry land!
I'm used to this!
Just try and catch up to me!
W-What the...
I found you, fishman!
You killed my daddy!
And I'm gonna kill you!
Don't mess with the fishmen!
Have you forgotten?!
Everyone here in Gosa
was slaughtered because just
one villager defied them!
Huh?
You look like a fishman,
but you're human. Just barely.
Just barely?!
Where are you?! Over there?!
He's coming!
A fishman!
There was a real one, too?
Get back!
I, Captain Usopp, will protect you!
I can handle one easily enough!
Take this! Special Attack: Lead Star!
No one ever listens!
I told you, the fishmen'll
kill us if we mess with them!
What is it?!
There was a long-nosed man!
Where'd he go?!
That way!
That way, huh?!
Hurry! We'll carry him to my house!
That looks great!
Lemme see, lemme see!
Guess that's good enough.
Momoo!
Time to eat! Momoo!
That's strange.
He should be starving by now...
Where could he have gone?
You're great, Big Bro Sanji!
This is topnotch seasoning!
I want to make dinner for Nami-san
more than I do for you guys.
I hope you manage to get
Big Sis Nami to join again!
We will! She's our navigator!
She's going to the Grand Line with us!
That's mine!
You just ate one! Let me have one, too!
--But it's mine!
--C'mon, just one!
--No! Give it back!
--C'mon! Let me have it!
Quit rockin' the damn boat!
You're going to make me
spill this fine alcohol!
Open the gate!
We've brought someone suspicious!
I'll ask again.
Just why have you come here?
I told you already-- I'm looking
for a girl! Half-fish bastard!
You've got a big mouth
for a lowly human.
I'll excuse you this time,
but never say "half-fish" again.
We fishmen are "evolved humans"
who've gained the ability
to breathe underwater.
Those fish abilities result
in us being superior to you.
As proof, we possess numerous
abilities that surpass those of humans!
Get it through your head that
fishmen are the lord of all things!
Humans defying fishmen is basically
defying the laws of nature!
I'm sick of those ridiculous
opinions of yours, Arlong.
Don't look so stern, Nami.
You may be human,
but you're an exception.
You're a skilled surveyor and prized
member of the Arlong Pirates!
You make truly accurate
sea charts for us!
I have far more smarts than you guys.
It's only natural.
Hey! Nami! What does
he mean, "surveyor"?!
Why are you acting all
friendly-like with this guy?!
Oh? He's an acquaintance of yours?
Don't be ridiculous.
He was just my prey.
I swiped a whole load of treasure
from this guy this time around.
To think he'd follow me here,
without any idea he'd been tricked...
Talk about unbelievably stupid.
So these are your true colors, huh?
After you hated pirates so much before.
Surprised? It was all an act.
Does this make it clear enough?
T-That's...
I'm a pirate, plain and simple!
And a leader of the Arlong Pirates!
My overflowing feelings don't connect
as I firmly squeeze your hand back
I'll set off by myself,
so keep watching me intently
as I go into the distance
I was thinking about it
a bit since this morning
Why is it so hot?
Starting from some point, I haven't
been able to get away from that
I want to catch those
feelings that rushed off,
and I'm already about
to overtake myself, even
I want to embrace my
dreams that have jumped out
With you, I can run there
Apparently Arlong and the
fishmen rule this village,
and no one can oppose them!
Eh? Don't tell me
fish cuisine isn't allowed.
I prefer meat with a bone in it!
Sanji! More meat!
To think she'd team up
with the fishmen...
Wasn't Nami one of us?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Witch of Cocoyashi Village!
Arlong's Female Leader"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!