Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves
caught up in the turmoil.
Uh, everybody on the Fish-Man Island.
Can you hear me?
I'm the captain of the New Fish-Man
Pirates from the Fish-Man District,
Hordy Jones!
"The Kingdom in Shock!
An Order to Execute Neptune Issued!"
All right. Next!
Next!
You won't step on it?!
I'm sure Queen Otohime would forgive us.
If I refuse, they'll kill
me! I have no choice!
I'm sorry, Queen Otohime!
Okay, you pass! Next!
This is boring! Surprisingly,
they're all just stepping on it.
Otohime was not that
well-respected after all!
Daruma-san, Captain Hordy is on the air now!
Huh?
--So he is the one who is behind all of this!
--He made us step on the picture!
Hey, wasn't he the one who killed
the assassin of Otohime-sama?
Yes, his name is Hordy Jones!
I'm sure it was him!
Wasn't he a soldier of Neptune's army?
There is something I want
to tell all citizens of...
SEA FOREST
...the Ryugu Kingdom.
This country will soon be destroyed.
And it will be rebuilt under a new king.
Namely, me!
What is he talking about?!
CORAL HILL
Who does he think he is?! Cut the crap!
--Where is he broadcasting from?
--What happened to the King?
I heard the Straw Hats occupied
the palace - what happened to them?
What's going on in this country?
The new Fish-Man Island over which I will
rule is going to be strict in discipline.
Those of you who hope for
friendly relations with humans,
get packing and leave this country!
Humans are weak and they
don't know their place.
They don't deserve any help
from us strong Fish-Men.
Instead, we will have new residents
from the Fish-Man District soon.
They hate humans and hope to
change this island like us.
They're in the same camp as us.
What? New residents?
WATERWHEEL TOWN
All those outlaws will come and live with us?
I bet you all witnessed how your
beloved Queen Otohime died.
She was so selfless and tried so hard to
build a bridge between Fish-Men and humans.
But who killed her?!
It was a human.
If you trust them and meet halfway
in friendship, they'll disappoint you again!
Why can't you see it?!
That bastard!
Duped by the Neptune family, you are
all heading down the path of death.
Their high-sounding
dream is just unfeasible.
It's a lie that will lead you to perdition.
No!
Look at this!
Father-sama!
Father!
King-sama!
The Great Knight Neptune
got old like anyone else.
There is no future for the Fish-Man
Island if the old guard remains in power.
Unfortunately the King
was captured because of us...
...or Zoro.
Don't worry, Nami-san.
It's all that Moss Head's fault.
What did you people do?!
B-B-But, Boss Jimbei!
Soldiers of Neptune's army attacked
Nami-chin and the others first!
Neptune's army?
Citizens of Fish-Man Island!
It's time to say goodbye...
...to the old Ryugu Kingdom!
Three hours from now, at Conchcorde Plaza,
I'm going to cut this
incompetent King's head off!
The Great Pirate Era began...
...when they executed a human -
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates.
That era saw humans grow
to persecute Fish-Men.
So this time, by executing Neptune,
I'll start the Great Fish-Man Era...
...where Fish-Men will dominate humans.
As you may know by now, I'm at the Ryugu Palace
as I speak. And we found something good.
It's the letter from the Celestial Dragons
that Queen Otohime got 10 years ago,
at the risk of her life!
If I destroy that letter, it's over.
You won't get another one.
And,
in this big box,
there are signatures from
the majority of this country.
I couldn't believe my eyes!
There are so many fools who
want to befriend humans!
Those of you who have signed your
name would oppose my new kingdom.
So this is actually...
...a list of traitors!
No more stepping on her picture.
It would be easy to pretend
you don't mind stepping on it.
But these signatures will tell
who is my enemy and who is not.
It's hard evidence!
I will take care of those enemies one by one.
First...
Togare from Coral Hill.
No, I... I'm not... I...
Next, Gotan from Waterwheel Town.
What?
Luca from Mermaid Cove.
Garcia from Fishverly Hills.
Meverly from the Coral Apartment.
There are a lot more!
Stop!
I won't let you hurt my folk!
Well, enough for now.
We don't have time anyway.
Lastly...
Straw Hat Pirates!
I'll show you something good.
I know you are somewhere on
the island watching this.
You people shattered Arlong's dream
- he was a symbol of Fish-Men's anger.
Zoro! Usopp! Brook!
--What fools...
--I can't believe they got caught!
Do it.
Yes, Boss!
--Oh? Oh? Oh? Oh?
--Wh-What's going on?!
Th-This is so high!
--What's this noise?
--It's like a roar...
--It's water!
That room will be filled with water by
the time we finish executing the King.
You lowly creatures can't
survive that, can you?
Straw Hat Luffy with a 400
million berry bounty!
Your people's heads will serve perfectly
as a lesson to humans above ground.
Now, let's start cleaning
up the old Ryugu Kingdom!
Bury the embarrassing past and shift
the helm towards the great future!
The Fish-Man Island will win
back its pride in three hours!
I-I can't believe it!
We won't let them do that!
Now, issue an order to Daruma
and the others to assemble.
It's gonna get busy.
Yes, Boss.
I'll make your execution a big show.
So that all citizens of the
Fish-Man Island will be afraid of me.
How could you be so selfish?
You can't govern a country like that!
All kings are selfish.
You were a selfish king to us.
You and Otohime's dream made me sick
ever since I was a soldier in your army.
When the leader changes,
a country will change, too.
I will be the "law" from now on!
Damn! The water level keeps rising!
Usopp-san, I just got dry.
I don't wanna soak in sea water again!
Me neither!
Do something, Zoro-kun!
All right. Then...
...untie me.
Got it!
I feel it! I feel my psychic power!
Chains, come off! Chains, come off!
Chains, come off! Come
off, chains! Come off...
...or not!
It's no good. I don't have any psychic power.
Hey hey, did you see it?
The look on those Fish-Men's
faces when I moved.
He isn't moving. Is he dead?
I should stay dead.
What should we do with
these skeletal remains?
How did they even get here?
I guess they flowed in with the water when
Captain Hordy broke the wall of the palace.
Let's pull them up onto the bridge.
Great!
Brook can free us later if he
keeps pretending to be dead.
He was adrift at sea. I feel sorry for him.
He must've been dead for 50 years or so.
That's correct!
You got it right!
H-He's moving!
Yes, I'm a dead skeleton--Brook!
Wait!
Nice, Brook!
Touch my bones!
Here, here, here! Here!
That's enough!
Damn.
Oh, I can't stop laughing
just thinking about it!
We got caught because of you!
Help! They're gonna kill me!
Oh, I'm already dead.
Well, at least Nami and the others got away.
They can bring Luffy and the others here.
What if they don't come?!
Robin would say,
"I hope Nami hasn't been
eaten by a deep-sea fish."
Sounds exactly like her!
This is different from any of
Poneglyphs than I've seen before.
This is like a letter... A letter of apology.
Who are you apologizing to? And who are you?
"Joy Boy."
Hey.
He said I'm worth 400 million!
When did they raise it?
This is no time for that!
Obviously, they want to fight us.
The War of the Best at Marineford
made you infamous instantly.
When it goes over 300 million,
it's not easily increased again.
But if somebody wants
to fight me, I'll fight!
Hey wait, Luffy-kun!
Father-sama...
Father-sama!
Father-sama! Father-sama!
Megalo!
I have to go save him!
Wait, Princess Shirahoshi!
Stop, Megalo!
Wait!
Boss Jimbei-sama! But...
Luffy-kun, Princess-sama,
both of you have to wait!
Princess, I don't think you should go either.
Hachi-sama...
What Hordy is most afraid of
in the Ryugu Kingdom now is...
...Princess Shirahoshi's ability!
Even if he reshapes the Fish-Man
Island exactly the way he wants,
once she controls the Sea Kings
to attack the island, it'll be gone.
He took the King hostage
to use him as a shield.
So what they're really going
for is Shirahoshi-chan.
Hordy is not planning to capture
her and get control of her power.
He prefers her power didn't exist at all.
That's why he teamed up with Decken
who is capable of killing her.
Hordy wants to get rid of everything
that could stand in his way.
He is right.
Rushing to the plaza is just what
Hordy wants Princess-sama to do!
I have been told about my power but...
...I have never communicated
with the Sea Kings-sama.
I don't even know if I really
have that kind of power...
But even so, I'm sure that
Hordy will try to kill you.
And we shouldn't let Hordy know
that you can't control the power.
It's good that he is afraid of it.
Is that all? Then I'll get going.
Shark! Take me to the Ryugu Palace!
Sanji, take care of Coward!
Yeah! Count on it.
I said "Wait," Luffy-kun!
Huh?
You people shouldn't fight Hordy!
Why are you trying to stop me?
Is it because we're humans?
You two shouldn't say that!
It makes things more complicated!
That's right! You humans shouldn't do that!
The surviving Fish-Men
will hate humans again!
You have to leave it to me.
Jimbei! They have my crew!
And I got to do something about Hordy
before my friends get into real trouble!
Luffy-chin...
Straw Hat.
Why can't you see it?!
--I'm going.
--You're impossible!
Just shut up!
Stop me if you can!
Luffy.
I shouldn't let my guard down
just because we fought together.
I almost forgot that
you're that man's brother.
If you're not going to
listen to me, I have no choice!
Whoa... Whoa!
You ready to do this?
Kid?
Luffy and Jinbei's emotional
battle has begun!
Luffy faces the overwhelming force
of Jimbei's Fish-Man Karate.
Their duel is interrupted,
and takes an unexpected turn!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Rift Opens Up!
Luffy vs. Jimbei!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!