Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
As night falls upon the
forest around these parts,
it becomes so perilous it hardly
seems like it belongs to this world.
If you please, feel free to take
my carriage to the mansion.
There's a mansion?
Indeed, there is. You're welcome
to visit Dr. Hogback's mansion.
What?!
What? What is it?
What's the big deal, Chopper?
Hogback...
Huh...?
"The Man Called a Genius!
Hogback Makes His Appearance!"
Hey... The fog kept me from
getting a good look at the horses,
but didn't they seem a bit strange?
Uh, you must be imagining things!
Really...? I hope that's all it is.
Anyway, you're a lifesaver!
Thanks for saving our hides!
It was nothing! Please, have a drink.
This forest is filled with unusual animals,
making it dangerous to simply walk around.
Yeah, I was surprised! I thought
Cerberus was an imaginary animal.
That terrifying beast must
be a mutant or something!
I was afraid we were gonna be stuck
in that tree when you found us.
The mansion is the best place
to wait for your friends.
It stands out and it's safe.
Plus...
...I'll get to meet Dr. Hogback!
Is he all that famous?
There isn't a single doctor
who doesn't know his name!
He's a famous surgeon.
With his miraculous operations, he's saved
as many people as there are stars!
He has obtained status, honor,
and everything you could get as a doctor!
He's earned the respect of
doctors around the world!
But then he suddenly vanished one day.
Some say he went missing,
while others say he was abducted.
It threw the medical world
into an uproar for a while,
but in the end, no one could find any leads.
Now he's on the verge of becoming a legend.
You meant that Dr. Hogback, right?
Indeed! The doctor is
still conducting research
that goes beyond the
boundary of human knowledge.
Would it be okay if I
asked for his autograph?
If that's all you want,
I'm sure that would be fine.
No way!
This forest... even has lions!
No!
What's your problem?! Don't freak me out!
What was it?!
J-Just now, I saw a l-lion outside!
I-It looked like this.
I don't buy that!
Then take a look for yourself!
Go on!
Prey... Fresh prey...
Prey! Fresh prey!
Weird stuff's out there!
Super weird stuff's out there!
Stop right here! Stop the
carriage, Hildon-san!
Why are you so worked up?
Are you having hallucinations?
That wasn't a hallucination!
I'm sure they were out there!
This forest is way too messed up!
I suppose. This forest is a little strange.
The combination of thick fog and fear
can induce hallucinations in some.
Huh? That was a hallucination?
What a relief!
Really, now? A hallucination?
Nah, it was too vivid for that!
Gulp, gulp, gulp!
Hildon-san! Sorry, but could
you take us back to the shore?
Even if it's dangerous, we'll manage somehow.
What?!
But then I won't get to meet Dr. Hogback!
I wanna meet him!
Yeah, yeah, I get how you feel!
But this is when we've gotta listen to
our special Something's Fishy Sensors!
Are you willing to die to meet that doctor?
Or will you skip meeting him
so we can leave this island alive?
Which will it be?!
Of course I don't want to die! Or get scared!
Is that right? I shall
go inform the coachmen.
Everyone, please wait here.
Stop the carriage!
I'm sorry, Chopper! I know
you're passing up a huge chance.
It can't be helped! I'm still green,
since I can't act on my own like Luffy.
"10 Minutes Later..."
"Shhh..."
How long is he going to keep us waiting?
He still isn't back yet...
That's strange. We're just
going back the way we...
What?! No one's there!
Even the horses are gone!
They abandoned us in a graveyard!
They what?! Why?!
Eh?! They abandoned us?!
Sure they aren't going potty?
Hildon! Hey!
Where'd you go?!
Of all the places, why'd they
have to choose a graveyard?
Stop it! Jeez, I'm so scared!
You don't have to remind me where we are!
What's going to happen to us now?
Chopper...
What?!
Beep! Beep!
N-N-No way...
Z-Zombies!
No!!
No!
No! That hurts! It hurts!
Usopp!
Please help me!
No!!
The carriage is gonna fall over!
They're insanely strong!
I've been bit!
Damn it! He bit me!
--Now I'm gonna turn into a zombie!
--Usopp!
I'm on my way!
No, don't bite me! Stop that!
Please save me!
Let go of Usopp!
You bastards!
I'm sorry!
Here, you dropped this.
Oh, thanks.
Hey, save me! They're about to bite me!
Nami!
Crap! Let go of me! Stay back!
Zombies are weak against...
Special Attack! Flame Star!
--Fire!
--That's rottin' bad!
That worked better than I could have hoped!
That was dangerous, you pyro punk!
What if I actually caught on fire,
you stupid jerk?!
Rotten scum!
That ticked off the zombies.
You'd better hurry, Nami!
This is our chance to escape!
R-Right!
At this point, the mansion's the
closest place to run to for safety.
Yeah, let's go there.
That was scary!
We'll be okay! They can't catch up
if we run like mad for the mansion
once we're outta the graveyard!
Zombies can only walk at a
snail's pace and groan at you.
"At a snail's pace"?
"At a snail's pace"? "At a snail's pace"?
"At a snail's pace"?!
Wait for us!
They're fast!
No! No! No--er, huh? Huh?
Just a sec... Time out!
Zero stamina!
Hurry, Usopp!
Y-Yeah!
The waves are carrying the ship away!
What's keeping you, Gah?!
Don't call me "Gah," punk!
The rudder won't budge!
If we used the paddle,
we could fight the waves, but...
I was planning on going to the island anyway.
Why don't we go with the flow?
Jerk! You've totally forgotten
about Nami-san, haven't you?
What's that?
A spider web on the water?
At this rate, we're going to
ram right into the spider web.
Hey, we need the paddle! Release the paddle!
Don't. It's too late for that.
Damn it! It didn't harm the ship,
but now we're stuck here!
And why is this spider
web so freakishly big?!
They... aren't chasing us anymore, are they?
What's with this island?! It's oozing
with stuff that shouldn't exist!
Guys, if I turn into a zombie,
finish me off in a single blow!
Where'd you come up with that?
It was in the Illustrated Zombie Guide
I read in Sunny's library!
For a scaredy-cat, you read
way too many of those books.
Well, we're here. Right now,
I just want a glass of water!
I get to meet him after all. I can't wait!
I don't think anyone in his right mind
would live on this island.
I'd bet on it!
Excuse me! Is this Dr. Hogback's mansion?
We're traveling pira--sailors!
We got lost and could use some help!
Please let us stay here!
Is anyone here?
What's with this mansion?
A tunnel runs through the center of it!
I can see a courtyard on the other side.
Excuse me!
Maybe no one's home.
That would stink! We'll have to
face zombies if we turn back.
Look! A light in the back turned on.
It's not just a light, it's
a spotlight for this well.
"Evil Be Gone"
Wh-What now?!
Welcome!
One, two, three!
What?! What gives?!
Four, five!
That woman's throwing plates!
Six, seven!
Doesn't it seem like she's goin' after me?!
Yes, I am! I cannot invite
you into the mansion.
Those two may step inside.
Huh? Why?
You may get lost!
Eight, nine!
Why me?!
That's enough! Hold your hand!
What was that?!
I can't take any more scary stuff!
Someone's coming out.
I think we can make this
one exception, Cindry-chan.
I'm sorry if she startled you guys.
A long time ago, this woman was
engaged to her wealthy master.
To test his love, she broke
all of his prized plates.
He tossed her out, and her
tragic past has made her
develop an aversion to plates.
She's my servant, Cindry-chan!
Okay, I really don't care.
And I've failed to introduce myself.
I am the world-renowned Dr. Hogback!
Also known as a genius!
--Ten!
--Usopp!
Hey, hey, hey! Cindry-chan,
I said you could stop!
It makes me look bad
when you don't listen to me.
Crap!
I wish plates would disappear
from the face of the earth!
I understand! I understand completely!
But I was in the middle of a conversation!
Chopper, is he the guy
you were talking about?
D-Dr. Hogback in the flesh!
He doesn't seem too bright.
Watch it, Nami!
You may talk inside.
Today, I will make an exception.
All three of you may enter.
Come in!
R-Right, right! Come inside my mansion.
I don't get why I wasn't welcome,
but should we take them up on the offer?
Sure. Beats the zombies outside.
I'm still...
I'm still outside...
It's a pleasure to welcome you to my mansion.
But my, you sure are grungy!
What brings you here?
A whole bunch of things, but for starters--
I'll explain everything in detail later.
Zombies attacked us in the graveyard,
so we ran here for cover.
Zombies, eh?
There was a whole bunch of stuff
that made us doubt our eyes.
What's the deal with this island?
Since you live here,
you've gotta know something!
I see. So they attacked you, huh?
I'm glad you made it here
in one piece. That's a relief!
To answer your question:
I don't know what they are,
which is why I live here.
So you're conducting research on the zombies?
Indeed, I am!
People are terrified when they hear "zombie."
But what if I rephrase it
to "resurrecting the dead"?
Hasn't that been all mankind's eternal dream?
Everyone has a special someone or two
they'd like to see return from the dead.
But toying with human mortality is
unorthodox medicine that disrespects God!
That's why I slipped away
from the public eye--
so I could continue my
research on this island in secret!
S-So that's the story!
But I'm sure tons of people
around the world
would be thrilled if your
research is a success!
I'll be rooting for you, Dr. Hogback!
You're rather open-minded!
Thank you, Dr. Chopper.
What?!
Sh-Shucks, Doctor! I'm not happy because
you thanked me or anything, you jerk!
May I have your autograph?
Why, certainly!
"To Dr. Chopper..."
To Dr. Chopper...
Could you show me your lab later?
By all means, steer clear of my laboratory!
Hey, Cindry-chan! Put the flan on plates!
Couldn't you at least do that for me?
I wish plates would disappear
from the face of the earth!
Guys, I wash the heck out of the
tablecloth for times just like this,
so feel free to eat away!
Don't mind if we do!
You can still use your spoons!
It's yummy and sweet!
I've drawn you a bath.
You're a filthy lot, so go hop in.
Hey, Pops. He doesn't mean anything to me,
but did a weird skeleton
drop by before we arrived?
A-A skeleton?
Yeah. He's tall with an afro
and he's oddly cheerful.
Of course, the fact that he's a talking,
walking skeleton makes him odd enough.
Do you know anything about him?
N-No, I don't...
Really? Then forget it.
Could it be him? Nah, it couldn't be...
Nami, why do I have to
stand watch while you bathe?
Don't look!
Listen! We're leaving as soon as night falls.
Whoa, how could you say that?!
There are zombies outside!
Listen to yourself! Do you seriously
think the mansion is safe?
Huh? Y-You don't mean...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Nami's in a Major Pinch! The Zombie
Mansion and the Invisible Man!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!