Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Those ranked Lieutenant
Commander or below, stay put!
To the two hundred elite Captains and
Commanders, go take them out quickly!
Get them!
Recapture Nico Robin!
I'm part of the Straw Hats, too.
When we fight, we fight together.
Hold strong until Luffy comes!
I'll pursue that woman who threatens
the World Government's plans
to the very ends of the
earth and eliminate her...
...in the name of dark justice!
We came to take Robin away from all that!
Jet Stamp!
Six King Gun!
Luffy!
--I got him!
--Watch out!
Hey! Now's not the time
to be spacing out, Soge...
Luffy!
What're you doing?!
Get up!
Luffy!
"Fists Full of Emotion!
Luffy Unleashes Gatling with All His Might"
Weapons Left!
Super...!
Commander!
What's with those pirates?!
What a crazy brawl! They're holding
their own against Captains!
Is that woman a power holder?!
I'll take care of her. Stay back!
Cien Fleurs!
Flip!
Here we go! Thunder Ball!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Done!
So I guess these guys aren't
the typical small fries, huh?
Two-Sword Style...
...Hawk Wave!
Who's next?!
Usopp...
Luffy!
Get up!
U-Usopp...
S-So... you came?
D-Don't get the wrong idea!
I came here to rescue Robin!
I didn't come here to see your face!
Geez... He's such a...
Hey, you! Boss cat of CP9!
I'm talking to you!
Now, I'll take you on! Bring it on!
Th-That's right! I'm your opponent!
Now, don't be surprised when I tell you this!
I'm the great Captain Usopp,
a pirate among pirates,
the great warrior of the sea who
has 8,000 men under his command!
I've traveled all over the Grand Line
and wreaked havoc on every single island!
Anyone who falls into my hands...
...even you guys, the World Government...
...will be crushed by the tip of my little finger!
If that pisses you off, then bring it on!
You no-good little kitten!
Hey...
Hey... don't! Don't! Hey!
Leave him alone!
You've already lost.
I have no business with you.
They're all gonna be killed anyway.
You just stay there and watch.
All right, come on, boss cat!
I'm gonna blow you away!
Are you stupid?! Stop it, Usopp! He'll kill you!
Shut up! What can you do
when you're almost dead?!
He's mine! I'm gonna beat him up!
Then get up already!
Then don't look like you're about to die!
It's not like you!
Even though there's nothing but smoke
above us, we can still see the sky!
We can see the sea, too!
This isn't... This isn't hell!
Don't look like you're about to die, you jerk!
Don't make us worry, you bastard!
Are you done?
You'd better be prepared.
I know...
This isn't hell or anything.
Luffy...!
Defeat him! We'll all go back together, Luffy!
Of course!
So you can still move...
I never said... I gave in.
Until I defeat you...
...I won't... sink to the ground ever again!
I'm terminating Life Return.
I've had enough with you guys' farce.
I'll crush you with pure power once and for all!
Don't worry about your friends, Straw Hat.
As you wish... to be together with them again...
...I'll send you all to the same hell!
Spots!
They've given us quite a bit of trouble!
If we're just careful about that thunderbolt...
Ahhh! There's another cloud!
Guys, don't gather in one place!
Spread out and attack all at...
What is it, at a time like this?!
What'd you do that for?!
--Guys!
--Hm?!
When the lightning strikes,
please be careful not to get electrocuted!
Thunder Ball!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
Good job, pirate ladies!
We're okay, so go up there
and help the guys already!
Leave the raccoon dog guy to us!
I'm not a raccoon dog. I'm a reindeer.
Okay! Then we'll leave Chopper to you!
--Robin!
--Yeah.
When everyone's fighting so hard,
to think that I can't do anything...
It's frustrating...!
Everyone! Hang in there!
H-Hey! What do you mean run away?!
It's our duty to guard this place!
This isn't the time for that!
This island will be entirely eliminated!
Click. Beep...
--Beep... beep... beep...
--Dammit!
Bingo!
Luffy...
Victory Bird!
Dammit! What's the deal
with them?! I can't hit them!
Hey! I beat them!
Oh, I see! All my shots
must've actually hit them!
That's right! I'm the king of snipers, Sogeking!
♪ I was born on the... ♪
Take this!
I'll show you the power of the Berry-Berry Fruit!
Dammit! I can't make a wrong move here!
You can't do anything, can you?!
Thanks!
Hey you, hold on a sec.
If you like flying so much...
Hey! D-Don't!
Weapons Left!
Be careful! There are some
power holders among them!
They could say the same about us!
Treinta Fleurs! Clutch!
So you're Roronoa Zoro?
And if I am?
I'll defeat you!
Fine!
I ate the Rust-Rust Fruit and became a rust man.
You can't defeat me.
Dammit! My Yubashiri...
I'll turn all your proud swords to rust.
Interesting...
I'll test you.
Now you get it, right?
You can't defeat me with swords!
I... I can't move my body!
I rusted your joint. I'll continue
until your entire body is rusted!
Dammit!
Firebird Star!
Are you okay, Zoro-kun?!
Gum-Gum... Jet Pistol!
I'm not gonna take that a second time!
Ultimate Radius...
Six King Gun!
Until I defeat you...
...I won't... sink to the ground ever again!
In the not-so-distant future, you'll regret
that you took in a troublesome woman.
Gum-Gum...
Yes, we are. I'll never see you guys again.
It's not a matter that people
like you can get involved in.
Robin intends to die for us!
Iron Body!
Are you insane?! Don't think
that you'll be able to survive
after making the entire world your enemy!
I'll pursue that woman to the very
ends of the earth and eliminate her...
I want to live!
...Jet...
...Gatling!
What's going on?!
What happened?!
Luffy!
Luffy...!
The first column is...!
H-Hey... What's that?
Hey! Look over there!
Th-This is a report to all ships.
This is a report to all ships!
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 has just...
Has just been defeated...
by pirate Straw Hat Luffy!
Luffy...
It's over...
We'll be okay now.
We're gonna go back together!
Robin!
So you came... You're such a... You're such a...
Luffy! Into the sea! Jump into the sea!
We've got one more friend, right?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"From the Sea, a Friend Arrives!
The Straw Hats Share the Strongest Bond"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!