Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Die!
Oni Giri!
Beaten by mere sneak thieves...
We ain't sneak thieves...
We're pirates!
Yes! The chart of the Grand Line!
I'll never forgive him!
"Who is the Victor?
Devil Fruit Power Showdown!"
In all my life, I've never been
as mad at someone as him!
That bastard Shanks stole
enormous riches from me!
I don't know how
you two are connected,
but I can say whatever
I want about him!
Get him! Get him! Fight!
Don't neither of you lose!
The North Pole!
No, the South Pole!
You still say that, huh?!
That's right! I'll always say it!
'Cause I'm right!
Oh, you got guts! I'm gonna
settle this once and for all today!
Go ahead and try it!
Alright, you bastard!
I'm gonna bust you up flashily!
Counterattack!
Knock that off!
Who cares which is colder,
the North Pole or the South Pole?!
If you wanna know that badly,
go to both and find out!
Now cool it!
A ship!
Enemy ship to the north-northeast!
Alright! Get ready! It's fightin' time!
Alright! I'm gonna plunder like crazy!
You sure seem happy, Buggy!
Obviously!
Enemy ships are like treasure chests.
It's natural for pirates
to raid 'em! Am I wrong?!
Well, there is some truth to that.
You're too weak!
You and everyone else here
never talk seriously about treasure!
You don't know what it
means to be a pirate!
W-What's this?!
A-A-A treasure map!
I-I've never seen
one before! Awesome!
Is it sitting on the
bottom of the ocean?
Yes! Now my life
is flashily decided!
Today was another easy win!
Hey! Drink up!
Hey, Buggy!
You're not gonna party with us?
We found some neat loot!
I-I don't got anything special!
I don't know anything!
What're you talking about?
Oh, uhh...
You said you were gonna
leave this ship sometime.
What do you plan to do?
I'm gonna have my own ship.
I'm gonna gather a reliable
crew and then see the world.
I'm gonna take my time.
All as a pirate, of course.
You always spew that weakling crap!
Say what?!
I only admire your fighting skill.
Were you just not soft-hearted,
I might've made you my henchman.
Your henchman? Get real!
Huh?
We think differently, so we should
just go in our own directions.
That's what pirates do.
Talking like you're an expert, huh?
But if we ever meet on the ocean,
it'll be a fight to the death.
Yeah. That's another thing pirates do.
You never make sense.
Anyways, you said
something about loot...
Yeah, we found a Devil Fruit.
Devil Fruit?
I heard they're incarnations
of the sea devil.
Supposedly, if you eat one,
you gain devil powers...
...but the sea will hate you
and take your ability to swim!
You'd have to be stupid
to eat something like that!
I'd never get that treasure on
the ocean floor if I couldn't swim!
Still, I bet it'd sell for
100 million Berries...
What?!
I, pirate apprentice Buggy,
will now eat this Devil Fruit!
Gotta love kids!
Never thinking about consequences...
He ate it!
Well, Buggy? Anything
different about your body?
No... Not really...
Aww, it was a fake?
Not surprising, I've only heard
about Devil Fruits from rumors...
Yes! That worked flashily well!
What I ate this afternoon
was a fake I made!
Can't believe everything
went so smoothly!
Now to jump ship before
they find out the truth!
With the money from the Devil Fruit
and the treasure on the map,
I could form my own
pirate group right away!
Hey, Buggy!
Whatcha grinnin' about?
O-Oh, it's you!
Don't scare me like that!
What kind of look is that?
Don't steal too much
food from the kitchen;
the cook'll get mad!
Whew, that was close...
Oh, that reminds me!
The captain just--
Shanks! Damn you!
My... My... I'm...
What's that scrap of paper?
Ahh! My map!
H-Hey, Buggy!
W-What the--? I can't move...
Was it true you lose
the ability to swim?!
Crap!
Hey! Buggy! What're you doing?
You're great at swimming!
Buggy!
H-Help me...
I'll save you, Buggy!
So Shanks saved you?
That's not what I'm trying to say!
Because of him, my plan in life
was suddenly delayed 10 years!
And then I had a revelation!
If underwater's no good,
I'll obtain all the treasure on land!
...Using this Chop-Chop power.
That's why I won't let anyone
who touches my treasure live!
Let go...
...of my treasure!
Crap! He spotted me!
Don't think you can escape me, Nami!
I'm going to flashily chop you up!
M-My balls... balls...
You're still dealing with me!
Something's wrong.
The mayor's never been
gone this long before...
Something must be
happening in town after all!
There's been more
cannon fire than usual, too!
Alright! I'll go into town and
check it out! You all stay here!
I'm coming too!
Fool! There are pirates in town!
The despicable Buggy Pirates!
Exactly! I'm coming too!
What kind of citizens are we...
...if we can't even
keep our mayor safe?!
It's no use trying to stop us!
This is all of our own accord!
Fine, whatever!
Let's go, everyone!
Hey!
Leave that treasure
and get out of here!
He'll come after you again!
No!
Leave the treasure and go?!
Absolutely not!
Why should I have to leave
my own treasure behind?!
Your treasure?!
Duh!
I'm a thief who only
steals from pirates,
and I just stole from one!
Which means this
treasure is mine now!
Ah, I see!
Nonsense! That's my treasure!
Do you think stealing
it makes it yours?!
Honestly! What kind of
upbringing did you have?!
A criminal, trying to lecture
another criminal? Ridiculous!
What?!
I haven't fallen so low that I
need to be corrected by pirates!
I hope you're ready to face
the consequences, Nami...
Chop-Chop...
...Festival!
Just try and help your friend,
if you can, Gum-Gum!
Damn, he broke into even more parts!
What the--?
Nami!
Give me my back my treasure!
You wish!
Coochie, coochie, coo!
Geez, you're stubborn!
Knock it off!
No, you knock it off!
Thanks for the treasure back!
--Let go! Let go! That's mine!
--Let go?! This is my treasure!
You let go!
Die!
I told you... you're dealing with me!
Consider that finishing move
a kick from the old mayor guy!
T-Thanks, I owe you one...
Yeah, no problem!
--Oh yeah! The map!
--My treasure--!
This isn't over yet, Gum-Gum!
He's still alive!
Shut up!
How dare you flashily
do this to me!
You'll pay for this!
Assemble! Chop-Chop Parts!
Huh?
Looking for these?!
My parts!
Way to go, thief!
S-Stop!
Go flying, Buggy!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!
I win!
Hey! Captain Buggy went flying off!
W-What do we do now?!
Act unconscious for now!
Good idea!
It's all torn up now...
Well, that's okay! I can still put it on,
plus I sent Buggy flying,
so I'm satisfied.
It's all right.
I'll fix it for you later.
Eh? What?
Nothing!
Hey, anyways, I split it into
two bags, so carry half of it!
It's too heavy for me!
There sure is a lot!
If anything, Buggy does know
quality treasure when he sees it!
All this should go for no less
than 10 million Berries!
Here you go.
Eh?
It's the chart of the Grand Line.
Didn't you want it?
You're giving it to me?!
You did save me.
Thanks, Nami!
I finally got a map of the Grand Line!
Hurray!
Oh! Does that mean you'll
join our crew now?!
I told you I'm never going
to join a pirate crew!
But okay! Staying with you
guys seems profitable enough.
But I'm only teaming up
with you, just so you know!
Always remember that!
Yeah!
Hey! Zoro! Wake up! Zoro!
We're going!
Did we take care of everything?
Yeah! We also got
the map and a navigator!
No good... Out of blood...
I don't think I can walk...
Of course you can't!
You wouldn't be human
if you two could walk!
Why am I included?
You're the most suspicious of all!
Anyways, we gotta help the mayor...
Oh yeah!
We gotta wake up
the old mayor guy now...
You, there!
Are you outsiders?!
Yeah... Who are you?
We're this town's citizens!
Did the pirates have
a falling out or something?!
If you know anything, tell us!
Oh, it's just the citizens!
I thought they were
more of the pirates...
Oh, Mayor!
Oh, no! Say something!
Hey! Mayor!
He's out cold!
The pirates definitely did this!
How horrible!
Sorry! I kicked that old man's ass!
What?!
Hold on! You don't
need to tell them that!
You saw it.
Yeah, but you had an actual reason...
Why did you guys do
this to our mayor?!
Don't give us your excuses!
Who are you?!
Are you with those pirates?!
They're really bloodthirsty...
If we accidentally say
we're thieves or pirates...
We're pirates!
--Just as we thought!
You idiot!
It's the truth!
Pirates! How dare
you ravage our town?!
We won't show mercy
just 'cause you're kids!
What now? Doesn't look
like they'll hear us out...
Run!
There's no escape!
How dare you hurt
our beloved mayor?!
Ugh! Why did you
make things worse?!
--This is a good town!
--Eh?!
Everyone's so mad,
just for the old mayor guy!
I think they'd get mad
at any excuse we give!
We're turning here!
H-Hold on!
Don't say that so suddenly!
They ran into the alley!
Chouchou?!
Dog!
H-Hey! Move, Chouchou! Hey!
Those guys are bad pirates!
You're barking at the wrong people!
Why are you getting in the way?!
Chouchou! Let us through!
Chouchou!
Later, dog!
That was scary!
We managed to escape
thanks to Chouchou!
Why do we have to put up with this?!
Does it matter now?
We're done here anyway...
--Maybe so, but...
--Hey, is this your boat?!
It's great!
I don't think it's so great.
I stole it from some idiot pirates.
That's a big mouth ya got!
Been waitin' for ya, thief girl!
Never thought you'd
run into us here, didja?!
You know them?
Yeah... sort of!
Not sort of! We're bound by fate!
So you had friends, huh?
Guess we'll hafta punish you, too!
You're gonna learn how bad it is
to steal other people's stuff!
Hey, you! Quit ignorin' me!
Huh?!
Mayor! Are you conscious?!
Thank goodness! You're all right!
What on earth happened?!
What in the--?!
It was already like this
when we got here!
There were some pirates left,
but they all ran off!
Did you not see anything
that happened?!
Where are the young'uns?!
Do you mean those three kids?
So they're alive?!
Those fools! How dare they
harm a senior citizen like me!
We just finished driving
those idiots away!
But it's still not enough!
They almost seemed
to be mocking us!
They'd never understand how we
felt when they attacked our town!
Yeah! Yeah!
There's still time to go
after them and catch--
Shut up!
I'm the only one who's allowed
to complain about them!
I won't let anyone else
talk badly about them!
W-What?! Why are you
protecting pirates?!
Damn them... So they
plan to just disappear?!
Where did they go?!
They, uhh, ran toward the port.
--Damn it!
--Mayor! Mayor!
They think they can do whatever
they please in my town!
I have lots to say to you all!
Alright! Let's get going!
Isn't that Buggy's mark
on your sail there?
Well, this is his boat.
I'll get rid of it sometime!
Hey! Wait!
Young'uns!
The old mayor guy!
I was ready to die!
I was ready to die
filled with despair!
Thanks! We're in your debt!
Don't worry about it! Take it easy!
Damn you young'uns...
I have no words...
What?!
You left one of the treasure bags?!
Yeah.
Just one is worth
5 million Berries, you know!
But they need money to fix
their destroyed town, right?
That was my treasure!
Do you know how much
I suffered trying to steal it?!
Why did you do that?!
Stop! I can't swim!
That's the whole idea!
If you want it,
go back and get it then!
I can't do that! You go get it!
No! Wahh, that's dangerous!
I could die, you know!
Die once!
Do that again and I really will
throw you into the ocean!
Well, for better or worse,
looks like a navigator's
joined our journey.
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
Wow! We actually reached land!
Of course we did!
We followed the map!
There's a village up ahead!
They got a place to eat, I hope?!
I wanna eat some meat!
Forget about food, you guys!
Hey! Who's he?!
Where?!
He says he's a pirate captain!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Liar of Justice? Captain Usopp"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!