Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
What're you doing, old guy?!
Move this rock!
Perfect timing!
What're you doing here, anyway?
What's the deal, Nami?
Dinosaur!
There's someone on this island!
Who is it?!
Why, you...!
10,000 Kilogram Press!
Mr. 3. Please excuse the codename.
I'm a mere formative artist.
And this is my realist painter assistant,
Miss Golden Week.
Mr. 3?! The Wax-Wax Fruit man?!
He's a "candle man" who controls
the wax he secretes from his body.
You guys are gonna pay for this!
"The Devilish Candle!
Tears of Regret and Tears of Anger"
Curse you! What are you doing?!
What am I doing?
This is why I can't stand
unsophisticated dolts.
I'm creating a work of art, obviously.
Just be a good little girl.
Did you honestly think you
could escape from Baroque Works?
Especially when someone with a
30 million-Berry bounty winds up like that?
I'm happy I could thank them
for what happened at Whisky Peak.
You wannabe pirates should
never have stuck your noses
into such delicate issues as this.
We've already captured your
swordsman friend and the other girl.
You caught Zoro?
Then you guys're gonna get cut down!
Oh?
You still talk big,
even after one of my
Kicky Bombs to the face?
You can't hurt me with that!
I'm gonna kick you guys' asses!
Unbelievable.
Luffy-san!
Die!
--Fool!
--Luffy-san!
Luffy-san! Luffy-san!
Let's go, Miss Valentine.
Luffy-san!
Usopp-san! Karoo!
Damn you...
Give it up! Give it up!
Once solidified,
my Candle Jacket is as hard as iron!
You giants may have brutish strength,
but it becomes all but useless
once you've been caught.
Using your brain is the key.
There's no need to
uselessly face you head-on.
You lowered your guard
as you reveled in victory,
Red Ogre Broggy.
Don't glare at me like that.
You're terrifying me so!
You should be happy! Your long,
long battle has come to an end!
You fought for a whole century
for your so-called pride, right?
Shouldn't the taste of victory
be especially sweet, then?
Even if it is the fruit
of others' assistance...
Am I wrong?
Damn you! You don't mean to say...!
But the final victory belongs to me!
Are you aware that the large
bounties on your heads from long ago
come to 200 million Berries total?
Even today this holds true!
Why, you...!
I feel as if I've discovered
a long-lost treasure!
So that's what you're after, huh?!
Mr. 3!
We brought her.
Our company's little traitor.
What took so long?
I was getting sick of waiting.
Your methods are too underhanded, Mr. 3!
Planting bombs in Dorry-san's alcohol...!
What?!
Alcohol?
The alcohol I gave him?!
Dorry! How was your drink?!
Hit the spot, didn't it?!
Yeah... It tasted "godly"...
That's what you meant, Dorry?!
Wretched little girl,
giving our tricks away.
Well, no matter.
There's nothing you can do now, anyway.
Candle...
...Lock!
Mr. 5!
Bring the swordsman and the girl!
We're about to begin!
Extra Big Candle Set!
T-This is Mr. 3's ability?!
What's going on?!
Here they are.
How naive.
Being ridiculed by people of
their caliber is so embarrassing
that I'm pissed at myself.
You can't help that you're weak.
Huh? What was that?
Nothing! Just set
the candles up quickly!
Set?
What is that?!
Nami-san... Mr. Bushido...
Vivi! What happened?!
Weren't you with Luffy?!
Yes, I was, but...
If you're wondering about Straw Hat,
I took care of him myself!
It was an easy job, too.
You did?
Welcome, friends, to my service set!
Is this how it feels to be
a candle stuck in a cake?
What's that spinning thing up there?
And I can't move my legs...
Of course they're not gonna let us move.
They're the enemy.
Damn. It's hard.
Plus I can't put any strength
into it from this stance.
Something's raining down!
May you enjoy my "Candle Service"!
The wax haze falling from above you
will eventually change
you into wax figures!
You'll become perfect "human models"
that not even I could
achieve with my skills!
Your wax figures will have
literally captured your spirit!
Now die, in the name of art.
Screw that!
Why do we have to turn
into your works of art?!
Broggy-san! Quit sitting
there and go on a rampage!
You're gonna get turned into
a wax figure too, you know!
Man, talk about a huge person...
Anything you say to him is pointless!
He just now realized he foolishly
shed proud, joyful tears of victory
after killing his friend Dorry,
with whom he fought for 100 years,
but without even noticing that he
had suffered injuries beforehand!
Or did you perhaps cry
for your friend, instead?
Whatever the case, there's no
undoing what you've done now, fool!
I knew...
I knew about it.
From the moment we
first exchanged blows...
...I knew Dorry was hiding something.
You knew, huh?
You lie!
If so, then why didn't
you cease your fighting?
I didn't see a shred of pity in
the way you heartily cut him down!
A pipsqueak who doesn't even
know the first thing about duels
would never understand
the meaning of those tears!
What would you know?!
Are you saying I should shame a warrior
who hides the fact he's been
weakened and tries to fight anyway?!
A warrior who'll go that far to
keep fighting doesn't deserve pity!
And now... I know the reason behind it.
Now that I know, I'm going to
finish things with my own two hands!
That's the very least I can
do for my dear friend Dorry!
Broggy-san!
--Broggy-san!
What an annoying, talkative monster.
U-Usopp...
Usopp...
Can you let them get away with this?
No... I can't...
Can you... not stand this?
Alright! Let's all three of us
go beat them senseless!
Broggy-san!
How dumb!
I underestimated how brutishly
strong these giants can be!
It would seem you need
to be seized completely!
Wax-Wax Arts! Handcuffs!
I'm just getting started!
And now for the finishing touch!
Take this!
Can't move now, can you?!
How can he be so horrific?!
Now, then! Accelerate, Candle Service!
Turn these people into wax figures!
M-My chest is starting to hurt...
The wax haze is getting into our lungs!
At this rate, we're going to turn
into wax figures from the inside out!
Yes! Yes! Make it look like
you're in as much pain as you can!
Expressions of pain and agony
are the very things I seek in art!
May you solidify
while filled with terror!
You call this art,
you creepy topknot freak?!
How dare you do that to Broggy-san?!
You guys are going to
regret this! You got that?!
Scream and holler all you want!
For 100 years...
...day in and day out,
we fought and fought...
...and dueled only because of our
pride of Elbaf, village of warriors!
Yet... why are we being subjected
to this, Elbaf, god of war?!
If this is how we're
to meet our end, Elbaf...
...don't you think it's unfair?!
Why won't you let us die in battle?!
What a look!
Yes! That sorrow!
That grief! That struggle!
What a marvelous work of art!
Elbaf!
Oh no! My hands won't move!
I don't wanna die this way!
Can't we do something?!
My body's already turning stiff!
What do we do?!
Zoro! Do something!
Hey, old man.
You can still move, can't you?
So can I.
Whadya say we crush these guys together?
Hold on, Zoro! What are you doing?!
You're not seriously gonna--!
Yeah.
You're gonna cut your own legs?!
Quit joking around!
It's no joke.
It's the only way out of here.
What're you two gonna do?
What are you talking about?!
It's pointless!
Even if you do get down from here
that way, they'll catch you again!
There's no way to
know that unless we try!
We're gonna kick the bucket
if we stay here anyway.
So let's put up some ugly struggling!
There's no reason to die heroically
for these pieces of scum!
Right?!
What the hell? Is he crazy?
He's bluffing!
There's no way he could do that!
He's merely acting tough!
What a cheeky runt.
I'm pathetic. It seems I had
even lost the will to fight.
I'll fight alongside you
and your fighting spirit!
You can't be serious, right?!
How will you be able
to fight afterward?!
Who knows?
But... I plan to win.
Who are these guys?!
They're off their rocker!
What kind of man is he?!
But I've seen this
look somewhere before...
Princess Vivi!
Are you prepared not to die?
W-Wait! I'll fight, too!
--Vivi!
--Alright, then.
Let's do it, runt!
Don't be stupid!
What can you possibly do?!
Hey, you guys!
I'm gonna kick your asses,
just so you know!
What?
--Let's do it, Usopp!
--Yeah!
Bird!
Luffy! Usopp!
Karoo!
Master Broggy!
We've taken on your frustration!
Usopp...
Beat those guys up so much
they lose their original forms
and send them flying far off somewhere!
Yeah! I will!
These guys spoiled
the old giant guys' duel!
So you're the one with the
highest bounty in the East Blue?
My, how Navy Headquarters'
standards have fallen!
--Whoa! What a weird head!
--Quiet, you!
--It's the number 3, and it's on fire!
--Shut up!
Break this pillar first, Luffy!
We're about to turn into wax figures!
Oh? You're in trouble?
No, there was no problem at all.
Hey! Your leg!
Yeah. I went about
halfway through, I'd say.
How is that no problem at all?!
For now, could you bust
this pillar for us, Luffy?
I leave the rest to you.
Alright, no problem!
I wouldn't be so sure.
Dunno what it is,
but let's break that thing!
Alright! Got it!
I'm a bit of a different person today!
Hurry it up! We're gonna solidify!
The world is awfully big
so even if there is treasure somewhere,
the odds are astronomical
So relying on dumb luck
won't get you anywhere
So even...
...if someone stops me or
laughs at me from the shadows
the ship will continue forward
Bon voyage!
Forget about them!
I know I'm a fool, but I gotta go
The crazier the dream,
the cooler the ambition
I know I'm a fool, but I'm gonna fight
The farther the sea,
the more heavenly it surely is
Do everything you can, and you'll
get a little nearer to any horizon
Gum-Gum Mallet!
Alright! The pillar broke!
Huh? Why didn't you run away?
We can't move!
The wax has us stuck!
Oh, that's why?
Hurry and break this set!
No.
Quit joking and hurry up!
What should I do?
I don't feel like saving you guys!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Hex on Luffy! Colors Trap"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!