Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in
search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu
kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to
the unbelievable world
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
your toughness, that's what it takes
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
Wanted->means Winner:D
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece,
I'll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It's important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn't come
yet and I can't wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won't left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that's our pledge
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
Since the day that the dream began
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I'm
aiming at hasn't changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can't stand still, I can't stop
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
we go!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has
ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after
he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the
King of the Pirates!
The Straw Hats finally
entered the New World,
the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors
and landed on Punk Hazard;
an island with two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
They learned about the ruler of the island
and the puppet master
of Shinokuni - Caesar Clown's motive
and along with their pirate
ally - the Warlord -
Trafalgar Law, were drawn
into a climactic battle
which ended with Caesar's defeat.
However...
Goodbye, Young Master.
I know you will become...
...the King of the Pirates.
Goodbye, Smoker!
What happened, Monet?
Young Master...
Weapon-morphosis!
Revolver Girl!
Oh! It doesn't work!
It just made me itchy!
Alright, we're almost there!
Go faster!
Is it still safe there?
Which means the island and those squirts
haven't been wiped out.
You two.
Take care of that guard.
I'm on my way!
"Capture Caesar!
General Cannon Blasts!"
THE SEACOAST OF PUNK HAZARD
Now, with that much
ordinance, he must be...
What?!
I am an invincible Iron Pirate!
Super!
Even a Pacifista would
take damage from that!
What is that bastard?!
Why does he stand in our way?!
Because you guys are
trying to steal my cola!
Cola?! What is he talking about?!
Cola is my energy source!
So what?!
What's wrong, Weapon Woman?
Aren't you gonna transform?
I liked those looks on you!
Then I'll show you!
Weapon-morphosis!
Flying Disc Girl!
Here we go-dasuyan!
That's nothing!
Weapon-morphosis!
Oh? What is it this time?
Fire Girl!
I'm gonna finish you off
with this one-dasuyan!
Oh! Ouch! Ow, ow... Ouch! Ow, ow, ow...
Burn up-dasuyan!
Fire Girl's "flame of love" burns any enemy -
it's the most...
Just kidding!
General I'm-Okay!
What?!
N-No way!
Come on, Fan Man and Weapon Woman!
The tunnel is gonna collapse!
Don't collapse before
we get to the exit!
Even if we can make it out,
there's the gas to deal with!
Hey girl, can you really generate wind?!
Are we gonna be okay?
Hey, hey!
Those of you who don't
trust Nami-san, get off!
No, I'm gonna kick you out!
You're scaring us, brother.
We'll be counting on you, Nami!
You're our only hope now!
Trust me!
What is that iron soldier?!
Nothing works on him!
I can't let you have my cola!
I said we're not
interested in your cola!
He's keeping us too long!
We got to take care of him already!
Let's do it, Baby 5!
No one's ever warded off
this attack of ours!
No matter what you try,
super nothing will work!
We're gonna chop up your body!
Weapon-morphosis!
Feast your eyes on this
weapon that I'm swinging...
Sickle Girl!
Okay, I praise you...
...for your power - you made
it through this General body!
But this is like a mantis
going up against a warship!
The Thousand Sunny will
conquer the whole sea someday.
And I'm gonna give you a taste of
its ultimate secret weapon although
you guys don't deserve to see it!
This is a land-based
version of Gaon Cannon!
I call it...
General Cannon!
Who is he-dasuyan?!
Why is he preventing us
from recovering Caesar?!
Pops! Hold my hand! Hurry!
Isn't that Caesar who's lying there?
How did he get there?
We can't fail!
No matter who you're working for!
Whoa-whoa, I can't believe it!
They are so tough.
Don't think that we're
just ordinary underdogs.
In the name of Joker...
...We're gonna recover Caesar
no matter what it takes!
So what you're trying to do is...
recover Caesar over there, isn't it?
Go, truck!
We're almost there!
Alright, we can make it...
What?
Look! The deadly gas is
everywhere at the exit!
N-No!
The gas is coming from
both front and back!
We have no choice but go through that!
Sis, save us! Please!
Please!
Get us out of here!
Sis, please! Help us!
You can't turn your back
on a child crying for help!
I'll keep my word at any cost!
Let's go!
Sorcery Climate Baton!
Gust Sword!
Let's get out!
Keep the wind going, Nami!
The gas will be everywhere outside, too!
I'll accomplish the mission
from Joker at any price!
Although I'll kill him when I get back!
You iron soldier!
We won't let you mess
with us anymore-dasuyan!
We made it out!
What?!
Yeah!
Oh? Why isn't the gas here?
You've made it here finally!
I was getting tired of waiting!
Wow! Look at that!
It's the General!
What?
Super!
--It's a robot!
--The ultimate one!
--Wow! Cool!
--That's what we boys love!
Yeah, isn't it?!
Buffalo!
Are you Baby 5?!
Law! Are you really going
to stand against Joker?!
You traitor!
Joker is still saving the
"heart seat" for you!
Who are they? Are they your friends?
No.
They're my enemies!
All of the Straw Hats and the Navy G-5!
Odds are against us!
Wh-What's going on, Baby 5?
In any case, we gotta take
Caesar to the Young Master!
They took Caesar and ran!
Alright, I got it!
It's a sniper's work to
take down a flying enemy!
--Those bastards!
--Whoa-whoa!
Usopp said he can handle it.
Don't underestimate our sniper.
Even his nose is too long.
The last part isn't necessary!
No way! If we let them get away,
our plan is...
You allied with us, didn't you?
You saw what I did earlier.
I need you to trust us a little bit.
Allied? What are you talking about?
I've been running around
all this time so...
...I feel like attacking now!
I'm not afraid of enemies
who are far away
and have no intention to fight!
On top of that, they're wounded
and turning their backs on us!
Alright! Let's just do it!
Now I give you some water.
Okay, let's do it!
Grow Up!
Chomping Grass on Black Kabuto!
Now, eat up and get your fill!
Be careful, Buffalo!
They're up to something!
You have to watch my back, Baby 5!
Neither of you can fly so I have to!
Let's complete the mission!
What?!
Okay! You need me, don't you?
I'll defend you with my life!
Go! Weather Egg!
Something's flying this way!
Now, hatch! Thunder-chan!
Thundercloud?!
Buffalo! I have a bad feeling!
I can't go any faster than this!
No, you can't get away!
The Science of Weather!
Thunder Breed...
No!
...Tempo!
Baby 5! Damn, she got hit!
Here is a final blow!
Go, Chomping Grass!
Special Attack - Charging Shooting Star!
Go!
H-Hey, Buffalo! You got to protect me.
I can't move myself!
O-Of course! Don't underestimate me.
I'm a member of Don Quixote's family!
I'll complete a mission at any cost!
Idiot! What a good-for-nothing!
You can't hit me, fool! I'm a gas man!
I-I must make it to Dressrosa
with or without them!
You can't run! The last ammo is...
Wh-What is this?!
Sea Prism Stone handcuffs!
Alright, I caught him!
That serves you right, Caesar!
You can count on me
when an enemy turns his back...
Alright!
All right. the initial
phase is accomplished.
See? They are strong, aren't they?
Wait for me!
Squirts!
I overslept.
Which way is Punk Hazard?