Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned to rubber
after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Seeking a ship coating craftsman
to help them reach Fishman Island,
the Straw Hat crew landed
on the Sabaody Archipelago,
where they met Rayleigh, a craftsman and the
former vice-captain of the Roger Pirates.
Luffy and company headed into town to
hide while Rayleigh coated the Sunny,
but Admiral Kizaru, an assassin
dispatched from Navy Headquarters,
has already arrived at the
Sabaody Archipelago...
Hello? This is Kizaru. Hmm? How odd...
Hello?
--Now! Take this!
--S-Stop...!
Hello?
Fierce battles broke out everywhere
between the navy and the rookies...
It turned big--!
What's going on?!
He didn't do anything himself!
Well, actually, if I can't find him,
then that leaves me with spare time...
And if I'm not busy, I obviously
can't let a wanted man go...
Especially one like you,
with a 249 million bounty...
..."Magician" Basil Hawkins!
Speed is weight!
Have you ever been kicked
at the speed of light?
Captain!
Impressive. You far surpass what I imagined.
And yet another "Bartholomew Kuma"
appeared before Luffy and company...
--Get back, Luffy!
--He's one of the Warlords of the Sea!
A Warlord?! How come you guys know that?!
Don't let that attack hit
you! It's a shockwave!
What is this?!
He can do this, too?!
Hey! You lied about it being a shockwave!
Second Gear!
We know he's strong, so let's
go all-out at the very start!
Something's off here...
He seems different from last time.
He better hurry.
They're going to...
...get rid of all the rookies!
"Overwhelming!
The Navy's Fighting Weapons, the Pacifistas"
Unbelievable...
From his hands and his mouth...
Frightening!
Here comes another! Here comes another!
Here it comes!
Wh-What the hell are those things?!
They're beams, obviously!
Beams of light would make incredible
weapons, but that's just fantasy!
Wait... what are you doing?
Playing dead.
He's already seen through that!
Three-Sword Style...
...Gum-Gum...
...Diable...
...Mouton...
...Jet...
...600 Pound...
...Cannon!
Yes! Did they get him?!
They're amazing!
This is a Warlord of the Sea.
I don't think it'll be that easy,
judging from their expressions...
He's that different?!
Maybe he's a twin, then?!
Yeah, it's a possibility!
Anyway, the real one would've
teleported and dodged our attacks...
More than that, he doesn't use shockwaves,
and doesn't got paws, either!
But if this is a fake,
then that's the real problem.
That'd mean there are
two guys who're this strong.
You gave me quite a thrashing.
Don't think I'm the same
as I was before, though!
Karma Exposure!
That must've hurt a little...
Mad Monk Urouge, a man who has
continually escaped death to this day,
has such power after growing in size...
So how can this be?
Hot!
That was Kizaru's laser!
Vegapunk! You've recreated
Kizaru's offensive abilities
using Bartholomew Kuma's body?!
I had no idea the Pacifistas
had already reached this point!
This is no ordinary situation!
Definitely not! Not even three
people worth over 100 million
can survive against a
Warlord and a navy admiral!
Rear Admiral Drake.
Oh, I mean former Rear Admiral.
Don't tell me you're here to
conduct surveillance on them?
Go ahead, try fighting it.
I think your inside knowledge will make
your despair all the greater, though.
I suggest that you little
hatchlings exercise caution.
I'm here too, you see!
What another incredible sight!
A rare ancient Zoan type!
I've never seen one before!
Oh? I'm surprised red blood flows inside you.
What a rare sight...
As I said, I'm here too.
All you people worth over 100 million
are monstrous and frightening...
Demon-Conquering Form!
He disappeared?!
M-My eyes!
Captain Hawkins!
I... can't see...
I don't know what power you have,
but you do have a physical form.
You don't seem to be a Logia type...
Captain!
This is bad!
He's going over his damage limit!
He's really gonna die!
You'll be the first to go...
You did well to journey all this way.
Who is that?
♪ Yo! Yo-yo-yo! Yeah! Yo! ♪
♪ Is this music reaching you?!
If you can hear it, stay tuned! ♪
♪ Navy Admiral Kizaru! ♪
♪ Yeah! Yo-yo-yo! Yo! ♪
He's "Sea Roar"...
♪ Everybody! Listen to
this fighting music! ♪
♪ Scratch! ♪
What's this?
Here we go!
Check it out!
Got 'em!
Though I doubt that'd be
enough to beat a navy admiral!
Whew, I managed to see
so much interesting stuff!
Well, it's time for me to scram! So long!
How terrible...
What a shock that was...
Yata Mirror.
What's that?
Hello?
Huh? Hello?
Oh, here it is.
This is Borsalino.
What the hell, Uncle!
You do have a Baby Transponder Snail!
Why didn't you contact me?!
Oh?
Oh, Sentomaru-kun!
Don't give me, "Oh!" What are you doing?!
You're on the island now, right?!
Oh, I wasn't able to get
ahold of you, you see...
Don't tell me you were talking into
the Black Transponder Snail again!
I told you before that the black one
on your wrist is for eavesdropping!
Oh, yes...
Whatever! Just get to work now!
The culprits have split up!
Straw Hat Luffy,
Captain Kid, Trafalgar Law...
Which do we start with?
Oh, you don't say? In that case...
108 Pound Cannon!
Concasser!
108 Pound...
You idiot! What're you doing?!
Zoro!
Hey, Zoro! You got hurt so
much you can't even move?!
Forget about him, Luffy!
We need to beat this thing first!
Yeah...!
He hasn't even had the chance
to fully heal from last time!
Just standing up to him
must be pretty damn painful,
judging by that look of his again!
Bastard...
If you ain't Bartholomew Kuma,
then who are you?!
You look exactly like
the Warlord of the Sea...
What the hell's goin' on here?!
Another enemy?!
I got the toughest defense in the world!
As such, my mouth is sealed just as tight!
Who are you?!
I have no reason to answer anything!
I'm the most tight-lipped guy in the world!
And my name is...
You're gonna tell us, then?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"An Even Stronger Enemy Appears!
The Battle Axe-Carrying Sentomaru"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!