Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
saa yukou
So let's go
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
Wicked rain will get in my way
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Without stopping
Tachidomaru koto naku
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
I'll keep getting back up
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
He and the Whitebeards finally got over the
cling walls to make it to the scaffold!
As an all-out battle between the Navy and
the Whitebeards continues at the Oris Plaza,
Luffy runs toward Ace!
Damn!
Even you can't win out against the
onslaught of time, Whitebeard!
That's what I was afraid of the most!
If you have an unguarded moment,
you will lose the fight!
Marco!
You can't look away like that!
Should I be the last voice
you hear before you die?
Pops!
If I'd be able to do all I could...
I'd be happy to die!
Let me fight, Ivan-chan!
If I can't fight now
and if I can't rescue Ace, I...
I'd rather take my own life afterwards!!
Let me have the strength to fight for now!
All right!
Do whatever you want!
Luffy!
Ace!!
"To Live Up to a Promise!
Luffy and Coby Collide!"
So slow! What's taking them so long?!
I'm sorry for being late!
I brought two executioners as replacements!
--Finally! Hurry and get ready!
--Yes, sir!
Straw boy, once again,
you better keep in mind that the next time
you drop, you won't be able to bounce back!
The Energy Hormone is just fooling your body!
It isn't repairing any of the damage!
I...
I won't fall again!
What?! Another foolhardy statement!
Look at them!
Wait!
They're trying to execute Ace again!
Oh, well, my words can't change Straw
boy's mind under these circumstances!
All I can do is keep them from beating him!
Straw Hat?!
Straw Hat is coming!
Kill Straw Hat!
Leave it to me!
I'm gonna finish him!
It's not over! I won't let
you pass through here!
--If you wanna advance...
--...You gotta beat all of us!
We'll show you the spirit of the Navy!
Heads up!
Death Wink!
10 points! I'll back you up!
Thanks, Ivan-chan!
Luffy-san...
You're...
Coby!
That day...
I've decided to be the King of the Pirates,
so if I die fighting for
that, that's fine with me!
Do you suppose I can do it, too?
If I'm prepared to die for it?
Do what?
Do you think... even I could join the Navy?
Navy?
Yes! Catching bad guys is my dream!
It's been my dream ever since I was little!
If I hadn't met Luffy-san, I
couldn't have become what I am now.
That's right! In order to
live as a Navy soldier,
I have to fight to change myself!
Because this is a battlefield!
I have to commit myself towards killing him!
Gum-Gum...
Shave!
I'll become a Navy...
...ad...
...admiral someday!
Whoa! Oh, I mean...
I-I-I'm sorry! I got carried away!
It's embarrassing! I wanna crawl in a hole!
After I met you, I became
emboldened a little bit...
Coby!
You wanna fight me, right?
Then, of course you have to
become such a heavy hitter!
Do you think I can become an admiral?
Next time we see each other,
we'll be much stronger!
And much greater!
Why?
They know that it's just a wild dream that
makes me lightheaded at just the thought of it.
Then how can they believe in it?
...Bullet!
He's as strong as I thought!
It's useless. I have to
become much much stronger...
Hey, Coby!
Damn!
What is it this time?!
You guys are...
...the Kuma imposters!
Monkey D. Luffy.
Oh no! What a pain in the ass!
Hey you, watch out!
Boa Hancock. The Seven Warlords.
Abort attack. Friendly operative.
That's right! You guys are on the same side!
Thank you, Hancock!
She's the empress, right?
How do you know her?
Luffy! He called my name again...
Thank you, Hancock.
Every time he calls me like that, I'm so...!
Hancock.
Yes.
Hancock!
Yes!
Hancock.
Move aside, Boa Hancock.
I don't want you to call my name!
Magma brat!
P-Pops...
I-I'm on my way!
You are off guard!
Take a couple more of these
and get yourself a good rest!
Pops!
Things don't always go the way you want!
Of course,  Marco the Phoenix regenerates!
Hey! It's your turn now!
Sea Prism Stone?!
Commander Marco!
It looks painful!
Commander Jozu has been beaten, too!
They even beat our commanders one by one...
They're falling apart!
The Whitebeard Pirates!
Old man!
You Fish-Man monster!
Grr! Let me go!
Now move it!
Everyone, beat Whitebeard!
Pops!
JUSTICE
Stay away!
They think that they can beat me...
...this easily!
I don't need any help because I'm...
I'm...
I'm Whitebeard!
H-He's a monster!
Don't hesitate! He's wounded!
--Everybody, follow me!
--Yes, sir!
Did he call me wounded?
That's ridiculous! I won't
die from such a small wound!
I won't die from... such a small...!
I know...
...what will happen...
...if I die!
Then, you know,
I can't allow myself to die until...
...I see a bright future ahead for my sons!
Right, Ace?
Pops!
You dotard!
What is it?!
W-What are they doing?! Guarding
the back of Whitebeard?!
Are they willing to die with Whitebeard?!
You guys don't have to understand!
We'll defend Pops' glory!
That's too thoughtful, you fools!
Pops...
Captain Squard,  let's go
and fight with Pops, too!
Captain? Where are you going?
Don't come with me.
I'll pay the price in my own way.
If you wanna see the future,
I'll show you now, Whitebeard!
Do it!
Ace!
It's no use!
Do you think that I can't
stop you for doing it?!
See it for yourself, Whitebeard!
Don't do it!
Don't do it!!
I'm on my way!
Hey, was that...?!
Conqueror's... Haki!
Hey, come on! For real?!
That was surprising!
That brat...
Luffy unconsciously used the Conqueror's
Haki and stopped Ace's execution.
But the Navy, wary of his
display of latent power,
combine their efforts in an
attempt to eliminate him.
Just then, Iva-san finally
reveals his last trump card!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Scaffold at Last! The
Way to Ace Has Opened!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!