Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
After surviving a fierce battle,
the Straw Hats finally entered the New
World, the harshest sea ruled by the Four Emperors.
They landed on Punk Hazard; an island with
two parts, one burning, the other frozen.
After forming an alliance with Trafalgar Law,
Luffy finally encountered Caesar
Clown who rules the island
but was beaten by his mysterious power.
My strong soldiers!
Tie these five up!
Use Sea Prism Stone chains
for the Devil Fruit eaters!
When did you come here?
Vergo!
Just arrived. Luckily, I was at Dressrosa.
I got a ride in an SAD tanker
that was about to leave.
"Shocking! The True Identity
of the Mystery Man Vergo!"
THE ICE LANDS--THE LABORATORY
You have no mercy.
If I had mercy, it wouldn't
make good punishment.
Vergo... The Navy soldiers of the
G-5 are here on the island now.
Since you're their base commander,
I think you're gonna be in
trouble if you run into them.
Don't try to give me your advice.
You should know your place.
Also, don't make me repeat myself.
You have to address me with "san."
Oh, scary!
THE NEW WORLD--AN ISLAND
Hey, look! Soldiers of the G-5.
Getting drunk and partying in the
daytime? They're so obnoxious!
Do you have a problem?!
This island is safe from pirates
who are worth over 100 million
because we obnoxious soldiers are
going around like this for you
people, don't you think so?!
Huh?!
We deserve to take a little break, don't we?
W-Well...
THE NAVY "G-5" UNIT 06
COMMODORE YARISUGI
It's good! Too good!
Owner, give me a thousand of these!
W-We don't have that many in stock!
What?! Why?! It's too good!
Navy people!
Please! Search for our children!
What are you talking about?
Did you forget?!
Our children went missing three years ago!
Please! Just one more time!
They were just playing in
the neighborhood and then,
they got involved in an accident at sea?!
It doesn't make any sense!
I'm begging you! For one last time!
Please search for them!
Can we talk to the officer
named Captain Tashigi?!
I heard she listens
empathetically to the people!
--I'm begging you! Let us talk to Captain Tashigi!
--Please! One more time!
Cut it out!
How insulting! We're Navy
soldiers of the G-5, too!
First of all, you fools
doubt the Navy's report,
and also complain about us who
are in charge of this area?!
Too much complaining, don't you think?!
I-It's not like that!
It's no use! Too useless!
You have to accept it
already! Too much evidence!
Your children died in an accident!
Commodore, that's a bit yarisugi (too much).
I asked Vice Admiral Vergo,
the head of the G-5,
about this too many times--a thousand times!
And we investigated ten thousand times!
But...
If you're gonna carry on about this,
I will kill you fools for interfering with us
and burn down your town!
Commodore, that's yarisugi (too much)!
You wanna talk to Tashigi-chan?
Don't push your luck too much!
I mean, it'd be nice if she were
working under me! Too nice!
Imagining too much!
But unfortunately,
she works for Unit 01 as Vice
Admiral Smoker's right-hand girl.
Too right-handy!
She's too busy to deal with you fools
who are obsessed with an
incident from three years ago!
Too busy!
Shitheads!
That's too much!
They're not gonna listen to us!
I wonder if it's true that Vice
Admiral Vergo knows about this.
He saved this island from pirates once.
I couldn't believe that he was
part of that rough group, the G-5,
because he was such a gentleman!
He thinks that it was an accident, too?!
They are still alive!
Our children are still alive.
Somewhere in this world!
PUNK HAZARD ISLAND
THE REMAINS OF THE FIRST AND SECOND
LABORATORY NAMI AND USOPP'S GROUP
My head is gonna explode!
Usopp, make them fall asleep already!
I'm doing it but it's not
gonna work that many times!
Unchain me, brothers!
I guess the withdrawal
symptoms are way too painful!
Then, what should we do?!
Just do everything we can!
I'm counting on you, Sanji!
I'm Nami!
Oh, that's right!
Damn, you look so dependable on the outside!
I'm sorry!
Brothers!
Candy... Give me the candy!
Candy! Candy!
My head hurts!
I can't stand it!
The candy will stop this pain!
Candy!
Candy! Candy! Candy!
I'm begging you!
Why can't you give it to me?!
Give me the candy!
They're coming!
Can I... Can I attack them
now?! They're like monsters!
No! Don't be ridiculous, they're just kids!
But we can't just run around like this!
Master!
Are you okay, children?
Let's go back to the laboratory!
It's dangerous here.
It's the candy!
Master!
Master! Master! Master!
Master?
THE MIDDLE LAKE
The Slime got mad!
Why, all of a sudden?
Probably because those
small Slimes were blown up.
They were like a parent and its children?
But I had no choice.
He's transforming!
What is that?!
What? Is it a frog?
Looks like a lizard to me.
Run!
He can make as many copies
of himself as he wants?!
No, it looks like the one on
the other side is shrinking.
It means that one will disappear in the end?
Maybe he's flinging pieces of
himself over to cross the lake!
We don't want that monster
to run wild on this side!
You're right! If we cut it, it spews
gas. If we burn it, it explodes.
And it's way bigger than
the ones from before!
The lab could be in danger, too!
What? Then, we'd better hurry!
Momonosuke!
What are you guys gonna
do?! I'm going to the lab!
Then we gotta go, too! Idiot!
Who're you calling "idiot"?!
You're such a pain!
If you get separated from
Kin'emon and wander off,
we have to look for you all over the island!
You can't fight now, Zoro-san, Sanji-san!
I want to see his swordplay, too!
Let's go to the lab!
You awake?
What are you doing here?
I was gonna ask you the same thing.
It looks like we're all captured.
Oh, we're in a cell?!
When did that happen?
Oh, you're here, too, Smokey!
It's no use. That's Sea Prism Stone chain.
You're awake, huh?
What is she?
You all look better than I thought.
What?! You're...
You're the head of the G-5!
Why the hell are you here?!
Vergo!
Give us back Smo-yan, Caesar!
CAESAR'S LABORATORY - THE FRONT
Give us back Tashigi-chan!
All clear!
Alright, close the shutters!
Don't let the Navy soldiers in at any cost!
As soon as everybody gets
in, activate it immediately!
What?!
Wh-What is it?!
Wh-What the hell is that?!
They're closing the entrance!
Dammit! It was too late!
Open it! Assholes!
Let me handle this!
The shutter is too thick!
It's as solid as rock!
Even a bazooka doesn't work?!
What about the back entrance?!
It's all closed! The shutters
were down everywhere!
Damn, that gas bastard!
Hey, looks like we've been trapped, huh?
Don't be ridiculous!
Because, although those creepy
jellies stopped falling suddenly,
if you take a good look, they're merging
into one another and getting bigger!
We can't steal another ship! All
the paths have been cut off!
They took our Transponder Snails
away so we can't make a call!
What should we do?!
All the shutters are closed!
Okay.
Clank.
Sounds like they're moving
ahead with preparations.
Poor Navy soldiers.
What is Caesar up to?
Well, I don't know exactly
but he woke his pet Smiley up so...
...I think he's planning
to do a big experiment.
Looks like it's going to
be a very dangerous one.
By the way, Vergo,
did you eat a hamburger this morning?
How did you know? It's my favorite.
There is a piece of it still
stuck beside your mouth.
I would like to see the
experiment before I go.
Everyone outside will die?
Probably. But you will be safe in here.
Hey, Vergo!
They're all Navy soldiers of the G-5 outside!
Your subordinates!
Are you gonna leave them to die?!
Yeah, I think so.
What did he just say?!
Anyway,
I can't believe there are
such big names in one cell.
I like the view.
It brings back memories.
To see you two in the same cell.
Oh yeah, Smokey and I got caught
by you and the others at Alabasta!
Shut up, you fools!
You people can never read the atmosphere!
Smoker-san, I don't know what to
do with this feeling right now!
You were right and this is
the worst-case scenario.
Those news articles were false...
...meaning somebody in the G-5 covered
up those child abduction cases.
So Caesar abducted those kids and...
...Vergo covered it up as accidents at sea.
Of all others, the head of
the base was a double agent.
That's characteristic of G-5 in a
way but it's a dishonor to the Navy!
How dare you?!
What? Is he a bad person?
It seems like he is.
No wonder you didn't notice it.
It's not like Vergo was selling the Navy out.
He was a pirate originally.
A pirate... You were?!
That's right.
Before he made his name, he
joined the Navy by Joker's order
and spent fifteen years climbing
up the ranks from the very bottom.
There is no Navy soldier who is more
reliable and convenient for Joker than him.
Vergo had been working for
Joker from the very start!
No way!
Joker is a name of an underworld
broker if I'm correct.
I feel so pathetic! I can't believe I
didn't smell this rat so close to me!
Don't be so negative.
Why don't you just praise the rat for
eluding the eyes of the great "White Chase,"
Smoker-kun.
From the day that you transferred from the
headquarters, I was on the highest alert.
I'm so happy that now I can
free myself from that stress.
Anyway, you blabbed out so much, Law.
Didn't I punish you enough?
But that's okay.
You said that I'd be in trouble in
case I ran into the G-5 soldiers
but that's not true.
I have been taming them for a long time
- I don't think they would suspect me.
Even if they find out about
my background like this,
I know what to do.
You know what I mean, don't you?
Vice Admiral Smoker, Captain Tashigi.
You two will die here
so you can keep your mouths shut forever.
And I'll let Caesar handle
those soldiers outside.
It's inevitable. This is
Joker's important territory.
I can't just let those who learn
about his identity walk away.
Don't worry. I will process it
as an accident like I always did.
Vergo!
Hey, Tra-guy, who's Joker?
I was working for him, too, once.
Huh?
That's why I knew Vergo.
Joker is just his alias
as an underground broker.
His true identity?  He's a
man that you know very well.
What do you mean?
One of the seven most notorious pirates.
He is a member of the Seven Warlords
authorized by the World Government.
He is Don Quixote Doflamingo.
The revelation of the name, Doflamingo,
one of the Seven Warlords, causes quite the stir.
With the children in tow, Nami and
the others are already at a disadvantage,
and are put in an even bigger life-or-death situation
due to the Gas Gas Fruit's fearsome power.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Save the Children!
The Master's Evil Hands Close in!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!