Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
I'll never give up on this ship!
Are you guys stupid or what?!
You probably got fooled by the shipwrights'
convincing argument, didn't you?!
The Luffy I know would've believed
in the strength of the Merry first
rather than buying those guys' sales talk!
Such a clear-cut answer that sounds
like one made by an old man
who understands everything...
How can you make a decision like that,
suddenly acting all captain-like?!
I misjudged you, Luffy!
Wait a sec, Usopp! Luffy, too, first--
Stay out of this, Nami!
This is something I decided!
I won't change my opinion.
No matter what you say now,
we're gonna get a new ship!
We'll say goodbye to the Merry here!
Listen, Luffy! It's not like everyone
can live looking ahead like you do!
I can't just leave our wounded friend
here and move on to the seas ahead!
Don't be ridiculous! Even if she's a friend,
ships and humans are different!
They're the same! Merry has
the strength to live left in her!
--Considering how you are, aren't you
excited thinking about the new ship
--Hey, that's enough, you guys!
--while pretending to be concerned about Merry?!
--You can't have a conversation
if you're worked up like that!
Enough, already!
Luffy!
Don't think that you're the only
one who feels pain over this!
Everyone feels the same way!
If so, there's no way you'd
decide to get a new ship!
Fine! If you dislike what I decide
that much, then get off this--
Sanji...!
You idiot... What were you about to say?!
Cool down! Be careful about what you say!
Sorry. I just...
That's okay, Luffy. That's how
you really feel, isn't it?
What'd you say?!
Go ahead and cut off useless friends
one after another and move on.
If you're gonna abandon the Merry...
...why don't you do that to me, too?!
You don't need weak friends, right?
Luffy... you're the man
who'll be king of the pirates.
But I don't have to go that high up.
Hey, where're you going, Usopp?!
Where I'm going is my own business.
I'm...
...leaving the gang.
Usopp!
Wait! It shouldn't be like this!
Hey! Turn around!
Luffy! I can't go along with you anymore.
Sorry to cause you trouble until the end.
It's true that the ship
belongs to you, the captain.
So fight me...
Monkey D. Luffy!
Fight a duel with me!
At 10 o'clock tonight, I'll come back here.
Then, we'll fight a duel over the Merry!
I'll defeat you and take the Merry.
That's...
...the end of the bond
between you guys and me.
"Luffy vs. Usopp! Collision of Two Men's Pride"
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
People praise me-- and then praise
me more-- as "Captain Usopp"!
You're neat!
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
I'm a very proud man!
Because of my great pride,
people call me "Proud Usopp"!
You guys take care, too!
Let's meet again sometime!
--How come?
--Huh? How come? Man, you're antisocial...
I'm gonna be a pirate too, so we'll
meet on the high seas eventually!
What're you talkin' about? Get on already.
Eh?
We're friends now, aren't we?
I... I get to be captain, right?!
Don't be dumb! I'm the captain!
So you didn't get cold feet, huh?
You'd better be sure you're not going
to regret this, no matter what happens.
This is the duel you wanted.
Of course. You'd better fight seriously.
I'll turn the tables on you.
I've already figured out how to defeat you.
Can't we stop them?
Usopp is wounded quite badly!
If you can't bear to watch this, go inside.
Don't lump me in with your past
enemies who didn't know your skills.
Luffy... We've known each other for a long time.
I know about your powers very well.
Don't be surprised when you hear this, Luffy.
I have 8,000 men under me!
If you don't wanna die, surrender now!
What?! 8,000?! That many?!
You go inside.
You don't have any subordinates.
I know that much!
Usopp Spell!
You've got razors stuck between all your teeth!
It hurts just to imagine that!
Go inside.
You've got cactus spines inside your fingernails!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Usopp!
See?! His body is already...
Special Attack... Ketchup Star!
What? Are you sympathizing with
your enemy? What confidence...!
Flash Dial!
Special Attack! Egg Star!
Star! Star! Star!
It stinks! They're rotten!
Dammit! You jerk! Be serious!
Is this silly? I'm very serious, Luffy!
--What?
--This is my way of fighting!
Hey, if you open your mouth
that big, you'll have a burn!
Special Attack! Tabasco Star!
It's hooot!!
Watch out when you wriggle!
Beneath your feet, it's already Caltrop Hell!
Ouch!
Usopp is in control of the fight!
Listen, Luffy!
I'll defeat you without fail and take the Merry...
...no matter what it takes!
Usopp...
Special Attack! Pepper Star!
Owwww!
I told you. I won't use attacks
that won't work on you.
Dammit. It stinks... My mouth is burning...
And it hurts!
I won't give you even the
slightest chance to attack!
Special Attack! Shuriken Shooting Stars!
Smoke?
I'm using a Breath Dial.
You didn't notice the smell
because of the eggs, did you?
The smell of the gas that's
filling the area around you...!
Gas?
Don't tell me...!
Sorry! Take this!
Flame Star!
What an explosion!
Luffy! Usopp!
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
People praise me-- and then praise
me more-- as "Captain Usopp"!
You're neat!
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
How come?
We're friends now, aren't we?
I see an island!
Whoa! Incredible! What kind of island is that?!
All right! Go!
Merry! Full speed ahead!
Full speed ahead!
I can't stand this.
Luffy! Usopp!
I know... that an attack like
that wouldn't take you out.
I know, Luffy...
...that you fight every battle
with all your strength.
I know every detail of your skills!
Special Attack...!
Gum-Gum... Gatling!
...Bursting Cactus Star!
Ouch!
Triple Exploding Stars!
Gum-Gum... Pistol!
Gum-Gum... Bazooka!
I have a dial here.
I got... your impact!
Impact!
An Impact Dial!
How'd you like that?! Dammit!
I am Usopp, leader of the great
pirates who reign over this village!
To our new ship and crewmate!
Cheers!
I guess that's more like it.
It's good! Let's draw it on the sail, too!
Alright! All done!
Now the Going Merry pirate ship is all set!
Gum-Gum...
...Bullet!
Usopp!
Game over.
You fool...!
There's no way that you
could defeat me, is there?!
I can't stand this...
Do what you want with the Merry.
We'll get a new ship and
move on to the seas ahead!
Hey! Let me sit there, too, Luffy!
No! This is my special seat!
Oh? What's that?!
What're you making, Usopp?
Whoa! Hey, you guys!
No shoes in Usopp Factory!
Someday, I will go to Elbaf!
To the village of warriors!
All right, Usopp! Let's go there for sure!
Let's get this party goin'! It's the
night festival before gold-hunting!
Well then, bye, Usopp...
It's been fun.
Hey, don't go, Chopper!
Why not?! He was already
wounded so badly to start with,
and now he got beat up worse!
This isn't a quarrel or a game.
So what?! I'm a doctor!
Let me at least treat him!
He lost the duel. On top of that, he gets pitied.
Imagine just how miserable
that must make him feel!
Imagine how much suffering careless
kindness can cause the loser!
He fought a duel knowing full well
this was how it might turn out!
This is really tough...
That's what it means to be a captain, isn't it?
Don't lose yourself.
If you waver, who can we trust?
Let's vacate the ship.
We can't come back... to this ship, so...
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Luffy, there's trouble! The whole
town is talking about this!
--What's the matter?
--They say that Iceberg-san was
shot at home and is unconscious.
Ice pops is?! I'll go check.
--I'll go, too.
--Then, Chopper and I'll go look for Robin-chan.
I kinda have a bad feeling.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Severe Shock Hits the City
of Water! Iceberg Targeted!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!