Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
Fight, crash in, rise up
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
Here we go, always, don't run away
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
We're still far from our goal
gooru mada tooku
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Let's do it again sou doredake, Baby
Let's do it again, yes, how many times, baby
tachiagareba My dream come true
do I have to get up to
make my dream come true
towareru kakugo no tsuyosa
Feels like the strength of my resolve is
tamesareteru youna Everyday
put to the test everyday
Hey Let's go
I don't want to settle for
small success, making excuses
iiwake de chiisaku matomaru ki nakute
Hey Let's go
tobidashita sekai wa araburu noo ruuru
The world I got out into is wild and lawless
karaburi no sukima ni
sematteta genjitsu kauntaa
Whiffing through the air,
off-guard, reality countered me
yousha naku Beat me Hit me mata taoretemo
Mercilessly, beat me, hit
me, and even if I fall again
Oh
mou ichido tachiagari
mae wo mita mono dake ga
Only those who get back on
their feet and look forward
will have the last laugh, only winner
saigo ni warau nosa Only winner
(We gotta go, till we make
it there, on the glory road)
(We gotta go todoku made Glory road)
Fight, crash in, rise up
Fight butsukatte hamukatte
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
Those are our Hard knock days
heibon na mainichi ja kawaki iyasenai
Ordinary days won't quench our thirst
Here we go, always, don't run away
Here we go itsudatte nigenaide
kazeatari tsuyoku ikiteyukou
Let's go on living buffeted
by the mighty winds
We're still far from our goal,
we got to carry on the way
gooru mada tooku susumubeki michi
Fight, shake it off, act strong
Fight kechirashite tsuyogatte
Those are our Hard knock days
sore ga boku tachi no Hard knock days
bunan na sentaku? sonnano aru wake nai
A safe bet? There's no such thing
Here we go, always, be the best
Here we go itsudatte saikou de
atosaki nante kangaezu ni yukou
and keep going without
thinking of the consequences
Put all our wishes together
negai wo tabanete
susumubeki Hard knock days
We got to carry on Hard knock days
Beyond the light, make my day
hikari no saki Make my day
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and
have come to Dressrosa.
But caught up in the current
king Doflamingo's agenda,
they were trapped in the Birdcage
along with the entire island.
On top of that, he put prices
on the heads of Luffy and
11 others, and now they're being
hunted by all the citizens.
And with the Straw Hats fighting
the Don Quixote Family fiercely,
Luffy and Law are heading
to the Royal Palace!
Damn! Those meatheads were
disorganized before
but now they've teamed up!
All right! Go straight to
the fourth level like this!
Horse!
What's the matter, Farul?
What are those giant dolls?!
"A Hard-Fought Battle Against Pica!
Zoro's Deadly Attack!"
Tin soldiers?!
They're a little too big to be children's toys
but...
...more than that...
They're in bad taste!
Let's shear through them all at once! Farul!
Go!
Oh! One of them tripped!
Are they that clumsy?!
What the...!
It tried to chew on my head!
Stay alert!
We're gonna go like this!
Each of you, defend yourself!
Okay!
How could you even think
you were good enough to kill Straw Hat?
You bastard!
Damn!
I guess he got away!
Pulpostone!
What?!
Why're you guys flying?!
Zoro!
Z-Z-Z-Z-Zoro-senpai!
Oh! D-Do you remember
you promised me your autograph?!
That's...
Pica!
Rebecca!
Who is it?
He's one of the Top Executives of the
Don Quixote Family along
with Trebol and Diamante!
Oh no! If he attacks us now,
we can't avoid it!
Zoro! Keep the enemy there for us!
We have to move beyond this stone figure!
THE FLOWER FIELD
THE CURRENT LOCATION
I can do that but...
...that aside, why're you guys flying...?
Oh? The enemy got away, didn't he?!
Oh boy!
Did he run because he's got frighten by
how strong Zoro-senpai is?!
No, he didn't get away!
I won't let you get to the Palace!
He got in there...
What?!
H-He's targeting us!
--Oh yeah! Your barrier!
--It's impossible!
First, I can't use my hands!
Plus, I can't put up a barrier that
can cover us from that massive punch!
No!
But if nothing is done, we're gonna...
...get blown away!
Three-Sword Style!
Thousand-and-Eighty Pound Phoenix!
I'm starting to see how your power works!
Hey, you soprano-voiced fool!
I forgot to tell you one thing.
The Straw Hats are...
...not just Straw Hat Luffy and God Usopp.
Don't forget!
I'm the man who's destined to become
the greatest swordsman in the world one day!
Doro-tenpai!
--The Little People are going crazy!
--Keep them down!
Ouch!
Open the door to the factory
and let our friends in!
Yeah!
Let's go with them!
Oh no! Oh no!
MOUJI - AN AIDE TO THE PRINCESS
Is the princess okay?!
Princess!
Mouji! Seems like Princess
Mansherry's not here on this floor!
What?!
Are... you... sure?!!
Then, where is she?!
The advance unit's making a dash for...
That way?!
I am coming! Princess!
No, Mouji!
Choo-choo! Huff-puff!
He's gone...
Manager!
W-We have a problem!
The Little People raised a revolt!
We're struggling to bring them
under control so we need you...
What are you guys doing?!
How pathetic!
I-I'm sorry!
What useless pieces of shit!
Stupid shrimps!
They're pushing their luck!
This is a good opportunity!
I'm gonna teach them a lot of lessons!
It's no good!
We can't get control of them!
Don't give up! Keep shooting!
What?!
We're not gonna get hit by
bad people's bullets!
W-Wait!
Aren't you worried about Princess Mansherry?!
What?
If you guys get out of here,
Princess Mansherry will never get cured!
Th-That's not good!
Right?! If you guys leave,
I'm sure Princess-san will be very sad!
Princess...
No! Don't listen to them, Chao!
Okay, if you understand,
quit fighting and just obey us...
What?!
I put in earplugs so I can't
hear your stupid lies anymore!
Tontatta Swing!
--Report Young Master-sama!
--O-Okay!
You can't do that!
Tontatta: Tail...
...Four-man Hammer!
Everybody! Release all
their Transponder Snails
into the wild so they can't call for backup!
Are you listening?!
What?
Earplugs!
Now, let's hurry up and open the door!
What?! Princess is...
Princess Mansherry is not sick?!
Inhel and the others outside said...
That's what I thought!
We've been totally fooled, haven't we?!
Where's the princess?!
--U-Ummm...
--They split up and went to look...
I see!
That way, huh?!
Oh, wait!
It's good that her illness was a lie!
But she's been alone all
this time in the factory...
I understand!
--Mouji... I Mouji understand your feelings!
--Wait!
I know the princess is crying now!
She's crying and calling out my name!
There's a Little Person!
Calling "Mouji! Mouji!"
Princess!
Mouji!
Please wait for me!
Oh, it says "Don't run" in this hallway.
We have to keep left.
Mouji!
There is the isolation ward!
Princess Mansherry must be in there!
I'm gonna save you now!
Oh, wait a second!
Why did you stop me?!
Look at that sign!
It says "Keep out"! We can't go in!
Gah! What?!
You should've told me earlier!
I can't slow down now!
Mouji broke the door with
the "Keep out" sign!
I'm disappointed in you!
It means you're not allowed
to go in without permission!
I'm sorry...
No one's in here! Is it just storage?
No... Can't believe it...
P-Princess... Where is the princess?!
Are you ready?!
Here we go!
Hurry up!
IN FRONT OF THE SMILE FACTORY
Oh! You're so relentless, Señor!
Hurry up!
There!
Is that it?
Boy... You're such a tough guy.
Almost!
Franky Ear.
Which is not to say...
...it's a special mechanism or something.
It's just Franky naturally has good hearing.
Hey, swimming guy...
It's none of your concern but...
...earlier...
I saw a weak old granny having trouble
in the back street on the right!
Oh yeah? That's sad.
Señor?
I just remembered
I have some minor business to attend to.
Oh! Wait a second!
Turn the wheel and open the door!
--Let's help them!
--Yeah!
Hold on! Shrimps!
What?!
KUWEEN (20 YEARS OLD, FEMALE)
FACTORY MANAGER OF THE SMILE FACTORY
You're pushing your luck!
I won't let you get out!
No! It's the factory manager!
You guys were slaves for manufacturing SMILEs
right from the start!
Didn't you notice until now?!
Stop making a ruckus like fools!
Watch out for the suction device!
She wants to suck us all up
and recapture us!
You can't get away!
Cleaning, cleaning!
If nothing is done,
we're all gonna get caught!
Open the door already!
--Hurry up!
--I'll help you!
Won't let you do it!
Vacuuming power up!
You're persistent!
Just give up already!
No, we won't! We're gonna
open the door no matter what!
Well done. Guys!
Finally released from the SMILE Factory,
the Tontattas are ecstatic!
But their princess
Mansherry's whereabouts is still a mystery
and concerns and confusion spread among them!
Meanwhile, the hard-boiled fight
between Franky and Señor
grows to include Kuween
and gets even more heated!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Little People's Princess! Captive Mansherry!"
I'm gonna be the King of the Pirates!