Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
It’s important not to wake up
samenai koto ga daiji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since
the War of the Best.
Luffy and his crew returned
to Sabaody Archipelago
and on their way to the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after Shirahoshi,
are engaging in secret maneuvers.
Luffy and the others find
themselves caught up in the turmoil.
Zoro and the others facing Hordy
and the New Fish-Man Pirates...
...tried to escape after the
tides turned against them
but were caught by Hordy whose
strength was multiplied tremendously
by taking the Energy Steroid.
Meanwhile, Luffy and the others
finally got to the Sea Forest...
The person who is responsible for setting
Arlong loose into the East Blue was...
...me!
"The Haunting Ties!
Nami and the Fish-Man Pirates!"
I'm sure there is a key to the
void in history somewhere here.
The missing piece must have been
lying here secretly at this serene
place for several centuries.
If I keep going, there'll be...
Here it is!
King Neptune...
Don't look back!
Think about what the King did for us!
I see the exit!
Yeah!
We made it outside!
Use the Bubbly Coral!
What a disaster!
So few soldiers made it out even
after we left the King there!
We failed!
Stop moaning! It was the King's order!
Men, this is not a retreat!
We will exterminate the pirates in the
palace and rescue the King at any cost!
First, we need to communicate with
Prince Fukaboshi and the others!
Get in touch with the Princes A.S.A.P.
and reorganize the forces...
...and let's go back to the palace!
Yes, sir!
The nearest town from here is...
Fishverly Hills, sir!
Look out!
FISHVERLY HILLS
Meanwhile, at the high-class
district - Fishverly Hills...
Run!
--All of you, get in line!
--Hurry up if you don't wanna die!
Th-This is... What do you want from us?!
--Step on it!
--What?
--It's a test!
--No way!
Much...
Shut up! Captain Hordy's
gonna rule this country-ch!
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW FISH-MAN
PIRATES - IKAROS MUCH
Now, step on the image!
No, I can't...
Step on it now!
CANDY FACTORY TOWN
At Candy Factory Town in the northeast...
Hey, just do it already!
I can't!
Huh?!
Please forgive me! I can't
tread on the image of her face!
Shut up!
Those who can't do it are human sympathizers.
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW
FISH-MAN PIRATES - DARUMA
Which means they're our enemies!
IN FRONT OF THE FISH-MAN CULTURAL HALL
In front of the Fish-Man Culture
Hall in the southeast...
Whoa, whoa! It's easy!
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW
FISH-MAN PIRATES - HYOUZOU
It's either step on this image
or flee from this island.
Screw you!
Damn! I can't take it anymore!
Just do it! If somebody
refused to do either...
...I've been told to slice 'em up!
MARINE SHOPPING MALL
At the Marine Shopping Mall in the east...
"Leave the country"? Don't be ridiculous!
This is the only place on the
seafloor that has light.
And we can't live in the humans' world!
See?
You can see how heartlessly the
humans discriminate against others.
What is it?! What are you doing?!
What's going on?
There is no way that humans
and Fish-Men can get along.
You must submit to King Hordy!
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW FISH-MAN PIRATES - ZEO
We will reign over humans and change history!
WATERWHEEL TOWN
At Waterwheel Town in the north...
Dosun!
--Now, you're next.
--It's gonna be easy.
I can't!
AN OFFICER OF THE NEW
FISH-MAN PIRATES - DOSUN
I'm gonna pummel those who
won't step on it-dosun!
Take this!
You're... Fukaboshi! Don't get in my way!
What do you think you are doing?!
How dare you make people of this country
tread on the image of my late mother!
CORAL HILL
At Coral Hill, after Luffy
and the others left...
--What should we do?!
--We let Vander Decken get away...
...and we couldn't stop the Straw Hats
from taking Princess Shirahoshi away!
But the Princess said that
she'd be back by dinner.
You fool! They made her say it!
A group from the Fish-Man District
is rampaging all over the island!
--What?!
--What's going on on the island?!
Mermaid girls are going
missing all around the island!
If they sell the Princess
to the Celestial Dragons...
Hey, it seems like another
Mermaid girl went missing!
I'm scared!
Oh no!
I took her!
That aside, I just saw something great!
A big size Mermaid-san!
A human-sized Mermaid is worth 70 million
so if I can catch a Mermaid
who is 7 or 8 times bigger
and sell her...
I'll make a bundle!
Y-You are...
Hello.
Good afternoon!
SEA FOREST
Father-sama!
Princess Shirahoshi, don't worry.
Maybe they got the King but
they can't really take his life!
What? Are you sure?
Yes. And I will save the King at any cost!
Okay. I will be counting on you, Boss-sama!
Now let me talk to Luffy-kun
and the others for a while.
Ladies!
Have some tea!
Thanks. Leave it there, Sanji-kun.
And we're having a serious
conversation so stop acting like that!
I love you, Nami-san, even
when you're so severe!
Sanji-chin hasn't changed a bit.
Good!
It's not for you!
Now, Jimbei-san.
What do you mean?
You set Arlong loose into the East Blue?
Jimbei-san!
I know.
That's what I heard.
What?
When Luffy and I first heard the
name Jimbei of the Seven Warlords,
that's what Yosaku told us.
In exchange for joining the Warlords,
Jimbei set loose a terrible
man into the East Blue.
--Was that what he said?
--I bet you don't remember it.
I wonder how Yosaku is doing.
When I read that you were with
Jimbei 2 years ago in the newspaper,
it raised so many questions in my mind.
Because I thought Jimbei was the key
figure who was pulling Arlong's strings.
Hey, Jimbei.
If you wanna make excuses, I'll listen.
But you better watch what you say.
As a matter of fact, this beautiful navigator
- Nami-san here had her home island...
...taken over by Arlong!
And she's been through hell because of it!
Depending on what you have
to say, I might not forgive you!
--Jimbei-san!
--Hatchin!
Your wounds are gonna
open up again! Don't get up!
He's right! We gave her so much pain...
...that we can't heal no matter
how much we apologize.
I’m gonna use my navigation skills
to travel to all the world’s oceans!
And then I’m gonna make a
world map of everything I see!
So your map of this island is your
first step toward your dream, then?
Yeah!
I'm a fill-in mother for
you two, Nami and Nojiko.
You two are my dear family!
Pirates, everyone!
Pirates are coming!
You seem to be in excellent spirits,
pathetic humans!
As of this moment,
this village - no,
this island - is now under my control!
100,000 Berries per adult.
50,000 Berries per kid.
Those who can’t pay… die!
I just can’t say I don’t have a family…
Even… if it costs me my life…
Yeah, maybe we’re not related by blood…
…but we’re a family.
I want to be their parent,
even if it’s only in name.
They’re… my kids.
Die with your pathetic love.
Nojiko! Nami!
I love you!
What's this?
--A sea chart?
--No!
I drew that! It's important
to me! Give it back!
You drew it?
--Give it back!
--Nami! No!
Oh? This is quite impressive.
She’s an invaluable
asset! Bring her with us!
--Right!
--No!
Let go! Let go! No!
We have no food for humans!
Shut up and keep drawing maps!
Gather up 100 million
Berries and bring it here.
Do so and I’ll let the village
go and give you freedom.
Thief! She stole our treasure!
--She's a kid!
--Who cares! Shoot her!
Shit! Go after her!
70 million more...
70 million more to free the village!
Oh, you're back!
Humph! It seems like you
have nowhere else to go.
Welcome home, my dear navigator!
Sounds like you had a terrible experience.
You bastard! Don't distance yourself!
Yes.
It would never make me change
the way I feel about Arlong,
but until I went to Sabaody
Archipelago 2 years ago,
I never knew that such tough
Fish-Men were persecuted by humans.
When Camie was kidnapped
and I was going after her,
I couldn't believe what I saw!
The Sabaody Park in front of me looked exactly
like the Arlong Park that Arlong built!
We were yearning for it.
I'm not just saying this
to make you forgive me.
Nami! Arlong-san really didn't like humans!
He hated them.
We went too far.
But ever since we were kids,
we yearned for the world that humans live in.
Me, Arlong-san...
Everybody...
But we hurt so many humans!
Hachi, don't push yourself!
I'm gonna prepare some medicine so lie down.
I heard that Fish-Men and Merfolk were
considered mere fish a long time ago.
But 200 years ago, the Ryugu Kingdom became
a member country of the World Government.
They established friendly
relations with humans
and the king was allowed to
participate in the World Summit.
Despite that,
humans kept disliking Fish-Men.
The worst time that I experienced was
the beginning of the Great Pirate Era.
I vividly remember the fear of seeing
human pirates running wild on the island.
I can't get it off of my mind!
The Fish-Man Island was
taken over by humans.
And then, the late,
good-old Whitebeard saved us.
He claimed the Fish-Man Island as his own
and peace returned to the island.
However, it didn't stop humans
from disliking Fish-Men.
I know that you people saw
it at Sabaody Archipelago.
The reality.
The funny thing is those who seize
power tend to be more afraid of change.
Even though the Government bridged
the gap between Fish-Men and humans
those who held the real power ended up being
much more bigoted than all the others!
The relationship between Fish-Men
and humans remained the same.
Then, two people rose up on the Fish-Man Island,
to change our hopeless history.
One was Queen Otohime.
She kept trying to tell the islanders
to live in harmony with humans.
She was Princess Shirahoshi's mother.
And the other is the hero who
freed the slaves - Fisher Tiger.
Something Tiger... I heard that name before.
Calling for parting ways with humans,
he broke an unspoken rule
and invaded the Holyland of Marie
Jois by himself and freed the slaves.
Later, he formed the Sun Pirates
with the Fish-Men who were slaves.
The Sun...?
Yes! Me, Arlong, and Hachi joined the...
...crew of the Sun Pirates, naturally.
However, having the "Fish-Man Pirates"
who went against the Government...
...made it harder for Queen Otohime to
establish good relations with humans.
Queen Otohime was trying to weather
great hardships and change the future.
Fisher Tiger threw his future away
to save the slaves of his race
who were suffering at the time.
No one can say which one was right or wrong.
Let's talk.
They fought for the future
of Fish-Men and humans.
They were two monumental figures!
But what was their hidden angst?!
Queen Otohime tried to
guide the Ryugu Kingdom
toward a future where humans and
Fish-Men could live together.
There was also Fisher Tiger,
a hero who rescued Fish-Man
from enslavement by humans.
Their fates intertwined as they imagined
a new future for Fish-Man Island,
and an incident that shaped history occurred!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"A Hero Who Freed the Slaves!
An Adventurer Tiger!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!