Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the
Grand Line in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!!
Oh, no!
If I can get my arms and
legs out, the game is mine!
What?!
This is gonna end it... for sure!
He can be defeated by someone
with a spear of blind determination.
I know an idiot who's holding back
that spear for a stupid reason...
All... Blue...
I'm the strongest man!!
Don Krieg... We lost.
Chief Commander!
Thanks for everything, Sanji-san.
When he wakes up, could you tell him...
Maybe... I can live
only a few more hours...
It's kind of stupid that I'm resolved
because I don't have much time left,
but this time, I want to do it with
my own will... in my own way...
Then, there'll be nowhere
for me to escape, right?
You don't have to think about stupid
things like fearing your enemy
or how to keep from getting hurt...
I learned it from that guy.
Well, then! We gratefully
accept the boat.
We don't have to return it, right?
Right. If you have the courage
to come here to return it,
try it, you small fry.
He's right! Just keep
this in your brain!!
This is the sea restaurant
Baratie, where cooks fight!
Hmph! What a scary restaurant...
"Set Sail! The Seafaring Cook
Sets off with Luffy"
Ahh! My hat! My straw hat!!
It's right there.
Huh? Oh, yeah. Here it is.
So you're awake?
Oh? Where're those guys?
They left... thanks to you.
Me?
Ghin said, "I'll see you
again in the Grand Line."
Ghin did?
To you?
No, to you!!
Speaking of which,
since I drove them away,
today is my last day
to do chores, right?
Congrats.
By the way, will you...
I'm not going!
I won't become a pirate.
I'll continue to work as a cook here
until I get that damn geezer
to acknowledge my skills.
Okay, then I give up.
Your hand hasn't given up yet!
I can't leave here...
since they're all undependable...
But I'm hoping to go some day...
to the Grand Line.
Then let's go now.
It's not the right time yet.
Say... do you know the All Blue?
No...
Oh, you don't?! It's a miracle sea!
The East Blue, West Blue,
North Blue, and South Blue...
Fish from all those
four seas live in that sea!
To us cooks,
it's a dream-like paradise!
That's what the Grand Line is like.
So, have you heard...
He looks so happy...
That idiot...
Guys!! Meal time!!
Aw, man...
We can finally eat!
Food! Food! Food!
Hey, where do we sit?
Where's our food?
There're no chairs for you.
Sit on the floor and eat.
No chairs? That can't be true!
This is a restaurant!
Guess we can't help it...
They're acting kinda weird...
Hmph! Nothing new...
Hey! Who prepared
the soup this morning?!
Hey, I did it! I did! Isn't it good?
I made it especially good today!
I can't eat damn nasty soup like this!
What is this, pig feed?!
Hey, is human food not to your liking,
you damn racoon dog?
Ha! When it's this bad, it's art now.
It makes me sick to my stomach!
I'm sorry, but I'm really
confident about today's soup.
There's something wrong
with your taste buds!
Ugh! This is nasty!
I can't eat it!
Right, guys?!
I can't eat something like this!
This is damn nasty soup!
I can't eat soup like this!
This is terrible!
Someone, give me some water!
What do you think
you're doing, you bastards?!
You're a sham Sous Chef after all...
You're just an old-timer.
We're sick and tired of you
settling matters with violence!
If the food's bad, we're gonna say so!
What'd you say?!
We're seafaring cooks.
Don't waste even a drop of soup.
Owner!!
You geezer!
What is this damn nasty soup?
It's like sludge!
If we serve something like this,
our restaurant will go out of business!
Don't be ridiculous,
you damn geezer!
Just how is this soup
different from yours?! Tell me!
From my soup?
Don't flatter yourself!
Owner punched him...
He didn't kick...
It'll be a billion years before you can
give me a lecture on cooking, little brat!
I'm a man who has cooked
on seas around the world.
Dammit!
That damn geezer! I... I...
I'm not a "little brat" any more!!
This soup is super good, you know...
We know that.
Huh?
Sanji's cooking skills are
recognized by everyone here.
It's not bad at all.
Yeah, this soup is very well made.
Boy, that was scary...
He seriously snapped...
Yeah...
But that idiot won't listen
unless we go this far...
Say, kid...
Hm?
You were saying that you wanted
a cook for your ship, right?
This isn't a favor that I'd
like to ask of you or anything,
but would you take that
little brat with you...
...to the Grand Line?
The Grand Line... is his dream.
Man, Owner, you really
made us put on quite a show.
I was worried that he might figure
it out because of your bad acting.
Your acting was horrible, too.
I'll have another bowl of soup!
--Me, too!
I can hear everything,
you damn idiots...
So what do you say, kid?
No.
What?!
I thought you wanted
a cook for your ship.
Or are you saying that he's
not good enough for you?
He's good enough, all right.
I do want him to come with me.
But he says that he wants to
continue working here as a cook.
Even if you guys ask me to
take him with me, I can't.
So you're saying that
you can't agree to it
until he tells you so himself, huh?
Exactly. More, please!
Well... fair enough.
But who knows if that twisted
damn brat can just say he'll go...
There's no way he can, since he's
an idiot through and through...
More, please!
Dammit!
Sanji!
What is he? A fishman?
He came all the way from the
Fishman Island to eat our dishes?
Idiot! It's a human and a panshark!
Hm? What's going on?
Oh? Hey, it's you, Yosaku!
Oh, Big Bro Luffy!
Why are you alone?
Where're the others?
What happened to Nami?
It's not that we caught up with her,
but from the direction
Big Sis Nami was heading,
we figured out roughly
where she was going.
I see... We can bring her back then.
Well... If what we're thinking is right,
her destination is a crazy place...
In any case, we need your help,
Big Bro Luffy. Please come with me.
Okay! I don't really get it, but got it.
I'll come with you.
Wait!
Hm?
We both have foolish dreams.
In order to achieve
my goal, the All Blue...
Sanji?
Yeah. I'll come along...
...on your journey to become
"King of the Pirates"!
What?
I'll be the cook for your ship.
Is that okay or not?
It's okay!! All right!!
I'm happy for you, Big Bro Luffy!
Yeah!
Yaay! Yaay! We got a cook!
We'll have good food!
So that's how it is, everyone.
Sorry for causing you
all sorts of trouble.
Ha! I don't like it! I wanted to
kick you out from here myself.
And you decide it so easily?
Sorry for making you
resort to bad acting.
You knew?!
I could hear everything,
since you're all stupid.
What?!
That is to say, you're willing
to go that far to kick me out,
huh, you damn geezer?!
Why do you always have to
talk like that?! You bastard!
Hmph! That's right, little brat!
I don't like kids to begin with.
Not a single day passed
where I didn't regret
letting a useless one live,
you damn brat.
Ha! Fine by me, you damn geezer!
Enjoy the rest of your life to the utmost.
Whoa! This is a nice ship.
Is it okay for us to use it?
Of course! It's Sanji's boat.
You still need more?!
Yeah. Give me more meat.
Just how many days
will you be at sea?
Don't know...
Kid...
Hm? Pops!
Do you wanna take this?
It's a record of my one-year
journey in the Grand Line.
Don't need it.
I knew it...
I want that marbled meat, too!
Enough already!
Whoa!! Damn geezer,
is this the sea restaurant?
"Baratie Employee Guidelines
1. Serving customers... That is 'love'!
And 'love' means 'restaurant'! 2. Motto! Motto! Service motto!"
For example, Sanji...
Hm? What is it?
Be they arch rogues or jail breakers,
if these damn bastards
badly want to eat
and find their way to this restaurant,
there may be a point in our
continuing to fight at this restaurant...
Yeah!
We're gonna be busy!
We'll be fine 'cause I'm here!
Ah...
Uh! Ow! Ouch...
Geez...
You peeled the skin
too thick, little brat!
That hurt!
When someone's cooking seriously,
you should just watch quietly!
What?! Don't get smart,
you little brat!
I'm not a little brat!
You damn geezer!!
Try this.
Did you make it by yourself?
Yeah.
How is it?
Cripes, this is damn nasty,
you little brat!
You damn geezer!!
Big Bro Cook sure is taking time...
Yeah...
This is for my longstanding grudge!
Be prepared, Sanji!
There's no way you guys
can defeat him.
Let's go.
You don't have to say goodbye?
That's okay.
Sanji!
Don't catch cold.
Owner Zeff!!
Thank you for all the damn things
you've done for me
over all these years!!
I'll never forget your kindness...
for the rest of my life!!
You asshole!!
I'll miss you, dammit!
I'll miss you!!
I feel sad, dammit!
You idiots!
Men should part without a word.
Let's go!! Set sail!!
I'll see you again, you damn bastards!
As long as you don't fear even death
because you have faith in yourself,
you'll find the All Blue... for sure...
Guys! Customers are
gonna show up soon!
Get to work already!
When I was little, I had
a vision of a treasure map
and I always searched
for that miraculous place
before someone else could
beat me to it
If the world is going to change
before I can even attain my dream
then take me to the time
when I knew nothing
so that my memories won't fade
It sounds like Nami-san
headed to Arlong Park.
What's that?
It's a place dominated
by fishman pirates.
She couldn't be...
Considering her cuteness...
she might be a mermaid...
A water imp?
I'll kill you!
"Nami"
Then a half fishman?
No meals for you!
Why?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Worst Man in the Eastern Seas!
Fishman Pirate Arlong!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!