Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
What speed!
--He's well on his way to
catching up with Porche-chan!
--Flower Shurikens!
I'm a wall...
Oh! But he clears the wall with a skillful toss!
Is it only a matter of time
until he catches Porche-chan?!
He's already back?!
Take this!
--Oh...
--Oh?!
That's it.
Now do it just like I explained!
That's it! Stand up, Luffy!
"A Seriously Heated Race!
Into the Final Round!"
C'mon! You can do it! Just a little more!
Man, this is great!
This is so moving! Seriously!
All right! I'm up!
Hang on, Usopp!
Luffy!
And then...
...like this?!
It's so fast! Awesome!
I won't let you win!
Amazing!
It's hard to believe Straw Hat Luffy
couldn't even stand up moments ago!
He's keeping pace with Chiqicheetah,
who's powered up with his
Double Speed Full Dash!
Crap! I never taught him how to turn corners!
Straw Hat Luffy has left the course once again!
He's out of Round #3 as well!
Darn it...!
I knew it! He's hopeless...!
There goes the Speed King, Chiqicheetah!
He's four laps in the lead now!
Long-nose! Grab on! Hurry!
Right! Whoa...!
What's this?! Archaeologist
Nico Robin uses a Long Whip!
Will this help him rally back?!
Oh, that woman!
Porche-chan! Just leave it to me, ya know?!
There it is! Chiqicheetah's
Triple Speed Rocket Dash!
Hey! He went off the course just now, dammit!
He was only in the air! Only in the air!
Violent coach Sanji's desperate
complaint is shot down!
I have to do something before it's too late!
Mucha Caramente!
Oh, no!
I wouldn't move if I were you!
The more you struggle,
the tighter it gets, ya know!
It's no use! I'm soft-bodied!
That doesn't hurt me one bit, ya know!
Well done, Jube!
That's one down, ya know!
Damn! They got Robin-chan!
Hey, idiot coach!
We're gonna lose unless we do
something about that Chiqicheetah guy!
Don't need you to tell me that!
"Chiqi... cheetah"...
Cheetah?
Could it be?!
Old guy!
Old guy with the horse! You here?!
Oh, you mean me?
That Long Kiwi you gave Luffy!
Where'd you get it?!
--What are you talking about?!
--Shut it!
Hurry! Tell me where!
There! They grow on those trees!
Hey, Shrub Head! Run and get us a kiwi branch!
Is that how you ask for stuff?!
It might be the only way to stop him!
Stop him?!
Yeah! So get goin'!
--Wh-What the...?!
--What's he doing?!
--You can ride Shelly!
--Thanks!
Dunno if it'll work or not,
but it's better than nothing!
After four minutes,
Chiqicheetah has a huge 13-lap lead!
Four and a half minutes have passed!
His lead has increased to 15 laps!
Things are looking bleak
for the Straw Hat Dangers!
What's taking that loser so long?!
Is that it?!
Four minutes and fifty seconds have passed!
Ten more seconds and the Foxy Devils
will clinch a shut-out victory!
Not gonna make it...!
Five seconds to go!
Wh-What's happening?!
I-Is that...?!
O-Oh, my! What on earth
happened to Chiqicheetah?!
Chiqicheetah left the course
just before the round ended!
What a conclusion!
The Straw Hat Dangers come from
behind to win the third round!
Oh, no! Chiqicheetah!
What?!
H-Hooray!
--What happened?!
--What's the deal?!
Kiwifruits have catnip-like properties.
Just like with catnip, the smell of the
plant itself mesmerizes some cats.
Cheetahs are cats too,
so I figured it was worth a shot.
So that's why he was sniffing Luffy earlier!
I'm guessing so.
Excellent thinking, Cook!
Oh! It was nothing!
Whew, just barely made it...
The Straw Hat Dangers have
scored a point of their own!
But the Foxy Devils still have the advantage!
There's no time to bask in the
afterglow of victory, though!
It's time for Round #4 to begin!
The scorers will be Nico Robin the archaeologist
versus Jube the fishman!
A great match-up, indeed!
Listen up, Luffy! When you reach a curve...
I got it! I'm fine now!
What do you mean "fine"?
You screwed up just a second ago...
Don't you remember, Zoro? You told
me to watch everyone else earlier...
He's definitely going to shoot that beam again.
Yeah. That Idiot-Idiot Beam is bad news.
--Idiot-Idiot Beam...?!
--B-Boss!
Usopp! Hear me out!
What is it?
You're a wicked one, all right!
Good idea, huh?!
Oh! Does the heartless Nami
have a secret plan?!
Her dishonest face is on par
with that of our own boss!
Who're you calling dishonest?!
You.
It's time for Round #4!
Got ya good earlier, huh?
Ready! Go!
Oh, no, you don't!
I'm no Chiqicheetah, but I'm
pretty fast too, ya know!
Twenty seconds are up! Defense, go!
I-Is Luffy gonna be okay?!
--Yes!
--Way to go, Luffy!
Bring it on anytime! I'll give you
another taste of my Mucha Caramente!
No, you won't!
Oh! Is he finally in fighting form?!
Straw Hat Luffy sends Jube flying!
Go, Robin! I'll take care of this guy!
Right!
Huh?! My baton is gone!
So sorry!
Oh! How could you?!
I'd stay down if I were you!
Okay...!
Incredible! The Straw Hat Dangers are on a roll!
They've taken a one-lap lead!
We'll just see about that!
Hamburg! Prepare for a full dash!
Right!
Get ready, Usopp!
Yeah! I dub it "Operation
Laugh and Fall"! Ready?!
Okay!
Lousy Split-Head! Shootin' your
Idiot-Idiot Beam again, huh?!
Split-Head?! Idiot-Idiot Beam?!
He's not like that! He's an
intelligent, handsome man!
Don't listen to her, you stupid fox!
No, I'm serious! I'm head over heels for you!
No one would like you, Crappy Split-Head!
He added "Crappy" to "Split-Head"...!
So handsome!
--Split-Head!
--Handsome!
--I'm in love!
All lies!
Split-Head! Split-Head--!
What are you doing, Nami?!
You need to compliment him!
I can't go on... It's making me sick...
Switch places with me...
Why, you... How dare you?!
I can't think of any nice things to say...
--All right! Let's just keep repeating stuff!
--Right!
--You're manly! You're manly!...
--Split-Head! Split-Head!...
He can't fire his Slow-Slow Beam!
Has our boss been KOed by
this ingenious verbal assault?!
Time is nearly up!
--Manly! Manly! Manly!...
--Split-Head! Split-Head!...
--Split-Head!
--Manly!
Incredible! Just incredible!
The Straw Hat Dangers win
Round #4 by a landslide!
There'll now be a five-minute break
before the final round begins!
I can't believe I fell for that childish trick!
Or that this would drag out to the final round!
We can't lose the next one!
We'll use you-know-what to win for sure!
The plan?!
All right! Let's win this thing!
The final round is about to begin!
Both teams, to the starting line!
Oh! The Foxy Devils' scorer,
Girarin, is all alone!
All the others are off the track!
Could they be planning to
unleash that huge technique?!
Huge technique?
Just gonna be another Idiot Beam, obviously.
Oh, my. How did you know?
Yes. This tactic is all about getting
the Slow-Slow Beam to hit its mark.
But knowing that still won't help ya!
As if! Weren't you paying attention last time?!
We have Operation Laugh and Fall!
Don't worry, Luffy! Just skate like crazy!
Yeah! Leave it to me!
Okay, it's time!
Ready! Go!
What?! Already?!
--Manly! Manly! Manly!...
--Split-Head! Split-Head!...
Slow-Slow Beam!
There it is! A barrage of Slow-Slow Beams!
Why isn't Operation Laugh and Fall working?!
Huh? Did you say somethin'?!
Earplugs!
The Straw Hat Dangers have been bested!
That's our boss for you!
C-Crap!
Is it me, or do the Idiot Beams
bounce off that guy?!
Oh! You noticed?
Slow-Slow Beams don't work on Girarin!
Oh, really? Why not?
Oh, I'm afraid that's a secret!
Oh, a secret? That's what I thought!
That's why you're already off the course, huh?
That's right. All your guys are gonna
turn into slowpokes, but not us!
And they can't hide behind us!
So that's their deal! This is bad! Really bad!
Twenty seconds are up! Defenders, go!
Time for you all to slow down!
No!
Nami-san!
Direct hit!
Navigator Nami and Sniper Usopp
have fallen prey to the Slow-Slow Beam!
Luffy! Look out behind you!
They finally got Straw Hat Luffy!
Is victory a near-certainty now?!
That just leaves you!
I can't risk it! We'll be
done for if that beam hits me!
Oh! What's this?!
Nico Robin was keeping the
Straw Hat Dangers in the game!
And now... she's given up?
She's exited the course of her own
accord with only one minute left!
The Slow-Slow Beam lasts for 30 seconds...
If Luffy can dodge the next attack,
he'll still have a chance...!
Failure isn't an option!
I have to wait for my chance!
What's going on, Robin-chan?
I can avoid those beams by staying here, right?
Robin-chan...?
Forty seconds remain!
Girarin has an easy, three-lap lead!
Ouch...!
Time for another dose, just to be safe!
Wha...?!
It's been fun, Straw Hat Luffy...
...but this is the end!
Thirty seconds left!
Victory is guaranteed if he can hit
Straw Hat Luffy with another beam!
End of the line!
Crap!
Skate, Luffy! There's no time!
All right!
Twenty seconds left!
Mucha Cara...
Grilled or deep-fried... Which do you prefer?
D-Damn!
D-Damn...!
Ten seconds left!
Straw Hat Luffy is moving at incredible speed!
This could turn into a mad dash for the finish!
Oh! Our boss slowed himself down!
Five seconds left!
Swords that can't cut...
...won't work on me!
The Straw Hat Dangers
come from behind to win!
Yes!
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
--Thank you, Luffy!
--You know we'd never lose!
As a pirate, I refuse this outcome!
I challenge you to extra rounds!
--Are you an idiot?!
--Id--?!
Who'd agree to more of these lame games?!
All right! You're on!
What a surprise.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Screaming-Hot Bombardment!
Pirate Dodgeball!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!