Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Franky and Robin have been
taken to the Tower of Law.
I feel on top of the world!
I'm surprised to see you survived that
accident eight years ago, Cutty Flam.
Goals can't be achieved without sacrifice.
We're working in order to
ensure peace for all of humanity.
You're crazy!
Tom-san put his life on the line
to protect the blueprints
because idiots like you exist!
Yoi!
Around that time, Luffy was
fighting against 10,000 soldiers
on the main island of Enies Lobby.
Chief Spandam! Please come in!
Please advise us on countermeasures!
We can't stop Straw Hat Luffy!
Meanwhile, Zoro and the others,
who had been waiting on Rocketman
for the gates to be opened, charged in
after thorough preparation and...
What?! This is terrible!
We're gonna crash into the gate!
What're we gonna do?! What're we gonna do?!
--Dodge it, Kokoro-san!
--What're we gonna do?!
Don't worry. There's a way.
...they passed over the main gate
and headed straight to
the main island front gate.
Wh-Who are those two?!
Big bazooka unit, step forward!
I have to hurry up or Robin will...
I guess I'll try that thing.
Just give up, Straw Hat!
Fire!
--Did we do it?
--He fell into the waterfall!
Hey, look! He's still clinging onto the edge!
Straw Hat! If you surrender
peacefully, we can pull you up.
Why would I?!
How stubborn! Fall into the waterfall already!
You bastard!
Hey, guys! Give me a foot here!
Yeah!
Hey, he went over to your side!
This way! This way!
I got lucky!
It's Straw Hat! Fire!
Boy, what a crazy place I wandered off into.
But since I was able to take care of a
lot of them at once, I guess it's okay.
If I remember right, I should move forward
towards that serious looking building, right?
--All right!
--He went that way! After him!
H-Heavy...
C-Climb up in order,
starting with those at the bottom!
Slowly, okay?! Slowly!
Don't shake!
It's not me! It was a wind gust!
It's just wind! Stop it with your willpower!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Let's cross this endless sea to go in search of
a global miracle no one
has yet been able to find
With our hearts pounding,
we'll just charge ahead as we please
following the footprints of
those who chase their dreams
No matter how stormy the night,
if we join our hearts as one,
we will be able to make it through
Always!
Get running, get running,
holding our flag high in the sky
Even though there are tears
we don't want anyone to see
Chase it, chase it,
if we want to achieve our dream,
we should always look
straight ahead without fear
We can't stop here
Around the world
Start me up!
Get running, get running,
head past everyone else
So long as we don't run from it,
we can grasp tomorrow in our hands
Chase it, chase it,
everything we see before us,
let's carve it into the blank pages of our hearts
Brand New World
Start me up!
"Catch Up with Luffy!
The Straw Hats' All-Out Battle"
H-Hey! I know who that swordsman is!
Yeah, he's one of Straw Hat's
underlings, Pirate Hunter Zoro!
They called you an underling.
Then, you're even lower
than that, right, "Pirate A"?
Huh?!
Then, "B."
Huh?! If I had a bounty, it'd be
at least twice as much as yours!
Then, "C."
Hey, listen to what I'm saying, you bastard!
Hey, stop it, you two.
Sogeking, they can't hear you.
This is part of my plan, Chopper-kun.
--Oh, I didn't know.
--Hm?
There are more of them in the train!
They found us!
There have to be more!
Blow it up before they come out!
Hey, hold it! Nami-san is still in there!
Fire!
Those bastards! I'm gonna
cut them into three pieces!
Hold on, Pirate A.
What?!
An attack like that isn't enough
to take someone like her out.
You're only "Pirate A" because you
don't get something as obvious as that.
You damn Moss Head!
Boy, that scared me!
Are you okay, Sogeking?
I-I-I'm okay, Chopper-kun.
Stop firing!
What's the matter?
--Look at that!
--Hello!
Stop it! I'm a senior citizen!
I'm a child and here is a
small animal! We're weak!
The Straw Hat Pirates threatened me
and made me operate the train!
They did!
Who lets their hostages drink?
That was close! We almost
killed the hostages, too!
Of all people, to think that those
pirates took a senior, a child,
and a small animal hostage... How despicable!
Hm?
What's that?! That smoke looks like clouds.
Using cool balls and heat balls,
the moisture in the air is turned into clouds.
Nami-san! So you escaped the attack!
Hey, the cloud is getting bigger and bigger.
Grandma, Grandma. The cloud is getting bigger.
That cloud looks a little dangerous.
Chimney, Gonbe. Come this way.
It sure wasn't named the
"Perfect Clima Takt" for nothing.
It develops much bigger clouds now,
and it does it much faster too.
Now, I'm gonna see how
powerful its thunderbolt is.
That lady's gonna do something!
We might wanna get out of here!
Here it comes!
Thunderbolt... Tempo!
Grandma, Grandma. That's an
incredible thunderbolt, isn't it?
That girl is something else.
Grandma, are we gonna be
okay under this umbrella?
Trust me. You'll be fine as long as you're here.
Nooo!
It's attacking everyone! We'll die, too!
Ahh! Sogeking!
Why'd you hit Sogeking, Nami?!
Don't worry about it.
D-Don't take it out on me.
The problem lies in how you're using it.
Besides, Usopp-kun says that he
doesn't remember adding that feature!
At any rate...
...that thing is crazy powerful!
You brought down a bunch of them.
--Ah...
--Hey, Nami!
What the hell did you do that for?!
Apologize to him, Sogeking!
You apologize, idiot!
Nami-san! That reminded me of the
shock I had the first time I met you!
What's with those pirates?
I thought that girl was here just
for support, but she sure can fight.
Looks like it's over.
Pirate lady, you're incredible!
Looks like you guys're okay, too, Granny!
It's no accident that I've lived
for several decades, you know!
By the way, where's that idiot
who rushed out by himself?
Beats me... This island isn't small,
so if we are to find him...
What was that?!
That's definitely where he is!
Well, then...
...let's go after him, shall we?
They're mere pirates...
How dare they make a ruckus...?!
They won't get away with this!
Take this!
Gum-Gum... Spear!
He jumped onto the tree!
Those jerks! This is endless!
I can't move forward!
Hey, this way!
They're running in the opposite direction?!
Half of you guys, head to
the main island front gate!
Pirates broke open the gate and
are invading! Stop them at any cost!
They must be here! Good!
That makes things quite a bit easier!
All right!
Sorry, you missed!
He's over there! Fire!
If I remember right, it was this way, wasn't it?!
Hey, it wouldn't be good if you led the way.
Why not?!
It'll be fine if we go straight!
Seriously, that darn idiot!
He rushed out by himself, as usual!
Well, our sticking with that idiot
makes us quite the idiots as well.
But thanks to Luffy, it seems that the
marines are scattered for the time being.
So all we have to do now is
head straight to the courthouse!
Oh, no, my chronic disease is coming back...
If you wanna die, you can remain here.
--It's cured now!
--That's more like it.
Wh-What's the matter?
We have guests.
We Watchdogs are ordered
to guard the front gate!
No one can cross this line!
Just give up, you damn rogues!
Doggie policemen, this time?
Don't think that it's just us, pirates!
Looks like we're completely surrounded.
Now that I look a little closer,
there are too many enemies!
Now, the jig is up, pirates.
So what?
You sure are cocky! Guys, get them!
Grab hold!
Hey, you could've at least
let us have a little fun...
You idiot!
Don't forget why you came here.
This isn't where you should
be focusing your energy.
It's true that it'd take a whole
day to fight this many enemies.
They're quite energetic. Don't die, okay?!
Charge ahead!
Guards! Get back!
That's a King Bull from Water Seven!
Prepare the cannons immediately!
Dammit!
Take this!
We've got one more!
Watchdogs! Get back in formation!
Yeah!
We won't let you go!
Our dogs are faster than your fish!
This is bad! They're gonna try jumping on!
No way!
--Can't we go faster?!
--Hey, cook guy.
Hm?
What's the matter?
Take the reins.
Hm? You guys...
When you see... those guys, tell them...
"You guys're fired."
Sure will.
Jump onto it!
We won't let you!
We'll leave them to you, Galley-La!
We'll skewer you!
Half Knot Air Drive!
Ahhh! S-Some Watchdogs were taken out!
Those fools! They let their guard down!
There's no way ordinary people
can match our speed. Go!
Yeah!
We'll pierce you before you notice!
More went down!
What's with them?!
They're strong!
We'll take care of these guys.
It seems that your temperament
hasn't changed at all, huh, Cutty Flam?
If I had realized sooner that you
were alive and had the blueprints,
I wouldn't have had to go
through all this trouble...
...since we could just have brought
you in for your past crimes!
On the contrary, your older fellow
disciple Iceberg was a hassle.
After Tom died,
he brought the shipbuilding
companies in Water Seven together
and organized a big company
by himself. And then,
he approached the World Government,
which he must've had a grudge against,
and soon his company established its position
as a purveyor to the World Government.
He's the president of the
shipbuilding company Galley-La
and the mayor of the
city of water, Water Seven.
After he became a figure
that everyone supported
and that was indispensable to the Government,
we couldn't meddle with him carelessly.
I heard that your company contracts to
build ships for the World Government!
Give me a break! I'm not gonna tolerate it!
So that's why he's been
contracting with the Government...
He was a smart man.
However, the winds started blowing in my favor.
Just when I couldn't wait any longer and
was about to take forceful measures...
...Admiral Aokiji sent me the good news...
...that Nico Robin was headed
to Water Seven on a pirate ship.
I drank a cup of coffee to calm myself down
and put all the conditions, including
Buster Call, into the plan of operations.
Well, there was a bit of change in the plans,
but look! Both triggers for the
ancient weapon's revival are here!
Do you get it? The winds the entire
world over are blowing in my favor.
A power strong enough to give me control
over any large country I might desire
is in my hands now!
Why did Aokiji give you the
authority to exercise Buster Call?
Huh?
You're in no position to ask me
questions, you insolent woman!
If I hadn't recognized
the value of your existence,
it would've been practically worthless!
So you should appreciate me!
You, the repugnant kin of Ohara,
the land of devils...
Nico Robin...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
We'll become No. 1
We'll aim for freedom in wonderland
Look, there's a faint light
showing us the road to tomorrow,
an era created by risking everything
We always try our best, let's go!
If we want to achieve glory,
now is the time--don't be afraid
We'll surely win the future
together with friends
Now, we start running faster
towards the vast world
We can take off with unknown powers
We don't fear, and we don't waver
No matter what happens,
in the end we'll surely...
We fight harder against
the wall that confronts us
We charge ahead stronger
with overflowing power
We won't fear even if we
have to give up everything
Charge ahead
Let's start running towards tomorrow
Because it's all to ensure we smile in the end
Wait! That's not what we agreed upon!
What we agreed?
That the Straw Hats would
leave Water Seven safely!
That's right!
They left Water Seven safely...
and so, now, they're here, right?
No...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Robin Betrayed! The Motive
of the World Government!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!