Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Every time I look up to
the sky after the rain
ame agari no sora wo aogu tabi
I think back to when I was a crybaby
nakimushi datta koro no boku wo omou
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
dareka no senaka wo gamushara ni oikaketa
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
"tsuyoku naritai" tte
ima wa kaze ni kieta "arigatou"
The word "thank you" has
faded into the wind now
boku wa tsuyoku nareteiru no kana?
Am I getting stronger?
kotae wa mada desou ni nai kara sa
I don't know the answer yet
yappari mada aruiteiku yo
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
saa yukou
tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
boku no naka ni nagareru koe wa
The voice inside of me
zutto zutto boku wo sasaeteru
keeps sustaining me
itazura na ame ga jama suru kedo
Wicked rain will get in my way
nigedasanai kara
But I won't walk away
So let's go
saa yukou
Tachidomaru koto naku
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
nagareru toki ni makenai youni
I'll keep getting back up
nando mo tachimukai tsuzukeyou
taisetsu na mono ushinaitakunai kara
Because I don't want to
lose something precious
shinjita sono saki e to...
To the future I believe in...
The time is the Great Pirate Era.
Countless pirates fight
desperately for the One Piece,
the great treasure left behind by
Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
also takes to the sea to become
the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his friends
overcome numerous adventures,
the World Government is less and
less able to ignore their existence.
This is exciting!
What kind of adventure
is waiting for us next?!
The crew, on its way to the New World,
will speed along the Grand Line again today!
Separated from the rest of the Straw Hats,
Luffy made it to Marineford to rescue
his brother, Ace who will be executed!
Inside the bay, Luffy and the Whitebeards
are trying to get to the scaffold
but the Navy stands in their
way. The battle is heating up!
I'm sorry, "Red-Haired."
I will not hold back my power.
That's...
..."Hawk-Eye!"
Now, I wonder if fate...
...will end the life of the child
of the next generation here.
Or, if it will save him
from this Black Sword!
"The Great Swordsman Mihawk! Luffy Comes
Under the Attack of the Black Sword!"
I don't have time to face such a strong guy.
I'm here to save Ace!
Second Gear!
Heehaw!
Death Wink!
Galaxy Wink!
That's it, Straw boy.
Just focus on advancing.
We'll handle the rest!
--We'll get this guy!
--Heehaw!
"Hawk-Eye," do you remember us?!
We're the guys who challenged you once!
But now we're powered up as New Kamas!
I don't remember the face of every worm.
Great! Just gotta keep running and...
You are in range.
Ow... Ouch! I got cut!
Only Ace-san's brother could avoid
getting a fatal wound like that.
"First Son of the Sea" Jimbei!
I won't let you so much
as touch Luffy-kun again!
Even if it means death!
Why are you doing this?
I want to rescue Ace-san!
For one reason, to save our sea!
It is too late to stop this war
now but we still have hope.
Namely, Luffy-kun over there.
I understand. But I still don't
know what fate has in store.
Therefore, I need you to step back.
Fish-Man Karate!
Arabesque Brick Fist!
Sharkskin Palm Thrust!
Shark Brick Fist!
He's really strong as I thought.
"Hawk-Eye" is in the sky!
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Bazoo...!
That was close! If I had reached
out, my arms would've been severed!
You could be level-headed.
He sliced the mountain of ice
with just the swing of a sword!
S-So this is what the world's
strongest swordsman can do!
How strong is he?!
Straw Hat's dead because he's the target now!
The blocks of ice are falling on us!
Stealthy footsteps oily feet.
Ready, guys?
Let's get the "Make Captain Buggy a Star
in Front of Everyone" plan in action!
I know that they're broadcasting
the war to the whole world.
There must be a Video
Transponder Snail somewhere.
Find it!
Yeah!
"Find it?" "Yeah?" I don't think
that things are that simple.
Team up? Me and you?
Yes. The reign of outdated pirates
like Whitebeard will end soon.
And the new era will be our era
where power conquers everything.
Don't you wanna get a piece of it?
Not bad, is it?
Your title has been stripped away but...
...when you get down to it,
we're both Warlords, aren't we?
You better stop looking at
me as if I'm on par with you.
You should be pledging
to work under me instead.
I thought that you became a better person
in hell--Impel Down, the great prison!
If so, then I wouldn't be here now.
Sables!
Get lost, Flamingo shit!
I thought that you could be reasoned with.
If you don't fight the Navy, it's easy!
We can breeze through!
B-Breeze through! Breeze...!
Captain Buggy!
He got caught up in the whirlwind
of someone else's fight!
You're not gonna move aside
at any cost, Hancock?
Of course not! I won't let
you hurt my beloved husband!
Husband?
Yes, my husband!
After the wedding, we will go on a honeymoon!
It's a sweet sweet honeymoon
with Luffy my love!
But what if...
It's about time to eat.
But the food storage is empty.
There are a lot of things
that we can catch and eat!
My honey! I wanna eat your homemade dishes!
Okay! If you want it... Could
you give me a little time?
If things go like that,
I'll have to make tons of dishes
that could satisfy Luffy's
appetite all by myself!
Snake Princess-sama! Let us make it for you!
Luffy wants to eat my homemade
dishes! Keep your hands away!
Honey! Isn't it ready yet?
--It's coming!
--How admirable!
I'm ready for any trouble.
Because I'm... I'm...
...his wife!
"Wife?"
I don't know if she wants to fight or not.
I'll get Straw Hat!
I told you, you outrageous fool, that
I won't let you pass through here!
Perfume Femur!
Hancock! You...!
What are you gonna do now?!
You're getting farther from your brother!
Damn!
So this is it after all.
Breeze through! Breeze! Breeze!
His fighting capability has improved
a bit but I've already seen it all.
I won't miss it again from this distance!
Don't mind me! Just breezing through!
Gum-Gum...
Oh, you save...
...Jet Human Shield!
You! What're you doing?! Straw Hat!
What?! I'm not the one who cut you!
Plus you just said "Don't mind
me! I'm here to save you!"
How deluded is your hearing?
--Gum-Gum Human Shield!
--Stop it!
I can't take it! You must be "Hawk-Eye!"
The Special Muggy Ball! Blow away!
Here's a joke!
How is the Muggy Ball useful
for tunnel construction?
And the answer is?
Say it together, everyone! Because it goes...
BOOM!
Great, Buggy!
--Yeah, red nose!
--That was a good one!
Thank you, Buggy! I'll
never forget about you!
It's far from over!
Vista, Pops said that we
can't let Ace's brother die!
Back him up!
I got it! Count on me!
5th division commander of the
Whitebeards - Flower Sword Vista!
Nice to meet you, "Hawk-Eye" Mihawk.
You've heard of me?
Everybody knows you.
That was close! Who is that old guy?
It's not because of his power or skills!
Whatever! Thank you!
He seems to rally all those
around him to his side!
Stay at it! Straw boy!
He made it through fine.
Luffy! Save your brother!
Outta my way!
Among all people on the sea,
he has the most formidable ability!
Ace!
S-Straw Hat! I'll get even with you!
You're great, Captain Buggy!
You pretended that you were beaten by
"Hawk-Eye" but shrewdly executed the plan!
What do you mean?
Don't play dumb, Captain Buggy!
Video Transponder Snail?!
Y-Yeah, that's right!
A hero who can change the world is someone
who can open his own way to
the future by his own hands!
I'll follow you to the end, Captain Buggy!
Shh...
Yeah!
Now, the important part begins here.
How optimistic can you be?
As time ticks down toward the execution,
shocking truths have been
revealed one after another.
From the great, iron-tight prison Impel Down,
surprisingly more than 200 people had escaped
and those same notorious prisoners
have been caught up in the war.
The expanse of the battlefield
is an unearthly site.
It's certainly the showdown at the
summit that will change history!
People all over the world can do nothing...
...but follow the war that
will change their future
that seems so changeable now.
Fleet Admiral, we are all set.
Those at the bay area, too?
Yes, everything.
Huh?
They're getting ready for the execution.
Those bastards!
What are they gonna do to
Ace? It's not time yet!
Will it begin already?!
That's impossible! It's
before the announced time!
Cut the connection of the Video
Transponder Snail right away!
We the Navy and the World Government
must win this war in the
name of absolute justice!
No matter what it takes.
But it's too much to see,
for this naive world.
We don't have to show them the horrific
images that will unfold here soon.
Pops...
Hurry up!
They're really gonna
execute Ace ahead of time!
Ace!
The news that will go around
the world afterwards...
...should be of our victory and only that!
Our ships!
Look at the bay head! There's something!
They're not our buddies!
The Navy soldiers must've
gotten around the ice wall!
They still have soldiers
who can destroy big ships?
That's...!
Wh-What are they?!
So that's the Government's
human weapon that I heard of.
The bear guy from the Sabaody!
There're so many of them!
K-Kuma?
An hour and a half since the war began,
the Navy makes a big move!
The tide of the war changes
its course quickly and
flows into its final stage!
Alright, guys! I'm getting tired of waiting!
It's showtime!
The Whitebeard Pirates and the Navy
seem to have fallen into
a stalemate as neither
force can manage to get the upper hand.
But then an army of human weapons that
look like Bartholomew Kuma appears,
and the Whitebeard Pirates and Luffy
are under attack from both sides.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Extermination Strategy in Action!
The Power of the Pacifistas!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!