Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
What's the matter, Usopp?
The money... The money is gone!
Whaaat?!
Ahh! Over there!
Thanks for the money!
Hold it!
We did it!
The Franky Family...
Those bags... They're ours...!
Money! Money!
"Galley-La Company! A Grand Sight, Dock #1!"
Hold it, Paulie!
Today, I'm not
gonna let you get away!
I'm saying, wait a bit longer!
Who's that?
That's Paulie.
He's being chased by debt collectors again.
--Give us our 200 million Berries back!
--Sorry, mister! Thanks for giving us the money!
--Hey!
--Goodbye!
Did you give them the money?!
Why would I do that?! They stole it!
What?!
Pay back the money!
Like I said, I don't have money today.
That's not gonna cut it!
They're really persistent!
Hm? This is perfect! I see Yagara bulls!
Rope... Action!
--Ahhh!
--He's one of the shipwrights at Galley-La!
Sorry, but I'd like to borrow
one of your Yagaras for a bit!
Round Turn!
Dammit! He got away again!
Well then, everyone, take care!
Let's run together again!
Dammit!
Seriously... you came at just the right time!
What a relief! He's one of
your shipwrights, right?
That's right.
Hey! Thanks!
That money belongs to us!
What? Money?
Oh, this...
Hello...! Hm? Hey!
Come back here!
That son of a bitch!
I'm gonna catch him--! Huh?
I'll go.
What? A... A pigeon?
This must be a guy's room.
At first glance, it looks tidy, but...
The floorboards have to be replaced, too.
Hey, what're you doing?
Hm?
Don't worry. I'll put it back once
I check beneath the floorboards.
--Oh, my...
--Hm?
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow! Hey, hey, let me go!
What the hell are you doing?!
I won't run! I'm saying I got it, aren't I?!
Let go of my ear!
Here I was lucky enough to
find a lot of money and now...!
You'll regret this, Lucci!
Don't pay back your debts with
someone else's money, you fool!
I found this money!
You're still saying that?! Coo coo!
It just happened to be on
the Yagara that I borrowed!
They're back.
Well, I'm happy for you, Usopp!
You talk like it was someone else's problem!
It's our 200 million Berries!
That's right! Why the hell weren't
you the first one to go get it back?!
But that pigeon said he'd go.
Well... I'm sorry.
Please let us take care of our idiot coworker,
as if you guys were to capture him,
it would create bitter feelings.
Well, please excuse him. Consider it good that
the money wasn't stolen by the Franky Family.
Hmm... That's true, but...
Yeah, that's true, that's true.
Say... who were those
weird-looking guys earlier?
The Franky Family is a group
of ship demolition workers.
Demolition workers? They didn't look
like such decent craftsmen, though.
Right. They're also bounty hunters on the side.
Every time they find pirates coming
through this city, they cause quarrels.
They're a public nuisance.
If they crush the pirates who come to our town,
they can take their ship, too, right?
They demolish the ship
and sell the useable lumber.
That's how their business works.
How bad-natured...! Are they trying to
completely wipe the pirate groups out?
Well, if you become their victims,
not even your bones will remain.
But they didn't look that strong.
They're just underlings.
Whatever you do, don't underestimate the
family's boss, Franky, who's behind them.
Dammit! We were a little too late!
Hey! Are you okay?!
Yeah... That was close.
Hey! Where are the Straw Hats?!
Th-They're probably still at Dock #1.
We brought him over, Iceberg-san.
You're doing it again! You're hurting my ear!
Thanks, Lucci.
We're sorry that that idiot caused you trouble.
Ahh! He spoke again!
Coo coo!
Ow!
Now, apologize to them, Paulie!
That pigeon is doing all the talking!
It's as if he's speaking for that man with a hat.
In any case, I'm glad we got the money back.
Hey, you're the owner of the money?
I picked it up for you.
Oh, thanks!
If you wanna thank me, then give me 10%.
Sorry, mister.
This guy racked up a gambling debt,
so he's greedy and has no manners.
So, why the heck are you talking?!
You bastard! You're really
running your mouth, Lucci!
I won't take it anymore!
Rope Action!
Coo coo!
Bowline Knot!
Punishment...
Ahh...
Wait! Oh, no! He's serious!
...Pole-and-Line Fishing!
I-Is he okay?
Well... it's nothing new.
Whoa! L-L-Look at that!
He's parried that impact with just one arm!
His fingers are sinking into the ground.
Wh-What the heck kind of fingers does he have?
What's with the shipwrights working here?
Hey! You, with the goggles!
Hm?
Hey, think about it carefully.
The one who mocked or
provoked you was that pigeon!
That's fine! The one who hit me was Lucci!
The pigeon can't hit you himself,
so he had that guy hit you!
Hey, pigeon!
If you wanna fight, fight yourself!
Say something!
Coo coo!
Oh? You wanna fight? Bring it on, you bastard!
Stop it, Paulie.
Coo coo. Well, sorry for the fuss.
I'm Rob L... No, I mean, Hattori the pigeon.
And this is Rob Lucci. He works here.
Nice to meet you. Coo coo!
Oh? He almost introduced
himself as if he were human!
A-ha! Yeah, I got it!
That's ventriloquism, isn't it?!
Whoa! Seriously?! Then it
was you who was complaining!
You're really, really good! I didn't notice!
Stop it. It's no big deal. Coo coo.
He's a weirdo who can't talk to people properly.
Wait a sec! What's with that woman?!
Wh-What?
You're shameless!
Huh?
You're showing your legs too much!
This is a workplace for men!
Look how you're dressed!
Now, Paulie, calm down.
You, too, Kalifa!
You haven't learned your lesson and are
wearing such outrageous clothes again!
How many times do I have to tell you?!
Wear pants! Long pants!
--What the heck...?
--Long pants...?
He's a weirdo, too!
Well, that's it. Let's open the
door and go inside already.
At any rate, what a huge door!
And this requires manual operation?
Can those two weirdos open it by themselves?
Whoa! It's moving!
Well... each dock has only
five shipwright foremen.
They may not look like it, but their
skills made them foremen at Dock #1.
Kaku, who we talked about earlier,
is one of them, too.
This is a world where craftsmen's
skills are all that matters.
Even if their personalities are weird,
don't worry about it.
Yeah, they're weird.
Ah, the door's started opening.
Don't let the money leave your hands.
I don't think we have thieves inside, but...
Well, it was also my fault earlier,
and it caused you trouble, too.
--Hey, Luffy!
--Huh?
Make sure you guard me good!
Okay, got it. Leave it to me!
--I'm worried.
--Leave it to me!
This Dock #1 comprises the main
force of the Galley-La Company,
and it undertakes the most difficult work.
Here, come inside.
Wow!
Whoooa!
Whoooa! Huge!
A shipyard has a tremendous
impact when seen up close!
--Yeah!
--True!
Oh? They're building a
huge galleon! Whose is that?
It's full of craftsmen.
Now, this way.
Oh, it's Iceberg-san!
Hey! Boss is here!
Good morning, Iceberg-san!
Good morning!
Boss! Could you take a look at
how the outer panels turned out?
Sure! I'll come by later!
Good day, Iceberg-san!
Well... Hello, are things going well?
Yes, sir! They're going pretty well!
Whoa! Ice pops is quite popular.
Of course he is. In this city,
skills are all that matters.
On this island, shipbuilding was
well-developed from the start,
and seven shipbuilding companies
were competing with each other.
Meanwhile, he attracted craftsmen
with his genius shipbuilding skills.
Then he put those seven companies together
to form a company five years ago.
And that's this Galley-La Company.
His passion and skills in
shipbuilding have never changed,
and the craftsmen won't forget
their respect towards him.
And, because the craftsmen
are proud of their skills,
they never give in to pirates or authority.
This is that kind of place.
Hm?
Hey, pops. I heard that
you're a topnotch shipwright.
Do you wanna be a pirate with me?
What the hell are you saying,
you son of a bitch?!
H-How insolent!
Now, now... He's always like that.
Sorry about that.
Well... you guys don't even
have a single shipwright?
That's right. We came to this island
in order to have our ship repaired
and to find a new crew member.
It's true that we have tons of shipwrights,
but I wonder if anyone would
want to go on board a pirate ship.
If you find someone who wants to
go with you, you can headhunt him.
Really?! You're generous!
Can't I ask you to join us, pops?
Well... I can't. I'm the mayor.
Who cares?!
By the way, is the woman named
Nico Robin really on board your ship?
Yeah, she is. She's really smart.
What? Is something matter with Robin?
No...
Hey, pops, is it okay to go
closer and see that ship?
Sure, that's fine.
Thanks!
In any case, it's really amazing!
Keep that steady! Don't rush! Go slowly!
If we could install a cannon like that,
the Merry would also be... Hm?
Whoa! A demi-culverin!
How cool! It's so long...! And shining!
I wanna fire something like that, one time!
This is a good chance.
It looks like it's made of copper.
That must be expensive!
I wonder if they'd let me try firing it.
Oh, wait. We've now got 300 million Berries.
We should be able to buy
one or more cannons like that!
Hm?
Wasn't there someone there?
Where did Robin go?
It's this way.
Hm? This smell is...
I knew it!
Hmm... At any rate, who the heck was that
masked man who was with Robin-chan?
Was that Chopper after all?
Sanji!
Hm?
Chopper?
Hm? Kaku...
--Where have you been?
--An assessment.
Ah! You're the guy from earlier!
So you checked our ship?
Yeah, I did.
So you were here, Iceberg-san.
I know the situation. How was it?
Well...
Luffy! Come down now!
Okay! I'll be right down!
What?! Is that true?!
If you're lying, you'll pay for it!
I never lie on the job.
Hm? Where's Usopp?
He was wandering about over
there up until just a moment ago.
Hey, you guys! Don't these bags belong to you?
Ahh! They're the bags Usopp was carrying!
Yeah, they're ours.
Thanks!
Geez... Where did Usopp go...
leaving our precious money alone?!
--Money?
--Yeah. Those bags hold 200 million Berries.
200 million Berries?
No way. See ya!
There's no way...
So how much does it look like it'll cost?
We can pay as much as you like!
We've got tons of money!
If possible, I'd like her to be stronger,
have more cannons, and be faster!
Can you also add pretty
decorations on the outer panels?
Can you renovate inside as well?
Also, I want a bronze statue!
I want it to be as huge as possible!
Well, hold on a sec...
You've been having some
tremendous journeys, haven't you?
Oh, yeah! We flew in the sky, and fell as well.
We climbed a mountain and got skewered.
We've gone through quite a bit!
So we'd like to have her fixed good!
I'm not lying, you know.
I believe it.
Hm?
Her scars from battle are too deep.
Do you mean it'll take
quite a long time to fix her?
No...
Frankly speaking, your ship...
...can no longer be fixed, even with our skills.
Is her keel damaged or something?
Yeah, it's taken a lot of damage.
Oh, no...
But we've been traveling
just fine up until today!
Let's suppose that we did
what we could anyway.
The probability of her
reaching the next island is...
...zero.
Merry... Can you really not...
...sail anymore?
A piece of a dream that we started grasping
Chasing after something constant
We send our aspirations sailing into the sky
Even when we're exhausted
We have a compass that can
search for something constant
Say, do you think we can keep it forever?
At the end of the dream
that we will reach someday
We want to be adults as we
are now as much as possible
We pray to this endless sky that we look up at
Eternally... Eternally...
Wild fantasies from our childhood
We trace unforgettable memories
And try to keep the embers
burning that still consume us
To this familiar sunny sky
Together we entrust our feelings
We go beyond the changing time
Eternally... Eternally...
Hey, Merry... Can you really not sail anymore?
Just give up. The damage is too serious.
--Oh, no...
--All your ship can do is wait for her end.
--That can't be true...
--I can't believe that! We have this much money!
The 200 million Berries are gone!
Hey, Usopp is gone, too!
What? Don't tell me...
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Pirate Abduction Incident and a Pirate
Ship That Can Only Await Her End"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!