Edited at https://subtitletools.com
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
Everytime we overcome something,
norikoeru tabi
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy,
a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law and have come to Dressrosa.
Luffy entered a fighting competition
- in which a winner will
get the Flare-Flare Fruit as the
prize - and won the first round.
And Rebecca, the gladiator
girl Luffy supports,
is fighting hard in the last match of the first round.
"A Big Surprise!
A True Identity of the Toy Soldier!"
L-L-L-L....
Luffy-senpai!
L-L-Luffy-senpai!
Hey! You must be Bartolomeo-kun.
You were pretty impressive in the Block B match!
Yes, I am, Luffy-senpai!
Y-Y-You know my name?!
Of course, I do!
Let's wish each other good luck in the finals!
I have no chance!
I'm just a guy who set out to the sea
wanting to be like you!
Let's see...
Which way was it to the
place to watch the fight?
Oh, that way!
Luffy-senpai!
Whoa-whoa, people keep
falling one after another.
Oh, grandpa!
Brother!
It stinks!
Hi, Boo.
Where are we?
A stack of toys and trash?
What is this place, brother?
How do we know?
The next one will fall there.
Get out of his way!
I can't believe there is such a huge
junkyard underneath the kingdom.
Sorry if I'm wrong.
But I have the slight suspicion that...
...you're...
I mean, you, sir, are...
...King Riku-sama, aren't you?
--King Riku?!
--No way!
He's King Riku?! That's absurd!
I thought he was dead.
I heard the former king of Dressrosa...
...resorted to unbelievable
violence and got killed!
Since I'm deep underground now,
I no longer need to disguise myself.
You're right.
But don't call me "King" anymore,
Captain Tank!
THE FORMER KING OF DRESSROSA
He's King Riku!
RIKU DOLDO III
(REBECCA'S GRANDFATHER)
I can't believe he's alive!
King Riku-sama!
I'm so happy to see you again!
I'm just another old man now.
Just a sinful old man who can't
even save his own granddaughter.
It's been a while!
I am now...
...Doflamingo's...
Don't say it!
I know.
You're watching over Viola.
How could I disbelieve
a dutiful man like you?
It must've been hard for you.
It's nothing compared with
what you've gone through.
I can't believe it! You are King Riku!
Oh! You're the king of Prodence!
Long time no see!
You saved my kingdom when we
were in trouble many times!
I'm glad that you're alive!
Whoa-whoa!
Since you've been gone,
the countries around here lost balance
and there's been war after war!
I'm sick and tired of it.
Wait a minute, Elizabello!
Maybe you're tired of it but
each time somebody cries,
somebody else laughs!
Someone is agitating the countries to fight
and making millions!
By selling tons of weapons
to those countries at war!
Boy... That broker is named Joker.
And that's Doflamingo's alias.
But we don't know where they manufacture
those weapons or keep them.
Our country, the Kano Kingdom,
is at war now
and we're in trouble because the
enemy keeps getting weapons.
We entered the competition in the Colosseum
just to search for the weapons!
We Happo Navy's true purpose is
to break down the smuggling ring of weapons...
...by the request of the king
of the Kano Kingdom!
King Riku! Because you did such a foolish thing
and Doflamingo became king,
the neighboring countries are in trouble!
He's right, Elizabello-sama!
Yes, we were deeply indebted to
Dressrosa in the past
but there's no need to keep affection for
that man anymore!
The name "King Riku" is now...
Shut up, Dagama!
You don't know what really
happened 10 years ago -
the tragedy of that day!
So don't talk shit
about the king's personality!
Tank! It's okay!
It's too late to say anything!
King Riku-sama, I, too, was...
...a soldier of the army!
Me, too!
Me, too, King Riku-sama!
What the...
The toys are starting to move!
I thought they were all broken!
Dressrosa's former soldiers
and even the toys are bowing to him!
What's going on?
I thought all the people hated King Riku!
Yeah. Since they have this wide area here,
I think there is...
...something more underground.
I see.
Keep looking.
Clank.
Brother!
What?! What?!
What is it this time?!
Enough with this annoying crap!
Whoever it is,
if you hurt Sai, I'll carry my anger
even towards your grandchildren!
What's this sticky thing?!
Sai!
Brother!
What is this?! What's going on?!
Stay away! Hey, stop!
Who are you?! Hey!
Stop it!
Hey, hey!
It's done so you can go now.
Do not harm any human
and follow any orders from the Family.
Those are the rules.
If you go straight out that door,
there is a factory and a trade port.
Go.
No talking! Just work hard!
Since the contenders were all so powerful,
they're not gonna break easily!
What's going on?!
I can't move my own body as I want!
I can only can move as he directed me!
What the hell is happening to me?!
THE FLOWER FIELD
THE KING RIKU ARMY HEADQUARTERS
A long time ago, the ancestors of the Tontatta Tribe
kept going out to the sea...
...looking for natural resources
that their land lacked.
But Big Humans kept discovering them,
and they were facing extinction.
I found them! The Little People!
Catch them!
But one day, the king of Dressrosa,
one of the neighboring countries,
offered them a deal...
...that he would provide
resources and guarantee
their safety in exchange
for a little bit of work.
That king's name was Don Quixote!
That led to the worst times of
the Tontatta Tribe's history...
...which continued on until 900 years ago.
The slave era!
There are some surviving manuscripts that
describe how cruel the royal family was.
They were literally like devils!
Our ancestors were forced to work and work
deep underground unnoticed by anyone
while the Big Humans were
living lavishly on the wealth
provided by the work of the Tontatta Tribe.
Records from the subsequent Hundred Year Void
are lost
but 800 years ago,
a new king took the throne of Dressrosa.
It was King Riku!
When King Riku heard...
...that the Little People were being treated
as less than humans for centuries,
he cried and apologized profusely.
Then, the new king devised
a form of compensation for them!
He told them they
could simply take anything
that they needed from the country.
They didn't have to work.
--Oh, my bag is gone!
--So is my watch!
I can't find my wallet!
Oh no! My jacket got stolen, too!
My Shusui that was here a minute ago!
They stole from everybody.
It was fairies who took your stuff.
What are you talking about?!
Fairies are fairies.
All you can do is laugh it off and let it go.
How can I laugh it off?!
Those invisible fairies are
the guardian deities of
Dressrosa from ancient times.
We have to turn a blind
eye to whatever they do.
--Well, if fairies did it...
--We should just forget about it!
The king called it the work of fairies and
calmed his citizens down by laughing it off
and he established successfully the
legend of fairies in this country.
How cool! The first King Riku!
The country was governed by
the gentle Riku Family...
...unstintingly supporting its neighboring countries
when they were in trouble.
I can't say the country was wealthy
but it became renowned
and the people were always smiling.
Our ancestors paid tribute
to King Riku's kindness
and they voluntarily filled the country with
lots of greens and beautiful flowers.
That's how we Tontatta Kingdom and...
...the successive Riku Family
deepened our bonds over 800 years.
But now, after 900 years,
Doflamingo, the descendent of
the Don Quixote Family, has returned
and he is trying
to repeat that horrible history!
My daughter - Mancherie
and 500 of our people already
fell victim to that man.
We can't let him repeat history!
No, we can't!
So we fight!
That's right!
The return of the Don Quixote line is
doing Dressrosa and Tontatta...
...no good -- and much harm!
We fight with the heroes!
Usoland will help us tremendously!
Usoland! Usoland! Usoland! Usoland!
Th-That's exactly what I was thinking!
That's our hero!
King Riku is a good guy!
He has been so nice
even to these worm-like people!
What did you just call us?!
I meant it in a good way.
It's okay, then!
Rot in hell, granddaughter of King Riku!
Drop dead, Rebecca!
Commander-san.
That gladiator girl who is fighting
in the Colosseum is...
...being called King Riku's granddaughter
and getting insulted.
It seems like the people
of this country hate King Riku.
That's what I thought!
Usoland! Usoland!
10 years ago,
there was an incident in which
King Riku lost the trust
of all his citizens overnight.
The king was trying to protect
his country until the end but...
The corrupted King Riku's family!
Screw you, Rebecca!
Cut her to pieces!
The people don't know
what really happened that day.
I'm sorry!
I couldn't protect your mother!
Doflamingo tried to kill every
member of the King Riku Family
but I took Rebecca who has
King Riku's blood in her veins
and ran away for a very long time.
But she got caught in the end
and they keep her
on public display at the Colosseum.
If I can regain the people's trust in King Riku
and save Rebecca's life,
I wouldn't mind sacrificing my life
anytime, anywhere!
I put everything on the line for this war!
Who are you?
I couldn't protect Rebecca's mother.
Mother-sama...
Mother-sama!
Mother-sama!!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry!!
I'll never forget what happened that day.
She doesn't remember me
after I turned into a toy but...
Soldier-san is a brave man
He will always be by your side
...I'm...
...Rebecca's real father!