Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Inherited will...
The tide of the times...
People's dreams...
These things cannot be stopped.
As long as people seek
the answer of freedom,
these things will never cease to be!
I only believe in the future--
I don't care if anyone laughs
That racing passion makes you shine
It's too bright, but I want to gaze at it
I sense "aesthetics" somewhere
I'm really, really stuck on you
I follow, follow in the footsteps
of a dream that resembles no one
Until I dramatically get it
Believe In Wonderland!
I'm going to catch, catch the shape
of a dream no one can see
I'm going to go with you,
so passionate feelings
I don't really need
everything to add up
Rather than run-of-the-mill daily life,
run for paradise instead
Believe In Wonderland!
"Rainbase"                 "Alubarna"
"Yuba" "Erumalu" "Nanohana" "Katorea"
"Spiders Café"
Three years have passed
since a single drop of rain fell
in the kingdom of oases.
The scorching land was now
engulfed in wails of grief,
along with tremendous upheaval.
Luffy and the others had been
caught in a trap inside Raindinners,
but as a result of Sanji's actions,
they were finally able to escape.
Marine Captain Smoker, having
been saved by Luffy and company,
then allowed them to get away.
Will Alabasta fall?
Or will it find true peace?
Moment by moment, the hourglass
of fate marks the final hour.
"Merciless Mortal Combat!
Luffy vs. Crocodile"
I see them!
After them!
Captain, aren't you going after them?
No. I'm too tired.
You're too tired?
Hey...
Sir!
It's no use going after those guys.
Tell them to stop.
And have everyone assemble here.
Contact HQ, too.
Tell them to have all
military vessels in the vicinity
of the Kingdom of Alabasta
gather here, to this land.
You're calling for reinforcements?
But Captain, I'm not sure
our superiors will be willing
to move those ships against
such a small number of pirates.
When did I ask for the
opinions of our superiors?
Er, y-yes, sir! Right away!
Hey! Come back! Come back here!
Hurry!
Mm-hmm, this way.
The scent of Nami's perfume
is getting stronger.
Hey, we're not, by any chance,
just going to run all the way
to Alubarna like this, right?!
That's right, Lashes!
Where has Lashes gone?!
Now that you mention it,
this town has a stable or something!
Let's get horses!
But the marines are in town.
Not to worry. Look in front of you.
Hey, guys!
A crab?!
Chopper!
That's a Moving Crab!
Looks yummy!
Awesome! Awesome! Awesome!
That's awesome!
Hop on board!
We get to ride it?! Woo-hoo!
The pleasure's mine!
Its face looks kind of iffy, doesn't it?
And you've got yet another
amazing thing in tow, huh?
He's Lashes's friend.
Lashes was born in this town,
and has lots of friends in the area.
He is kind of pervy, though.
Amazing! Moving Crabs are
always submerged under the sand,
so they're very nearly phantom crabs!
This guy's pretty fast, isn't he?
Guys, hang on tight!
All right, let's go! We're off!
What?!
Stop, Chopper!
It's him! Why, you...!
Hey! Luffy!
That idiot!
Luffy-san!
You guys go on ahead!
I can handle this myself!
Make sure you deliver Vivi back
to her home! Make sure, now!
Make sure, now.
That idiot...
Hey!
Go, Chopper! Keep going, to Alubarna!
G-Got it.
We're off!
Hold on...!
Hey Zoro, are we leaving
him behind?! Hey, that's cold!
That's cold of you!
From now on, you've got
to protect me, got it?!
Where do you get off always doing this?!
Luffy-san!
It's all right, Vivi! He'll be fine!
I feel sorry for the other guys.
After all, there isn't a single person
that Luffy has gone after before,
who has come out all right.
Listen to me, Vivi.
He will keep Crocodile under control.
The moment that the
rebel army started running,
the time limit on this land was set.
Once the royal army
and the rebel army meet,
this land, the Kingdom
of Alabasta, will be gone.
If you are the one and only
hope for preventing that,
then you have to survive, no matter what.
No matter what might happen
to any of us here, from now on!
B-But...
Vivi-chan, this is a fight that you started.
You're the one who ran out
of this land years ago,
and challenged this unknown
organization to battle.
However...
...don't go thinking that
you're fighting alone anymore.
V-V-Vivi! Don't you wor-- wor--
don't worry! I'm g-gonna...
Luffy-san!
We'll be waiting for
you in Alubarna, okay?!
Yeah!
Princess Vivi got away from us, huh?
Either way, the Agents are
scheduled to gather in Alubarna.
Contact them at once.
You've taken your nonsense
a little too far, Straw Hat Luffy.
She tries, you see,
to help everyone she sees,
despite how weak she might be.
She can't bear to abandon anything,
so she's always in pain.
She doesn't think that anyone
needs to die in this revolt.
Nobody needs to die?
There are many maudlin,
peace-loving fools like that.
That's because they don't
know what a real fight is.
You think so too, don't you?
Yeah.
But as long as you're around,
she's going to go at you, until she dies.
So I'm going to put you down, right here!
That's worse than nonsense.
You're the unsalvageable fool here.
This is a good example.
You get close to someone,
and then die because of it.
I've forsaken tons of people like that.
Then, you're the fool, aren't you?
What's so funny?
You want to die, too, Nico Robin?
If you feel like it, go right ahead.
Besides, didn't you promise
not to call me by that name?
Where are you going?
I'm going on ahead to Alubarna.
I can't figure that woman out.
I'll give you three minutes.
I don't have time...
...to mess with you any longer than that.
I'll give you three minutes.
I don't have time to mess
with you any longer than that.
You don't mind, do you?
No, that's fine.
Gum-Gum...
...Pistol!!
...Stamp!!
I should warn you, Straw Hat Luffy,
that no matter how hard you try,
there is no way that you'll ever beat me.
Gum-Gum Gatling!!
Listen here, Straw Hat Luffy,
you can continue these mosquito-like
attacks of yours forever,
but you will never--
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!!
Why, you... you... you...!
Did that smash you?!
You sand gator!
I told you, that won't work.
You bastard...!
No matter how hard a
rubber man like you might try,
there is no way...
...you'll ever peat--
"Peat"? What was that
you were just trying to say?
I think that is just about
enough fun and games,
Straw Hat Luffy.
I've been taking this
seriously the whole time!
But he's got me.
I can't slug him at all like this.
He's too dry and grainy.
There's a difference in the level
of pirate that you and I are.
Desert Spada!!
Nicely judged.
If you'd taken that, it would have
gotten more than an "ow" from you.
What?! The desert's been split!
Depending on one's training and
how they're used, Devil Fruit abilities
can become a means of
fighting as powerful as any.
I'm not like you other fools, who are
only preoccupied with your abilities.
You can regret defying me
as much as you want, now.
Desert Girasole!!
What?! What?! What?! What?!
The sand! It's being
sucked into the ground!
You don't know about quicksand?
It makes for a handy desert coffin,
with no need for a tombstone.
The sand is drawn down
into underground waterways.
I am able to detect where those are.
No one in the world can stand up
to me when fighting in the desert.
I'm not about...
...to let myself be buried alive in sand!
You bastard!
Gum-Gum...
...Bazooka!!
If I can't slug you,
then how about I catch you?
Gum-Gum Finger Net!!
Can't you learn anything?
That won't work.
Gum-Gum...
...Whip!!
Are you planning to keep doing that?
Let go of me, you bastard!
Crescent Cutlass!!
M-My arm!
My arm...! My arm...!
It's turned into a mummy!
My arm has become a mummy!
Because of the sand.
The hydration in your arm
has been sucked out.
I could go on wringing the water
out of your whole body like that,
until you shrivel up and die.
Such is the essence of the desert.
Y-You've gotta be kidding me!
I know! Water!
That was worthless.
Nothing worthless about it!
The dried-up old man
in Yuba spent all night
preparing this water for me!
Luffy-kun, take this with you.
The old guy told me...
...Yuba wasn't going to give in to the sand.
Gum-Gum...
Are you still planning to do something?
...Munch-Munch!!
Don't go pulling ridiculous crap like that!
Die. You, along with the
indomitable land of Yuba.
Your three minutes are up.
Like I said at the start,
I don't have time to hang
around with you any longer.
Sables!!
The sand is nice and dry.
It's a sandstorm! I can see a
sandstorm in the sky to the south!
Take shelter!
Wait, the sandstorm isn't coming this way!
It's headed to the south!
Captain Smoker, over there!
Vivi, what's wrong?
There's a sandstorm over toward Rainbase!
It's him.
Luffy...
Listen here, Straw Hat Luffy.
The prevailing winds here
always blow from north to south.
If this baby sandstorm of mine
were to catch one of them
and grow as it headed south,
where do you think the
larger sandstorm will hit?
South, you say?
Yuba.
Why?!
Hey, you! What are you doing?! Stop it!
Look. Little by little,
it's starting to head south.
That dried-up old man
has nothing to do with this!
Why, you...! Stop it, you!
Stop, you bastard! Stop!
Give it up, it won't work.
That sandstorm will pick up strength,
and obtain wind speeds
that even I can't stop.
You've gotta be yanking me!
Yuba is finished.
Stop it! Right now! Stop--
Who do you think I am?
There are any number
of rookies like you,
who are nothing but talk,
Straw Hat Luffy,
here in the Grand Line.
I always wanted to talk about it
I couldn't even say half of it
I'm by your side, I glitter
every time we share a dream
The smile you gently gave me
was a very happy and kind one
Glory glory you're my shine
Because you're here, even
these tears turn to courage
I want to be strong,
I want to share with you
I'm sure I'll make it there
What?! The crab can't cross this river?!
He's a desert creature,
so he can't handle the water.
But it's still a crab. Do something!
Do something. Scissors-kun.
I know! Scissors loves dancing girls!
Will this do?
You're messing him up with this nonsense!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Dash For a Miracle!
Alabasta Animal Land"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!