Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between
the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good
time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave
the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Previously...
Boss Luffy and company entered
a festival's Great Portable Shrine Race,
with the prize being a sacred treasure
passed down in Grand Jipang.
Together with an amnesic Brook,
they enjoyed their time before the festival.
But, the night before the festival,
everyone's shrines were destroyed
by Hogback of Thriller Co.,
which is bent on having the sacred treasure.
It's all over!
We can't enter the race like this!
Our only choice is to drop out now...
If this was all meant to destroy
their portable shrine before the race...
...then ours is in danger too!
I remember.
Your memory is back?!
Yes.
I remember everything now.
Wh-What's with that get-up?
Where are you going?
I should not be here.
This is because...
...I'm actually a member of Thriller Company.
And so, with his memory returned,
Brook disappeared into the dark night alone.
"Feudal Era Side Story -
Defeat Thriller Company's Trap"
That was a great rampage tonight!
Perona-sama should be quite pleased.
Who're you?!
You have strayed from the path of humanity...
Though you aren't human to begin with.
I will punish you on Heaven's behalf!
Oww, oww...
There, that should do it.
Thanks...
The race is tomorrow,
but I let them destroy the portable shrine...
I'm a failure as a carpenter!
It's not your fault, Master Builder!
So it's Hogback's cronies who're to blame...
Brook...
Where do you suppose Brook went?
Would you like me to tell you?
Who're you?!
Just a city girl who's passing by.
How beautiful!
Again?!
That skeleton was indeed a
member of Thriller Company,
but he grew sick of its despicable
ways and left the organization.
But he may feel responsible for
the shrines that were destroyed today.
Boss Luffy...
"Thriller Company"
Pinwheel members...
I will make amends for how I have lived.
Wait, Boss!
Sheesh, he never thinks things through!
Brook!
Fool!
I don't like hurting!
Shut up!
I never imagined you were still alive!
Not after we hurt you so much
and sent you down the river
when you left the organization...
Why have you come to throw away
the life you managed to cling to?
There is no point in explaining!
You would never understand!
Add another weight!
Right! Another weight!
You're acting unsightly!
Enough! Finish him off!
Hold on! Time out! I don't want to die yet!
Wait, I'm already long dead...
But I don't want this!
Shut the hell up!
Brook!
Boss!
What's the big idea, leaving like that?
Come on! Let's go back!
Not so fast!
You're that policeman from earlier!
Move.
You guys piss me off, but I have
no business with you right now.
We can't quietly let an enemy leave,
not even if he's a public official!
Destroy him!
You're annoying the neighborhood, dammit!
Three-Sword Style! Tatsu-Maki!
Gum-Gum Billy Club!
Don't falter!
Overwhelm them with sheer numbers!
There's no end to 'em!
They're...
...gone!
Where they hell did they go?! Find them!
We're back!
My word...
Boss! Brook! Welcome back!
Welcome back!
You must be hungry!
Have some special Stamina Rice Balls!
Ooh! They look yum!
What are you all doing?
We're fixing our portable shrine!
You can't be serious...
The race is tomorrow, you know!
You'll never make it in time!
Not if we can help it!
Why? Why would you go to such lengths?!
Pride!
Turning tail and running
isn't our style at all!
Yes!
We're the exact same way!
Rolling Express!
I hear you're lacking raw materials!
Please use any pieces you want
from our broken portable shrine!
You're the Flying Fish Riders!
We brought ours too, so you can use it!
We're placing our spirit in your hands!
Really?!
Guys...!
Now I can build a super portable
shrine just like the one I imagined!
That's right!
Let's do it!
Looks like we're going to
need more food for supper!
I'll go and make a lot!
Sanji-kun! We're counting on you!
Nami-swan!
Just leave it to me!
What's the matter, Brook?
Don't just stand there, help!
But how can I ever have the face to?
Just come on!
Not the knees!
You're already one of the
shrine bearers, you know!
Do I have to spell it out for you?
He means you're our friend.
Friend...?
Thank you!
Hey, you! There are no free meals, boy!
Oh.
Oh! I'll play a song to liven things up!
Oh, I'm rarin' to go now!
Alright! Let's do it!
Yeah!
What is that?!
It's huge!
It's enormous!
None of the other entrants
even stand a chance!
What other entrants?
We destroyed everyone's shrines
and made them drop out of the race!
It won't be long now!
We only need to get this jumbo
portable shrine across the finish line
and the treasure's all ours!
Hold on, Cindry-chan! Why
are you in front of me?!
It's almost noon.
Let the victory parade begin.
Please wait!
The Pinwheel Eatery will
also be participating!
What?!
Thriller Company!
The treasure is ours!
You can do it, Pinwheel!
Bring it on, then!
The Great Portable Shrine Race for
the sacred treasure will now take place!
Thriller Company!
Pinwheel Eatery!
Both teams will battle it out!
Ready!
You're in the way!
I can't see!
This is no time to be foolin' around!
They've taken the lead!
My Flying Fish!
I'm borrowing this!
Thief!
This is too heavy, Master...
You feeble fools!
Now they'll catch up to us!
Stay calm!
The genius Hogback-sama's
portable shrine isn't on this low a level!
So long!
Huh?! What is that?!
Looks like it's time to
show off our true power, too!
Boss! Feed this cola to the shrine!
Okay!
Here?
Wh-Whoa!
Everyone get on the shrine!
Here we go!
Hey! That's against the rules!
Like you're one to talk!
Neither one is a portable shrine anymore...
We're getting nowhere like this!
Leave it to me!
Try this on for size!
That's a cannon!
Look out!
If that's how it's gonna be...!
Victory is ours now!
This can't be!
Look!
Support Paddle!
I can't talk!
Keep it as a pet.
Guys! Keep moving along the river!
It's a quicker route than on land!
Got it!
You're not going anywhere!
Get them!
They just keep coming...!
I thought this might happen!
You have a trick of your own?!
Drive right, now!
Talk and you'll bite your tongue off!
Shut up!
36 Pound Phoenix!
It's the Grand Shrine!
Boss! This is the last of the cola!
Alright!
What?!
This sucks!
They're not getting away!
Look! It's the goal!
Marry me!
Go!
This...
...is the giant portable shrine's...
...true form?
Monkey! Monkey!
What a huge spider!
I commend you for forcing my trump card!
However...!
This is the end!
Spider Sticky Net!
We're stuck!
Hey! Can't you do something?!
I do have one last trick up my sleeve...
...but I'm out of cola!
Cola?!
Onami-san! Down there!
This is the end!
Monkey! Monkey!
Boss!
Win!
Yeah!
Gaon Cannon!
Fire!
No way!
Th-This can't be!
Hold on!
Wait, where is Cindry-chan?!
When did she...?!
W-Wait! Let's discuss this!
You ruined the festival everyone
was looking forward to!
Now you're going to pay!
We are?!
And the winner is Pinwheel Eatery!
Congratulations!
Now, then...
The million Ryo-Berry prize!
I'm afraid I'm going to have to keep this.
Huh?!
Just look at the disastrous
state of this town!
You can't be serious...!
But...
As promised, the sacred treasure is yours!
Alright!
We did it!
I wonder what the sacred treasure is like!
It's been 100 years since
its last exhibition,
so this will be my first
time seeing it as well.
Okay!
This is the magical sacred treasure
passed down in Grand Jipang...
"Instructions for the Maiden Panties..."
"Make a wish with these panties on
and it will be granted forthwith."
"Limited to beautiful women only"?!
Wonderful!
Omao-san.
Do you think you could
put those panties on for me?
Yuck!
Huh? Where am I? Who am I?
You've lost your memory again?!
Brook-san!
After being sent flying away from
Sabaody Archipelago by Kuma,
Luffy lands on a unique island.
In the jungle, Luffy eats the
wrong mushrooms and collapse.
There, he is found by a group of beautiful
female warriors bearing snakes.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Landing! The All-Female Island,
Amazon Lily"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!