Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
jitto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
Make waves, jump from your sleep
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
arienai sekai wo iku nara
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
Being brazen, is it a crime?
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
Freedom is our only rule
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
It's not our way to worry
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
ttai one piece ichibannori
My dreaming heart is huge
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
dare mo oitekanaize--
We won’t left anyone behind
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
tto dekinai tomarenai
The sun of my heart will never set
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World, the
second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body
turned to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
On their way to the New World,
Luffy and his crew reached the Fish-Man
Island located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates  who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom...
...assisted by Vander Decken, who is after
Shirahoshi, are engaging in secret maneuvers.
The Straw Hats find themselves caught up in
the turmoil and involved in an all-out war.
Now, Hordy's merciless plot puts the
Fish-Man Island in unprecedented danger!
Everything will come to an end soon.
Whether it's Shirahoshi or the
Fish-Man Island or your friends!
A fool like you can't protect anything!
No.
I'll protect them all!
That's what I worked for those 2 years!
"A Massive Confused Fight! The Straw
Hats vs. The New Fish-Man Pirates!"
Protect them all? Don't make me laugh!
You've got such a big mouth,
haven't you, Straw Hat?
I can't believe he'd even harm Decken!
Shirahoshi! Get away!
Draw the Noah away from the island!
It's too late.
What did he mean by "too late"?
Wait a minute!
He just beat Decken, right?
What would happen to the Noah if
Decken dies or loses consciousness?
Decken's power would become ineffective!
And the Noah would fall...
...onto the island!
Why did you kick me?! It hurts!
Shut up or I'll kick your fat ass again!
Even Captain Decken wouldn't
kick me for no reason at all!
You damn Steamed Bun bastard! How dare you...
...bring Nami-san down with the wind blast!
This is my payback to you!
--This is for...
--Huh?
...the wind blast that Nami-san took!
Ouch!
Oh no!
Watch out for the wind blast, Nami-san!
A wind blast, again?! Please!
Keep your guard up! Look out!
Something came out from that stick earlier!
Black Ball!
--What is it this time?!
--Is she a magician?
No, don't call me a magician!
Call me a charmer!
Although it's not really a
charm. It's based on science!
Clouds?
Storm Cloud Rod!
Ouch!
Help me!
Stay away! I don't wanna
become a dried squid-ch!
--Damn that woman!
--Hey, Ikaros.
That guy in the black suit was overreacting
because that woman got hurt.
I think that woman may be
the Straw Hat's weak link.
Really?
I'll hold her legs and you
kill her with your spear!
I got it-much!
Well, if you don't wanna
get burned, leave me alone!
What?
I can't move my feet!
You're gonna become a dried squid-ch!
W-W-Wait a minute!
Why can't I move my feet?! Somebody!
Nami-san! Oh yeah!
Take this! The Squid Spear!
Could I look at your panties...
No!
Is he on their side?
Why don't you dry up?
Become a dried squid-ch!
Huh?
Hm? What's wrong-ch?
Suck all the fluid out of
his body and dry him up-ch!
Hey, Squid! What's up?
What's wrong? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Why?!
Excuse me.
I'm pretty dried up already.
What?!
I don't believe you-ch!
It's a long story. How I
became a dried-up skeleton.
I don't believe you-ch!
--No, believe me. It was over 50 years ago...
--Help me!
Hey hey, isn't there anybody
who is strong enough to fight?!
Huh?
Are you all right?
Who are you-ch?!
It's me!
--I don't know you-ch!
--What?! You don't know this super robot?!
Hm? You must be one of their officers, huh?
Then I bet you have backbone.
Though I'm a squid, I'm still
a Fish-Man! I have backbone!
Oh, he has a backbone
even though he's a squid!
Sympathy!
That's not what he meant.
Hey, Skeleton, get out of there already.
Huh? Why?
Your foot! Your foot!
What about my foot?
You're stepping on him!
Huh? What is he?! I couldn't
move because of him?!
Um... Who are you?
How did you like it?!
What?
Getting a head-butt to
the bottom of your foot!
--What?
--Huh?
It may take some time for
you to feel the pain!
What?!
He doesn't wanna admit
that  he got stepped on!
Sorry that I stepped on your face!
Don't say that!
This technique allows me to give you a
head-butt to the bottom of your foot!
It's called Super Sole Head-Butt!
He named it!
Where did you go, Coral
Head?! I'll bite you good!
No one can beat me in the
ground. I can move freely!
Daruma-san!
Don't make too many tunnels in the ground!
We're all gonna fall into them!
Yes!
Chopper! Did you finish it?
Come out this way!
What a fool! That guy is off his guard-dogon!
I'm gonna beat him up!
Hey, Chopper? Can't he hear me?
Get squashed and go to hell-zugan!
Usopp! Get down!
Horn Cannon Elf!
Nice, Chopper! Did you
connect all the tunnels?
Yes, it's nice and ready!
All right! Here we go!
Special Attack - Green Star!
Skull Bombgrass!
How did you like that?!
We fought a ground digger
once in Alabasta already!
Our experience gave us the upper hand!
Yeah!
Damn you coral monster!
Is this all your doing?
I'll show you my extraordinary power!
Speaking of power, I have
one up my sleeve, too.
I'm gonna bite your nose off!
Try it if you like!
Back me up, Chopper!
Hey, back me up!
Oh?
Chopper?
Now, it's my turn!
Damn you! You made me angry!
I won't forgive you even if you say sorry!
I'm gonna beat you up!
Great! That's how a swordsman should be!
You're strong!
--Help me...
--Are you okay? I'll treat you right away!
--Honey, stay with me!
--Daddy!
Treat him now!
Damn Hordy! He can't do
this to unarmed citizens!
Is the Princess okay?
I don't know...
But I'm sure she's still fighting for us!
Madam Sharley!
What's gonna happen to the island?!
Is it really gonna fall?!
That Straw Hat pirate guy will
save the island, won't he?
Won't he, Madam Sharley?!
--Let's pray.
--What?
All we can do now is pray for the
safety of the Princess and the others.
Pray that they will save the Fish-Man Island!
Go further! More!
She's desperate!
Stay away from the island!
Noah!
Shirahoshi!
If the Noah falls,  everything
will be destroyed!
--Oh no! She couldn't hear us!
--Don't go up!
Turn to the side! You have
to change your course!
They noticed!
Shirahoshi!
Shark Slicer!
Brother!
Ryuboshi!
Don't mess with my plan!
Brother! Stay with me!
Decken's power must have
become ineffective by now.
That's why I stabbed him.
I see!
If she just keeps going up, the
ship could fall onto the island!
Then, Yowahoshi's effort to draw
the ship away means nothing!
Brother-hoshi, let's catch up with Yowahoshi!
Alright!
Shirahoshi!
Yowahoshi!
You can't go any further!
The Fish-Man Island will be destroyed
along with all the islanders!
And Straw Hat,
I'll make sure that all
of your friends are dead!
Are you all right?
Shirahoshi!
Turn to the side!
Yowahoshi!
Stupid Mermaid!
That little shit!
--She heard you!
--She turned to the side!
How annoying!
You can't do that!
Wait!
Let go of me!
I won't let you go after her!
Damn you!
Noah! Come this way!
I can't hold on...
Noah! Come after me!
--Let's go!
--Yeah!
Damn you, Decken! Drop dead already!
Dammit.
Hordy that bastard, I won't forgive him!
Noah! I'm right here!
The ship's starting to go sideways!
Good! Keep going, Yowahoshi!
Shirahoshi!
Keep going!
I touched Hordy with my left hand.
You're my target! Don't forget it!
I'll drive you into the ground physically
and mentally, until you die!
Noah!
Shirahoshi! Keep going - a little bit more!
There is no point if it
doesn't fall onto the island!
I'll hunt you down... to the ends of hell!
I won't let you go!
Hordy!
A little more to go, Yowahoshi!
Decken!
I will... kill you!
I'll pass through by force!
You can't!
My axe! Hit Hordy!
Shark Slicer!
I will protect!
The Noah is falling!
Just in time!
The Fish-Man Island...
...is in danger!
No!
I win!
The Noah begins to fall again,
and Luffy tries to stop it
to save Fish-Man Island,
but underwater, he's at a
disadvantage as he battles Hordy,
and can't get the upper hand.
Furthermore, the last air
on the Noah's deck is lost,
making Luffy's demise eminent!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Luffy Loses the Fight?!
Hordy's Long-Awaited Revenge!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!