Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
We've left the established course
Right now, we're rowing straight toward
The borderline between the sky and the ocean
In the dark depths of the ocean,
adventure holds its breath
Don't you have a good time just imagining it?
Travel across the oceans of the world
Bellow a battle cry
Once your heart feels refreshed,
let the signal to set sail ring out
"That feeling" I get when embarking
Is something I hope to remember always
If I can, I won't be afraid of anything
With our pulses racing,
let's go on a trip now
Shy hearts engrave the rhythm of adventure
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Life is "Adventurous"
Be aware it's "Dangerous"
Who's gonna be "One of us"
And a trip goes on because
We da pirate of the "Mass"
To the West, To the East
Gotta find my way, Sail away
All the way to "One piece"!!
Stuff a dream into your empty chest
And spread your wings
If the wind blowing through
them dyes your heart
Let's press forward
Snatch up the treasure here and there
While laughing out loud
As we dash by like a noisy party
Make some waves...
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
It isn't night yet, but with this thick fog,
it's creepy how dark it is.
Yep! Don't let your guard down.
From the looks of it, we're already
caught in the infamous...
...Florian Triangle!
These seas are haunted!
♪ Yo ho ho ho ♪
--One appeared!
--♪ Yo ho ho ho ♪
It's a ghost ship!
♪ We're on our way... ♪
♪ ...to deliver Bink's booze ♪
I bet he's the treasure's guardian!
Let's go look for him.
H-Huh?
No!
You gave me quite a start!
How many decades have passed
since I saw people in the flesh?
Putting that aside...
...join my crew!
Yeah, okay.
Hey!
"The Joy of Seeing People!
The Gentleman Skeleton's True Identity!"
Hi! Hello, everyone! Good day to you.
I shall be imposing upon
you here on your vessel!
I am the dead and skeletonized Brook.
It's a pleasure to meet you!
Don't be stupid! And what the heck is he?!
My, my! They're harsh!
It's a skeleton!
Goodness, aren't you a lovely lady?
May I please see your panties?
Stop that, Harassment Skeleton!
Armed... and... ready!
"Evil Be Gone"
Tada!
You're fully decked out in anti-evil stuff!
S-Stupid skeleton! B-Beat it already!
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
H-Hey...
Wow, it's working! Usopp, that's amazing!
"Evil Be Gone"
You know it! This is my full
"Anti-Evil Spirit Arsenal."
An evil spirit?! Where? Where is it?
--It's you!
--What?!
Damn it! There's no way a skeleton
can walk, talk, and grow an afro!
This is a dream! It has to be a dream!
Really?!
Phew! It's just a dream...
Hello? Please wake up.
Good morning.
Shuddup!
Hey, Luffy! What's up with this guy?
Isn't he funny? I had him join our crew.
No, you didn't! I won't allow it!
Do you know why you went with him?!
It was to keep Luffy from
doing anything crazy!
We're ashamed of ourselves...
Now, don't get so worked up.
Come on inside! Let's have dinner.
That's not for you to decide!
You're funny!
Honestly, you have a splendid
dining room! And that kitchen!
This is all so wonderful!
Isn't it?
You bet it is! It was made
by someone as super as me!
Man, you've got a pretty keen eye.
Hey! Don't get all chummy with him, Franky.
But I can't wait to eat!
I haven't had a decent meal in decades.
I've had to endure terrible agony every day
as the skin on my belly caved
in until it touched my back!
But since I'm a skeleton, I don't
have any skin on my belly or back!
It's a skull joke!
A skull joke!
As a gentleman, I adore the laid-back
time spent while waiting for my meal.
--Dinner, yay! Dinner! C'mon, baby!
--Food! Food! Food! Food!
Chef! For my drink, I'll take milk.
Shut up! Wait quietly!
Before I forget, Kroobuckle...
No, I'm Brook.
Um, actually, you'll have to forgive me,
but I still don't know your name...
Me? I'm Luffy.
So before I forget, what exactly are you?
Just how little do you
know about each other?!
All right, it's ready!
Help yourselves. We can
kick the skeleton out later.
For now, enjoy the meal!
I used up all the octopi.
Looks good!
Hey, Brook! Eat all you want!
Sanji's an awesome cook!
But... my heart feels full
instead of my stomach...
You're...
Miss, you seem to have gotten a bit more.
Would you mind if we swapped plates?
There's extra, so eat your own!
Aw dese octopuses were awive in da
aquaweeam undil naw too wong ago!
They were alive until just
recently in the aquarium?
Your ship has its own aquarium?
You bether beweeb it! Fwanky made
dis swip and it hash evewyding!
It truly is an amazing ship!
I've never seen one like it before.
Wanna deck it ow wader?
Yes, I'd love to take a tour!
How could he understand that?
It rocks! Yay! Show it off! C'mon!
Eat quietly!
The Revive-Revive Fruit?
I figured a Devil Fruit was behind this.
Indeed, it is.
To be honest, I have already
died once, decades ago.
Wipe your face first! How'd you
manage to get food all over yourself?
The Revive-Revive Fruit lets you...
...come back to life.
In other words, I'm a revived human.
It guarantees the mysterious
power of a second shot at life.
A revived human!
So it gave you the power to come
back to life once after dying?
Yeah, that's right.
Oh, excuse me.
And a long time ago,
I was a pirate just like you!
You're a fellow pirate?
That's right. Oh, pardon me.
I wish I could beat some manners into you.
Long, long ago, my crewmates and I
sailed into the Devil's Sea
on the ship you saw earlier.
However, we had the misfortune of running
into some terribly powerful pirates.
Our entire crew was
annihilated in the battle.
Naturally, I died with them.
When I was alive, the Revive-Revive's
only power was that I couldn't swim.
But on that day, the Fruit's
power finally took effect!
My soul returned from the Underworld!
My soul should have quickly returned
to my body, thus reviving me!
But I died on the Devil's Sea and as
you can see, it is dreadfully foggy.
So I got lost!
My soul wandered through
the fog for an entire year.
I finally managed to find my body!
But by then, it had already turned
into a pearly white skeleton!
I was so surprised that my eyes
nearly popped out of my head.
Not that I have any eyeballs!
What a moron! You're just like Zoro.
Watch it!
And that's how you became a talking skeleton?
It's scary how the Devil's Fruit
still brought you back
even though you're just a skeleton...
But now that the Fruit has done its job,
isn't it just stealing your ability to swim?
That's practically a curse!
And skeletons normally
don't have hair, do they?
Who ever heard of a skeleton with an afro?
I had strong roots.
I don't really care.
So you aren't a ghost?
You're actually a human?
No, you aren't quite human anymore...
Anyway, you aren't a ghost, right?
Right! I hate ghosts!
I'll start screaming if I see one.
You hate ghosts? Have you ever
taken a look in the mirror?
No! Please put that mirror away!
What's wrong?
Wh-Whoa! T-Time out!
W-Why...
Why doesn't the mirror show your reflection?!
He's a vampire!
Really?! That's awesome!
N-Now that I take a closer look,
you don't have a shadow!
You're right! What are you, really?
Don't soothe yourself!
We're freaking out! And it's your fault!
I have spent far too many
years drifting on these seas
to tell my story in one sitting.
The story behind why I am a skeleton
and the story behind why I lack a
shadow are completely unrelated.
To be continued.
Tell us now!
A certain man stole my
shadow a few years ago.
It was stolen?
Your shadow?
After seeing you move and talk,
nothing could surprise me.
But does that sorta thing actually happen?
Yes, it does.
And having lost my shadow, I am no
longer able to exist in the world of light.
But aren't you alive?
No, I cannot live under the light of the sun.
I'm only alive now because I avoid the
sunlight here on these foggy waters.
What would happen if you
were hit by the sunlight?
If I was directly hit by sunlight, my body...
...would be obliterated!
If I was directly hit by sunlight,
my body would be obliterated!
Obliterated?!
Right...
I have witnessed someone who lost his shadow
disappear under the light of the sun.
It was truly terrifying!
A hair-raising sight to behold!
And here I'm a skeleton!
Your shadow appears on the ground
when you stand in the light.
Since I lack a shadow,
my body cannot reflect light.
That's why I cannot be seen
in mirrors or pictures.
In other words, the light
rejects my very existence!
And my crewmates are all dead!
Your life sucks!
Even so, I've scraped by!
Scraped down to the bone!
I am the dead and skeletonized
Brook. It's a pleasure!
Why are you so cheerful?
"Evil Be Gone"
H-Hey! What's wrong? You okay?
Today is truly a wonderful day! I met people!
Is it today or tomorrow?
On these dark, foggy seas, I can't tell
when one day moves to the next...
All of my crewmates passed away...
I was all alone on a large ship
with a broken rudder...
I merely rocked on the water
as I drifted for several decades.
I was really lonely!
I was lonely! And scared!
"Evil Be Gone"
I wanted to die!
But I'm glad I've lived such a long life.
People are joy!
I see you as "joy"!
If only my tears hadn't gone dry,
so I could shed tears of joy!
You invited me to join your crew, didn't you?
That made me truly happy! Thank you!
But I'm afraid I must turn your offer down.
Eh?! Why?!
As I just explained, my
shadow has been stolen.
I cannot live under the sun.
I'm currently protected by the fog that
blocks the sunlight here in the Devil's Sea.
But if I left with you, it would be a matter
of time before my body was obliterated.
I will stay here and wait
for the miraculous day
when I reclaim my shadow!
Don't act like such a stranger!
If you need your shadow,
I'll take it back for you!
Didn't you say someone stole it?
Who was it? Where is he?
You're a really great guy...
I'm surprised! However, I cannot tell you.
I could not ask you to die
for me when we've just met!
Meaning the foe's too strong?
It wouldn't kill you!
At least give us a name.
No, my lips are sealed.
Honestly, I don't know where he is.
I don't even know if I'll see him again
before my second life comes to an end.
But if our paths should ever cross,
I have decided to fight him!
Putting that aside...
...let's sing!
Instruments are my pride and joy.
I was a musician on my pirate ship.
Really?! You're a musician?
Please! Join my crew, moron!
Let's enjoy a fun sailor song!
No!
Hey! What is it? What's wrong?
G... G-G-G...
Ghost!
Gah! Something's there!
Evil be gone! Evil be gone!
I'm scared! It's a ghost!
Awesome!
It's running away!
Wh-What's causing that tremor?!
I-It couldn't be!
How horrible!
This ship was already under observation.
Come look! They've blocked
the path in front of you.
This is what caused that tremor!
What is that?
H-Hey, did a sea monster gobble us up?
What's going on?
This is the back of the gate.
The gate...?
Which means...
Let's look out the aft!
What's going on?
By any chance, did you pick up a
drifting barrel while out at sea?
"Offering of Treasure to the Sea God"
Something's floating on the water.
"Treasure"
You're right! Maybe a treasure
ship accidentally dropped it!
Cool, it opened!
What's that?
We found one.
I knew it! That was a trap.
They've been after your ship ever since then.
What do you mean by that?
Our ship has been here this whole time...
So how'd an island get there?
This is the ghost island
that wanders the seas...
...Thriller Bark!
Thriller Bark...
Where the heck did that skeleton go?
H-Hey, shouldn't you slow down, Nami?
Don't underestimate my navigation technique!
I'm gonna let her rip!
N-Nami, I don't think there's
any water over there!
Of course there--what?!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"One Unnatural Phenomenon After the Next!
Disembarking on Thriller Bark!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!