Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
Don't be ridiculous!
You think you can buy a real sword
for that paltry amount of money?!
Oh, well...
If you're not gonna buy anything, scram!
Geez...
At any rate...
If I remember right, they're...
Please go on ahead!
Well, really...
We're sorry that we tried to extort you!
Well, don't worry about it!
Thanks for showing me the way! Later!
...the brats who showed me the way that time.
Zoro-san! Zoro-san!
Please be our big brother!
Huh?!
"Mothers Are Strong!
Zoro's Hectic Household Chores!"
--I refuse.
--What?! Really?!
Why do I have to become a
big brother to brats like you?
Now, now, don't be like that.
Having seen you beat marines,
we've taken quite a liking to you!
Oh, I'm Michael. Glad to see you again.
I'm Hoichael.
Around the backstreets,
we brothers are a bit famous for...
You should hear people out!
Bro, we'll take you wherever you wanna go.
Wanna go buy some meat?
How about vegetables?
--I refuse.
--You refuse? Refuse what?
Both becoming your big brother
and having you show me the way.
Get lost already.
Oh, yeah, that's right!
Bro, you're looking to buy a sword, right?
The sword shop owner turned me down earlier,
since I don't have much money.
Then you should go to a secondhand store.
I bet you'll find quite a bargain!
Yep! We'll show our big brother
the way to the secondhand store!
I guess it couldn't hurt.
But let me just point out that I'm not
agreeing to become your big brother.
Yes, sir, Bro!
Now, make way, make way!
Pirate Hunter Zoro-sama coming through!
Cut that out!
They're skipping school
and wandering about again.
They're gonna grow up to be
good-for-nothings. What ungrateful kids...
Well, at their home,
it's rather the mother that's...
I feel sorry for those kids.
So no luck here, either.
Hey, what're you looking at?!
That's rude to Big Bro Zoro!
Hey, isn't that swordsman who's with them
one of the pirates who saved Iceberg-san?
What the heck? I thought he was a hero.
So he's just a punk? I misjudged him.
You guys have got quite a reputation.
The townspeople are clueless.
They can say whatever they
want about us. We don't care.
Oh, yeah? Good for you, then.
Well then, take care.
Wh-What do you mean?
Are you abandoning your dear little brothers?!
Like I said, I don't remember
becoming your big brother!
Oh? Did you say something?
We can't hear anything.
Whoa! What the hell is that?!
What is it?! What is it?!
All right, I shook them off.
Bro!
What?!
Bro! Bro! Bro!
Bro!
We know this town like the back of our hands.
There's no way you can get away from us.
Shut up! Stop mocking me, you brats!
That's harsh, Bro!
Don't call me "Bro"!
Who the hell are you?
Just what do you think
you're doing, hitting my kids?
"My kids"? Then...
What strength! What's with this woman?!
Oh? Not bad, lad.
Then... Special Attack! Bam-Bam Tornado!
Stop it, Mom! He didn't do anything wrong!
It was all our fault!
You guys were misbehaving again?! You idiots!
Ow!
Sorry about that.
But I guess it's okay, right,
since you became their big brother?
No, I didn't.
You guys, come out and say hello.
I'm Yoko.
I'm Yuuya.
--I'm Shou.
--I'm Ayako.
I'm Akihiro.
Guys, this is Big Bro Zoro!
He's our new oldest brother!
Oldest brother...? Don't tell me you
want me to be your big brother for real?
Come with us. We're behind
with our household chores,
since we've had to spend a lot of time
repairing our house after Aqua Laguna.
Huh?!
Bro! Bro!
Hey, wait! I didn't agree to this!
Let go of me! Hey!
Now, let's go home, kids!
Yeah!
By the way, what's that?
When Mom is out working,
we go pick up scrap wood at the harbor
while we're babysitting our siblings,
and once we get enough wood,
we go sell it to Galley-La on the weekend.
We can make quite a bit of
allowance money that way.
Well then, say goodbye to your mom for me.
Are you really leaving?
Sorry, but this has nothing to do with me, so...
Watch out!
--Geez...
--Nice babysitting!
Bro!
Not bad at all.
Just as I thought, you're good with babies!
Whoa! He wet himself!
Give him to me.
Go change his diaper.
Okay!
H-Hey! What're you doing?!
What are you, a perv?!
We're gonna wash it. Wear this until it's dried.
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Take care of him, okay?
Okay, kids! Let's work hard
and clean up the house!
Yeah!
Hey, Hoichael. Sorry, but I...
Hey, hey... Hey!
Stop it!
Hey, Michael! Do something about these...
Stop!
Hey! Where do I put these...
You're quite a natural at this. Keep it up.
Okay, be good, you guys.
Hey, lady. I'm going back now.
Give me my shirt back.
What're you talking about?
Do you even have a place to
go back to besides this house?
Yeah. My friends are waiting for me.
How stupid! Friends or family--
which one's more important?
I'm not your family. I don't
remember you giving birth to me,
and we're not blood-related, either.
Shut up! The hell with blood relationships!
Are blood relationships that important?!
We're gonna settle this today for sure.
Get lost.
I came here yesterday and the day before,
but you didn't pay us back, you bitch!
Hm? Who are you?
I feel like I've seen you somewhere before.
Another new family member?
--That's right.
--No.
--Which is it?!
I guess it doesn't matter.
Anyway, it's not like you're
Paulie from Galley-La.
Quit dragging your feet
and pay us back, you old hag!
Like I told you before, I already
paid back what I borrowed!
You fool. Debts come with interest.
That interest also accrued more interest,
so it's now several dozen times more
than the amount you borrowed!
That's none of my concern.
Why don't you pay it yourself?!
What'd you say, you damn old hag?!
I'm not telling you to suffer all by yourself.
If you work those brats hard,
you can earn money easily.
They're not your real family anyway, right?
What'd you say?!
Hm?
Come to think of it...
...they don't look alike at all.
That hurt! What're you doing, you old hag?!
Just say that one more time,
and I'll blow your head off!
Get her!
Well... I'll let you off the hook for today.
Guys, let's go!
You won't get away with this!
--Cool!
--Just as we'd expect from you, bro!
Good boy. Mom's proud of you.
--"Good boy"...?
--Okay, kids!
Let's go shopping for dinner, shall we?!
Yeah!
Well then, I'll get going now.
Hurry up. You're coming, too.
You got a job for me?
Pops, knock the price down a bit more!
Who do you think you're dealing with?!
Don't take us lightly!
Knock it off.
Dammit! However you look at it,
this doesn't make sense.
Why do I have to do things like this?!
If they see me like this...
Shoot!
Of all people, it had to be that damn cook...!
So that alley over there is a shortcut? Thanks.
Seriously...
Now that I've come this far...
Seriously... I'm exhausted.
Seems like you're having a rough time.
Yeah, tell me about it.
How could this be happening to...
It's you?!
--Dammit!
--Robin!
Huh? Where did she go?
Robin!
Don't worry. I won't tell anyone.
Oh, and... that look suits you.
I've had enough! I'm going back!
Oh? You're going home ahead of us?
Then I'll give you the key to the house.
Clean the restroom or something.
No! I'm not going back to your house!
I'm going back to my friends!
Don't speak nonsense!
You're the one who's speaking nonsense!
Don't speak like that to your mother!
You're not my mother!
Shut up, you Broccoli Head!
It's not Broccoli Head! It's Moss Head!
Ah, Moss Head...
I see, Moss Head.
Yep, yep.
Right? Hey, no! That's not what I meant!
Well then, bye.
What am I gonna do with my oldest son?
Michael, Hoichael. Go get him later.
Okay!
Well then, let's go home.
Sorry about earlier.
Looks like your bodyguard is gone,
so I'd like to continue our discussion.
Could you come with me for a bit?
Hoichael, go get Bro.
I bet they'll take us to that place.
Okay.
I'm not your family. I don't
remember you giving birth to me,
and we're not blood-related, either.
Shut up! The hell with blood relationships!
Are blood relationships that important?!
Bro!
Bro, there's trouble!
The debt collector took our mom away!
Sorry, but it has nothing to do with me.
And that lady can take care of herself.
But this time, he brought a bunch of his buddies
and took Michael and my siblings away, too!
What?!
You sure got cocky with me before.
As thanks for that, I brought
some scary guys with me.
Don't be scared out of your wits!
Sir! Please come here!
This is the captain of the
Big Helmet Pirate Gang, Mikazuki-san.
He's got a 36-million-Berry bounty on his head.
Kids, stay back. Don't do anything, got that?
Ahem.
Mikazuki-san has a vicious past.
He tried to walk out of Dock #1
at Galley-La without paying
for the repair of his ship...
...although he was regrettably
defeated by Galley-La's foremen.
Hence, in order to earn money for the repairs,
he's been earnestly working
part-time at our company and...
Well, you guys, think hard...
...about which is better--hurrying up
and paying so you can survive,
or defying me and becoming prey for my sword.
I'll give you five seconds to think it over.
Oh? You wanna fight with me,
the great Mikazuki-sama?
What a fool. As mentioned already,
my bounty is 36 million Berries, and...
Bang-Bang Tornado!
Go, Mom!
An attack like that won't work on me!
Do you know where they took them to?
They always take people to the
same place. We've seen it before.
Dammit!
Don't take a man with a
36-million bounty lightly!
I told you kids to stay back!
Don't do anything dangerous!
What're you saying, Mom?! We're a family!
What's a family for if we
don't help each other?!
What a sassy thing to say, you stupid son.
Bro! Over there!
Guys, teach them a lesson
they won't soon forget.
Mom!
Bro!
You small fry...
Seventy-two Pound Phoenix!
Die!
D-Dammit!
--Incredible!
--Just as we'd expect from you, bro!
Yeah! Amazing!
All right! Good job! That's my oldest son!
You're still saying that? Hey, lady. Listen to me.
Now, to start with, I...
Are your friends as good as our family?
Yeah, they're like that.
Then why didn't you tell me sooner?!
I told you a bunch of times!
You're a member of our precious family,
but, well, if you're gonna run away
from home for a bit, I won't stop you.
"Run away from home"?
Take care of yourself.
Bro, congrats on running away from home!
You should go now before
Mom changes her mind.
See you later!
Well then, bye.
Bye-bye, bro!
--Take care!
--Bro!
--Thank you!
--See you again!
Wait a sec!
I can't wait!
I've come this far. I should be fine now.
Hold it!
That woman!
He never learns, does he...?
He can't run from us.
Geez, he forgot to change his shirt.
What am I gonna do with my oldest son?
Seriously...!
Wait! I said, wait!
Give me a break!
H-Hey, don't pull me, Chimney!
Grandma told me about this place.
A stall, huh?
Oh, hey, pops! How're you doing?!
A petty stall like this wouldn't...
Hm? Looks like the cook here
is better than I expected.
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Sanji's Shock! Mysterious Old Man
and His Super Yummy Cooking!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!