Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
What's that?
Don't...
...die!
Is Nami-san okay?
You guys are as tough as ever.
I'm glad you're alive!
Ahhh! So it was real!
Mermaids really don't exist!
So the tales were true about
people seeing a mermaid
then realizing it was actually a dugong!
You morons! She still hasn't
said she's a mermaid yet!
Don't give up on the dream yet!
I'm an icefish mermaid.
Stop it! Don't say "icefish"!
Dammit!
It's a cannon attack!
Bro!
At the front gate, we identified about
fifty pirates, including the giants.
Those guys...!
That's Zambai and the others!
See, I told you! They escaped the island okay!
I wasn't worried about them at all!
Really, they wouldn't die
even if you killed them!
The other day, too...
We have finished eliminating them
with a barrage of cannon fire.
All are dead.
Under the circumstances, no one could
possibly survive on the main island.
Hence, the number of survivors on
Enies Lobby's main island is zero!
Is it really okay...
...for people to die so easily like this?
You can't see people on the map.
They just erase a small island from the
world map, without a shred of emotion.
That's what Buster Call is.
Hurry up! Straw Hat!
Your friends are waiting for you here!
Don't you dare die on us!
This will be the last time!
Until I bring you down, I won't stop it.
Are you gonna try to use up
all your power and die?
I don't know what's gonna happen.
Second... Gear!
"Wait for Luffy! Mortal Combat
on the Bridge of Hesitation!"
Luffy...
Hurry up and get here!
Gum-Gum...
...Jet Pistol!
He jumped backwards to reduce the impact!
Moon Walk!
Finger Pistol!
Jet Bullet!
Twin Jet Pistol!
Gum-Gum...
I'll show you...
...my strongest technique, one that
pushes the Six Powers to their limit!
Six Powers Secret Technique!
Six King Gun!
It's like... the Impact Dial from the sky island...
But it's several times more
powerful than the Impact Dial...
Tempest Kick! Victory Bird!
Luffy...!
Lucci is strong.
If Straw Hat hadn't kept him
restrained in that place,
I don't know how many of us
would've died, to be honest.
You know, I sometimes feel...
...that Luffy always seems to know
whom he has to fight from the start.
I'm definitely gonna beat up the pigeon guy.
He just has animal instincts...
even better than yours.
I have a report, sir!
Straw Hat Luffy is in the first column!
So he's alive...
Tell all ships to take up positions
around the Bridge of Hesitation!
--Yes, sir!
--Let's go! Hurry up!
He won't... die, right?
Are you an idiot?
What'd you say?!
Only an idiot calls others idiots!
What's going on?
The wall is...
The first column is now cut off!
They destroyed half of the bridge!
Why did they do that?!
Mr. Rob Lucci of CP9 and Straw Hat
Luffy are in the first column!
The battleships are coming this way!
All ships! Take up positions
around the Bridge of Hesitation!
On the bridge and the escort ship,
we've identified nine pirates,
including pirate hunter Zoro and Nico Robin!
It appears that they're the main force
that defeated CP9 in the Tower of Law!
They're coming to take Robin again.
We're not gonna let them!
At any rate, they're unbelievable.
The 800-year-old legend of the
impregnability of Enies Lobby
came about due to the reign
of many generations of CP9.
And yet, to think that a pirate
group defeated its members
and their captain is vying with
Mr. Rob Lucci, of all people...
It seems that Straw Hat Luffy
wasn't a mere rookie.
But he can't defeat Mr. Lucci.
And it's very clear that their
group will be annihilated here.
This is the end of the road for those villains.
Hey, look over there!
Luffy-kun!
We're here!
We all got to the bridge safely!
We're okay!
You don't have to worry about us, Luffy-kun!
We rescued Robin-chan, too!
All that's left is for you to defeat him!
Defeat him, Luffy!
We'll all make it through this...
...and leave this place!
Now it's just a matter of how
long we can hold them off.
As you said, they're all still alive.
That's incredible.
But we'll see if you can still keep
that face a few minutes later.
Evil cannot thrive in this world!
Those ranked Lieutenant
Commander or below, stay put!
To the two hundred elite Captains and
Commanders, go take them out quickly!
C-Captains from Headquarters?!
They're in the same class as that smoke freak!
We're facing that many guys of that level?!
That's proof that they're scared of us.
Grandma, I'm scared.
Hm? Where's Sanji?
He was right there just a moment ago.
What? Where'd that idiot
cook go at a time like this?
All hands prepare for battle! Let's go!
Yeah!
Enough talking--bring it on already!
Interesting. I'll go wild one more time.
We'll stand our ground here
with everything we've got!
Hold your ground until
Luffy comes, at any cost!
We have to get off the ship! If they hurt
the ship, we won't be able to escape!
I'll never get caught again!
I can't... move!
Get them!
Those ranked Lieutenant
Commander or below, stay put!
To the two hundred elite Captains and
Commanders, go take them out quickly!
Get them!
Recapture Nico Robin!
We've come this far! We're not
gonna let them take her back!
Two hundred elites from
Navy Headquarters... Fine by me!
But there are so many of them!
Weapons...
...Left!
Dealing with one or two at a time is too
much of a pain. Attack me all at once!
Experience the power of Sogeking!
Sunflower Star!
So you want me to fight
with guns and cannons?!
Take this!
Those things won't work on me! Weapons Left!
I won't let you get away! Strong Right!
Hey! Whoa! Hey! Time out! Time out!
Y-You bastard! If you're using a sword,
go to Zoro! Go to Zoro!
That's how it should be, right?!
Ah...!
What's that?!
Gunpowder Star!
All right! My feint strategy was a success!
Hey... What the heck is this?!
I almost fell off!
"Phew"
That was close!
At any rate, more and more
keep crawling out... What a pain!
Isn't there someone here with some backbone?!
Don't think you can defeat me just
by attacking me in large numbers!
Oh?
A broadax? How daring.
I like it.
What's the matter?!
Just swinging that thing around
powerfully isn't enough to defeat me.
Three-Sword Style... Oni... Giri!
Not again! Like I said, instead of
coming to me, go to Zoro! Go to Zoro!
Good job, Zoro-kun!
Sogeking! Duck!
Nice, Zoro-kun!
Grandma! The Navy's coming here, too!
That's not good.
Robin, stay here. I'll hold them back!
Here I come! Thunder Charge!
Swing Arm!
Thunder Ball!
--What's this?!
--Clouds?!
Thunderbolt Tempo!
I did it!
How dare you fight us
with that joke of a weapon?!
You pirate bitch!
Robin...!
I'm part of the Straw Hats, too.
When we fight, we fight together.
Gah! There's more?!
Hello! We're hostages!
We're weak!
Hold strong until Luffy comes!
Shave!
What's the matter?
It seems to me that doping
technique of yours is losing its edge.
It's pointless to struggle!
You guys won't be able to
get past Enies Lobby after all!
That's just reality!
Gum-Gum... Jet Axe!
Even if this island gets
destroyed in the process...
...I'll pursue that woman who
threatens the World Government's plans
to the very ends of the
earth and eliminate her...
...in the name of dark justice!
We came to take Robin away from all that!
Jet Stamp!
Six King Gun!
Luffy!
--I got him!
--Watch out!
Hey! Now's not the time
to be spacing out, Soge...
Luffy!
They're all alive!
All I have to do now is beat up
this guy... The pigeon guy!
We're gonna go back together, Robin!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Fists Full of Emotion!
Luffy Unleashes Gatling with All His Might"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!