Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for being bullheaded!
I was wrong!
Luffy...
You idiot! Grab my hand already!
"Wanted Posters Make It Around the World!
Celebration in Their Hometowns
as the Ship Moves Forward!"
Meteor... Fist!
L-Luffy-san...
Vice Admiral Garp sure doesn't show
any mercy, even to his own grandson.
"Navy"
Go, our town's heroes!
Don't be taken out by the Navy!
Hey, rooting for them could get us in trouble!
Go, Straw Hats!
Run, run, then keep running!
Bro!
Huh?
Wh-What the heck? They're furling the sails?
I wonder if they gave up.
Give up?
I doubt Luffy's given up,
but then, just what is he up to?
Hurry up! Furl the sails!
Yeah! Furl the sails!
Hey! Are you really sure about this, Franky?!
Huh? Are you asking me if I'm really sure?!
You dummy! Have faith in this ship!
He's right! Have faith in it, you dummy!
You jerk! You dummy!
Usopp, just a minute ago, you were...
Well, I guess it doesn't matter.
Give me a hand, you bastards!
Seriously, what the hell are they
thinking at a damn busy time like this?!
Franky, I've furled the sails, as you said to.
We'd better hurry up, or the
battleship will catch up with us.
Not quite yet.
Huh?
We still haven't named this ship yet.
Name?! At a time like this?!
That's right. You don't wanna depart
in an unnamed ship, do you?
What the hell?
Then, a name like "Something-or-other Lion"?
Okay! I got a name that sounds strong!
The "Bear! Polar Bear! Lion!"
No one would give a ship
a weird name like that!
Then, the "Tiger! Wolf! Lion!"
Stop just listing animal names like that!
What is it, some sort of a curse?!
"Squid! Octopus! Chimpanzee!"
Now you're not even putting "lion" in it!
Well, "lion" is on the right track.
But the Galley-La guys were like...
This figurehead looks good.
Oh, that's a nice sunflower!
It's not a sunflower, you idiots!
Well, it's just natural that
you guys wouldn't get it right.
But this is a ship that the future
King of the Pirates will board.
So you made it with that
hope in mind, right, Franky?
That's right. He'll set sail into
a sea filled with savage beasts
and rise to the top. So I wanted
a figurehead suitable for that.
That's a splendid sun!
It's not a sun, you idiot!
A ship that'll cross a thousand rigorous
oceans cheerfully, just like the sun...
It's perfect for them!
I said it's not a sun, you Stupid-berg!
What do you think about this
for the ship's name, Franky?
The pirate ship...
...Thousand Sunny!
Whoa!
That sounds cool!
That's better than the "Dumpling!
Gorilla! Lion!" name I came up with!
What is this, a word game?!
That sounds better than
"Boss Lionel" that crossed my mind...
Better than the "Darkness" that I thought of...
Better than the "Monsieur
Sunflower" that I thought of...
Have you guys lost your marbles?!
A ship that crosses a thousand oceans...
How lovely! And so is the sun!
Wait, you guys! That was
just to start things off.
The one I came up with sounds a lot better!
Here's my name for the ship!
--The "New Battle Franky,
Lion Gang Champion"!
--Let's use what Ice pops came up with! I like it!
--"Lion Gang Champion"!
--"Thousand Sunny," huh? That's a good name!
--I agree!
--Let's get along, Sunny!
I guess deciding on the ship's name has
helped us brace ourselves for departure.
I agree.
Hey, Franky, what're you
booing about over there?
Hurry up and shake them off with
the secret weapon or whatever.
Yeah, you'd better hurry up.
The battleship is already nearby.
All right, fine, stop bugging me!
Take a last look at this beautiful
city of water while you can.
In just a second, this island
is going to be out of sight.
I see. Then...
Grandpa!
And Coby and...
I was glad I got to see you
after such a long time!
Call my name, too!
What, Luffy? I've got more cannonballs left!
Meteor... Fist!
It's no use!
We're gonna run with all our might now!
I'll see you guys again someday!
Luffy-san's cool!
How dare you talk cheeky?!
You're nothing but my kid's kid! Luffy!
Vice Admiral Garp, please calm down a little!
Ice pops! We decided to use the
name you came up with for the ship!
Thanks for the nice name!
Everyone! Thanks for everything!
We're taking off!
It sounds like he's saying something.
We can't even make it out.
Seems like pirates can't even
depart without making a racket.
Here we go!
This is an astonishing emergency
accelerator made with a huge air cannon
taking advantage of the strength
of the treasure tree Adam!
"Navy"
A-A massive iron ball!
Luffy!
What the heck is that?
Ahhh! We're gonna die!
No way we'll survive that! That's not possible!
If you underestimate me...
R-Run, Luffy-san! You're gonna get killed!
Franky! Hurry!
...you'll get hurt!
We're gonna die!
Coup de Burst!
The ship... flew... away.
Not bad.
Cool!
I remember experiencing this feeling before.
Merry...
It consumes three barrels of cola,
but it lets us fly one kilometer.
There's nothing the Going Merry
could do that this ship can't.
It exceeds the Merry in every way.
But the Merry's brave soul will be
inherited by the Thousand Sunny.
If it breaks down, I'll fix it perfectly!
When it comes to the ship and weapons,
rely on me for anything!
From today on, this is your ship!
Yeah!
"Navy"
They sure showed me.
They escaped.
That's my grandson!
After all, he didn't come with us.
Of course he wouldn't.
But the king of snipers promised us
that he'd come to Elbaf
some day with his friends.
I'll look forward to it.
We'll wait patiently.
A giant's life span is 300 years.
We did some good work!
Yeah. Now, let's go back
to our work place, shall we?
Or do we wanna go get a drink?
All right, I'm in!
We're heading back to
the station, Chimney, Gonbe.
Let's see... How did Bro do things?
Beats me.
We were just doing whatever
he told us to do, so...
We're gonna starve to death like this, huh?
Iceberg!
Well... I knew this would happen.
Wh-What?! What'd you come here for?!
If you're worried about work,
I can give you some.
Come to Galley-La's headquarters
one by one, one per day, every day.
What?! Are you sure, Iceber... I mean, Bro?!
New Bro!
Don't call me that.
"An island in the Grand Line"
Commodore Smoker!
Thank you for your help, sir!
Huh? The bounty on that pirate
I just caught is 50 million?
Yes, sir!
How ridiculous! What kind of
criteria does the Navy use?!
Geez, the days sure are boring...
Smoker-san!
Ensign Tashigi!
Have you seen the wanted posters?
The Straw Hats are...
Who are you talking to?
What?
Ah! I-I'm sorry!
Wear your glasses, you idiot.
We're marines after all.
Since the Navy is hierarchical in nature,
there's a limit to my freedom
so long as I'm only a captain.
What we need now is higher ranks.
After the incident in Enies Lobby,
pirates all around the world
started acknowledging that
the Straw Hats have the edge.
Yes.
On my pride, I'm gonna crush
them in the New World!
"Sea Restaurant 'Baratie,'
East Blue"
The judicial island Enies Lobby is the front door
that leads to the World Government,
a huge organization.
Now that they've caused it to fall,
neither the Navy nor pirates
will leave them alone.
You can say that the Straw Hats
are now known all around the world.
And so is this wanted poster.
Sanji! You're the best!
Isn't this incredible?!
It's the spitting image of him!
Black Foot Sanji with a
77-million bounty used to work here!
We hope you'll come visit us again
here at the sea restaurant Baratie!
"'Fusha Village' (Luffy's hometown),
East Blue"
Party time! Let's have a party today!
He's the most successful one in the
East Blue with a 300-million bounty!
Cheers to our Luffy!
Shut up, you idiots!
Shame on you!
Cheers!
Stop it!
Seriously... No one's listening to me,
the mayor of the village.
Luffy seems like he's having a fun life.
He's got such a cute pet, too.
So these kids are his friends, huh?
"Friends"? They don't look friendly to me!
Someone from our village
became a vicious criminal
that made the entire world his enemy!
I've never heard of pirates picking
a fight with the World Government!
Yeah, that's true.
To start with, what is Garp doing,
allowing his own grandson to run
free and commit such a crime?
Something's wrong with that whole family.
Does Dadan know about this?
Cheers!
Like I said, shut up!
"'Syrup Village' (Usopp's hometown),
East Blue"
King of snipers... Yes!
There's no mistake about it!
This is Usopp-san!
--Right?
--This nose has to be our captain's!
Yes!
People at the village wouldn't believe us!
Well, his bounty is 30 million, so...
But we thought you'd agree, Kaya-san!
They don't know how incredible our captain is!
Our captain turns all lies into truth!
This mask looks cool!
Let's make it using clay!
Oh? Where are you going, Kaya-san?
I'll go home and continue
studying to become a doctor.
I'd better hurry up and
become a full-fledged doctor
so that I can treat Usopp-san if
he's injured when he comes back.
I envy Captain.
Let's hit him if he makes Kaya-san unhappy.
Yep!
"'Shimotsuki Village' (Zoro's hometown),
East Blue"
Sensei! Sensei!
Is it true that the Pirate Hunter Zoro
used to train at this dojo?
Yes, that's true.
But you kids shouldn't look up to him, okay?
What?
Why? He's so cool!
Teach us how to become pirates, too!
I didn't teach him how to become a pirate.
Are you telling the truth?
Don't play favorites, Sensei!
--Good grief, what a troublesome alumnus.
--He's amazing! I wanna
be a swordsman like him!
I sure was surprised to hear about
the incident on the judicial island,
but Zoro-kun, I think there's
no doubt in your mind.
No matter who you become,
if you're faithful to your swordsmanship,
that's all that matters.
"'Cocoyashi Village' (Nami's hometown),
East Blue"
Gen-san!
Here, I brought some tangerines.
What, you brought them again, Nojiko?
I told you I'd buy them at the store.
Well, just take them.
Don't act like we're strangers.
I think of you like a father to Nami and I, so...
I was never consulted.
What're you doing?
Hm? Oh, this...
I've been calling the Navy Headquarters
to complain, but I can't get through at all!
Complain?
That's right!
They can't just release a lewd wanted
poster like this to the entire world!
She'll have more suitors after her
than bounty hunters! Outrageous!
But you like that picture itself, right?
You did blow it up quite a bit.
Well, let it go, because this
proves that they're keeping...
But if you guys ever do anything
to take away Nami's smile...
...I will come kill you!
...the promise they made you, right?
W-Well, it's true, but...
...that's those pirates' business, not mine.
Then, would you have preferred
if she looked rough in the picture?
No! That'd be outrageous!
"'Sakura Kingdom' (Chopper's hometown),
Grand Line"
Dr. Kureha.
What did you have me come here for, Dalton?
I'm pretty busy, you know.
Well, I'm sorry, but I definitely
wanted to show these to you, too.
What is it? You wanna know
my secret to staying young?
To start with, Dalton, why don't you live
in the castle like kings normally do?
I can let you use some of the rooms.
Well, I like living in this familiar village.
Also, I like rice cooked with chestnuts.
Oh? These are those Straw Hat lads.
These wanted posters were issued
after the big incident the other day.
Chopper...!
I think his bounty amount
is some sort of a mistake.
I don't care as long as I can see his face.
I see... This is wonderful news.
"The sand kingdom 'Alabasta,'
Grand Line"
Wh-What?!
Nico Robin... Why is Miss All Sunday
a member of Luffy-kun's gang?
She surely was a mysterious woman,
so much so that something about
her stuck in my mind, but...
If Vivi-sama finds this out,
she'll probably feel very sad.
Oh, that. I already know,
but it doesn't bother me at all.
I-It doesn't bother you at all? I thought
you'd be more shocked than anyone.
Even if you stayed close to Luffy-san,
you wouldn't understand what he's thinking.
It's just a waste of time thinking about it,
but you can trust everything they do.
He's the man who'll be King of the Pirates.
He's of quite a different caliber.
How magnanimous! You've grown, Vivi-sama.
Hey, why are you crying?
"Land of white soil 'Baltigo,'
Grand Line"
The rebel group took Centaurea in the South Blue.
Another country has fallen...
We did it! Now the North Blue's--
This is no cause for rejoicing. This is a war.
Y-Yes, sir, I'm sorry.
What's this?
Oh, it's Straw Hat Luffy.
He's the guy who actually
defeated Crocodile in Alabasta.
After the incident in Enies Lobby,
his pirate group is becoming so big
that the government can no
longer hide their existence.
The total bounty for the entire group
is 667 million and 50 Berries.
I heard that their captain is the
grandson of Garp from the Na...
Where are you going?
I'm going to get some air.
Live as you please, Luffy.
In the flow of time, as a result of
various circumstances and strong spirits...
"'The World's Most Heinous Criminal'
Revolutionist Dragon (Monkey D. Dragon)"
...people come to question the world they live in!
The day we meet will come at some point.
Guys!
Do you have it?
Yeah!
Well then, once again...
To Robin and Usopp, who came back to us,
to our new friend, Franky...
...and to our pirate ship, the Thousand Sunny!
--Cheers!
Let's go! Our next destination is Fishman Island!
Yeah!
Blackbeard, is that the power you
gained by killing your comrade?
Ace, you can't defeat me now.
What?
I've gained the power I need
to fulfill my ambition!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Most Heinous Power!
Blackbeard's Darkness Attacks Ace!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!