Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Did you know there's an awesometreasure
at the end of this sea?!
And whoever gets it can be Kingof
the Pirates! Isn't that exciting?!
Unheard-of adventures are waiting!
Bon voyage! Let that shred of courage grow
I caught a glimpse ofthe
tail end to the future
The horizons everyonedreamed
of were separate at first
but now they can be seenthrough
a single telescope
A bitter compass of destinyis
leading your heart astray
so turn the wheel in the other direction!
Bon voyage!
Toss aside your bonds and your past
We can surely smile despite that
Tears shed trying to achieveyour
dreams aren't for naught
Precious in my life
I caught a glimpse ofthe
tail end to the future
The Going Merry fell right into
themiddle of a Naval base, Navarone.
Luffy and the others dispersedunder
the cover of darkness.
"On Duty"
Nami successfully disguisedherself
as a cleaning person.
Luffy and Sanji slipped
intothe dining hall as cooks.
However, one of the crew,Zoro,
has been captured.
Welcome to Navarone.
"Captured Zoro andChopper's
Emergency Operations!"
So six more, huh?
One of the Straw Hat Pirates, Roronoa Zoro...
Drake, shall we try questioning him?
But you told us to checkthe
dining hall, Commander.
Hm? I did?
You said that everyone gets hungry,so
they're likely to appear in the dining hall.
I'll go to the dining hall.
Jessica told me that new cooks
fromheadquarters are coming as well, so...
How should we proceedwith questioning Zoro?
"Justice"
I'll leave it to you.
Man... What the hell's with these guys?
Well, I guess I'll take it easy for a while.
Open the cell.
Yes, sir, Lt. Commander Drake!But
he's extremely dangerous.
By order of Vice Admiral Jonathan,I'll
question Roronoa Zoro.
Yes, sir! Please be careful.
Roronoa Zoro... You usedto
be called a pirate hunter.
I would never have imagined that you'dbe
a member of the Straw Hat Pirates.
What, you came all theway
here to tell me that?
Where did you come from?!How
many of you are there?!
What is your purposein
invading this fortress?!
It was a good strategy to invade
this"hedgehog" fortress from the sky.
How did you do it?Did
you build a launch pad?!
Oh, we came from heaven.
Don't mock me!
I'm not mocking you or anything.We
really came from the sky.
I don't intend to go along with such a joke!
Like I said, we came from heavenby
riding a floating octopus balloon.
Got it?
So you insist on that, no matter what?
Don't make light of the Navy!
I'm gonna make you tellus
the truth at any cost!
"On Duty"
Next, you'll be in charge
ofcleaning this exercise hall.
Okay, Boss!
"On Duty"
What is this...?
I have to clean this... by myself?!
Give the floor a good polish!You'll
enjoy lunch after your hard work!
This disguise may have been a mistake!
I heard that one of theStraw
Hat Pirates was captured!
What?! That wasn't a ghost ship, then?!
Yeah, in a sense, it's scarier than
ghosts.Don't be surprised when I tell you this.
It's Roronoa Zoro, the pirate hunter!
Whoa!
What?!
There should be othercrewmembers hiding, too.
If we could find even oneof
them, we'd get noticed!
Y-Yeah!
To think that Zoro was
caught...!What am I gonna do?!
According to what they just
said,everyone else seems to be okay.
Darn! I wanna get out of here already!But
I don't know where they are,
and I don't know what to do...
What's that?!
If I continue to live like this,I'll
break down before I get caught!
Hold it!
Help!!
So it wasn't me...
But I have to come up witha
different disguise... Hm?
This is it!
Th-This isn't good! It's a dead end!
The raccoon dog went that way!
All right! The corner is raccoon
dogged...no, the raccoon dog is cornered!
What should I do?! What should I do?!
He's not here.
So he really was a raccoon
dog.He disappeared!
Hm?
He's in there.
It'll be a lot of work finding him in here!
Ah!
Shh!
Here we go!
What're these?!
Did he leave just his antlers?!
Who knows? But with just antlers,we
can't even make a pot dish.
Dammit! Did we lose him on our way here?!
I'm saved...
Where is the package?
It's probably that way.
Ah! This is it!
What're they doing with deer antlers?
I heard that they'll be usedas
ingredients for medicine.
What?! What happened?!
They said that they ran into a
storm.Many were injured. Hurry it up!
Take them to the medical room quickly!
Let me see... Plunge the scalpelvertically,
and if it bleeds...
Blood, blood, blood...!
Honestly! Why did all the doctorshave
to go on a business trip at once?
Oh, God, please don'tsend
any surgery patients!
Medical Room Chief!
Yes...
We brought the deer antlers,the
medicine ingredient.
Oh... Please leave them there.
Okay!
Where am I?
I look pretty good in this
uniform,if I do say so myself.
I'll be fine if I look like this!
Ugh! I'm sorry!
What're you apologizing for?!Go
to the medical room already!
What?! Hm? Huh?
There's an emergency!All the
nurses are being called in!
I knew it... I'm screwed
nomatter what clothes I wear!
Dr. Kobato! It's an emergency!
I-Internal case? Pediatrics? Or...
There're quite a few seriouslyinjured
marines on the Stan Marey!
S-Surgery?!
I-I'll leave them to you nurses,since
surgery isn't my field.
What're you saying?! You're theonly
doctor in this base right now!
But...! I'm a pediatrician and,um,
surgery is outside my field!
Oh... This seems to be a medical room.
But I wonder if that doctor
is gonna be okay...
One, two, three!
This is crazy! Did they runinto
a cyclone or something?!
Here, treat their injuries!
Okay!
Darn! I don't have time for stuff like this!
We have to quickly find the Going
Merryand leave this place right away!
I-I'm sorry!
Stop daydreaming!
Doctor, what should we do?!
Right... right... Give
him 50 mg of painkiller!
What about preparing the operation room?
Operation?! Operation...Yeah,
he needs an operation...
Doctor!
Doctor! There's no time to lose!
Please get a grip!
Please advise us on treating the patients!
Doctor...
I can't just stand back and watch!
I'll advise you all!
First, give this patient
phenicol,cardiotonic and tialcillin.
Respond if you got that!
Yes, doctor!
Perform cross-matchingwith
each patient's blood type!
Those who require an operation,give
them preoperative treatment!
Give that patient a tetanustoxoid
and 5 mg of morphine!
Yes, doctor!
Is the operation room ready?!
It's ready!
Then bring the patients in,starting
with seriously injured ones!
Yes, doctor!
Get a grip, doctor!
Chopper!
Nami! What are you doing
in a place like this?!
What're you doing here?!
Excuse me... I don't knowwhat's
going on, since I fainted...
You're... a doctor, right?
I don't know who you are, but yousaved
us with your apt instructions.
You're not saved yet!
What?!
There're a number of soldiers whose
livesare in danger without an operation!
Yes...
Start the operations on seriouslyinjured
patients as soon as possible!
Yes... Operations...
What's with you?!
I-I can't...
Can't do what?
I can't bear things like seeingpeople
in pain and bleeding at all.
When I'm really terrible
even at giving shots,
to think of cutting a human
bodyor putting stitches on it...
I can't believe this! This
is a naval base, right?!
How have you been giving treatmentsuntil
now if you're like this?!
My field is pediatrics. Since the
otherdoctors are all out on business trips,
I was asked to serve as
adeputy Medical Room Chief.
Deputy...?
Deputy or not, you're theMedical
Room Chief right now, right?!
Y-Yes, more or less...
More or less?!
Chopper! Let's get out of here already!
But...
We can get out! This place isn'ta
lake! It's connected to the sea!
We can get out with the Going Merry!
I can't go yet.
What?!
You're a doctor, a person thatsaves
people's lives, aren't you?!
Yes... but even for a doctor,there're
things they can and can't do...
The person who taught memedicine
told me this story.
There was a man who was told byhis
doctor that he was going to die.
He wandered in despair,searching
for a place to die.
But as he was passing over a mountain,
he saw vivid cherry blossomsblooming
all over the mountain.
He went to see a doctor again.And
the doctor said to him...
"You're completely healthy."
You're the only doctor to the patients here!
You're the only one who can save them!
You mustn't give up! There's no illnessin
this world that can't be healed!
You mustn't say thatthere're
things you can't do!
There're no patients thatwe
doctors can't heal!
Doctors can make miracles happen!At
least, we have to believe that!
Say...
...will I be able to seethe
cherry blossoms, too?
Or rather... can I show the cherryblossoms
to people who're suffering?
Yeah, of course! I'll help you!
H-Hey! We don't have time for that!
We don't, but people's lives havepriority
over anything! I'm a doctor!
Are you serious?! You'll get left
behind,you know! Is that what you want?!
Doctor, preparations forthe
operations are ready!
Okay! I'll be right over!
Chop... Dr. Chopper!
All right.
Chopper!
It's okay to leave me behind.
If I leave here now,I'll
be scolded by Doctorine!
Geez, you know we can'tjust
leave without you!
"Operating Room"
We had a doctor like that here?
We'll start the emergency operations.
There's a piece of iron in his
chest.We need to remove it.
The patient is already sleepingsoundly
from the anesthesia.
Scalpel!
Yes, doctor!
Dr. Kobato! You'll be fine!
You're the one who can showcherry
blossoms to this patient!
Yes!
It's near an artery, so be careful.
Yes.
Nami, suction!
Yes, doctor!
The iron piece has been removed.
I did it!
This is no time to celebrate!
There're many other patients!
Yes!
Let's give it our best!
What?! A doctor you've neverseen
is performing an operation?
Yes, sir!
It might be one of the Straw Hats.
Chopper...
Pardon me!
We're in the middle ofan
operation. Please leave!
It's an emergency! Dr. Kobato,I
wanna ask you something.
Dr. Kobato! His blood pressure is dropping!
Give him 6 units of red blood
cellsuspension and 1 unit of platelets!
Yes, doctor!
It's all right. Continue the
bloodtransfusion! Also have dopamine ready!
Dr. Kobato!
We're in the middle of anemergency
operation! Please be quiet!
You're operating?! You fainted whenyou
saw blood flowing out of my arm!
A doctor we've never seenbefore
should be in there.
You're interrupting!
All you'll find in here are doctors and
nursesgiving their all to save precious lives!
Let's go.
Monitor them.
Yes, sir.
Suture completed!
Doctor, that was the last patient.
Good work, Dr. Kobato!
Ch-Chopper!
You're a great doctor, Dr. Kobato.
Not at all... but you are agreat
doctor, Mr. Raccoon Dog.
You dummy! I'm not araccoon
dog! I'm a reindeer!
Shouldn't she be rather surprisedto
see Chopper like that?
Honestly, what am I doing
in a place like this?!
We don't even know if Nami-sanand
Robin-chan are okay.
Ahh! But out of regard for Jessica-san,I
can't just abandon this task.
Yeah, exactly.
Hey, what're you doing?!
Well, I was watching this thingand
admiring how incredible it is.
Either help me out or come upwith
a way to get us out of here.
Just do something!
But I wonder why we're
notgetting out of this place?
It's come to this because you were dawdling!
Say, Sanji...
What?!
Octopuses can be eaten raw, right?
So what?!
How is it? Is your stuff ready?
If you take your time, the next100
soldiers are gonna show up.
Oh, Jessica-san! I've just finished it!
Oh, yeah?! It's finally
break time? I'm tired!
You didn't do anything!
Then I'd like you to chop up 300 more onions.
What?! Is she a devil?
Okay! I'm your servant, Jessica-san!
I get it! It's your fault
it's come to this, Sanji!
Hurry up and get moving towards the future!
Let's move ahead, pursuing our dreams
All the answers are right here, pouring out
Rush forth, rush forth,on
the road opened before us
Let's keep moving forward! We can do it!
We won't give in, we won't give
in,even if the obstacle is big
It's nothing to be scared
of,we can overcome it
Dammit! That bastard! That hurt!
Anyway, are the others okay?
Oh, hey, Usopp! Is our ship all right?!
Robin, why're you dressed like that?
Captain and the idiot
cook...Never mind about them.
Looks like the situation
is starting to change.
On the next episode of One Piece!
Don't read my line!
"The Navy's Dragnet Closes
In!The Second Member Captured!"
I'm gonna be a great swordsman!!
Hey!