Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Keep on advancing
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Freedom is our only compass,
We are best friends
jiyuu dake ga rashinban
sa We are best friends
ore tachi no ruuto kore kara
mo ore tachi de kirihiraku ze
We will keep making our own route
zenryoku shissou no hibi wa Go east, Go west
Running at full speed
everyday, Go east, Go west!
We keep finding the things we
want to do and doing them all
tsugitsugi mitsukaru yaritai
koto subete kuria shite
We can't wait until the
morning (I can't wait)
asa ga machikirenakute
uzukidasu (I can't wait)
sore nara isso taiyou
sora e to hikizuridashite
Why not drag the sun out into the sky
Force it and go
go-in Go
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Put the pieces of our dreams together
yume no kakera hitotsu ni
kasaneawase gutto kitara sore ga torejaa sa
and if that makes you feel
something - that's the treasure
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
mae e tsukisusumuno sa
Keep on advancing
The unchanging bond will light
up the "end of the dream"
kawaru koto no nai kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" terashidasu
Wake up! Wake up! Wake
up! Wake up heart beat!
We are the one! Go ahead!
Get dragged into darkness, Straw Hat!
I'll never lose!
I'm gonna find the One Piece
and become the King of the Pirates!
norikoeru tabi
Everytime we overcome something,
it stirs possibility (I can't stay)
zawameku kanousei (I can't stay)
asu mo asatte mo
Tomorrow and the day after,
atsuku hageshii wakuwaku no rensa daze!
there will be a chain of
burning, intense excitement!
sou sa Shining! Running! Forever
Yes, Shining! Running! Forever
Go along with your curiosity
koukishin ni makasete
and go wherever you want to
go - that's the adventure
omoi no mama mezasu basho
e sore ga adobenchaa
Let's go, Shining! Running! Forever
iku ze Shining! Running! Forever
Open up the sailing chart in your heart
kokoro no chizu hirogete
chikara wo himeta kizuna wa
kitto "yume no hate" tsukamitoru
The bond with potential power
will seize the "end of the dream"
Never! Never! Never! Never Stop it!
We are the one! Go ahead!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined
many pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
To take down one of the Four Emperors -
the rulers of the New World,
Luffy and the others formed a pirate alliance
with Trafalgar Law
and have come to Dressrosa
to hand Caesar over to Doflamingo.
When Luffy found out that the
prize for a fighting event
was the Flare-Flare Fruit,
he decided to enter.
Burgess from the Blackbeard Pirates won
the match of Block A.
Now, the battle of Block B has begun.
Meanwhile, Law and the others are...
Hey, Tra-guy!
You have to change the handing-over spot now!
I'm not gonna change.
We're already here. Stop making a fuss.
More importantly,
I'm worried about the situation of this country.
Their king quit all of a sudden.
How come they are so calm?
We're in unexpected circumstances already.
That's what worries me!
King...
...Punch!
Barrier!
I'm a barrier human who ate
the Barrier-Barrier Fruit!
Barrier Crash!
The winner of Block B is...
Dammit!
...Bartolomeo!
"The Fighting Fish Strike!
Across the Deadly Iron Bridge!"
I can't believe it!
Now it's clear, the battle of
Block B ended with Bartolomeo as its winner!
That strange guy won after all.
Now...
The giant old pops and Cabbage are gone.
I better run now!
--Move!
--You're in our way!
Bellamy?
You...
Bellamy.
Why did you cheer me on?
That was so embarrassing!
I haven't changed a bit.
You've changed, Bellamy.
No, you have changed.
You now use Haki that's far greater
than anyone can imagine.
That pisses me off!
My pride has been broken to pieces!
Straw Hat!
S... S... S... S...
S...
Straw Hat?!
45 MINUTES BEFORE THE HANDOVER
CAESAR HANDOVER TEAM
Wow... It's a very solid-looking bridge.
We'll be okay if that Fighting Fish thing
attacks us on this, won't we?
I hope so.
It's coming.
--Huh?!
--What's coming?
Hey hey, don't tell me
you're talking about...
Oh? What is that noise?!
Hey, look!
It...
It's here!
It showed itself!
I thought a Fighting Fish would be a fish.
It is a fish.
You can't call that a fish!
It's no different from a sea monster!
It's a beast!
It's coming again!
There is more than one!
There are a bunch of them!
The guy said they reinforced the bridge
with iron to protect it from them!
I-It's going to be alright, isn't it?!
The bridge is a piece of crap!
Can we make it to Green Bit like this?!
We're gonna be okay.
They can take care of them.
You handle it, Warlord!
I can't fight now.
Here it comes!
Special Attack - Green Star...
Another one from the opposite side!
They're gonna crush us!
Mil Fleurs!
Gigantesco Mano!
Spank!
Skull Bombgrass!
You're doing great!
No, we're not!
Can't you see how many there are?!
It's a school!
Let's just run!
It'll take forever to fight them all!
Skull Bombgrass!
Nose-ya, uncuff Caesar!
I want him to fight, too!
What are you saying?!
He's gonna fly away then!
He wouldn't dare make a move like that.
Don't tell me it's...
My heart!
You won't die a peaceful death...
...after pushing around a
great scientist like me!
Gastille!
Oh, that's so powerful!
Only a criminal with a 300 million
berry bounty could do that!
Gastille!
Run!
Like I said, why aren't you fighting?!
Yeah, don't just make me fight all of them!
It takes so much energy to use my ability.
And I have to be at my best on our way back!
Do you understand?!
I want to keep my strength up
as much as possible!
Because our enemy is Doflamingo!
Law... Is he really going
to fight against Joker?!
Oh no! What should we do?!
The bridge is collapsed.
On top of that, I can't see the other
side clearly because of the fog!
A Fighting Fish is coming towards us!
Damn! I can't let it destroy
anymore of the bridge!
Roo...
It stopped.
--We caught it!
--Alright, let's pull it in!
We had a decisive battle today!
Let's eat Fighting Fish stew
to boost up our energy!
Yeah!
Who's voice is that?
Residents of the island?
I thought it was a deserted island.
Hey! Who is over there on the other side?!
We want to cross the bridge!
Oh no! It's a human!
Hurry up! Run!
What was that all about?
Anyway, let's keep moving!
Guys! Enough already!
Caesar!
What?
Fly us to the island.
Law, you bastard!
I'll get even with you, I mean it!
Wow, what a view! What a lovely view!
We should have flown ourselves
like this from the beginning.
Oh, you're right!
Cut that crap!
How much gas energy do you think
you need to fly three people?!
I'm an important hostage for you!
THE DESERTED ISLAND NORTH OF DRESSROSA
The drag marks from the fish end there.
Nobody is here yet.
What was that about?
Shipwrecks from Fighting Fish attacks
are filling up the water around here.
What's that?!
What is this place?!
GREEN BIT
A very wild forest?!
Now, the battle of Block C!
The battle will commence shortly
after they finish fixing the ring!
All competitors of Block C,
please go to the entrance gate!
Oh, it's about time, huh?
I repeat! All competitors of Block C,
please go to the entrance gate!
Alright! I'm ready to go!
Now let me introduce
the competitors who everyone
should keep an eye on!
He is the two-time champion of
the New World Central Fighting Tournament!
"Destruction Cannon" Ideo!
They are savage assassins
who are able to kill pirates
with more than a 100 million bounty!
The Funk Brothers!
He is from the famous
Giants' country - Elbaf!
The most formidable "Pirate Mercenary"!
Hajrudin!
There are a lot more!
Known for his violence
which he uses in order to drive
his target into the corner!
Jean the Bandit!
Who can stop this bull?!
The Colosseum's Grim Reaper!
Brutal Bull!
Today's likely winner!
The gang from the Kano Kingdom!
Sai!
Boo!
And the legendary former
pirate - Don Chinjao!
Straw Hat!
There are also a lot more tough contenders!
It's going to be an exciting match!
The battle of Block C will
be a very fierce one!
Get ready for it!
A little while ago...
In the "next town" over in Dressrosa...
What's the matter?
This was a bad idea! Why don't you go back?!
Sanji-san, I must've been out of my mind!
How horrible I was to ask you such a thing!
To ask you to kill that man!
How could I ask you such a thing?!
Even though you're quite a strong man!
I tried to use you.
Please! Just walk away!
Don't get involved with me anymore!
I don't want you to die because of me!
You said the man is in that storage room,
didn't you, Violet-chan?
I'm going in.
What?
Aren't you gonna ask me why?!
Ask you why?
I mean, the reason I want you to kill him!
I don't need to hear that.
Seeing your tears is good enough for me.
Sanji-san!
Wait for me!
I'll take care of everything and be back!
I'm your bodyguard!
What the...
Who is it?!
Why don't you have your last cigarette?
I'll give you a few minutes to do that.
Huh? Who the hell are you?
Are you the asshole
who makes Violet-chan cry?
What? So that woman asked you to do this?
Poor Violet-chan...
She shouldn't be fooled by a crumb like him.
What?! Screw you!
Guys!
Kill that son of a bitch!
Go away, small fry.
--What did you say?!
--Kill him!
Oeil!
Flanchet!
Joue!
Poitrine!
Party Table Kick Course!
I told you.
Go away, small fry.
Violet-chan!
Sanji-san!
Dammit! You bastard!
Get your filthy hands off of her!
Shut up!
If you don't want me to kill her,
you better not move...
Damn!
Where... Where did he go?!
Hey!
I won't forgive a man like you
who makes a woman cry!
Diable Jambe!
Amour Shot!
Nobody can stop...
...our love!
Sanji-san, I was scared!
You're not hurt, are you, Violet-chan?
No! Thank you!
That's good.
Sanji-san,
can I ask you a favor?
What is it?
I would do anything for you, Violet-chan!
Yeah?
Huh?
Then will you...
...die for me, "Black Foot" Sanji?
What? V-Violet-chan?
What are you talking about?
What an idiot.