Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything this
world has to offer there!
Now everyone is in search of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
jitto dekinai tomarenai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
yoake ga osokute jirettai
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
Fly the flag, Break of Romance Dawn
hata wo ageyou Break of Romance Dawn
Make waves, jump from your sleep
namikaze tateyou suriipu kara no janpusutaato
arienai sekai wo iku nara
If you want to go to the unbelievable world
your toughness, that’s what it takes
kimi no tafunesu sore ga hitsuyou
medachisugi sorette tsumi?
Being brazen, is it a crime?
shimeitehai->tsumari Winner
Wanted->means Winner:D
Freedom is our only rule
jiyuu dakega ore tachi no ruuru
It's not our way to worry
shinpai nante dokofuku kaze--
ttai one piece ichibannori
At any cost, One Piece, I’ll be the first
yume miru kokoro wa choo dekai
My dreaming heart is huge
samenai koto ga daiji--
It’s important not to wake up
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
yoake ga osokute jirettai
Daybreak hasn’t come yet and I can’t wait
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
ore tachi wa...koko made kitaze
We...made it this far
ore tachi wa iku...yume no arika e
We go...to where the dream is
We won’t left anyone behind
dare mo oitekanaize--
Keep going forward, that’s our pledge
nshin aru nomi sore ga chikai
Since the day that the dream began
yume ga hajimatta ano hi kara
the future that I’m
aiming at hasn’t changed
mezasu mirai wa onaji--
tto dekinai tomarenai
I can’t stand still, I can’t stop
kokoro no taiyou shizumanai
The sun of my heart will never set
ichi, ni, Sunshine
One, two, Sunshine
ichi, ni, Sunshine yon...we go!
One, two, Sunshine four...WE GO!
WE GO!
All the pirates who are
after the One Piece...
...head for the New World,
the second half of the Grand Line.
However, no one has ever fully explored it
except for Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
The New World has ruined many
pirates' dreams and ambitions.
Now, Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned
to rubber after he ate the Gum-Gum Fruit,
and his friends venture into that sea.
I'm gonna become the King of the Pirates!
2 years have passed since the
War of the Best in Marineford.
Luffy and his crew returned
to Sabaody Archipelago.
And on their way to the
next stage - the New World,
they reached the Fish-Man Island
located 10,000 meters below sea level,
where the New Fish-Man Pirates who are
looking to destroy the Ryugu Kingdom
along with Vander Decken who is after
the Mermaid Princess are
engaging in secret maneuvers.
Nice to meet you, Hordy Jones!
The Straw Hats find themselves caught
up in the turmoil little by little...
Isn't there anywhere you wanna go?
Huh?
Of course, there are a lot
of places that I want to go...
That's what I thought.
Then let's get out of here!
If something's thrown at
you again, I'll deflect it!
He's formidable!
Take this!
Zoro!
I thought you'd been captured!
I heard the sound of this
festival so I let myself out!
"It's an Emergency!
The Ryugu Place Is Occupied!"
What the...
How did he get out of jail?!
What a fighter!
He warded off the God of the Sea -
King Neptune's attack easily!
If you resist, we'll have
casualties on both sides.
Surrender with good grace-jamon, Zori!
It's Zoro!
You guys! Rupture the
bubbles around them at once!
Minister of the Right!
It's better for us to
fight them in the water.
Hurry up!
Ah, we've been driven to the wall.
You're right. This is no good. Hey, Nami!
Oh? Nami?
Wh-What the...
What?! All the water is gone?!
Sorry!
I just found a Bubbly Coral, this big.
Wow, that's big!
Now...
let's continue where we left off.
Wait, wait. I'll fight him-jamon.
No! Don't bother, Neptune-sama!
No, that man is strong.
And I don't want anyone else
to get hurt anymore-jamon!
Well, hurry up and get ready!
Let's go out, right now!
Huh? R-R-Right now?
B-But I... I mean, I still...
Still what?
I-It's too sudden so I still... Um...
I can't sort my feelings out.
Could you give me a little more time?
It's just a walk, it's not a big deal.
Boy. Don't take too long.
I don't like you after all.
Alright, alright.
I'll wait so just make up your mind.
What have you guys done?!
No matter how I look at it, this is overkill!
He's right! You should regret your actions!
You guys started this fight!
So you're my accomplices, you idiots!
We were gonna just intimidate them and run!
I was just enjoying
sightseeing and shopping.
What's done is done! Stop complaining!
"What's done is done"?!
Stopping by the Fish-Man Island
and occupying the palace accidentally
- what are we? Some kind of evil pirates?!
Ow, ow, ow...
Then we should've allowed
ourselves to be beaten?
I told you "Let's wait for a
chance and run" many times!
I don't know the way out
and Luffy is missing!
That's right. Luffy is missing!
Where did he go?
Dunno.
We really have to go so
don't be mean and tell me!
Yeah, where is Luffy...
Where is the treasure chamber?
No!
What? Why?
Stop pretending you're naive! Be sensible!
Hey, everybody! When you're
sad, let's sing and be happy!
Come on!
It's gonna be alright! It's gonna be alright!
If it's not,
-- you're gonna die someday anyway, yeah!
Shut up already, Soul King!
Neptune-sama, are you alright?
I can't believe that this is happening to
King Neptune, the Great Knight of the Sea!
I can't fight when I've thrown out my back...
I-I got old...
It's my fault-jamon. I'm sorry.
We should've broken their bubbles and
made them fight in the water earlier.
I can't believe we let
them drain all the water...
Can't take it!
Hey, you bastards!
When the 3 formidable princes
of Neptune's army - Fukaboshi,
Ryuboshi, Manboshi come back,
you won't get away with this!
Yeah!
In any case, we can't
stay here on this island.
Where's the Sunny? Let's bring
everybody together and sail out soon.
But the coating on the Sunny came
off when we entered this island.
The Log Pose hasn't been
working right for a while too.
It has been unstable since we got here.
I can't take it! That Pose is not good
enough to sail across the New World.
You ignorant pirates!
What? This is not good
enough? What do you mean?
I'll tell you if you untie me.
Ding dong!
It must be Prince Fukaboshi!
This is weird. What are the guards doing?
Clank.
Hello? Who is it?
Don't pick it up!
--Prince Fukaboshi!
--Help us!
Shut up, you guys!
--Prince Ryuboshi!
--Prince Manboshi!
I think, Brother,
something is going on-la-ti-do!
I agree! Are Father and Shirahoshi alright?
It's me, Fukaboshi. What
is going on in there?
Lower the gate now and let us in.
And then what?
I can't do that.
Hey! What are you saying?!
Just be honest and tell him!
Yeah guys, tie me and Camie up too!
They'll think we're your accomplices.
Zoro-chin's scary!
--Help us!
--Prince Fukaboshi!
Are you a member of the Straw Hats?
Fukaboshi! That's the Three-Sword
Style swordsman of the Straw Hats -
"Pirate Hunter" Zori!
--It's Zoro!
--Father!
You have Father too!
Like you just heard, we have
Neptune and many other hostages.
If you don't want me to kill them,
prepare for us to set sail!
We need our ship - Sunny,
with a fresh coating on.
We don't know where it is
so go find it on your own.
And we need the rest of our crew - a gloomy
woman, a robot, a racoon, and a dirty water imp.
And Zoro, one billion berries in cash.
No, you stop!
"Dirty water imp"... That's funny!
Can't stop laughing!
Stop laughing, you fool!
--"Dirty water imp"...
--What about "gloomy woman"...
I understand your conditions.
I'll make an arrangement for you
to leave this country immediately
with all of your friends.
However,
I want all the hostages back alive!
That's fine.
Brother!
We have no choice.
This gateway is the only way to
enter the Ryugu Palace even for us.
It's impossible to break in elsewhere
since it's covered with
several layers of bubbles.
There is one more thing, Zoro-kun?
I wouldn't normally tell you
this under the circumstances
but I can't ignore my duty to Jimbei.
What is it?
This is from the former Warlord - "First
Son of the Sea" Jimbei to Straw Hat Luffy.
He left 2 messages for me to
give you when you arrived.
Jimbei...
--Jimbei...
--Boss Jimbei...
Jimbei?!
Luffy said that he became
friends with Jimbei!
Ah, he was in the newspaper with Luffy-san.
Although he's a pirate, he's a big
figure that people on the island trust.
Luffy is not here but I'll
tell him later. Go ahead.
First, he says to not fight against Hordy.
Second, he'll be waiting at the Sea Forest.
That's all.
Clank.
The Sea Forest?
Hordy?
And that's what happened.
So I want you to find the Straw Hats' ship
and the rest of them as soon as possible.
Roger that.
Hey hey, did you hear that?
The Straw Hat Pirates did it!
They took over the Ryugu Palace!
What do they want?!
No way! They looked like really good people
- I can't believe they did such a thing!
I can't believe it!
--Can't believe it!
--Yes, I can believe it.
--Maybe I can't either.
--I can't believe it, so what?
I'm sure they're the ones who kidnapped
the Mermaids and the prediction is true!
That's how things are progressing!
They finally showed their true colors!
I heard the 2 of them are hiding
in the back of the Mermaid Cafe.
Guards are heading there to catch them!
--What is this animal?
--He transformed himself!
Kung Fu Boost!
Sanji just got better! Stay away from him!
"Come to the Ryugu Palace"?
You're trying to catch us, aren't you?
Hey, guys...
Sanji, you should still be in bed!
Hey, are you ready?
Let's go out!
I'm sorry. I can't go...
Why? You said there's a place
you wanna go, didn't you?
But if I do something like that,
it's going to cause a lot of trouble
for everybody in the palace!
If I stayed here for 10 years, I'd go crazy!
It's in return for the
food - I'm coming with you!
Where do you want to go?
Well...
The Sea...
The Sea Forest!
No but it's just a dream.
I can't do such a selfish thing,
I can't just go out...
Why are you crying just from
saying where you wanna go?!
I-I'm sorry. It's because I
summoned all my courage to say it.
Please don't get mad!
You are scaring me, Luffy-sama!
You're such a pain in the butt!
What is that? That was so loud!
Is he throwing something again?
What a sick guy!
What's this?
What's this noise-jamon?
Don't tell me it's Decken again!
It's coming from the Hard Shell Tower-jamon!
Shirahoshi must be in danger!
Are there guards with her?!
No, they're all tied up here!
What?!
Hey, pirates! Go see if the Princess is okay!
Huh? What are you talking about?
Neptune-sama! Then they'll
find out about the Princess!
We have no choice-jamon!
The Hard Shell Tower is on the northeast
side of the palace! You guys, go there now!
Why are we being ordered
around by our hostages?!
Silence! Shirahoshi is
my only daughter-jamon!
Somebody is trying to kill her constantly!
If something happens to my daughter,
I'll shove you all off the end of an ocean trench!
So she is the Mermaid Princess, am I right?!
Then I'll go there as soon as possible!
And...
...can I ask her to show me her panties?
Hey wait, Brook!
Oh, I can't take it! He's heading
there with lascivious intent!
Now she's in a different kind of danger!
Wait, Skeleton! You don't have
to untie me but take me with you!
I have jurisdiction over the tower!
If something happened to the Princess,
I would be beside myself with regret!
I assume... you...
...wanna see her too!
--Don't be ridiculous!
--How lecherous!
He's wrong!
Sanji-san, excuse me for seeing her first!
I've always wanted to go to the Sea Forest.
For this 10 years.
But everybody is kind enough to tell me that
it's too dangerous to go out of the tower.
And I am scared of going out, too!
Luffy-sama, are you really
going to take me out of here?
Uh-huh.
Are you really going to protect me?
Count on me! You're gonna be fine!
Whoa-whoa, I'm not gonna take you if you cry.
Plus, to be accurate,
you take me since I can't swim.
I-I am so sorry. I am too delighted...
You really are a crybaby and a coward.
But once you go out,
everybody will recognize you.
Yes, I'm sorry.
So I have an idea!
Mermaid Princess?! Are you alright?!
Hey, Skeleton! Look at the tower!
I can't believe this!
Those aren't knives or axes like usual!
It was the sound of human
pirates hitting the tower!
How eccentric! He's not normal,
that man - Vander Decken!
Huh?! V-Vander Decken?!
Oh, this is no good!
They're getting on their feet!
Does this mean that the
impregnable Ryugu Palace...
...has been invaded by enemy forces?!
This is a surprise attack!
The King is in danger!
The Princess is in danger!
The attack stopped, huh?
Let's go, Coward!
Y-Yes! We are ready, Megalo!
Go, Shark!
Megalo?!
Luffy-san?!
To the Sea Forest!
When Shirahoshi is discovered missing,
the Ryugu Palace is thrown into a panic.
Furthermore, a group of unknown
pirates have infiltrated the palace.
These pirates seem driven to attack
the Straw Hats at all costs.
Meanwhile, in Coral Hill, a critically
wounded Hachi appears before Sanji and Chopper!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"The Ryugu Palace in Shock!
The Kidnapping of Shirahoshi!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!