Edited at https://subtitletools.com
If you're prepared to die, then come with me.
I'll give you a ride... on a sea train!
Whoooa! There it is!
Its name is Rocketman.
We can't even allow passengers to be on board.
Rocketman!
It sounds fast!
Use it. I've finished servicing it.
Water and coal have been loaded
and it's storing the steam right now.
So you were getting it ready for us, pops?!
Wait to rejoice until you survive the ride.
After all, this was a failure built
before Puffing Tom was completed.
No matter how much you tune it up,
its steam engine can't control the speed.
I can't guarantee your lives.
Okay! Thanks, Ice pops!
Straw Hat!
Please... take us with you!
Our Bro, Franky, was taken
in by the Government!
We want to go after them... but we can't
get through Aqua Laguna by ourselves!
Please!
We want to save Bro!
Get on.
Hurry!
Straw Hat...
Thank you!
We're deeply indebted to you!
Well then, let's go, shall we?!
Now... pirates!
Don't go getting thrown off, okay?!
Now departing Water Seven for Enies Lobby...
Here comes the sea train Rocketman!
All right! Depart!
We're gonna go...!
To get everything back!
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
As power passes through our clasped hands
let's grab hold of our wishes
Working together, let's ride the giant waves
Let's hurry toward the excitement--
there's the starting signal
Now's the time to set sail-- let's raise anchor
Cut through the rainbow-colored wind
and head for a sea of adventure
It'll be a journey fraught with injury
but what you cherish most will be right there
And if you get into a jam
I'll always be there to protect you
It's all right! Now let's move forward
with the sun always in our hearts
If a storm hits, let's put
our arms around each other
and gaze at the light beyond
If we gather up the pieces of our dreams
they'll make a map leading to tomorrow
So let's grab hold of our wishes
under the same flag-- together, we're one
One Piece
"Rescue Our Friends! A Bond
Among Foes Sworn with Fists!"
We're coming out at a place like this?!
It's an underground canal.
Luffy! Are you okay?!
I-I got some water in my nose.
Huh?
That's gonna happen when you stand out there!
Be careful!
Boy, I didn't see that coming!
But... it's getting fun!
H-H-Hey, monster granny!
Hey, aren't we falling?!
The exit is real close now.
We'll keep on going and go down in one shot!
What? No way... What?!
All right! The sea train has come out!
Guys! Now we're gonna charge forth, too!
Yeah!
Jump! Sodom! Gomorrah!
Wh-What the heck...?!
Straw Hat!
Thank you for helping us,
the entire Franky Family!
Fire the connection cannons!
Whoa! Cool!
Those must be the highest-grade bulls.
Not bad!
Dammit! Those bastards!
You idiots!
Don't be reckless!
Thanks for your help!
What a cheerful bunch!
Hey, monster granny!
Is this as fast as it goes?
It's not fast at all.
Well, just hold your horses.
Once it gets on the railway, you'll see.
Railway?
Where the heck is that?
Looks like it's drifted quite a ways away.
But I've observed the sea train
since its development.
Don't underestimate me!
I see it! Let's go!
Urgent message from the engine room!
The train will get on the railway shortly.
Once it does, it'll rapidly accelerate!
Hold on tight to something so
that your injuries won't be severe.
So, we'll get injured regardless?
Tsk! I missed it.
But I'm just getting started!
Hey! Behave!
Grandma! That was close!
That was close! A little to the right!
Just wait and see!
I'll make it next... Huh?!
Chimney! Gonbe!
You guys came with us?!
Yep, we did!
For God's sake!
Hurry up and
come inside!
Or you'll be blown away!
We're okay! We're okay!
Chimney!
I'm gonna fall!
D-Don't let go!
I'm being blown away!
H-Hold on a sec, okay?
I'll stop the train right away!
Oh, that's right!
The brake doesn't work on this train!
Oops! Hm? What the heck?
That kinda looks fun.
Ah! Straw Hat brother! Hello!
Straw Hat! Hurry and get
Chimney and Gonbe inside!
Once we get on the railway,
they'll be blown away!
Okay!
Ah! All right! They got on the railway!
Really?! Hey! Let me see!
Yeah, you're right. I see, I see...
Just as you'd expect from Kokoro-san!
She's something else!
Yeah, indeed.
For a while, I was afraid of
what was going to happen.
Indeed, indeed.
That's exactly right.
With those high waves, it must've
been hard to find the railway.
Yeah, indeed.
You're exactly righ... Ah...
Indeed, indeed, indeed. Ah...
Well, well, well, she's something...
She's something else!
I-I-Indeed...
W-We definitely have to let Iceberg-san know.
Y-You're right.
I-I'm sure he's worried.
Well, well, well, indeed. Indeed!
Rock...!
Paper...!
Well, I bet he's fine.
We're talking about a guy who
survived being hit by a sea train...
Did you know... that the violent
disciple of Tom, Cutty Flam, died?
He was hit by the sea train.
Iceberg...
you can do it.
You're the first disciple of Tom,
the world's greatest shipwright.
I'm sure you can do it... I'm sure...
Kokoro-san, let's drink
together one of these days...
...when we have something to drink to.
Yeah.
Tom-san... please just watch.
I'll take over your will.
I'll protect... everything...
This town... and these blueprints as well.
"Four years later"
Iceberg-san, you have a guest.
He said you'd know who if I tell you "Cutty Flam."
Franky...?
Shall I show him in here?
No...
turn him away.
What a roundabout way of meeting.
Well... anyway, what's up with
that funny looking body of yours?
Shut up! Since my whole
body came to be of no use,
I rebuilt my body using
iron scraps and escaped death!
More importantly,
I heard that your company contracts to
build ships for the World Government!
I'm not gonna tolerate you doing
things that help the Government!
They took Tom-san and...
And who made the weapons
that caused the incident?!
I'm sure you have things you wanna say to me,
but don't think that I've forgiven
you in the past four years.
I'm surprised that you had the nerve
to show your face after what happened!
What'd you say?!
I completely thought that you were dead...
...since the Government told me so.
Even if Tom-san forgave you,
I'm not going to forgive you!
H-Hey! What the hell are these?!
Aren't these the blueprints we
saw for that ancient weapon?!
Don't use the name Cutty Flam from now on.
The Government couldn't
get this out of Tom-san.
It's only a matter of time before I get targeted.
Leave the island with them... Franky.
Leave this island?
Cutty Flam from Tom's Workers is dead.
As long as you don't use that name,
there'll be no connection between us.
In addition, if you leave the island,
the blueprints' whereabouts
will vanish into the darkness.
H-Hold on a sec!
What happens if they come after you
when you don't have them?!
I've said what I came to say.
Hey! Hey, Iceberg!
We may not see each other again.
Hey! Wait!
Do you want to end up like Tom-san?
Keep the blueprints with you!
If, by any chance, you find that your
life is in danger, just hand them over!
If you don't wanna do that, then you
can even burn them before their eyes!
If you were me, would you do that?
Tom-san achieved so many great things,
and he gave up everything in order to
preserve these blueprints for the future.
At least, as long as there's a risk
that a woman named Nico Robin
can restore the weapon,
the world needs those blueprints to fight back.
If I continue to keep them with me...
...even if I am to be killed...
I won't give them to the Government!
Are you sure?
I may build this weapon.
Is it okay to trust me?
Doesn't my giving them
to you answer that question?
We never change, huh?
Whenever we meet face to face,
we yell at each other.
I still won't forgive you... and you
may feel the same about me, too.
Franky... I'm... really...
...glad that... you're alive.
Wait! Stupid-berg!
I'm not gonna leave this island!
I'll do what I wanna do!
I would never do what you
tell me to, even if it kills me!
Never!
You Moron-ky! Why don't
you get what I'm saying?!
This is in order to protect the blueprints!
Shut up! It's you who's not getting it!
I'm not gonna leave no matter what!
Tsk! Why am I remembering
him at a time like this?!
Is that idiot... Iceberg... doing okay?
We killed him.
Ahh... I thought I'd die.
Well, obviously!
Geez, I told you, didn't I?!
I said you'd get blown away!
Ow, ow...
Anyway, that acceleration sure was crazy.
--Geez...
--Yeah, really, that scared me!
I hit my lower back.
Hold on a sec...
There are weird guys in here.
What?! Who are they?!
You guys!
You, too!
I decided to go with you guys.
No matter how hard I tried
to stop you, you didn't stop.
The enemy you'd go this far
to rescue your friend from
is also the culprit who tried to kill Iceberg-san.
In addition, there are lots of
things that I wanna say to them!
Paulie! We're not gonna
let you steal all the glory!
Thinking that we'd be able to find
Iceberg-san's assassins if we followed you,
we hid in the tender together!
So... it seems we were right.
Let us join you guys in this battle.
And, of course...
...the foes you're gonna get revenge
on took Big Bro Franky as well.
That's right! And we clearly know who they are!
Hey, Galley-La!
How are you gonna take responsibility
if something happens to Bro?!
Shut up! It's Iceberg-san
who's endured the most!
What're you guys going on about?!
Paulie! First, explain it to us! What's going on?!
He's right, Paulie.
You know the true culprit, don't you?
Just tell us.
We're not that dense.
We have a rough idea as to who it is.
We're not gonna be surprised.
Well, I guess you could guess if they
suddenly disappeared for no reason.
Then, I'll tell you straight.
The true identities of those masked men are...
...Lucci, Kaku, Kalifa and Blueno from the bar.
It was them who tried to kill Iceberg-san!
What?! You never even guessed that?!
B-But you said they went
back to their hometowns!
Why would they, during an emergency like this?!
We thought it was Michael and
Hoichael from the backstreets.
--That's right!
--Who the hell are they?!
What?! You don't know them?!
They're famous in the backstreets!
That's right!
How would I know?!
To start with, you guys are--
All right! Boy, I ate a lot.
I'm finally full.
Oof.
Well, then...
Although we got in fights back in
town with both the Franky Family
and the Galley-La shipwrights,
we're all going after the same enemy now.
The strongest one among the guys
we're gonna fight is that pigeon guy.
He's mine. I'm definitely gonna beat him up.
Yeah. This is a battle to get back
what those four took from us.
In any case, if we don't
reach them, nothing will end.
Ahh! Grandma! Grandma!
It's Aqua Laguna!
Oh? It's already here?!
Chimney! Let me see it!
This is bad!
Kokoro-san! Is it okay for you to leave
the engine room at a time like this?!
We somehow need to dodge that high wave!
I told you, didn't I?
That we can't control Rocketman.
Even when we want to operate it,
nothing works, including the brake.
My job ended when the train got on the railway.
Hence, the train is always
running at full throttle.
No one can stop it anymore.
Oh, no... Luffy!
If we don't do anything, the train will
crash into the big wave! Hey, Luffy!
When we have the same goal...
...it's senseless to fight separately.
Yeah.
You're right.
Listen. We're comrades.
Our friends are also in
the train that left before us.
Our fighting force will still increase.
Guys! Don't let that big wave beat us!
We'll all achieve our goal!
Let's go!
Yeah!
We had a dream that day
Our belief in ourselves
makes us able to cross the wildly surging ocean
You're braver and more caring than anyone else
If you ever depart this ship
and live in a different world
In the end, we can all surely smile
Hey, look! That wave is really huge! Amazing!
Ahhh! If we don't do something,
it'll collide with Rocketman!
Everyone, brace yourself!
Are we gonna die?
Well then, let's do it, shall we, Captain?
--Yeah!
--What're you guys gonna do?!
We're gonna fire a cannon!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Smash the Wave! Luffy and Zoro
Use the Strongest Combo!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!