Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates,
attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before
his death drove people to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men head for the Grand Line
in pursuit of their dreams!
The world has truly
entered a Great Pirate Era!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever,
I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map
has been verified,
it's not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard
someone else's biorhythm
and pretend it isn't there!
We're going to gather up
all our dreams
and set out in search
of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and do you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered
just before his death
drove people around
the world to the seas.
My treasure?
If you want it, you can have it!
Find it!
I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered
a Great Pirate Era!
I can see the Gates of Justice now,
but is it possible to go there
on a regular boat?
I don't have much time anyway.
I guess I'll try something.
Here we go!
Whoa! Pirate guy!
What're you doing?!
Sanji-kun...
Were you really
not able to defeat her?
Did you really fight seriously?
It was that woman who
you fought, wasn't it?
You're soft with women.
I'm sorry about the key.
That's not it!
I'm saying that because
of that stupid chivalry,
you're gonna lose your life!
You're gonna stick to it even
after getting hurt like this?!
What're you gonna do if you die?!
It's not like...
I want to die.
But
I grew up having the idea that
I shouldn't kick women beat into me.
So...
even if it costs me my life...
...I won't kick a woman!
You're a fool.
Fool!
Hey! What're you doing, Nami?!
If running away is also
against your chivalry,
at least ditch that chivalry!
It's not worth dying in vain over.
Leave that woman to me.
Also...
I think a little more of
your chivalry than I did before.
What?!
Did she just say
that she loves me more?
No, she didn't!
I'm not kind.
Neither am I.
Sounds like we can get along.
Yoyoi!
Hold it!
The octopus guy!
I won't...
I won't let you get away!
Nami, you go deal with that woman!
I'll do something about this guy!
Okay!
Yoi! Yoi! Yoyoyoi!
Are you going to be in my way?!
Cloven...
Cross!
How dare she?!
She got away again!
You're dealing with me!
Come on!
"Fukurou's Miscalculation!
My Cola Is the Water of Life"
Seriously, there's no way you can cross
water like this on a boat, now is there?
Are you an idiot?!
But Robin was taken to those gates!
Unless I hurry up, I won't
be able to bring her back!
I should be able to reach the
building right in front of it, right?
Hey! What're you doing?!
Wait, pirate guy!
Calm down!
If I can't cross the sea,
then I have no choice but to jump!
We came to tell you how to
get to the Gates of Justice!
What?
What's this place?
A basement?
It's an undersea passage.
To get to the
Gates of Justice, you go under the sea.
I see.
Okay, then!
Hey, wait!
Do you know how to get there?!
In any case, you're amazing.
I'm impressed that you knew
about a passage like this!
I saw Lucci's servant going down
the stairs laughing very loudly.
So I followed them.
"The servant"
If they don't know where the entrance is,
they can't come after us!
Serves them right!
Lucci and that black-haired lady
went through the doors, too.
So these are the ones, huh?
These are quite strong iron doors.
Do you know how to open them?
The servant was touching around here,
so I bet you can operate
them with this keyhole...
...though we don't have the key.
You guys, stay back.
Huh? What're you gonna do?
We can go to the Gates of
Justice through here, right?
Er... Yeah...
Third Gear!
They opened...
All right! I'm heading there now!
What?! How come you're small now?!
That pirate guy sure is interesting!
Now, let's get back to work, too!
I-I just heard a loud noise.
Was that my imagination?
No, it couldn't have been.
Could that noise have been one of
the pirates destroying the doors?
What?! That's not possible!
Those are thick iron doors!
Besides, there's no way that
they could find those doors!
Well, they should know where they are,
since a child and her pet were following us.
What?!
I-If you knew that,
why didn't you kill them?!
Because...
...I was given no such order.
Wh...
What?! You idiot!
For something so trivial,
use your own discretion!
Can't you tell what'll happen if
you don't do anything about it?!
So what're you saying?!
Are you saying that
someone's headed this way?!
I would say that's the case.
Ahh! I'm scared!
Oh, shut up!
Oh, that was me.
Listen, Lucci!
Your main priority
is to protect my life!
You got that?!
Also, kill anyone
who tries to get in my way!
Defying me is an act of rebellion
against the World Government!
They deserve to be killed!
Huh?! What's that look?!
You have no time to worry
about others, Nico Robin.
Hell is already around the corner.
Lucci! Bring her already.
All right! My body's back to normal!
Just wait, Robin!
I'll be sure to beat the crap
out of that pigeon guy!
Well, it was his own fault
that Sanji-kun lost...
...but what in the world
did she do to him?
What's with this woman?
She's got some nerve.
Dammit! When I have to refill
my cola as soon as possible...
For someone with such a large body,
he sure does like to jump around.
Chapapa... I'm right here.
Seems like you're at least quick
when it comes to escaping.
Chapapa...
I'm under no obligation
to take your proud punches.
Franky Triangle Jacker!
Chapapa.
No way...
I'd get
hit by sideburns like that!
I've got you!
Weapons Left!
Seems like I'm almost out of cola.
I'd better go to the kitchen now!
Hold it!
Dammit! He dodged my attack!
Damn wimp, you're an
expert at running away!
Chapa!
What'd you say?!
What's the matter, wimp?
You're not running away this time?
You bastard!
You made me mad with that word!
Take my killer fist!
It's a super heavy punch combined
with Finger Pistol's speed!
Solid Beast!
Chapapa...!
Such a modest, ineffective punch...
Strong...
Iron Body!
...Hammer!
That was a pathetic punch.
Solid Beast!
Your punches are flabby.
No.
Your punches are limp.
Then, your punches are flimsy.
Your underpants are lazy.
Underpants?
They're not punches!
Underpants! That's what you are!
You damn bra jerk!
Shut up, socks!
Long johns!
Loose shorts!
Loincloth!
Chapapapapa!
Get off of me, you bastard!
Shut up, change purse!
All right!
I was able to enter the kitchen!
There it is! A huge refrigerator!
Is that him?
A gorilla
power holder... probably...
Dammit!
Three minutes have already passed?
I used the rumble ball too soon.
What am I gonna do?
Yoyoi!
Disappear from this world!
This is the finishing blow!
Yoyo...!
You bastard!
Good! It's got a lock!
Chapa! Kumadori!
All right! I locked him in!
How dare you...?
Hey, hold on a sec, gorilla!
I need that fridge!
Ahh! CP9 and the punk!
I'm Franky! I'm on your side, remember?!
Who'd you call a gorilla?!
You're too slow!
Listen.
Just like Luffy,
I haven't forgiven you yet.
The reason Usopp left us was...
It all goes back to you!
Give us Usopp back!
Like I said, you guys
were with him earlier.
That's not important right now!
Don't you wanna save Nico Robin?!
I do! Robin!
Then get three bottles of cola from
that fridge and give them to me!
With cola, I can power up!
I'll take care of these guys in
an instant and take their keys!
What kind of idiot actually
gets stronger with cola?
Shut up! That'd be me!
Just how long...
are you gonna
keep up the comedy act?!
On top of that, you were trying to
have a tea break during a battle?
How rude!
Solid Beast Secret Technique...
...Owl Thrashing!
Chapapapapa!
Beans Left!
What was that?!
Ahh! This is terrible!
That's right!
He's on our side right now!
I'll do what he told me to.
If I open and close the door
within a second, he can't come out!
Yoyoi!
The door has...
All right!
Franky!
Thanks!
Fresh!
What the...?
Freshness is most important!
Vegetable Punch! Take this!
Solid Beast.
Hey! That was vegetable juice!
Why would I want health to
be a priority, you bastard?!
Give me cola!
Oh, so it wasn't because he was thirsty.
Yoyoi! The door...
Here you go!
Thanks!
I'm feeling good!
Well...
...let me sit.
My work in
the field is done for now.
Stop being so upset.
Don't fight.
Why don't you have some tea?
Tea wouldn't...
...give me energy! You moron!
He's... funny.
Hey!
What's with that "I wonder what
happens with other drinks" look?!
This'll be the last time, you damn deer!
So it doesn't depend
on how you're feeling?
I need only cola!
That's cola! Cola without a doubt!
Thanks!
I don't know what the deal is,
but I'm not gonna let you have your way!
Tempest Kick!
Franky!
Super!
Chapapa... What's the deal?
It's not like drinking cola would
make a difference or anything.
Guard yourself.
Chapa? What a fool.
Are you gonna give me
another pathetic punch?
Strong... Hammer!
Whoooa! Amazing!
Sorry.
My punches earlier were...
...indeed pathetic.
Zoro-kun, what's your idea
to get these handcuffs off?
Yeah. Now that it's come to this,
we'll play rock-paper-scissors
to decide whose wrist
we'll resolutely...
Ahh! What's with you coming
up with such a scary idea?!
There's no way we could do that!
Really?
Then, I've got another idea.
Ahh! Ahh! I don't wanna hear it!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Zoro Busts Out a New Technique!
The Sword's Name is Sogeking?"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!