Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
ONE PIECE!
Compasses only cause delays
Delirious with fever, I take the helm
If the dusty treasure map has
been verified, it’s not a legend!
When it comes to personal storms,
simply ride aboard someone else’s biorhythm
and pretend it isn’t there!
We’re going to gather up all our dreams
and set out in search of something to find
A coin in my pocket,
and you wanna be my friend?
We are, We are on the cruise!
We are!
Wealth, fame, power...
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
once attained everything
this world has to offer.
The words he uttered just before his death
drove people around the world to the seas.
My treasure? If you want it, you can have it!
Find it! I left everything
this world has to offer there!
And so men rushed onto the
Grand Line in pursuit of romanticism!
The world has truly entered a Great Pirate Era!
--What does Gonbe's "Go" mean?
--Hey, pops. Give me that water-water candy.
Here you go, thanks!
Mister!
--What does Sanji's "Sa" mean?
--The barbecue last night was the best!
--Yeah.
--And you have a good eye for food, too!
Yeah, I'm a first-class cook, so... See you, then.
See you later, pops!
See you!
Ah! I see pirate ladies!
What?! Whoa!
Nami-san!
Please tell us how you two
joined the Straw Hat Pirates!
--Robin-chan! Mellorine!
--Please tell us everything there is to
know about the beautiful female pirates!
I can't really talk about
personal things like that.
We aren't going to get
much shopping done like this.
What type of men do you like?
Let's see...
Nami-san might say that
"Sanji-kun is my type"...!
--I wonder what the cook guy's doing...
--Nami-san! I love you, too!
How would you two feel about putting
out a swimsuit photo book with us?
What? Swimsuit?!
There's no doubt that it'll be a best seller!
Hey, you. You've got some guts!
Oh, I-I'm sorry!
I'll cost you a fortune.
So how much can you pay?
Huh?
Are you serious?
Sure, since Luffy used most
of that 100 million Berries,
we need to earn money through
photo books or whatever else we can.
Hold on a sec...
A swimsuit photo book of Nami-san
and Robin-chan would have...
...pics like this...
...and like this...
Hey! What were you guys
just fantasizing about?!
Whoa! This guy is the Straw Hats' cook!
Sanji-kun!
I'm gonna kill every single one of you
who just had a lewd look on your face!
Nami-san. Robin-chan.
I drove those damn noisy
flies away, so please rest easy.
Thanks, Sanji-kun. Now we can
do our shopping in peace.
This is my chance for a date. On top of that,
I'll be between two pretty women!
By the way, about today's schedule,
how does this sound?
The three of us will rent a pool
--Cook guy!
--and have a nice date on the water.
And then we'll go to a nice restaurant.
What?!
I'm hungry!
You just ate some water-water candy!
I'm hungry! I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
Okay, then. I'll give you some money,
so you guys buy some food and go home.
I might go out on a date with them,
so don't be so whiny!
I don't wanna go home yet!
Crying won't get you anywhere!
Don't worry, Chimney.
Sanji-kun has a harsh tongue,
but he's very nice to women.
That's right. He isn't someone
who'd overlook a lady in need.
Nami-san... Robin-chan...
Chimney, have Sanji-kun play
with you to your heart's content.
Yep!
Well, then...
Oh, no!
Seriously... you're the
very example of a burden.
I guess it can't be helped.
So... do you know a place
that serves good food?
All right!
--Now, let's go.
--Okay!
"Sanji's Shock! Mysterious Old Man
and His Super Yummy Cooking!"
Are you really sure there's a place that
serves good food in a place like this?
Yep! Grandma's friend is running it.
Granny Kokoro's friend?
Your dishes taste good, too, but Gramps
Bang-Bang's dishes are tastier!
Oh, is that right?
Oh, it's right after we go down those stairs.
Seriously, that food was awful.
I can't believe someone
said this place was good.
I thought I was finally gonna have a
decent meal after getting off the ship...
Hey, hey...
This way!
Hey, Gramps Bang-Bang!
Cook something for me!
Hey, is this drunk old man really a cook?
I'm hungry! Wake up!
Oh, leave him alone.
I've got some foodstuffs, so I'll cook for you.
This kitchen is unexpectedly well organized.
I'm hungry! I'm hungry!
He uses a fanatical kitchen knife!
It's well taken care of, too.
Let's see...
Oh, this is it.
Sorry, gramps! I'm borrowing your kitchen.
Good morning, Gramps Bang-Bang!
Hey, where'd you learn how
to use that kitchen knife?
Ah, at a restaurant I used
to work at called Baratie.
Here you go. It's done.
All right! Thanks!
Yummy!
Are you Zeff's apprentice?
What?! You know that damn geezer, gramps?!
Besides me, that lad Zeff is the only
one who uses that kitchen knife.
"Lad"?! That damn geezer used
to be the captain of a pirate group!
Ha! From my perspective, everyone's a lad!
So, what're you doing in Water Seven?
Were you kicked out of Zeff's restaurant?
It's not like that. I left there
in order to go to the All Blue.
All Blue, you said?
Yeah, a legendary sea that's said to
have the world's best foodstuffs...
It's a miracle sea.
I became a pirate in order to go there.
Yeah, I get it. You, too, are gonna
tell me that sea is just a legend, right?
The All Blue does exist.
It's a sea that any skilled cook
would dream of visiting at least once.
But it's definitely a place one can't
reach with halfhearted determination.
Many cooks have taken up
the challenge to go there
but ended up giving up on their dreams
without ever seeing that miracle.
It's a cruel sea.
Good heavens...!
So it really isn't just a legend?!
Could it possibly be... that you've
been to the All Blue, gramps?!
--Nope.
--You haven't?!
What I was watching just now
was a picture from my early days!
Don't act misleading!
Geez, what a cheeky old man.
Hm? I ran out of booze.
Thank you! That was good!
This is in return for you letting
me use your cooking tools.
Thanks!
Hey, we're going back now.
What? I wanna eat more.
You guys have been eating too much!
Well, wait, lad.
As thanks for the booze,
eat my food before you go.
Oh, don't worry about it.
I wanna eat it!
You're still young. Don't be so modest.
Hey, are you okay?
Lad, say that line after
you see my cooking skill...
See, what did I tell you?
Oh, yeah, we've got a good doctor,
so I'll introduce you to...
You fixed it yourself?!
Oops!
Is this old man serious?
Hey, gramps, you don't have to
push yourself. If you like, I can...
Don't panic, lad!
H-Huh? Me?
Sit there quietly and watch!
Okay, okay, I got it, I'll watch.
Hey, hey, his hand's shaking...
Hey, he's cutting them in a way
that makes use of his shaking hand.
Hm? He's adept for a drunk person.
Here you go!
Yaay!
Thank you!
Yummy!
He was indeed adept, but...
...any way you look at it,
it's just plain old fried rice.
What's the matter, lad?
Aren't you gonna eat it?
I have a policy of eating everything
served to me. So I'll gratefully eat it.
This is super damn good!
The way he cooked was nothing special.
No difference in the foodstuffs, either.
And yet, why is this flavor so deep?!
It's damn good!
What, was it so good that
it made you shake, lad?
Thanks! It was yummy!
S-Something like that.
So do you know why it was so good?
No, I don't.
It seems you're somewhat
confident in your ability,
but if you can't figure out something like that,
the All Blue will just be
an unfulfilled dream for you.
Chimney! Gonbe!
Stay here for a bit, will you?
Sure.
I'm gonna reveal the secret of gramps' flavor!
It's not how he cooks or the foodstuffs he uses.
In that case, that's the only decisive factor!
Oh, hey! You're the cook guy in the
Straw Hats. Looking for something?
Pops! Are these all the condiments you've got?
Yeah. Our product lineup is the best!
This isn't it.
This isn't it, either.
Pops! Don't you have other stuff?!
Other stuff, huh?
Since Water Seven is a city of trade,
our store has all sorts of condiments
from around the world, so...
Dammit... Is it a condiment
that gramps mixed himself?
No, it's more fundamental...
Ugh! Dammit! I can't figure it out!
Oh? Sanji-kun!
That's strange. He didn't notice us.
Wrong person?
Must be--Chimney and Gonbe
weren't with that guy, either.
Hm? I've come this far?
This area took quite a bit
of damage from Aqua Laguna.
That's Galley-La's restoration team.
Oh? You're one of the Straw Hats!
Thanks for the food yesterday!
Hey, guys! Have a little break! Let's have lunch!
Okay!
Whoa! That's what I've been waiting for!
Yummy!
Hey, would you like one, too?
You dummy. It's rude to offer a plain
salted rice ball to the Straw Hats' cook.
I guess you're right!
No, I'll have one, too.
Thinking made me hungry.
Oh, then don't stop at one.
Eat as many as you want!
Thanks.
At any rate, you guys astounded us.
You outwitted Navy Headquarters.
That's incredible!
Hey, cook guy! What's wrong?! Are you okay?!
That darn Gramps Bang-Bang!
I hope he wasn't so drunk that he
put weird stuff in the rice balls!
What?! Gramps Bang-Bang?!
Did that old man make these rice balls?!
They're compliments of that gramps!
If you have complaints, talk to him!
I get it now! I finally get what
the secret of his flavor is!
I appreciate this a damn lot. So, this is it!
Thanks!
Y-Yeah.
There.
Shhh.
Gramps!
I got it, gramps.
Oh, it's you.
Welcome back, cook guy!
Gramps, the decisive factor of your
flavor isn't some special ingredient.
Well, it's actually one of the
most basic ingredients... salt.
I heard you're the one who gave those
salted rice balls to the Galley-La guys.
You didn't?
Hm? Well, it's true. But that's
not the right answer yet.
The thing is that this salt is
unlike any I've ever used before.
It isn't simply salty like regular salt is.
It has a deep flavor.
How are you able to get such
a special salt on this island?
The answer is...
...Aqua Laguna.
Aqua Laguna is a detestable
and hated existence.
But it brings special seawater
that contains plentiful sea minerals.
The salt made from that
seawater is a special salt
that contains plentiful sea minerals.
That's the answer!
Correct! I've lost!
But, gramps, in order to make salt,
you need a large amount of seawater.
It's nearly impossible to
collect seawater in that storm.
There's gotta be a special way to do it.
Gramps, I'm responsible
for cooking for the gang.
I want to serve the best food
to the crew at all times.
I know it's a special salt.
But please give me some of your salt!
Say, lad...
Today is another fine day, isn't it...?
Huh? Y-Yeah.
We've been having sunny days
since the Aqua Laguna ebbed.
There's a place I wanna go.
Would you take me there?
A place you wanna go?
Lad, go up to one of the rooftops around here.
Rooftop?
Gramps, is this place okay?
Yeah.
Oh, it's ready!
Ready? You mean salt?
I see only roofs around here.
Take a closer look.
This area...
...gets submerged all the way up
to the rooftops during Aqua Laguna.
And after Aqua Laguna ebbs,
the seawater on the roof
gets completely evaporated.
And then, what's left is this.
I see! The salt of Aqua Laguna!
Hold on a sec... Does that mean...
...that all the roofs around here are like that?!
That's right. All the roofs around here
have finished making salt by now.
Take as much as you want.
This is more than enough!
Lad, the salt of Aqua Laguna is
different from the salt from any sea.
There are still unknown seas in the world.
The All Blue...
Whoa, that's quite a bit of salt you collected.
Is that all salt?!
Our journey has still a long way to go, so...
By the way, gramps, when we got here,
two guys came out complaining.
Seriously, that food was awful.
Oh, those guys... It's about time...
Hey, gramps!
Let us have the same food we had earlier.
Well, I thought the food tasted awful at first,
but now I've got a craving to eat it again.
Gramps, what's going on?
I served them herbal medicine food.
Sailors can't eat good food on the ship,
so their taste buds don't work well,
but once the herbs' effect kicks in,
food starts tasting good.
I somehow feel spry, too.
Gramps, please, we're starving here!
Gramps, why do you stay in
Water Seven when you're so skilled?
Because I can't get away
from that salt anymore.
I see... but gramps,
when I come here next time,
I'll tell you the stories about
my experience in the All Blue.
Oh, yeah? I'll be looking forward to it.
Gramps!
Is your stall open, gramps?
Whoa! You ladies can eat free!
You're so wonderful!
Ladies in Water Seven really are the best!
Isn't that the real reason, you dirty old man?!
Cook guy, thanks for today. I had fun!
It's me who should be saying thanks.
Thanks to you guys...
--Huh?
--No, nothing.
Well then, we're gonna
go back to Grandma now!
Yeah! Be careful!
Hm?
Usopp?
"What, Luffy? Now you're
saying that you want me back?
Seriously, what will I do with you guys?
You can't do anything without me.
Well, all right, if you're so insistent,
I suppose I could come back."
Yeah, it's best if I can make it
so that they'll ask me to rejoin.
So this is pattern 23.
"Oh, hey, Chopper. It's a fine day today.
Let's go fishing or something."
"Hey, Luffy! Wanna come along?"
This one's good, too. Operation
Act Like Nothing Happened... Or...
"I've decided to head to Elbaf!"
"What?! Please don't go!"
"I was just kidding. I know how you guys feel."
"So you're coming back, Usopp?!"
"Of course I am, silly!
Geez, you guys must like me so much!"
What the hell is that idiot doing?
Food's ready!
Whoa!
Yummy! Today's food is especially yummy!
What's this?!
This is delicious!
Yeah, it is!
It really is yummy! Hey, Sanji!
Hm?
Thanks for always making yummy food!
Thanks!
There's more if you want it!
Hey, eyebrows! Give me more!
You can get it yourself!
--Give me more!
Give me more, too!
I'll have some more, too.
My pleasure!
Lad! I'll be waiting to hear
the stories of your journey!
Whoa!
S-Straw Hat!
Th-There's trouble! The wanted
posters have been released!
Whoa! They're finally out?!
Straw Hat, the bounty on
your head has gotten crazy!
And the others have bounties, too!
Anyway, take a look at these!
On the next episode of One Piece!
"Everyone Finally Has A Bounty!
A Pirate Group Worth Over 600 Million!"
I'm gonna be King of the Pirates!!