Germany, Einzbern Castle
— Eight Years Ago —
Master Kiritsugu!
Your child is born!
She's so cute.
So small, so delicate...
Look, Kiritsugu.
She has your eyes.
I'm so glad that
she was born.
Iri.
I will be the cause
of your death.
I know.
The Einzberns have dreamed of this day.
It is the very reason I exist.
When I came to know your ideals,
I made your wish my own.
You made me
who I am today.
You have guided me.
You offered me a better life
than that of a simple puppet.
You needn't pity me.
I'm a part of you now.
- So...
- I...
I have no right
to hold that child.
Kiritsugu, do not forget.
You're striving to make a world where
no one needs to cry that way.
That is the ideal
of Kiritsugu Emiya.
Eight more years, and your fight
will come to an end.
And our ideal
will become reality.
The Holy Grail will save you.
I'm certain of it.
So take this child, Illyasviel,
and hold her.
And be proud,
like any other father.
Torino, Italy
— Three Years Ago —
Torino, Italy - Three Years Ago
A command seal?
Yes, the mark that appeared
on your right hand.
It identifies you as a participant
in the Holy Grail War.
A stigmata, bestowing upon you
the power to command a Servant.
Kirei Kotomine.
The Holy Grail War.
The battle for a relic
that performs miracles.
I have been chosen?
Normally, those chosen by the Grail as
Masters for the Servants are all mages.
It's highly unusual
for someone like you,
...with no connection to magic,
to be chosen so early on.
Servants...
I still find it strange to command
the summoned spirits...
...of ancient heroes
to fight as familiars.
I know it's hard
to believe.
Heroes from every age and nation will
come back to life in the modern world,
...killing one another
to vie for supremacy.
That is the Holy Grail War.
Naturally, there is an unspoken agreement
among all involved parties...
...to conduct the battles
in secret.
To ensure that this rule is upheld, we of
the Holy Church send an observer.
Can one of us really act
as a judge...
...in a battle between
magicians?
A Mages Association member...
...would be too partial to one party
to assure fairness.
And thus, as he did
sixty years ago,
...we will have your father
watch over our battle.
My father will be
coming to Fuyuki?
But wouldn't it pose
a problem...
...for the overseer's child
to be a participant?
Tokiomi.
Let's get to the point.
Kirei, everything we've spoken of
thus far is known to all participants.
But there is an
additional reason...
...I've asked you and
Tokiomi Tohsaka here today.
And what would
that be?
Actually, we found proof long ago
that the Holy Grail that will appear...
...in Fuyuki is not the sacred relic
that belonged to the Son of God.
So I gathered.
Otherwise, an order to retrieve it
would have been given...
...to us of the Eighth
Sacrament Assembly.
Be that as it may, Fuyuki's Holy Grail
is too powerful to ignore.
It is an omnipotent
wish-granting device.
Who knows what disaster
it could unleash,
...should it fall into
the wrong hands.
In which case, the next best course
of action would be to ensure...
...that the Fuyuki Grail at least
falls into the right hands.
The Tohsakas are
a family of mages,
...but mages with a long history
of friendship with the Church.
We know what kind
of person Tokiomi is.
And more than anything, their intentions
for the Grail are plain.
To reach the Root.
That is the Tohsaka family's
sole desire.
But the Einzberns and Matous
have both forgotten...
...the wish we once shared
with them.
The other Masters
go without saying.
Who knows what dark plans
they may harbor for the Grail.
Then the goal of my participation
is ensuring...
...Tokiomi Tohsaka's victory.
Of course, we will maintain
the appearance of enemies.
But in secret,
we will work together...
...to defeat the other five Masters
and assure our victory.
To that end, Kirei,
...you will be transferred from the
Church to the Mages Association,
...where you will
become my student.
The official orders have
already been issued.
You must go to Japan
and study magic,
...and become a mage
of sufficient strength...
...to command a Servant in the
Holy Grail War in three years' time.
Now then...
Any questions, Kirei?
Only one.
What is the Grail's criteria
when it selects its Masters?
The Grail gives precedence to
those Masters who need it most.
So all the Masters have a reason
to covet the Grail?
Not necessarily.
I'm told that in the past, there were cases
in which command seals appeared...
...on those whom you would never
have expected to be chosen.
I see.
Kirei, are you still upset
over being chosen?
I didn't expect him to give
his consent so quickly.
My son would jump into a fire
if the Church ordered it.
To be honest,
I'm almost disappointed.
From his perspective, he's been drawn into
a war that has nothing to do with him.
No, perhaps this will
do him some good.
Only a few days ago,
he lost his wife.
A change of scenery
and a new mission...
...may be exactly what he needs
to nurse his wounds.
Fuyuki City, Japan
— One Year Ago —
Aoi.
Kariya, it's good to see you again.
You're back from your business trip?
This one took
a long time.
Yeah, I guess
it did.
Uncle Kariya!
Uncle Kariya, welcome back!
Rin.
Did you bring me
a present again?
Rin! Don't be rude!
Here you go.
Thanks, Uncle!
I'm glad you like it.
Where's Sakura?
Sakura's gone now.
Aoi?
You see, Sakura is no longer
my daughter or Rin's little sister.
She's been sent to join
the Matou family.
Why?
You know better than anyone why
the Matous would want children...
...who carry the blood
of mages.
The Tohsaka family elders decided
to give our ancient allies,
...the Matous, that which
they requested.
It wasn't my place
to speak out.
You're all right
with that?
When I married into the Tohsaka family,
when I decided to marry a mage,
...I knew what might
be required of me.
And you're all right
with that?!
A clan bearing
mage blood...
...can never expect the happiness
of a normal family.
That's not true!
When you married him,
you wanted happiness-
This is between the Tohsakas
and the Matous.
You left the world
of mages.
It doesn't concern you.
If you ever see Sakura,
be kind to her.
She was always
fond of you.
So, the failure had the nerve
to show his face here.
I told you to never
darken my doorstep again,
...Kariya.
I heard you adopted the Tohsakas'
second daughter.
You have sharp ears.
Is it that important to keep mages
in the Matou lineage?
Would you tell me we're wrong to?
You, of all people?
Whose fault do you think our present
reduced circumstances are?
Kariya.
Had you agreed to carry on the family name
and learn the secrets of the Matou,
...things wouldn't be
this bad.
You're not fooling anyone,
you vampire.
You only want the Grail
to give yourself eternal youth.
Next year, sixty years
will have passed.
But the Matous have no pawns to offer
for the Fourth Holy Grail War.
Though you have it, your brother Byakuya
lacks the power to control a Servant.
But even if we forfeit this round,
we could still win the next in 60 years.
The Tohsaka girl's womb
will bear us a powerful mage.
She has a lot of potential,
that one.
So, as long as you get the Grail,
you don't need Sakura Tohsaka.
What are you scheming?
A trade, Zouken.
I'll return from the next war,
Grail in hand.
And in return,
you will release her.
Don't be stupid.
You're a failure, and you haven't
trained a day in your life.
In a single year, you'll achieve
the power to control a Servant?
You have the magic to make
that happen, and you know it.
With your special worm techniques.
Implant me
with Crest Worms.
Kariya, do you want
to kill yourself?
The Matous should rely on themselves
to gain what they want.
I won't let anyone else
get involved.
Surely you're not concerned
for my wellbeing, Father.
If you're trying to keep her
out of this, Kariya,
...you're a little late.
You old bastard,
you didn't!
For the first three days,
she screamed her head off.
But on the fourth,
she stopped.
This morning, I threw her into the
worm pit to see how long she'd last.
It's been twelve hours,
and she's still breathing.
The Tohsakas
are very powerful.
Sakura!
Well, what will you
do now?
A single broken girl, violated
by worms from head to toe.
If you still wish to save her,
...I might think about it.
I agree.
But I shall continue her education
until you show results.
I still expect victory to come
in the war after this one.
But should you somehow manage
to retrieve the Grail, all the better.
Naturally, I'll no longer need
the girl in that case.
Her education will
only last a year.
You won't renege on your word.
Right, Zouken Matou?
Start by serving as their
breeding ground for a week.
If you don't die or go insane,
then I'll concede that you're serious.
It's finally here.
What does it say?
It's a report from the spies I sent
to the London Clock Tower.
It says the Grail chose a Master
from within the Clock Tower,
...the highest authority within
the Mages Association.
Who?
A man who will be a problem.
The eldest son of the famous
Archibald family,
...which has produced
nine generations of mages.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald.
London Clock Tower
— Present Day —
London Clock Tower - Present Day
In the world of mages,
lineage is everything.
This is because magic will not yield up
her secrets in a single generation.
A parent passes on the fruits of
a lifetime of training to his child.
Thus, the older the family of mages,
the greater their power.
You are no doubt wondering why I am
beginning with something so basic.
It is because a student submitted
this paper to me yesterday.
The paper is entitled "How Wizardry
Should Be in the New Century."
It objects to the traditions
I just spoke of.
It claims that if one were to
achieve a deep understanding...
...of the techniques and precise
control over mana application,
...it would allow one to overcome
any difference in inherent ability.
In short, even someone with diluted
blood could become a master mage.
To be honest, I've learned something
from reading this.
Silence, please.
I will be frank. This paper is
nothing but juvenile fantasies.
Blood determines
a mage's power.
This is hard,
unchanging reality.
Waver Velvet.
I am very, very disappointed
that one of my students...
...would indulge
in this nonsense.
Sir, I was only trying to raise a
question the Mages Association...
...has become too reluctant
to address--
Waver.
As I recall, your family has produced
mages for only three generations.
Listen to me.
Compared to the Mages Association's
history, your family is a newborn baby.
Shouldn't a baby learn to speak
before it tries to voice an opinion?
He made a fool of me!
Is that any way for
a teacher to act?!
Reading my paper made
him jealous! He's afraid of my talent!
That's why he embarrassed me
in front of everyone!
I'm sorry.
Are you all right?
I'm fine.
You're in the Department of Spiritual
Evocation, right? Why aren't you in class?
Well...
Mr. Archibald asked me
to run an errand for him.
That's why I was in a hurry.
I see. That's great.
Would you give this to him?
This?
Make sure he gets it.
It's supposed to be important.
Important?
Package origin...
Macedonia?
This is it!
Those rumors that Kayneth
will be fighting...
...in some kind of mages' tournament
in the Far East soon were true.
The Holy Grail War.
Two hundred years ago, the Einzberns,
Makiris, and Tohsakas,
...collectively known as
the Three First Families,
...worked together to summon the Holy Grail,
said to have the power to grant any wish.
But the Holy Grail would grant
only one supplication.
Their cooperation
turned to bloody war.
That was the beginning
of the Holy Grail Wars.
Ever since then,
once every sixty years,
...the Holy Grail appears
in the city of Fuyuki.
It selects seven mages with the right
to hold it and grants them the power...
...to summon the powerful Heroic Spirits
known as Servants.
Archer. Saber.
Lancer.
Rider.
Assassin.
Caster.
Berserker.
Divided into these seven classes,
Servants fight to the death...
...to determine who is worthy
to win the Grail.
So this Holy Grail War is
a battle of pure strength,
...where titles and influence
mean nothing.
It's the perfect place
for me.
Furthermore, in order to
summon a Servant,
...a relic of theirs is needed
to act as a catalyst.
A relic...
No matter how often I see it, this device
still strikes me as indecent.
I have a report from
the Clock Tower.
Lord El-Melloi has acquired
another relic.
His participation
is certain now.
It troubles me that two slots
are still unaccounted for.
Don't worry.
When the time comes, the Grail will
select seven, regardless of skill.
The ones it rounds out the group with
are nearly always weak.
Don't concern yourself
with them.
Speaking of matters
of concern, Kirei,
...no one saw you enter
the mansion, I trust?
Don't worry.
No familiars or magical devices, visible
or invisible, are watching this mansion.
- On that, you have--
- You have my guarantee.
No matter what tricks
they use,
...no one can deceive the eyes
of Hassan, the spy Heroic Spirit.
There is no trace of anyone
following my Master.
Please put your minds
at ease.
If a Servant has manifested,
my father is sure to know.
The other mages will not take action
for a while longer.
Assassin, you may go.
Continue guarding the
surrounding area.
As you wish.
But it's only a matter of time.
Before long, this place will be swarming
with familiars sent by the other Masters.
- What is that?
- Another investigation.
I have been gathering information
on the Einzbern Master.
Nine years ago,
the Einzberns,
...a family notoriously proud
of their pure blood,
...suddenly allowed an outsider mage
to marry into the family.
The Einzbern mages have devoted
themselves solely to alchemy,
...rendering them unfit
for combat.
Their losses in previous Holy Grail Wars
can all be traced to that fact.
They must have run out
of patience.
The man they chose
was perfect for their needs.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
The man known as
the Mage-Killer.
We've finally found the relic we've been
searching for in Cornwall all these years.
If you use it as a catalyst,
you'll be able to summon...
...what is likely the strongest
of the sword-wielding Servants.
Kiritsugu.
This is the greatest gift
the Einzbern can offer.
I am honored, Elder.
This time, there are to be
no survivors.
Hunt down the six
other Servants,
...and fulfill the Third Magic,
"Heaven's Feel."
Understood.
Kiritsugu Emiya?
I know that name.
So even the Church
has heard of him?
Emiya the Mage-Killer
was quite infamous in his time.
On the surface, he was a rogue mage
who didn't belong to the Association.
But the higher-ups found him quite
convenient for their own purposes.
Similar to us Executors
of the Holy Church?
Far worse.
Essentially, he's a freelance assassin
who specializes in killing mages.
He knows what mages
are capable of,
...so he deals with them in the way
most unlike a mage possible.
Read this.
Sniping. Poisoning.
Bombs in public places.
He once brought down an entire jetliner
just because his target was on it.
A man who will do anything
without a second thought.
It is because the world's laws
do not apply to mages...
...that we must carefully obey
the laws we set for ourselves.
But this man lacks any trace
of a mage's pride.
These methods he employs
are unforgivable.
Then what does this Kiritsugu Emiya
gain by hiring himself out as a killer?
Money, I would imagine.
As you can read
in that report,
...he's been involved in more
than just mage assassinations.
He's appeared in war zones
all over the planet,
...offering his services
as a mercenary.
May I borrow this report
for a while?
Let's go over
what we know, Iri.
Of the seven masters the Grail
will choose, we have identified four.
Tokiomi Tohsaka,
Tohsaka family head.
Fire mage. Uses Jewel Magic.
Very formidable.
Kariya Matou.
So they took the kid who left the family
and made him a Master, huh?
That old man
must be desperate.
Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald.
Wind and water affinity.
Expert in Necromancy,
Summoning, and Alchemy.
- And...
- Kiritsugu Emiya.
Newest member of the Einzbern family,
and their trump card.
The man I love.
And the fourth... No, fifth, is
Kirei Kotomine, sent by the Church.
By the Church?
He's the son of the overseer,
Father Risei Kotomine.
Reports say he studied under Tokiomi
Tohsaka starting three years ago,
...splitting with him after his
command seal appeared.
Did something happen?
It has his personal
history here...
Read it.
"Kirei Kotomine.
Followed his father on
pilgrimages since childhood.
Graduated from the Saint Ignatius
School of Divinity in Manresa.
Skipped two years,
graduating as Valedictorian."
He sounds
pretty impressive.
But he suddenly leaves
the primrose path...
...and volunteers for
the Holy Church.
Why would someone like that go to work
for a secret Church organization?
Maybe because
of his father?
It says here that he's a member of the
Church's Eighth Sacrament Assembly.
Then he would have pursued
that path from the start.
But until he arrived at the
same place as his father,
...he changed positions
three times.
He was even
an Executor once.
An Executor?
A heretic hunter.
In essence...
Exactly what I once was.
A mage-killer.
Kiritsugu Emiya...
His assassinations were always carried
out in clusters over a short period.
During the same general time periods,
he appeared in war zones,
...but only when the combat
was at its fiercest.
As if he had some obsession
with chasing his own death.
These are clearly the actions
of a man bent on suicide.
What does this mean?
Alchemy, Necromancy, Summoning,
Divination, Healing.
Look at all the categories
of magic he's studied.
Why so many?
He gets almost to the point
of mastery,
...then switches to another type
and never looks back.
It's as if he throws away everything
he's learned like yesterday's trash.
Iri.
This Kirei Kotomine
terrifies me.
He has no concept
of self-interest.
His actions are completely disconnected
from any thought of risk versus reward.
There's no way he's just a freelancer,
in it for the money.
The man has never experienced
passion in his entire life.
He believes in nothing.
He has no wish of any kind
to be granted.
For a man like that...
Then what is he after?
Why would he risk his life
for the Grail?
But the Grail chose Kirei Kotomine
as one of its Masters.
That's right.
He must have some reason
to want the Grail.
But I can't even begin
to imagine what it is.
And that terrifies me.
Kirei Kotomine.
Kiritsugu Emiya.
His endless string of battles came
to a sudden halt nine years ago.
His encounter with the
mages of the North,
...the Einzberns, is where
he found his answer.
So I must ask the question...
What did he seek in those battles?
And what, exactly,
did he find?
You just barely made it.
If the Grail's chosen you, that means
you've made some progress as a mage.
I'll give you
that much, Kariya.
But you look
like hell.
Does your left leg
still work?
Don't get mad.
If you get the Crest Worms inside you
worked up, they'll devour you.
Either way, I'd give you
a month at best.
That's plenty.
What?
I said that's plenty
of time.
Kariya, this is your present
for surviving an entire year.
I found the perfect relic
for you.
Don't let your father's kindness
go to waste.
I've got a command seal, too!
The Grail chose me!
The Grail recognized
my talent!
I can't just sit here!
I have to prepare to
summon my Servant!
Mikina Nishimoto, the sixth-grade girl who
went missing in Fuyuki two nights ago,
Serial Killings in Fuyuki City Good morning, Waver. Mikina Nishimoto,
the sixth-grade girl who went missing in Fuyuki two nights ago,
Morning, Waver! ...was found dead this
morning in the woods near Fukuyama Town.
...was found dead this morning
in the woods near Fukuyama Town.
Morning, Grandpa... Grandma.
Even Fuyuki's getting bad
these days.
It really is.
Anyway, Martha, roosters have been
making a racket since the sun came up.
What's that all about?
There are three roosters
in our yard.
In ours?
That's right. I wonder
where they came from?
Waver, you want
some coffee?
Waver, what happened
to your hand?
Crap!
That mark!
Mark?
You didn't have that mark
on your hand yesterday.
Jeez... I wish you
hadn't noticed that.
What's wrong, Waver?
Waver?
Nothing's wrong.
Here, have some coffee.
I put lots of milk
in it.
You two
like coffee, right?
Do I have to start their
hypnosis all over again,
...starting from me being their grandson,
just back from studying abroad?
I need to think of a cover story
for those roosters I stole, too.
I can't believe they really found the
legendary Excalibur's scabbard.
There's not a scratch on it.
Is this thing really 1,500 years old?
The object itself is a type
of Conceptual Weapon.
It doesn't rust or degrade,
as ordinary physical objects do.
Just like in the legend, it heals its owner's
wounds and halts the aging process.
Of course, that's only when supplied
with its original owner's mana.
In other words, a Master
can use this in tandem...
...with the summoned Heroic Spirit
to protect himself.
That's just like you. You're saying
that a tool is just a tool?
That goes for
the Servant, too.
No matter how famous
the Heroic Spirit,
...when summoned as a Servant, they're
nothing but a tool for their Master.
Anyone who lets their fantasies
get the better of them...
...will never be able
to win this battle.
And because you're this way,
my great-grandfather decided...
...that this scabbard was
the perfect relic for you.
What do you think?
Does his present
not satisfy you?
Of course not. Acht did
a wonderful job.
None of the other Masters
have something this powerful.
What's wrong with it, then?
Given how perfectly the relic
is connected to it,
...the spirit we're after will surely
respond to the summons.
The legendary King of Knights,
Arthur Pendragon.
My own compatibility with him
is a secondary concern.
But the wielder of Excalibur is sure to
be the strongest Saber-class Servant.
That's true. I'll have a Servant
far stronger than any other.
The question is how
to use that power.
To be honest, in terms
of ease of use,
...Caster or Assassin would be
far better suited to me.
What good will it do to worry about that
before you've even summoned him?
After all, we don't know what
the King of Knights was like.
And besides, no matter what you decide,
once he learns of your ideal...
Of your dream...
He'll understand.
Just like I did.
What?
I've found my strategy.
The way I can get the best use
from the strongest Servant.
Hello, Rin.
Hello, Kirei.
Heading out? That's some
heavy luggage you have.
That's right. I'm going to live
with the Zenjo family.
You're staying to fight
with my dad, right?
That's why I'm here
as his student.
Kirei...
Can I believe in you?
Will you promise to protect
my father to the end?
I'm afraid that's impossible.
If this battle were simple enough
that I could make that promise,
...we wouldn't have to send
you or his wife away.
I guess I just can't
like you.
Rin, you shouldn't just blurt out
what you're really thinking.
People will start to cast aspersions on
your father, the man educating you.
My dad has nothing
to do with it!
Listen, Kirei!
If you get sloppy
and my dad gets hurt,
...I'll show you no mercy,
got it?!
Rin, what are you doing?
You're yelling.
Um...
Well...
She was giving me a pep talk
before we said goodbye, Ma'am.
Allow me. That suitcase
is far too heavy for you.
It's fine.
I'll carry it myself.
Mr. Kotomine, please take care
of my husband.
Help him achieve
his desire.
I will do my best.
Don't worry.
Excuse me.
You came at
an opportune time.
The relic I arranged for
finally arrived this morning.
Have a look.
What is it?
A fossil of the very first skin
shed by a snake on this world.
If we use it as a catalyst and are lucky
enough to summon what we're after,
...victory is as good
as ours.
Hey, Sakura.
Did I surprise you?
Your face...
Yeah, I know.
Seems I lost a little bit
to the worms inside me.
I guess I'm not as
tough as you are.
You're turning into a
different person, aren't you?
Maybe.
I don't have to go to
the worm pit tonight.
Grandfather said there will be
a more important ceremony.
Yeah, I know.
That's why I'm going to the basement
tonight instead of you.
Are you going away,
Uncle Kariya?
I have an important job
to do for a while.
I might not have much time
to talk to you then.
I see.
Hey, Sakura.
When my job's over, want to go
somewhere with everyone and have fun?
With your mom
and sister?
I don't have anyone I can
call Mom or Sister.
Grandfather said I should think of them
like they never existed.
I see...
Uncle?
Then let's take Aoi
and Rin...
...from the Tohsakas and go
somewhere far away.
We can hang out and have fun
like we used to.
I can see them again?
Yeah, you will.
You have my word.
Well, I have to get going.
Okay.
Bye-bye, Uncle Kariya.
BYE-bye...
You've memorized the
summoning spell, right?
Yes.
Very well. But I'll have you add
two extra lines to the incantation.
- What do you mean?
- It's simple.
Kariya, your rank as a mage is somewhat
lower than that of the other Masters.
That will affect the Servant's
base abilities.
This means that we have to
pick the Servant's class...
...so we can use its modifiers
to boost those abilities.
Kariya.
I want you to add the affinity "Berserk"
to the Servant you summon.
Fill, fill, fill, fill, fill!
Repeat five times.
But when each is filled,
destroy it.
For the elements,
silver and iron.
For the foundation, stone and
the Archduke of Pacts.
And for the ancestor,
my great master, Schweinorg.
Raise a wall to block the falling wind.
Close the gates of the four directions.
Come forth from the Crown and follow
the forked road leading to the Kingdom.
Is a simple ritual like this enough
to summon a Heroic Spirit?
Surprisingly, yes.
The summoning ritual doesn't
require an elaborate evocation.
The Grail itself does
the actual summoning.
As a Master, my job is to anchor
the spirit in this world once it appears,
...and to give it enough mana
to take physical form.
That should do it.
Iri, put the relic on the altar.
That's the last step.
Heed my words.
My will creates your body, and your
sword creates my destiny.
If you heed the Grail's call
and obey my will and reason,
...then answer me!
I hereby swear...
That I shall be all the good
in the world.
That I shall defeat all evil
But let thine eyes be
clouded with chaos.
Thou, who art trapped
in a cage of madness.
And I, who holds
thy chains!
Thou Seventh Heaven, clad in
the three great words of power,
...come forth from the circle of binding,
Guardian of the Scales!
We've won the battle, Kirei.
Victory is ours!
Who--
I ask you...
Are you my Master?
Episode 1:
The Summoning of Heroes
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
I think what you
and Kiritsugu seek is right.
The world cannot serve
two lords.
Then I promise you.
You aren't worthy
to look upon me.
You're so cool!
Eliminate Tokiomi Tohsaka
at once.