Rider?
Hey!
What are you thinking,
breaking the shutter open like that?
Why didn't you go to spirit form,
like when you entered?
I cannot carry these
while I'm in spirit form.
Don't whine so much.
You sound like a thief.
If you aren't a thief,
what are you?
Something entirely different.
A cowardly thief sneaks away
in the night.
If you stride away, bursting with song,
then you are a conquering king!
Just what I needed...
Get lost... Get lost now.
Right now!
Very well! Then I shall leave you
to carry the spoils.
Do not drop them.
Why is this happening
to me?!
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
The summoning worked,
so why do I have to do this?
What's so important about
these books, anyway?
I told you.
We prepare for war.
And one cannot wage war
without maps.
Hey, boy.
Where are Macedonia
and Persia?
Y-You can't talk to me
like that!
I'm your Master--
I am well aware of your status
as my Master.
We forged a pact,
did we not?
Yes.
But I'm more interested in learning
what has become of my old territories.
I think they're over here.
So tiny! I spent my life conquering
that land, and behold how puny it is!
Very well! I can't wait!
And where on the map
are we now, boy?
Here.
So, the other side
of the round land?
Pleasing news indeed!
This will guide us
in the coming battles.
Guide us?
First, we journey to the
other side of the world.
We go west.
Due west!
And we shall conquer
every land we pass through!
I shall return to Macedonia
in triumph,
...and my people will hold a festival
in honor of my revival!
How splendid will that be?!
Why do you think
you're here, anyway?
Don't forget about
the Holy Grail War!
Indeed!
That's right. Speaking of the Grail,
I have neglected to ask one thing.
What will you do
with the Grail?
Wh-What's it to you?
What do you care?
If you are also intent on world conquest,
that would make you my enemy.
The world cannot serve
two lords.
World conquest?
I-I'll tell you what I want...
I just want people
to treat me fairly.
I want to make all those at the Clock Tower
who never gave me a chance...
...to admit they were wrong!
Small!
So very small! And narrow-minded.
And stupid.
In this battle, your only concern
is for your reputation?
And you dare call yourself
my Master?
What a disappointment!
If you wish so desperately
for others to fear you,
...perhaps you should
use the Grail's power...
...to grow another
30 centimeters or so.
He's supposed to be my Servant...
He can't talk to me that way!
I'll show him!
I address the command seal.
In accordance with the Grail's laws, I order
this man, Iskandar the Conqueror--
Calm down, Waver.
A Master can only use his command seal
to compel his Servant's obedience three times.
If I use all my command seals,
I won't be able to control him.
As long as I get the Grail,
it doesn't matter.
I don't care what
you do after that, so-
I shall acquire the Grail
for you.
You seem confident.
Have you made any plans?
So, you wish to see my power.
Is that correct?
N-Naturally!
You need to prove
that I can rely on you!
I am Iskandar,
King of Conquerors!
With this swing of my sword,
I declare my supremacy!
This is the ox-chariot that
King Gordius once offered up to Zeus.
Its renown must be the source
of my designation as Rider class.
If you want the Grail, then find me
another hero or two!
Until then, I shall entertain myself
with these maps.
That will not pose a problem,
I take it?
All right... I won't lose today!
There it is.
No way! Where is it?
I'm sure I didn't overlook it!
That's the first
chestnut bud today.
First point goes to me.
I-I'm not going
to lose!
There's one!
I found one, too!
I found my second.
Hey, that isn't a
chestnut branch.
No, Ilya. That's called
a wingnut.
It's similar to a chestnut.
So it's a chestnut bud, too.
No fair!
No fair! No fair!
You've been cheating
this whole time!
But Daddy can't win
against you otherwise.
If you keep cheating,
I won't play with you, Kiritsugu!
I don't want that! I'm sorry!
I apologize!
Do you promise not
to cheat anymore?
I do, 1 do!
Very well. Then I'll
challenge you again.
A champion accepts
all challengers!
Indeed. I am honored,
Your Highness!
I'm SO high up!
What are you
looking at, Saber?
Your daughter and Kiritsugu
are playing outside.
Surprised?
I was under the impression that
my Master was colder than that.
Well, I can see how you
might think that.
If that is Kiritsugu's true self,
...I must have gravely
offended him.
Irisviel! You don't
have to laugh.
I'm sorry...
I was wondering if the incident during
your summoning still bothers you.
Some.
True, I did pretend
to be a man in life,
...but surely there was no need for you two
to be so shocked when you saw me.
Well, you know...
We couldn't help it.
Your legend... King Arthur's legend...
It's simply too famous.
Do you suppose Kiritsugu...
...might underestimate my ability
because I am a woman?
Never. But...
You're right... If he is upset,
there's another reason.
Another?
He's probably upset at the people
who were around you.
The ones cruel enough to force
the role of king upon a little girl.
It was inevitable.
I had resigned myself to that fate when
I drew forth the sword from the stone.
That upsets him even more.
Your resignation to your fate.
Then he forgets his place.
He hasn't the right to question
decisions made...
...by those of my time,
including myself.
That is why he says nothing.
Kiritsugu Emiya and the hero Arturia
will never see eye to eye.
He must have resigned
himself to that fact.
He wants to use the Grail's power
to save the world.
That is his ambition.
And yours, correct?
Yes, but I get my beliefs
from him.
My own desire for the Grail
is the same.
I wish to save Britain, since I was
unable to protect it in life.
I think what you
and Kiritsugu seek is right.
I believe it is something
you can be proud of.
Our next match won't be until you
come home from Japan, right?
That's right.
How long will your work keep you
and Mommy away, Kiritsugu?
When will you come back?
I'll be back in
two weeks or so.
Your mom won't be back for
quite a while, though.
Yeah, Mommy told me already.
She said we'd be apart
for a long time.
She said that even if we don't
see each other for a long time,
...she'd always be by my side.
So I shouldn't feel lonely.
She told me before I went to sleep.
I'm gonna be together with
Mommy forever and ever!
I see.
Listen, Ilya.
Kiritsugu?
Can you wait for me, Ilya?
Even if you're lonely, can you
hold on until I come home?
Yeah!
Then I promise you.
I'll be home before
you know it.
Fill, fill, fill 'er up, fill...
Repeat... Four times...
Or was it five?
Um, destroy each time
it is filled...
Right?
Fill, fill, fill, fill and fill.
That's five times!
Okay.
At all three murder scenes,
...a mysterious pentagram was found,
drawn in the victims' blood.
Maybe I went a bit too far...
This symbol's purpose remains unclear.
Today, we've invited a professor who
specializes in criminal psychology to-
Do you believe
in demons, kiddo?
All the papers and magazines
call me a demon.
But suppose demons really did exist.
Wouldn't that be rude?
You've gotta be clear
about these things.
Yo! I'm Ryunosuke Uryu,
and I'm a demon!
I dunno if that's exactly the
right way to go about it.
And then, I found this.
It's some old book
from our storehouse.
Looks like my ancestors were researching
how to summon demons.
Like, so I've just gotta find out
if there really are demons!
But you know...
If a demon really did appear,
...it'd be pretty stupid to just
chat with it and send it back.
So, kid...
If a demon does show up,
would you mind letting it kill you?
I wonder what it's like,
being killed by a demon?
Not many people
get to find out! Ow!
What's that?
I ask you...
You who calls to me...
You who seeks me...
O summoner who manifests me
within the vessel of a Caster,
...I ask your name.
Who...
n n
Um...
I'm Ryunosuke Uryu.
Currently working odd jobs.
My hobby is murder of all varieties.
I like kids and little girls.
Very well. The pact is sealed.
I desire the Grail, as do you.
The vessel of paradise
will be ours.
The Grai... What?
Anyway, how about a sacrifice?
Wanna eat this kid?
Wow... That's human skin, isn't it?
Cthulhu fhtagn...
Don't be scared, child.
Can you stand?
Now, child, you can leave the room
through that door.
Can you manage that
by yourself?
Yeah.
Hey, what're you thinking?
Terror has degrees of freshness.
The more intense the fear,
the more all other emotions die.
Terror, in its truest sense,
...is not a static state,
but rather a dynamic one.
It is the moment when hope
turns to despair.
Did you enjoy that?
The taste of fresh terror
and death.
Cool!
You're awesome!
You're so cool!
Okay!
I don't know about this Grail crap,
but from now on, I'm with you!
Let's go kill some people!
I want you to show me
even cooler ways to kill!
Ryunosuke, was it?
What a magnificent omen, to be blessed with
an understanding Master like yourself.
I feel my dream is nearly
within my grasp.
Oh, hey. I didn't get
your name.
MY name?
Let me see. In this era,
the most common name for me is...
I believe I will
call myself Bluebeard.
The Church contacted me.
They said that the seventh Servant,
Caster, has appeared.
The final Servant has been summoned?
Then it's time.
Indeed.
You are to head immediately
for Tohsaka manor.
And once I arrive?
The manor's powerful magical barriers
should be child's play to you.
Are you sure about this?
I was under the impression that you
were allies with Tokiomi Tohsaka.
Don't worry about that.
Even if it means fighting Archer,
...there's no need to fear.
No need to fear Archer, one of
the three Great Knight classes?
I leave the rest to you.
Eliminate Tokiomi Tohsaka
at once.
This will be easy.
You're nothing but a worm.
Who gave you permission
to come here?
No need...
...to fear that,
u-he
You are not worthy
to look upon me.
A worm should be
facing the ground...
...when it dies.
Episode 2:
The Fake First Shot
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
At last, it's time for the
Fourth Holy Grail War to begin.
It's unspeakably ugly.
Where is the item I left with you?
This will be fun!
Welcome.
Grant me victory!
Next Time: Fuyuki City
I will, without fail.