Everything went smoothly.
These games of yours
squander my time, Tokiomi.
I am very grateful,
Gilgamesh...
...king of all kings,
King of Heroes.
Your deeds tonight will establish your
prowess as the King of Heroes.
And they will reveal which
of our foes we must hunt.
I ask only that you stay your hand
for just a short while longer.
Very well.
For the time being, I shall amuse myself
with simple reconnaissance.
This age fascinates me.
The modern world
is to your liking?
It's unspeakably ugly.
But that is fine, in its own way.
The important thing is whether any
treasures here are worthy of me.
If there is nothing here
that deserves my adoration,
...you will pay dearly
for summoning me,
...Tokiomi.
Worry not.
The Holy Grail is surely an item fit
to please the King of Heroes.
That is for me to determine.
No matter.
I'll play along with
your schemes for now.
Everything of value in this world
belongs to me.
No matter how precious a treasure
this Grail of yours may be,
...I'll never let anyone have it
without my permission.
Tokiomi, I'll leave the details to you.
My, my...
Honestly...
I'm still amazed that
Gilgamesh materialized...
...within the Archer class,
considering their solo combat skills.
Well, I can let Kirei
handle things from here.
For now, everything is proceeding
according to plan.
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
Assassin was killed?
Hey, Rider... This is big news!
One of the seven has already
been knocked out.
Hey...
Battle of Sky Battle of
Sky II The Imperial Army
Come on! Don't you get it?
Assassin was killed!
The Holy Grail War has started!
I've been out
gathering information,
...and day after day after day!
Every single day!
You sit around eating cookies,
watching stuff on the VCR!
You're worse than a familiar...
Worse than a rat!
And I told you to take spirit form
when I don't need you!
I'm giving you all the mana
you need to do your job.
Kid, no one cares
about Assassin.
He's only good at skulking in the shadows.
He could never pose a threat to me.
Anvway, boy...
Here, this is what matters!
This! The big, black thing
they call a "B-2."
It's wonderful!
I'm thinking of buying ten or so.
What do you think?
With that much money, it'd be faster
to just buy the country outright.
Oh... I see!
So, the question is where
to procure the money...
Were there some major
city nearby, such as Persepolis,
...we could simply plunder it
and get what we need.
For the moment, our biggest obstacle
will be this "Clinton" guy!
He will prove a more formidable
opponent than Darius III.
R-Regardless...
It's good that Assassin
was eliminated first.
Aren't you the type who prefers
to face his enemy head-on?
So it's good news for us that the guy who
uses sneak attacks and tricks is out.
We could get some good use
from these "Tomahawk" things, too!
Saber, Lancer, Archer,
the three Great Knights...
And the Berserker, whose sole
skill is to break things.
They're gonna be toast when you use
that Noble Phantasm of yours!
That just leaves Caster!
If we knew his true identity, we-
How did Assassin fall?
Who was it that defeated him?
You saw it, right?
I think it was Tohsaka's Servant.
His appearance, his attacks,
everything was gold and flashy.
It all happened so fast,
I couldn't tell-
Fool!
If I am to fight someone,
it will be the victor!
Why weren't you paying
attention to him?
Well, it matters not.
Did anything else strike you
about the flashy gold guy?
B-But it was the middle
of the night...
And it was all over
in a second.
Hey, Rider... Normally, a Servant only
has one Noble Phantasm, right?
That's the rule.
But "how many" isn't the right way to
conceptualize a Noble Phantasm.
As you know,
a Noble Phantasm...
...is the physical manifestation
of a hero's legend or tale.
Sometimes, it may be a
specific ability or method of attack.
Then is there
a Noble Phantasm...
...that consists of throwing dozens
of swords at an opponent?
A sword that splits into
infinite copies?
It's possible...
That could still qualify as
a single Noble Phantasm.
But those weren't copies.
Each sword had a different shape.
Ah, forget it.
We'll learn each enemy's identity
as we encounter them.
I-Is that really wise?
It is!
Actually, it's more fun
this way!
Food, sex, sleep,
and war...
Whatever you do,
enjoy it to the fullest!
That is the secret of life.
Now, let's go find some
entertainment outside.
We ride forth, boy!
Prepare yourself.
R-Ride forth?
To where?
Somewhere!
Anywhere!
Oh, come on...
You can't have been the only one
who was watching Tohsaka.
Which means that news of Assassin's
death is making the rounds.
All the others are going to spring
into action all at once.
But we shall crush them
as we come across them.
Find and crush them...
It won't be that easy.
I am Rider.
My speed far exceeds
that of any other Servant.
Wait! Wait, wait!
Not here...
You'll blow up the house!
My Servant has been lost.
I have forfeited my rights as a Master
and cannot continue the Holy Grail War.
In accordance with the treaty,
I, Kirei Kotomine,
...ask that the Church
grant me sanctuary.
Your request is granted.
In my role as overseer, I,
Risei Kotomine, guarantee your safety.
Enter.
Father... Isn't anyone
watching this church?
No!
This place has been declared
a neutral sanctuary.
The Holy Church will censure any
Master who defies the decree.
Then it's safe...
Yes.
Keep watch, just in case.
Post one guard here at
all times, just to be sure.
Yes. Understood.
Who was watching the battle?
I detected the presence of familiars
from four separate Masters.
Two days ago, I confirmed the
summoning of the final Servant, Caster.
All the Holy Grail War Servants
have now arrived.
One unaccounted for, huh?
I had hoped that all the Masters
were watching.
At this point, observing the
three families' estates...
...is a Master's obvious
course of action.
If they can't even think
to do that,
...it would never occur to them
to worry about us Assassins.
We Heroic Spirits of the shadows
shall sneak up behind those Masters...
...who believe
Assassin to be dead.
And this time, we shall
become true shadow.
The battle has now begun.
At last, it's time for the
Fourth Holy Grail War to begin.
These old eyes of mine will finally
see a miracle performed.
So, this is where Kiritsugu
was born?
Well, Saber? How did you enjoy
your journey through the sky?
It was nothing to speak of.
Far simpler than I'd anticipated.
I suppose flying is nothing
to a hero, right?
That isn't it.
Upon materialization, Servants receive
knowledge of the modern world.
If required, I could even
pilot this aircraft.
You could pilot this?
My Riding skill allows me to
command any beast or vehicle,
...with the exception of
Phantasmal Beasts or Divine Beasts.
Once I put the saddle between my legs
and take the reins, intuition does the rest.
Put the saddle between
your legs and take the reins...
Did I say something amusing?
No.
Still, you must be the only Servant who has
flown in an airplane in physical form.
I apologize for that.
If only I could take spirit form...
No, I didn't mean it like that.
Don't worry about it.
I never get tired of watching you.
Irisviel, is there
something odd about me?
No, not at all.
When you laugh like that, there is
some hidden meaning behind it.
What is it? I want you
to be frank with me.
It means that your being stuck in
physical form isn't without its merits.
It's given me many enjoyable hours
choosing outfits for you.
Irisviel, is this manner of dress
truly common in this era?
I chose it to balance out my own outfit.
You don't care for it?
No, it is fine.
It is rather easy to move in, and besides,
I am used to dressing as a man.
This place is so alive...
Kiritsugu was set to have
arrived here already, yes?
Yes. Twelve hours before us.
But he'll find us.
Don't worry.
For the moment, we'll
keep an eye on things...
...so we can act when
the time comes.
We've come all this way to Japan.
I'd like to enjoy it before the fighting starts.
That's dangerous.
We should secure a base of operations
and then discuss plans with Kiritsugu.
I suppose you're right...
But it's such a waste.
We've come all this way.
And...
It's my first time.
Eh?
This is the first time I've ventured
into the world outside.
Then you've spent your
entire life in that castle?
Yes, I was a puppet created
for the Holy Grail War.
Of course, it isn't as though
I'm wholly ignorant of it.
Kiritsugu brought me
movies and pictures,
...and he's taught me all about
the outside world.
But this is the first time
I've seen it for myself.
So...
Forgive me.
I got overly excited.
Please stop the car.
Walking through the city will be
a new experience for me, as well.
But it is a knight's duty
to serve as escort.
I shall do my best.
Come with me.
The equipment you requested
has arrived.
The mistress and Saber
have arrived, as well.
The other Masters will likely
assume that she is Saber's Master.
Understood.
There was an incident last night
at the Tohsaka estate.
Here is the footage I recorded.
What do you make of this?
It seems too good to be true.
There is insufficient time
between Assassin's infiltration...
...and the Tohsaka
Servant's attack.
Assassin has a skill
that masks his presence,
...making it highly improbable that
he was detected in advance.
I believe Tohsaka was
expecting an intruder.
In a battle among Servants,
learning their identities is critical.
Why would Tohsaka expose
his Servant this way?
He had some reason to,
I suppose.
Maiya, what became of
Assassin's Master?
He took refuge in a church
last night.
The overseer declared him
to be under his protection.
Assassin's Master is Kirei Kotomine.
Maiya, set a familiar to watch
the Fuyuki Church.
Are you certain?
Masters are forbidden to take action
inside the neutral zone around a church.
Place it just far enough away
that the priest won't spot it.
Very well. Understood.
Where is the item
I left with you?
Right here.
Approximately two seconds,
I'd say.
I've slowed down.
Indeed.
Illya weighs less than
that Walther.
Even though she's eight
years old already...
Focus on the matter
at hand.
Think of nothing else.
It's wonderful, like a mirror
that reflects the night sky.
It's fun to walk around a new town,
accompanied by a gentleman.
Did I make an
acceptable gentleman?
You were perfect.
You were a wonderful
knight today.
You honor me, Highness.
Saber, do you like the sea?
I guess I don't really know.
In my country and in my time,
...the sea was the source of
constant barbarian attacks.
Sometimes, I hated it.
But I never felt any affection for it.
I feel kind of bad.
You're a girl, just as I am,
but when you were King Arthur,
...you never had the luxury of enjoying
simple things like this, did you?
What of you?
Surely, you would have preferred
Kiritsugu to escort you, right?
He couldn't...
It would only
cause him suffering.
Does Kiritsugu not enjoy the time
he spends with you?
When he's happy,
it causes him pain.
An enemy Servant?
Yes.
Making its presence known from
the shadows, 100 meters ahead.
It appears to be inviting us
to go see it.
How thoughtful.
It wishes to decide on
a battlefield.
Shall we take it up
on its invitation?
I'd like nothing better.
Rider... Let's go back down.
Right now!
What? This is the perfect
vantage point.
I'm climbing down!
No, take me back down!
I-I can't handle any more of this...
Calm yourself.
Waiting is a part of war.
I wanna go home. I wanna
go back to England...
I told you not to be
in such a hurry.
See? Things have finally
begun to unfold.
This will be fun!
Welcome.
I have spent the whole day
searching the city.
Everyone simply slinks away,
hiding in their little holes.
You alone have accepted
my offer.
That pure energy surrounding you...
You are Saber, I presume?
Indeed.
And you are Lancer.
Being unable to honorably name myself
to my opponent in combat troubles me.
I dislike these rules.
Saber... Be careful.
I can use healing magic
to act as support for you.
But more than that...
Leave Lancer to me.
But it troubles me that the other
Master has not shown himself.
Perhaps they plot something.
Watch yourself.
Irisviel, watch my back.
Very well, Saber.
Grant me victory!
I will.
Without fail!
Episode 3:
Fuyuki City
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
Let's see what you can do,
my adorable King of Knights.
Then the tales of the Saber-class
magic resistance were accurate.
This man is impressive!
That's enough fun
for now, Lancer.
What's happening?
I'll go... Take me with you, damn it!