A charm spell...
Sorry. It's a curse
I was born with.
There's nothing I can do about it.
Blame it on my birth or the fact
that you were born a woman.
Surely you don't believe
that a pleasant face...
...will save you from
my blade, spearman.
I certainly hope not.
It would spoil the fun.
I see.
Then the tales of the Saber-class
magic resistance were accurate.
Very well.
I prefer not to kill a girl who's
throwing herself at me, anyway.
It would sully my reputation.
I'm pleased that my first opponent
is made of stern stuff.
Oh? So you desire
a fair fight?
I consider myself fortunate to
encounter such a proud hero.
Then let us begin.
It's started.
Someone's put up a barrier.
Probably the Master of
the enemy Servant.
From up there, we can survey
the entire battlefield.
Indeed. That is certainly
the best vantage point.
Anyone seeing it would
think as much.
You circle around to the eastern wharf.
I'll take the west.
We'll find spots where we can monitor
both battle and that crane.
Understood.
Let us see what you're capable of,
my adorable King of Knights.
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
Saber is watching
both spears simultaneously.
Lancer's greatest advantage is his opponent's
uncertainty as to which he will use.
The long spear in the right hand,
or the short spear in the left.
I wonder which is
the Noble Phantasm.
If I were sure, I could attack.
If only we knew his true name...
Whoever he is,
he's a master of the spear.
However, that is not enough.
What's wrong, Saber?
You're on the defensive!
This man is impressive!
Curse that blade of hers.
Without knowing its exact length,
I cannot get close enough to strike.
The fact that she is able to
repel my strikes so easily...
...means that she must be
a master swordsman.
Maiya.
Northeast of Saber and Iri.
On the roof of that warehouse.
That is Lancer's Master.
Can you see him?
Negative. Not from my position.
Understood. I'll take him out
from here.
Assassin?
There is activity at the warehouse district
at the mouth of the Mion River.
The first battle has finally begun.
Not the first.
To the others, this would be
the second battle,
...Kirei.
It would appear that Lancer and Saber
are the combatants.
Can you ascertain their status
with Assassin's eyes?
With ease.
Saber's abilities are especially high.
Most of her parameters
are rank A or higher.
I see.
It's no wonder that they are considered
the strongest class.
Saber likely presents a greater
threat than Lancer.
Can you see either Master?
There's only one person besides
the Servants who is in the open.
Standing next to Saber...
A woman with silver hair.
Then Lancer's master is wise enough
to remain hidden.
That's no novice.
They understand the rules
of the Holy Grail War.
Wait. A silver-haired woman?
Yes. Caucasian.
With silver hair and red eyes.
That doesn't sound human.
An Einzbern homunculus?
Did they create an artificial Master?
I had thought the only pawn Jubstacheit
had on the board was Kiritsugu Emiya.
It would appear that I was wrong.
Then that woman is the Einzbern Master?
Either way, she'll be a critical factor
in the rest of the Grail War.
Kirei, keep a close eye on her.
Ag reed.
I shall keep one Assassin tasked to her
at all times.
I can see them.
But Assassin should be dead,
so why is he here?
I knew something was up.
Let's see how this plays out.
Continue to observe Assassin.
I'll watch Lancer.
Let me attack Assassin,
and while I have him distracted,
...you take out Lancer's Master.
No, Maiya.
Not against Assassin.
We're not equipped to fight
Servants right now.
Understood.
There is no honor in a battle fought
without an exchange of names.
But allow me to offer my regards.
It is quite impressive for a woman to fight
so hard without even breaking a sweat.
You needn't be so humble, Lancer.
Even without my knowing your name, those
words from such a master of the spear...
...do me honor.
I gratefully accept them.
That's enough fun for now, Lancer.
Lancer's Master?
Do not allow this battle to go on.
That Saber is a formidable opponent.
Eliminate her at once.
You may use your Noble Phantasm.
Yes, my Master.
So the long spear
is his Noble Phantasm?
You heard him.
I'll go for the kill now.
Saber, are you using focused wind mana...
...to keep your blade concealed?
I see.
You have a reason
to conceal your sword.
My guess is that the sword
reveals your true name.
How unfortunate, Lancer.
You will never know
the name of my blade.
I'll finish this before
you get that chance.
We'll see about that.
I will discover
what you hide, Saber.
You've exposed your sword.
The Invisible Air is disintegrating?
What's going on?
That red spear is chipping away
at the Invisible Air!
I have the length of your blade now.
Now I needn't worry about being struck!
But I still have ways to counter it.
If I wait for an attack...
One less powerful than the rest...
Saber?
My thanks, Irisviel.
I'm fine.
The healing is working.
So, this won't be
an easy victory.
But why?
My armor should have easily
deflected that strike.
So how did the blade
of his spear-
The armor itself isn't damaged?
What is at work here?
The only answer is that Lancer's spear
bypassed the magically woven armor.
So that's it. I see the secret
of your spear, Lancer.
Oh?
That red spear negates magic.
Your armor was created using magic.
If you were counting on it to protect you,
you should surrender, Saber.
You're as good as naked
before my spear.
Don't think that simply defeating
my armor gives you the upper hand.
If I cannot block your blade, I need
only kill you before it strikes.
Prepare to die, Lancer!
A bold move.
You're betting everything on one strike.
You attempted to overcome the disadvantage
of your broken armor...
...with the advantages you gain
by abandoning it.
A courageous decision.
I like it.
But in this case,
...it was a foolish mistake, Saber.
We shall see.
Tell me your opinion again
after my next attack.
That was a misstep.
A Noble Phantasm needn't be
merely a single weapon.
A trap?
This is bad... Extremely bad.
Wh-What is?
Lancer has begun his ultimate attack.
He intends to end the battle here.
Isn't that better for us?
Idiot! What are you talking about?
I wanted to sit back and watch
until we saw a few more Masters.
But at this rate, Saber may fall.
Then it will be too late.
T-Too late for what?
The plan was to attack once they'd
weakened each other!
I admit, I had hoped another Servant
would answer Lancer's challenge.
Of course...
It would be faster to fight them together
than to find them one by one.
Together?
Yes.
Rarely does one have the chance to exchange
blows with heroes from another time.
And with the chance to fight as many as six,
...I'd hate to miss out on a single one.
Observe Saber and Lancer!
Both are valiant warriors whom
I would dearly love to duel.
I cannot let either die.
But isn't that the point?
The Grail War's objective
is to kill one another!
To win, but not destroy.
To subjugate, but not humiliate.
That is true conquest!
We watch no longer!
We shall join the fray, boy!
You idiot!
What you're doing is insane!
If you don't approve,
will you stay here and observe?
I'll go... Take me with you, damn it!
Excellent... That is my Master!
Not good. He's severed the tendon.
I can't move my thumb.
You aren't going to make
this easy, are you?
Still, I really do like your
indomitable spirit!
Get to work, you fool.
You haven't finished her.
I apologize, my Master.
Irisviel.
I require healing, as well.
I have!
I have, but...
The healing worked. I'm certain.
Saber, you should already be fully healed!
You were sharp, realizing that my
Gae Dearg could penetrate any armor.
But it was foolish to abandon your armor.
Had you not done so, you would
have blocked my Gae Buidhe.
I understand now.
A cursed spear, whose wounds never heal...
I should have realized it sooner.
A red spear that destroys magic,
a cursed yellow spear,
...and beneath the right eye,
a mole that enchants women.
First of the Knights of Fianna,
Diarmuid of the Love Spot.
Never did I think I'd have
the honor of facing you.
Such is the pleasure
of the Holy Grail War.
But it is I who have the honor here.
No hero summoned by the Holy Grail...
...could ever mistake that golden blade.
To face the legendary King of Knights
and land even a single blow,
...I must be pretty damned good.
Now then, since we both know
the other's name,
...we can duel honorably, as knights should.
Or does this displease you, occurring
only after you've lost use of an arm?
You jest.
It's humiliating that you would
show me concern over such a scratch.
Prepare yourself, Saber.
Next time, you're mine.
Only if I fail to strike first, Lancer.
A chariot?
Both of you, sheathe your blades.
You are in the presence of the king!
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
In this Grail War,
I am of the Rider class.
Episode 4:
Spearhead
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
I am Iskandar, King of Conquerors!
I can't read his status
or anything else!
Irisviel, get back!
That is his Noble Phantasm.
With my Command Seal, I order you...
Believe in your Master!
At last, I have been revived!
Nothing will remain of your corpse!