My name is Iskandar,
the King of Conquerors!
In this Grail War,
I am of the Rider class.
Wh-What are you thinking,
you idiot?
Fate has brought us together
to do battle for the Grail.
But first, I wish to
make a proposition.
What think you of yielding
the Grail to me, and joining my army?
You would be treated
as honored allies.
And together, we shall share in
the joy of world conquest!
I am afraid I must decline.
I may give the Grail to but one man:
my new avowed lord.
Not to you, Rider!
Did you interfere with our battle merely
to proffer that ridiculous plan?
If so, it is a grave insult!
I'd be willing
to discuss compensation.
Shut up!
And further,
...I am the rightful King of Britain.
I could never lower myself to mere retainer,
even in service to a mighty king.
King of Britain, you say!
What a surprise!
I'd hardly have expected
the King of Knights to be a little girl.
Then would you like to taste
this little girl's blade,
...King of Conquerors?
I suppose negotiations have failed.
Such a waste. What a shame...
Rider!
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
That moron nearly conquered
the known world?
What is wrong with you?
So you were the one, eh?
I'd wondered what madness had
compelled you to steal my relic.
I never imagined that you yourself
planned to enter the Holy Grail War...
Waver Velvet.
How would you like me
to offer you a private lesson?
How mages really kill one another...
I'll teach you all about
the fear and pain involved.
You should feel honored.
Mage!
So you were to be my Master,
rather than this boy.
Absurd...
Only one brave enough to ride the battlefield
at my side could ever be my Master.
A coward who lacks sufficient
courage to show himself...
...is nowhere close
to being worthy!
And there are others, as well!
Out there, skulking in the darkness!
What do you speak of, Rider?
Saber. And Lancer.
Your duel was magnificent.
Surely, the sound of your blades...
...called other Heroic Spirits
than myself here.
Heroic Spirits, born again through
the Holy Grail, gather here and now!
Those too craven to show themselves...
...will draw the scorn of Iskandar,
King of Conquerors!
This is...
Yes.
Quite unfortunate.
Quite unfortunate indeed.
That's...
The Servant that defeated Assassin?
So, two lesser beings dare to name
themselves kings, even in my presence.
I fail to see where the problem lies...
I am Iskandar,
the legendary King of Conquerors.
What nonsense.
I am the one true king.
All others are mere pretenders.
If you're that insistent,
then why not name yourself?
No true king should be troubled
by giving his name.
So you would question me,
...pretender?
Me, the king?
If, even in the presence of my glory,
you cannot discern my identity,
your blindness will seal your doom!
I see.
So that is how he killed Assassin.
That is his Noble Phantasm.
Kill.
Berserker?
Hey, King of Conquerors.
Were you planning to ask him, too?
He doesn't seem terribly
interested in negotiations, does he?
Boy... How powerful a Servant is he?
I don't know.
I can't tell!
What?
Are you not a Master?
You can sense their strengths
and weaknesses, right?
I can't tell. That black thing is
definitely a Servant,
...but I can't read its status or
anything else about it!
It appears it will be
another difficult enemy.
That spirit has some curse
or other special ability...
...that entirely conceals
everything about him.
But that isn't all.
With four others present,
we have to be very careful.
Why did he materialize here?
No sane Master...
...would choose to send out
their Servant here.
Not into the middle
of all this chaos.
Maiya, keep watching Assassin.
I'll look for Berserker's Master.
Who gave you permission
to look upon me, you rabid dog?
May your death provide me
some modicum of entertainment, mongrel!
Is that truly Berserker?
For a madman, he's rather nimble.
What, you couldn't tell?
That black thing casually snatched the
first blade that was flying toward him,
...using it to destroy
the second spear as it approached.
You dare lay your filthy hands
on my treasures?
You must long for death, cur!
That's impossible!
Let us see just how long
your parlor tricks...
...can keep you alive!
Fool...
I belong among the heavens,
...yet you would have me
trod the same earth as you?!
Your impudence has
guaranteed your death!
Mongrel, nothing will
remain of your corpse!
Gilgamesh is serious.
He plans to open
the Gate of Babylon even further.
Repeatedly exposing
his Noble Phantasm to the others...
How rash.
Your decision, my Master?
By the power of my Command Seal,
...King of Heroes,
quell thine anger and withdraw.
You dare to order
a king to withdraw?
You have nerve, Tokiomi.
You were fortunate, mad dog.
Mongrels!
By our next meeting, see that
you've culled your numbers.
Only a true hero is worthy
to look upon me.
It would seem that Archer's Master
is less stubborn than he is.
Irisviel, get back!
What?
So that's it...
Whatever he grabs becomes
his Noble Phantasm.
Saber?
We", Maiya?
Do you have a visual on
Berserker's Master?
No, I don't.
This looks bad.
Damn.
What are you?
That's enough messing around, Berserker.
Saber has a prior engagement
with me.
If you insist on interfering,
you'll have to face me.
Lancer...
What are you doing, Lancer?
This is your chance to defeat Saber.
I, Diarmuid Ua Duibhne,
will defeat Saber...
I swear it on my honor!
If you insist I kill her here,
then I will first defeat that mad dog.
Please, my Master!
With my Command Seal,
I order you...
My lord!
Help Berserker kill Saber.
Lancer!
Saber, I'm sorry...
Irisviel, I shall hold them here.
While I do, you must run...
As far away as you can get.
Irisviel, please!
It's all right, Saber.
Believe in your Master!
Kiritsugu is here?
Kiritsugu, I know that
you can still turn this to victory.
I'll kill Lancer's Master now.
It's the only way out of this.
Maiya, attack Assassin on my mark.
Suppressive fire.
Acknowledged.
Six...
Five...
Four...
Three...
Two...
One.
Rider!
Ah...
This is a tough one.
As you can see, our black friend
will be retiring for the evening.
Master of Lancer. I know not
from whence you're watching,
...but do not sully a battle
between knights with your petty tricks.
Have Lancer withdraw.
If you insist on humiliating him further,
...then I shall join Saber.
Together, the two of us will
annihilate your Servant.
What will it be?
Withdraw, Lancer.
That's enough for tonight.
My thanks, King of Conquerors.
It was nothing. I enjoy watching
the flowers of a battlefield in bloom.
When you first arrived, what was
your intent, King of Conquerors?
I try not to think too hard
about such things.
Saber... First,
settle matters with Lancer.
And then, I shall face the victor,
be it you or Lancer.
King of Knights, goodbye for now!
I hope to enjoy our next meeting
as much as I did this one.
Boy, you got anything nice
to say to the lady?
I do wish he'd man up a little...
Farewell!
Saber, your left arm!
Yes, it was a painful blow.
It is as Rider says.
If I fail to deal with Lancer first and
undo the curse on this wound,
...it will damage my chances
against the other Servants.
Thank you, Saber.
I survived thanks to you...
The reason I could focus on
the battle before me...
...was that I had you to stand behind me.
Saber...
The battle is only beginning, Irisviel.
Tonight, we saw the mere opening gambits
of a battle that is just beginning to unfold.
That's right.
They were all powerful adversaries.
Not one of them was
a conventional enemy.
So this is the Holy Grail War.
They all turned and
ran from my Berserker...
And I embarrassed that arrogant ass!
Tokiomi, how I wish
I could have seen your face.
That damn Berserker broke free of
my control and started fighting Saber...
If he keeps doing that,
my body won't last long.
But if I can control him,
I can win.
Just hold on, Sakura.
Begging your pardon, Master Kirei.
What is it?
Right, I've come to report that I found
something of interest, outside the church.
A familiar?
Yes. It was outside the barrier,
...but it was clearly sent to
monitor this church.
Awesome!
That was so awesome!
Hey, Bluebeard...
That was all real, right?
It was for real, and not
some kind of special effect?
So awesome...
So, the Grail War, right?
You're gonna do it.
Right, big guy?
Big guy?
My wish has come true...
Come true...
Um..
Look at her! She is the answer!
Her beautiful face, her noble bearing...
She is none other than
the maiden of my dreams!
Someone you know?
Indeed!
She was forsaken by God,
died in shame, and now...
At last, she has
come back to life!
Such... Such a miracle.
What else could it be but
the fulfillment of my dreams?!
Oh, maiden...
MY holy virgin...
Soon, I will come for you.
Episode 5:
A Wicked Beast's Roar
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
I promise you Saber's head.
The next strike will be for real!
Aren't you the one who's mistaken?
Behold the magic of Kayneth El-Melloi...
You mean to lecture me?
I've come for you, my holy virgin.