See? See?
It goes really fast!
Y-You're a surprisingly good driver.
I know, right?! You may not believe it,
but I practice all the time.
Of all the toys Kiritsugu has
brought me, this is my favorite!
TOYS?
At the castle, I could only drive around
the courtyard, so this is great!
Shouldn't we have hired
a professional driver?
No, that would be boring!
I mean, dangerous!
What if the enemy attacks us?
That's true.
Stop!
Irisviel...
Get out of the car and
stay close to me.
This presence...
That's a Servant.
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
I've come for you, my holy virgin.
You know him?
I've never laid eyes on him.
Oh, “Q!
You say you have
forgotten this face?
Forgotten?
I've never met you in my life.
Perhaps you mistake me for another?
It's me! Gilles de Rais!
My one prayer has been
for your resurrection,
...and I've spent my life waiting
for a miracle to reunite us!
To that end, I've come all this way,
to the end of time!
Jeanne!
Jeanne?
I know not your name,
...nor have I any idea
who this Jeanne might be.
No...
You can't have forgotten...
Not your former identity!
As you've given me your name,
...in accordance with the chivalric code,
I must give you my own.
My name is Arturia.
Heir to Uther Pendragon,
...and King of Britain.
I enter this battle in the Saber class.
How tragic!
How sad...
She's lost her memory
and gone mad!
Curse him...
Curse him!
Such cruel tortures God inflicts
upon my beautiful maiden!
Enough! You embarrass yourself!
Awaken...
Call yourself Saber no longer.
The Holy Grail War has ended.
The Grail has chosen me, Gilles,
with no fighting at all!
For you see,
...my only wish, the resurrection of
Jeanne d'Arc, has been granted!
If you further mock
all the other heroes' prayers,
...the next strike will be real.
Now rise!
Has your heart been sealed
so tightly, Jeanne?
Very well, then.
If drastic measures are called for,
I will have to prepare.
I swear to you, Jeanne...
I will free your soul
from God's curse.
It's difficult to deal with one
who ignores what you are saying.
Next time, I shall strike
before he can speak.
His type infuriates me.
However, this may have been
fortunate for me.
I sensed that he was too dangerous
to face without the use of my left hand.
Following Saber's Master
has yielded unexpected fruit.
We found Caster, as well.
Of course, we must follow him.
Ah... No, no.
Here is what you do with the thumb.
Nice...
Perfect.
Welcome back, big guy.
Hey!
Accursed God!
He keeps an iron grip on Jeanne's soul,
refusing to let go!
By Jeanne, you mean your girl in the crystal ball?
We must prove it to her!
That God's power is gone...
That my love is wasted!
That no foul deed, no horrible crime,
is worthy of God's punishment!
Yeah, I get it.
You're even cooler!
Therefore!
We require greater depravities,
greater blasphemies.
We must erect a veritable Tower of Babel
of human sacrifices!
Uh, so basically...
From now on,
it's quantity over quality?
Indeed... Exactly so!
Impressive, Ryunosuke.
Our first step will be sacrificing
the eleven in their cells right away.
And then we'll go acquire
some more children.
Kind of a waste...
We interrupt this program
to bring you this breaking news.
Unexplained Explosion
An unexplained explosion has occurred...
...in the Fuyuki coastal district's warehouse area.
Unexplained Explosion
We go live to the scene...
Why weren't you able to
finish Saber tonight?
Not just once but twice.
You made me waste a Command Seal,
yet you still couldn't finish the job.
Was your fight with Saber
that much fun?
That had nothing to do with it...
I swear on my honor as a knight,
I will bring you Saber's head.
You don't need to swear it
to me again!
Of course you will!
You made a pact with me
for the Grail!
And now, you swear to defeat Saber?
What about this do you
not understand?!
Aren't you the one who's mistaken,
Lord El-Melloi?
Sola-Ui...
Lancer did well.
You were the one
who made the mistake.
Saber is a powerful Servant...
I couldn't allow a chance
to defeat her pass me by.
You inflicted a wound on her
that cannot heal.
By letting her go,
you can defeat her at your leisure.
If you're that concerned about her,
why didn't you go after her Master?
You merely stayed hidden
and watched. Pathetic.
Kayneth, it isn't that
you don't understand...
...your advantage over
the other Masters, right?
You made a special alteration to
the usual Master-Servant contract.
You get the Command Seals, and
I act as additional Master and supply mana.
You weren't the Evocation Division's
brightest star for nothing.
But we must take care at the start.
Must we, now?
So you'll hide, while you make
Lancer take all the risks...
That's enough.
Any more will be an insult
to my Master.
As a knight, I cannot allow it.
No, I didn't mean it like that...
I'm sorry. I've overstepped
my bounds.
What? What's going on?
Understood.
A fire on the lower levels.
It's arson, of course.
Arson? Tonight, of all nights?
They wish to empty the place.
Then it's an attack?
Saber's Master will want to lift
the Spear's curse as soon as possible.
Lancer, go downstairs and defeat her.
Don't just drive her off this time.
Understood.
Let's have our guest enjoy the magical
workshop of Kayneth El-Melloi.
A perfect workshop,
requiring an entire floor.
Twenty-four layered barriers.
Three mana generators.
Dozens of ghosts and evil spirits,
roaming as guard dogs.
Thousands of traps.
Parts of hallways that open
onto other worlds.
We shall both be able to avail ourselves
of all our magical techniques.
I will make you retract your statement
that I'm pathetic shortly.
I look forward to that.
Lord Archibald!
Lord Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald!
Are you present?
Yes.
That's me.
Don't worry.
Both Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald and
his wife, Sola-Ui, have evacuated.
I see.
Yes, that's fine.
Everyone has evacuated.
Excellent.
Everything is ready on my end.
And you?
All green.
Just give the word.
Maiya.
Target never even moved.
He didn't leave the hotel.
A free-fall from 150 meters...
No magical barrier could have
saved him from that.
Maiya, withdraw.
To blow up the entire building...
I can't believe a mage would do that.
Rather, I suppose you are a master
at outsmarting mages.
Kirei Kotomine...
I don't believe we've met.
Or do you have a reason that
you'd know me already?
In that case, I can guess
who you are.
Don't make me do
all the talking, woman.
One word will suffice.
Where is the man who should
have been here instead of you?
Not bad.
You seem to have training.
She didn't throw this.
Very well...
Just the knowledge that
someone was here to save her...
...means that tonight
was not a total waste.
Master Kirei.
I thought I told you
not to expose yourself.
My apologies, but there is something
you should hear.
We located Caster.
After having Assassin perform
a detailed investigation,
...we learned that Caster and
his Master have kidnapped children
from their beds, from Miyama
and the next town over.
By dawn, they had fifteen.
I would imagine that they
are the serial killer...
...that everyone is worked up over.
They use magic
without the slightest hesitation,
...doing nothing to hide their tracks.
It is quite possible that they are not
even thinking of the Holy Grail War.
A mad Servant, out of control,
and a Master who cannot control him.
Why is someone like that
participating in the Grail War?
We cannot ignore them, Tokiomi.
Their actions are in clear
violation of the rules.
Of course.
As one responsible for guarding
the secrets of magic, I cannot allow it.
We shall have to eliminate
Caster and his Master.
The problem is that defeating
a Servant requires a Servant.
And we can't send my Assassin.
Minor rule changes
fall under my purview.
We'll have all the Masters
work to defeat Caster.
Archer?
There are fewer bottles than in
Tokiomi's room, but of higher quality.
Some apprentice he has.
What do you want?
Apparently, there were those,
...other than myself,
with time on their hands.
Time on their hands?
Otherwise, a Master under
Church protection...
...would hardly need wander about.
What are you talking about?
Are you dissatisfied with
your contract, Gilgamesh?
Tokiomi invited me to this world,
and he maintains my form here.
And his greeting was worthy of my station.
I had to respond to that.
But I never thought
he'd be so boring a person...
You are unhappy with him
as your master?
To reach the Vortex of the Root?
What a tedious plan.
The desire for the Root...
...is unique to mages.
It's not for outsiders to comment upon.
In a sense, the path to the Root...
...is the path to an escape
from this world.
For us who are interested
only in the world itself,
...it may well be a tedious plan.
Is that so...
True, I am full of love for this
universe that is my playground.
I have no interest in realms
that lie outside my dominion.
This Root of yours does not
concern me in the least.
Perhaps, but the Grail is not a device
specifically designed to seek the Root.
When we say that it is omnipotent,
...we mean that it has limitless potential
to alter even the material world.
So you're saying that
the other Masters...
...have motives other than Tokiomi's
for wanting the Grail?
Tokiomi is an archetypal mage,
and at the same time, ultra right-wing.
What the others seek is success
here in the material world.
Prestige. Desires. Power.
That suits me fine.
I love all of those things.
You are a king who rules over
the vulgar, Gilgamesh.
Then what of you, Kirei?
What do you want from the Grail?
Me?
I have no real desire for it.
I doubt that.
Doesn't the Grail call only those
who are worthy of it?
So they say.
But I do not understand.
I have no ideal or other desire,
so why choose me for this battle?
No ideal or other desire...
Then why not wish for joy?
Ridiculous. Joy?
You'd ask me to long for something
that blasphemous and sinful?
Blasphemous?
Sinful?
That's going a little far.
Why draw a connection
between joy and sin?
I...
True, joy gained by evil
means could be a sin.
But joy may be attained
through good deeds, as well.
What kind of philosophy
calls joy itself a sin?
Joy is another quality I lack.
I seek it, but never find it.
Kirei Kotomine...
I find myself taking
an interest in you.
What do you mean?
Just what as I said.
Be seated.
Joy, you see, might be thought of
as a form of the soul.
The question isn't whether it exists,
but whether you know it.
Kirei, you have yet to see
what form your soul has taken.
That's what it means when you claim
that you lack joy.
A mere Servant means to lecture me?
Don't get cocky, mongrel.
These are words of a king who has tasted all
the pleasures and luxuries the world has to offer.
Hold your tongue and
mark my words.
Kirei, you ought to learn
what pleasure is.
Look first to the outside.
I know...
Why not begin by joining me
in my entertainment?
I have no time to waste on trivialities.
Don't be like that.
You can do it between
the jobs Tokiomi assigns you.
To begin with, Kirei,
...your task is to watch
the five other Masters, yes?
What Of it?
You should learn not only
their plans and strategies,
...but their motivations, as well.
Then tell them to me.
That would be possible
if I asked the Assassins.
But, Archer, what does it matter to you?
I told you. I enjoy watching humans.
One or two are sure to be interesting.
Compared to Tokiomi, at least.
Very well, Archer.
I accept.
But it will take some time.
That's fine. I shall be patient.
And avail myself of these drinks...
My reason for seeking the Grail?
I said far too much.
It certainly isn't joy.
However, if I can learn about that man,
...will I be able to also learn
what it is I seek?
Kiritsugu Emiya...
Episode 6:
A Night of Schemes
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
I'll explain the temporary change
in the rules.
They'll kill Kiritsugu Emiya...
We can escape!
If we go now, we can still...
It will be my lance
that takes Saber's life!
I'm not interested in fighting you
for the Grail!
Don't get any ideas, bitch!