This is it.
What is that?
All of you, return to your posts.
It looks like a ball of mercury.
It's almost as if it's alive.
I need to get this out of here.
Is something wrong?
Huh?
Load it onto the truck!
Quickly!
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
The Grail War is in grave peril.
We have identified
Caster's Master...
...as the person behind the recent
kidnappings in Fuyuki.
Thus, in accordance with my
emergency powers as overseer,
...I am temporarily altering
the rules of the Grail War.
All Masters are to cease
any ongoing combat,
...and eliminate Caster instead.
And the one who defeats
Caster and his Master...
...will receive an additional
Command Seal as their reward.
These are unused Command Seals left by
the fallen Masters of past Grail Wars.
They should prove to be of
immeasurable value to all of you.
Once Caster's destruction
has been confirmed,
...the Holy Grail War
will recommence.
If anyone has questions,
please ask them here.
Of course, that is limited to those
who can speak in human tongues.
Well played, Father.
Now the Masters will
all hunt him down.
Five familiars were gathered
at the church.
Which means...
Which means that the missing
Lord El-Melloi is still alive.
Indeed.
And the offer of a Command Seal
as the reward...
...should draw him out,
given that he's already used one.
And the other Masters, as well.
They'll seek to keep it from the rest...
...by claiming it for themselves.
But it also means that
the Master who wins the Seal...
...will gain a formidable advantage.
Naturally, it isn't an ideal solution.
Once Caster has been weakened
and is on the run from the others,
...Archer must be the one
to deal the final blow.
U-Um...
Is this the MacKenzie residence?
Just so. That is the name of
this domicile's residents.
Well, then...
Might there be a Mr. Iskandar,
King of Conquerors here?
That would be me.
Oh... I see.
Could I have your signature
on the receipt?
My signature?
Very well!
You have my thanks.
Th-Thank you for your business...
Conquest
What a feeling, to have the entire world
emblazoned across my chest!
Why are you dressed like that?
My package just arrived.
You went outside?
Ta-dah!
I merely tried out that
"mail order" thing.
I told you not to leave
the second floor!
If the residents are not at home
and you are occupied with your familiar,
...who else is there
to answer the door?
I had no choice...
A summons by the Holy Church
is a big deal.
Don't be so grouchy.
After seeing Saber last night,
I came to a realization.
If one wears modern attire,
...there should be no issue
with going outside.
Hey, wait!
At least put on some pants
before you go out!
Oh, leggings"-
That's true.
Everyone in this land wears them.
Must I?
Yes, you must!
And just to be clear,
...I'm definitely not going all the way
to town just to buy you XXXL pants.
What?
Boy, would you stand in the way
of my triumphant conquest?
Conquest and your pants
have nothing,
...not even in the slightest,
to do with each other!
Before you start planning to
screw around outside,
...go beat one of
the other Servants!
Then I'll buy you pants,
or anything else you want.
I understand. Very well.
Then you swear that
once I defeat an enemy,
...you will buy me pants?
You...
You really want to wear modern clothes
and go outside that much?
The King of Knights was doing it.
As a fellow king, I cannot
allow myself to be outdone.
I like the design on this shirt.
It is fitting attire for a ruler!
And we have to find Caster, too...
What are you doing?
There is a powerful barrier over Mt. Enzou,
with Ryudou Temple at its center.
Because of that, anything other than
natural spirits like Servants...
...can only enter
via the temple path.
Keep that in mind
as you're using Saber.
There are three other spots
where the leylines converge.
Tohsaka Manor
and the Fuyuki Chapel. And...
...this new residential area
east of the city center.
Consequently, this means that there
are four locations in Fuyuki...
...that have all the spiritual characteristics
needed for the Grail to appear.
When the war enters its second phase
and there are fewer Servants left,
...we'll have to secure one of these
as a base of operations, won't we?
That's right.
That covers the lay of the land.
Do you have any questions?
Is there anything that you
aren't clear on?
It was a perfectly
adequate explanation.
Kiritsugu, can we assume that
all the others will go after Caster?
It's a safe bet...
However, we have an advantage
as far as Caster is concerned.
Out of whatever madness,
...he believes Saber
to be his Jeanne d'Arc,
...which is to our benefit.
We need only wait for him
to come to us.
Master, that is not enough.
His evil deeds must be punished.
We should take the fight to him
before he can do any more damage.
Iri, do you have a handle on
this forest's barrier spells?
Yes. That's fine...
But our real problem is
the curse on Saber's left hand.
Eighteen hours have passed
since your defeat of Kayneth,
...but Saber's wound hasn't healed.
Lancer must still live.
Shouldn't we defeat Lancer first,
...so we can face Caster
at full strength?
That isn't necessary.
You just need to use
your knowledge of the area...
...to confuse the enemy,
keeping Saber away from him.
You won't have her
fight Caster?
Someone else will deal with him
even if we don't.
The ones hunting Caster in a frenzy
will make for better targets.
I'll attack from their flanks
and take them out.
Master, you are...
To what depths
do you intend to sink?!
You do an insult
to Heroic Spirits.
Why do you not allow me to fight?
Do you mean to imply that you cannot
trust me, your own Servant?!
There's a truce against
everyone but Caster, isn't there?
It will be fine.
This overseer of ours
can't be trusted.
He harbors Assassin's Master,
and doesn't say anything about it.
He may also be working
with Tohsaka.
We should be skeptical
of anything he does.
All right. Dismissed.
Kiritsugu...
If...
If I...
If I decided to abandon
everything and run away...
Iri, would you come with me?
What about Ilya?
She's still at our castle!
I'd return for her,
...killing anyone in our way.
And then...
I'd give all I have for you and Ilya!
And for no other!
Could we get away?
We could escape!
If we go now, it's not too late!
You're lying.
That's a lie.
You could never run away.
You'd never forgive yourself
for abandoning the Grail.
For failing to save the world.
As your first and final accuser,
...you would kill yourself.
I'm scared.
He...
Kirei Kotomine is after me.
Maiya told me.
He used Kayneth as bait
to draw me out.
He anticipated my actions.
I've already sacrificed you
to this conflict,
...and I've had to leave Ilya behind.
But the most dangerous of them all
has set his sights on me already.
The one that I'd hoped to never
cross paths with!
I won't allow you to fight alone.
I'll protect you.
Saber will protect you.
And... Maiya is here, as well.
Kiritsugu?
An enemy attack?
It's lucky that I hadn't
sent out Maiya yet.
We can mount
an all-out defense.
Iri, find a remote-viewing crystal ball.
There they are.
Irisviel, the enemy
is trying to lure us out.
Those must be hostages.
I'll have to go down and save them.
He knows we're watching!
As promised last night,
...I, Gilles De Rais,
have come for you.
I wish to see you, Jeanne.
My beautiful Holy Virgin...
Irisviel...
You may take your time if you wish.
I have come prepared
for a lengthy wait.
Now, children, it's time
to play hide-and-seek.
The rules are simple.
You need only elude me.
But if I find you...
Don't!
Run, children! When I count to
one hundred, the chase begins.
Well, Jeanne?
How long do you think
it will take me to catch them all?
Saber, defeat Caster!
I shall!
Welcome, Jeanne.
How do you like this horrible sight?
It pains you, does it not?
Do you despise me?
Yes, I'm sure you must.
I'm sure you'll never forgive me
for turning from God's love.
Unhand the child, monster!
Jeanne, if you so dearly wish
to save the boy...
Rejoice, child.
God's devout messenger
says that she will save you.
It's dangerous here.
Now, run away.
Follow this path, and you'll
come to a large castle.
Do you not remember?
I said that when next we met,
I would be prepared.
Very well...
My fight with you is no longer
over the Grail!
Oh, Jeanne...
How noble! How beautiful!
Holy Virgin,
even God's beauty pales before you!
Caster! I take up my sword
to destroy you!
If only I could use my left hand...
Even Caster's mana isn't infinite.
If she can last until it runs out,
...Saber can win, right?
Kiritsugu?
More importantly, is there still no sign of
the other Masters entering the forest?
Maiya.
Take Iri and flee the castle.
Head in the opposite direction
as Saber and Caster.
I can't stay here?
With Saber fighting away from you,
it isn't safe.
One of the others is sure to
have had the same idea.
All right.
What's wrong, Iri?
It appears another has arrived.
HOW?
Is there no end to his mana?
Impossible.
The source of his mana is...
So that book is your Noble Phantasm?
Just so. The grimoire left me
by my teacher Prélati...
...gives me the means to
command a demonic legion.
What do you think, Jeanne?
It brings back memories,
right, Jeanne?
Everything is just as it was then.
Your indomitable Warrior's spirit
and noble bearing...
...prove you to be
none other than Jeanne d'Arc!
So why?
Why do you not awaken?
Do you still believe in
God's grace even now?
Even when faced with mortal peril, you
still believe a miracle will save you?
How tragic... Have you forgotten
the Battle of Compiegne?
Even after enduring that humiliation,
you still remain God's puppet?
Pathetic, Saber.
Such swordsmanship is
unworthy of the title King of Knights.
Who are you?
Who gave you leave to
interfere with us?
That is my question, monster.
It will be my lance
that takes Saber's life!
It was my prayer!
It was my Holy Grail
that brought her back to life!
She is mine...
Every scrap of flesh, every drop of blood,
even her very soul is mine!
Hey, Caster.
I won't comment on your
notion of romance.
If you say you're going to make
Saber yours, then try it.
But know this...
I, Diarmuid,
will not allow you...
...to defeat a crippled Saber
before I can!
Lancer, you...
Don't get the wrong idea, Saber.
The only thing that brought me here today
was the order to defeat Caster.
To that end, I believe cooperation
to be our best option here.
What do you think?
Just to be clear, Lancer,
...I could kill a hundred of
those things with just the one arm.
A mere hundred
is child's play.
You'll pay for this...
Don't get any ideas,
you savage!
Fervor Mei Sanguis.
Kayneth El-Melloi,
ninth Archibald family head, is here.
Mage of the Einzbern, let us duel
for the Grail with our lives and our honor!
Mechanical traps, of all things...
Have you fallen so low, Einzbern?
Very well. Then this is no longer
a duel, but an extermination.
I see... Automated probes.
Found you, rat.
Sculp!
Time Alter: Double Accelerate!
He manipulated time to accelerate himself
by using his own body as a Reality Marble...
It seems that he knows
a little magic after all.
Still, only a coward would rely on
petty tricks after being trained as a mage.
Perhaps dying
will teach him his place.
Ire Sanctio!
If he's manipulating his inner time, it must
be placing enormous stress on his body.
I've found him.
Now then, how far can you run,
as exhausted as you are?
Time Alter: Triple Stagnate.
These things don't have eyes.
If I slow my internal time
to a third,
...and lower my pulse and respiration
as far as they can go,
...they can't sense me.
Kayneth!
You fool!
You're wasting your time!
Episode 7:
Dark Forest
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
Maiya, no!
I've shamed myself as a mage!
Tremble... Despair.
Strike! Gae Dearg!
By whose order
did you engage in battle?
You're ready. Right, monster?