Madam?
Please hurry.
Another intruder.
They're waiting in the direction
we're headed.
We'll run into them
if we go this way.
Understood.
Let's circle around
to the north side, then.
Madam?
The one who's coming is...
...Kirei Kotomine.
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
Kirei Kotomine?
Maiya, your orders from Kiritsugu were
to protect me, right?
Yes.
- But...
- But what?
We mustn't let him get to Kiritsugu,
no matter what.
Is that what you're thinking?
Madam. How did you-
What a coincidence,
I was thinking the same thing.
Kirei Kotomine...
He probably represents
the biggest threat to Kiritsugu.
You and I will hold him off here!
Understood, Maiya?
I apologize.
But please prepare yourself, Madam.
I will. Don't worry about me.
Do what you must do.
What you believe to be necessary,
not what Kiritsugu told you to do.
Yes, ma'am.
Is there something else?
No.
The human heart is a funny thing, isn't it?
You repeat an attack you know
to be futile...
Sculp!
He breached Volumen Hydragram's
autonomous defense?
No... His childish attacks lulled me
into lowering my guard.
I shall take steps to provide for a swifter,
more efficient defense.
You are a disgrace to mages everywhere.
You piece of lowborn trash!
For spilling my blood,
you will pay with your life.
He knows how powerful this is now.
It won't work on him twice.
Next time, he'll channel
all his mana into defense.
No...
That's exactly what I need him to do.
An illusion?
Maiya, no!
Madam... Don't!
Woman, this may come as a surprise,
...but I haven't come here
to defeat you.
I know that, Kirei Kotomine.
I know what you desire.
But I will not allow it.
You will never reach
Kiritsugu Emiya.
We will stop you.
Here.
Madam!
He is an Executor...
An expert at hunting mages!
Normal magic won't
be enough to stop him!
Kiritsugu taught me more...
...than how to drive a car.
He taught me to live.
And to survive!
Shape Ist Leben!
- Madam!
- It won't be that easy!
Maiya!
Finish him!
It can't be...
You bastard...
I'm honestly stunned that
we've made so little progress.
It's that grimoire, Lancer.
As long as he holds that Noble Phantasm,
our situation will not improve.
I see... So that's his secret.
But if you plan to knock the book
from that pale freak's hands,
...you'll need to get past
this wall of monsters.
Lancer... What say you to
taking an all-or-nothing gamble?
It feels a bit shameful, but there's
no glory simply in fighting these things.
Very well. Count me in, Saber.
I shall clear a path.
We shall have but one chance at this.
Lancer, can you run on the wind?
Ah, I understand you.
It is child's play.
Have you said your prayers?
Tremble... Despair.
Superior skill can only defeat so many
before being overwhelmed by sheer numbers.
It must be humiliating, right?
You will die, suffocated under a horde of
monsters that know nothing of honor or glory!
There can be no greater
disgrace for a hero.
That beautiful face...
Make it twist in pain
for me, Jeanne!
Strike Air!
Prepare yourself...
Strike home!
Gae Dearg!
Damn you...
Damn you, damn you, damn you...
Damn you! Damn you!
Damn you!
How did you like that?
Had Saber suddenly regained the use of
her left hand, this would have been the result.
Prepare to die.
Monster.
Pathetic.
I didn't join the Holy Grail War
to fight this sort of battle!
Where is he?
There you are...
You skulking rat.
Surely you don't expect the same trick
to work on me a second time, do you?
Lowborn scum!
The fact that you succeeded in
landing a single blow...
...wasn't due to any strategy of yours.
It was a fluke, plain and simple.
I'll see to it that you understand
the difference.
I shan't let you die easily.
I shall use healing magic to
regenerate your heart and lungs...
...while I rend every inch of flesh.
In pain and despair,
you will die as you suffer.
And while you die, you will curse them...
You will curse the cowardice
of those who hired you!
You will curse the Einzberns
for making a mockery of the Grail War!
Fervor Mei Sanguis!
I knew you'd do that, fool!
Your struggles are in vain!
How cowardly can he get?
Lancer...
Is something wrong?
My Master is in danger...
It seems he left me here
and breached the castle himself.
I'm certain that the danger
comes from my own Master.
Lancer, hurry to his side.
Go to your Master's aid.
King of Knights, you have my thanks.
Think nothing of it.
You and I have sworn to settle matters
in a manner befitting two knights.
Let us keep our pride intact.
This means that all went
according to Kiritsugu's plan, then?
Your origin is based on cutting and tying, kid.
To cut and tie...
The nuance is a little different than
destruction and regeneration.
If you cut a thread and then retie it,
...it will be thicker where
you cut it, right?
In that sense, it carries
a connotation of irreversible change.
I've powdered some of your ribs
and put part in here.
Your origin will materialize in
anything shot by this.
It's especially powerful
against mages.
If they use any magic against it,
your origin will destroy their Magic Circuits,
...which will then reconnect improperly.
The more powerful the mage, the more
their Magic Circuits will run haywire and short out.
Naturally, they won't recover,
either as a mage or a human.
This is for your Mystic Code,
origin rounds.
I've made 66 in total.
Don't waste them.
You know how easy it would be
for me to skewer you now, correct?
Master of Saber.
So that's it...
I shall not let you kill my Master.
Nor will I kill Saber's Master.
Neither of us wish for our duel
to be ended that way.
Never forget this.
The reason you survived our encounter...
...is the nobility demonstrated
by the King of Knights.
Woman, I have one question.
It appears that you challenged me...
...with the intent to protect Kiritsugu Emiya.
By whose order did you attack me?
You do not possess Command Seals,
...so you are not
the Einzbern Master.
Most likely, you are a homunculus,
charged with protecting the Grail Vessel.
Someone like that could not
be stupid enough...
...to risk going to the front lines of the battle.
So I ask again...
Who ordered you to fight?
Master Kirei...
Caster, as well as
Lancer and his Master, have left the forest.
Saber will arrive shortly.
My lord, it is dangerous here.
Fascinating.
So it's red, after all.
Impossible.
Could these women have challenged me
of their own accord,
...without being ordered to do so?
Impossible.
Kiritsugu Emiya is like me.
Alone and empty, understood by no one.
He must be.
Irisviel...
Irisviel!
Wake up.
Saber...
No!
You must stay awake!
I'll call Kiritsugu.
Be strong until then!
Where is Kirei?
The enemy who was just here?
He escaped.
Had I been only a second faster,
this would not have happened.
What about Maiya?
Her wounds are grave,
but not life-threatening.
I'm more concerned about you.
You've lost so much blood...
Irisviel?
How can this be?
I want you to carry Avalon, Iri.
But this is a Noble Phantasm that heals
its bearer's wounds.
I think you should keep it.
No.
Unless its original owner, Saber,
is nearby to supply it with mana,
...the scabbard won't work.
You'll be the one working with Saber
from now on.
So you should have it.
Keep it within you,
as a Conceptual Weapon.
Additionally, tell no one of this.
Indeed, not even Saber herself.
From the moment you touched me,
...I felt Avalon's power.
Thank you, Saber.
Kirei Kotomine...
That Executor is just as dangerous
as I imagined.
No, even more so.
We were lucky today, but there's
no telling what will happen next time.
All I know for certain is that
I can't let him get to Kiritsugu.
But I'm not the only one
who's protecting Kiritsugu.
Isn't that right, Maiya?
Next time, we'll win for sure.
We'll both protect Kiritsugu, okay?
Episode 8:
The Mage-Slayer
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
My Master is in mortal peril!
Dignity is required, even in battle.
I cannot consent to that.
Give me the Command Seals...
Lancer isn't the fine man you think he is!