Fionn mac Cumhaill, hero of Aillen
and leader of the knights of Fianna,
...and my daughter Gréinne
formally announce their engagement.
Everyone, tonight I want you
to celebrate!
That striking man with the mole
beneath his eye...
What is his name?
He is a knight of Fianna,
Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Diarmuid...
Traitor.
You will suffer for this, Diarmuid.
Take me with you.
And run!
Rejoice, Gréinne...
Fionn has recognized our marriage!
Did you believe I'd forgotten
what happened with Gréinne?
A dream?
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
That dream I had...
That was the legend of Diarmuid.
Were those my Servant's memories?
Where am I?
I see that you're awake.
Sola-Ui...
What is the meaning of this?
Wh-Why am I here?
You have no memory at all
of what happened?
I...
I was shot.
I defended myself with
the Volumen Hydragram, but...
What's wrong with my body?
Evidence suggests that
every Magic Circuit in your body misfired.
It's a miracle you didn't die instantly.
For now, all I've been able to do is
to regenerate your organs.
But your Magic Circuits were
utterly destroyed.
You'll never use magic again.
I...
Don't cry, Kayneth.
It's too soon to give up.
We haven't lost yet.
Sola-Ui...
If the Holy Grail is truly
an omnipotent wish-granting device,
...healing you should be
more than possible for it.
We need only win.
If we succeed and claim the Grail,
everything will return to how it was.
With that in mind, Kayneth...
Give me the Command Seals...
I'll take over as Lancer's Master,
...and bring you the Grail.
N-No!
You don't believe in me?
In me... The woman who will marry
into the Archibald family?
No... But...
Sola-Ui, do you think Lancer...
...would abandon me,
to swear fealty to you?
I do. He is a Heroic Spirit,
here by the Grail's invitation.
He desires the Grail, just as we do.
Even if he must change Masters,
...he will accept it,
for the sake of his goal.
Sola-Ui!
Lancer isn't the fine man you think he is!
Why do you say that?
When I asked him
what he'd wish for, he said,
..."I have no interest in
the Holy Grail."
A Servant with no desire for
the Grail is categorically impossible.
He's hiding something important...
But no matter what he hides,
...as long as I bear these Command Seals,
he must obey me.
Kayneth...
I won't give you the Command Seals...
Kayneth, you still don't understand,
do you?
You don't understand that
we must win, no matter the cost.
Listen, Kayneth.
It is beyond my skills
as a spiritual healer...
...to forcibly remove Command Seals
once they have been bestowed.
The bearer's willing consent is the sole way
for me to take them without resistance.
If you truly cannot
accept this,
...you will leave me no choice
but to amputate your right arm.
What will it be?
Irisviel?
It's all right.
Magical healing puts
tremendous stress on the patient.
I think it will take time yet
before she wakes up.
Watch her for a while, okay?
You're going to report to Kiritsugu?
I'm sure he's worried, too.
Irisviel, I have a request.
I'd like you to speak to
Kiritsugu for me.
Tell him I feel that we must pursue
Caster immediately.
Saber...
Inaction on our part will mean
the deaths of more innocent children.
Kiritsugu?
How long before
we can use Maiya again?
She has to stay in bed
for another day or two.
I see.
You and Saber stay here.
I'm going to follow Kayneth.
Wait, Kiritsugu!
Did Saber tell you
we should go after Caster right away?
Apparently so.
Are you angry at Saber for
not stopping Lancer?
Iri...
Saving a few children, or even a few dozen,
is not our goal.
Saber probably never doubted that
Lancer would spare me.
But if Lancer had betrayed her,
what would have happened?
Our Grail War
would have ended right then and there.
There's no need to tell her
where I'm going...
Lancer? Please show yourself.
Mistress Sola-Ui,
how fares Kayneth?
Not well.
I've done everything I can, but he...
This isn't your fault...
It's Kayneth's!
All it means is that
the Grail War was too much for him.
It's not that, I just...
Diarmuid, he isn't worthy
to be your Master.
Kayneth has abandoned the battle,
...entrusting me with his rights
as your Master!
As a knight, my loyalty is
pledged to Kayneth.
Mistress Sola-Ui,
I cannot consent to that.
Wait...
As a Servant, do you not manifest
physically using my mana?
And now I have
the Command Seals, as well.
Before I am a Servant,
I am first and foremost a knight.
A knight can serve but one lord.
Am I so unworthy of
being your Master?!
I've told you
that is not the issue...
Look me in the eye
when you speak to me!
Lancer, fight beside me.
Protect me!
Lend me your support.
Win the Holy Grail with me!
I cannot.
If Kayneth has given up
his battle,
...then I no longer have
any interest in the Grail.
We require a miracle to heal him!
Only the Grail can perform that miracle.
If you truly feel responsible
for what's happened to him...
If you desire to give him back
his dignity as Lord El-Melloi,
...then you must win
the Holy Grail for your Master!
Mistress Sola-Ui, do you speak
as Master Kayneth's wife,
...and seek the Grail only on his behalf?
Is that correct?
Y-Yes... Of course!
Will you swear to it? And that
you have no other desire?
I swear.
As the wife of Kayneth El-Melloi,
I shall bring my husband the Grail.
That look in her eyes...
It is the same as Gréinne had.
I don't hate them for what happened.
However, fate was simply too cruel.
What I seek from this life is
the loyalty denied me in my last.
I wish to keep that sad fate
from happening once again. But...
In my previous life, I threw myself
into many battles.
There were times when I had to ignore
the lives that would be lost.
That is why I can understand
Kiritsugu's reasoning in this matter.
Nevertheless, the Holy Grail War
has clear rules.
It is supposed to be a proxy war
over the Grail by means of Servants...
...to avoid unnecessary bloodshed.
Is that not the case, Irisviel?
If Lancer's Master and Kiritsugu had
not engaged in battle in secret,
...we could have
struck down Caster.
We would no longer have to worry about
more innocent children being killed.
Lancer and I could have finished
our duel in an honorable fashion.
Is there no chance
of Kiritsugu changing his mind?
If you believe only one thing, Saber,
believe this.
For Kiritsugu and me to make
our ideal world a reality,
...you are absolutely essential.
It does a man good to
watch you drink...
Oh, thank you.
You should have told us
you had a guest!
No, no.
Don't trouble yourself, ma'am.
The simple pleasures of home
are what is best.
Oh, you're such a flatterer!
We couldn't help but worry over how
Waver was doing in school in England,
...but if he's made friends with
a strapping man like you,
...well, we were worried
over nothing!
Not at all, it is I
who am in his debt.
See? He even picked out
these fine pants for me.
So, how long will you
be in Japan, Alexei?
Oh, I should have my work here
wrapped up in a week or so.
If you like, why don't you
stay here with us?
I'm sure that there's enough space
for another futon in Waver's room.
Right, Waver?
Futon? Oh, the bedding
they sleep on in this land!
It takes some getting used to.
It's strange to sleep on the floor
instead of in a bed.
That is what is best
about foreign lands!
My favorite thing in life
is the surprise of the unknown!
Surely, Asia gives me the
most enjoyment in any age!
RiQht you are!
I told you... to take spiritual form...
...when you come and go!
Had I done so, I could not
have retrieved this.
I even managed to procure
this fine pair of pants.
Anyway, boy, it was you
who ordered me to do it.
Why must I,
the King of Conquerors,
...go forth to draw water from
some country river?
Because it's more productive than
eating junk food and watching videos.
What's this? Are you playing
at being an alchemist?
I'm not playing.
I am an alchemist.
What is that?
The residue left by spell casting.
It's the remnant of magic,
left in the water.
And that means someone was
using magic near the river.
If we follow the trail,
it may show us where to look.
Boy, did you know ahead of time that
something like that was in the water?
Of course not.
But this town is unusual, in that
water flows straight through its center.
So starting with the water was
the obvious choice.
Rider. Was there anything
between here and here?
Maybe an irrigation channel
or a sewage pipe?
Oh! There was
one of considerable size.
That's it.
If we follow it, it will probably
lead us to Caster's laboratory.
Boy, are you certain you aren't
a mage of not inconsiderable skill?
A skilled mage wouldn't
have to do it this way.
It's probably the simplest
imaginable method.
You're making fun of me, aren't you?
Not in the least!
To accomplish something impressive
using a simple method...
...far outshines achieving the same result
with a more complex technique!
As your Servant, I am proud.
Right, then...
Once we have his location,
he's as good as ours.
Shall we go give him
a good beating right away, boy?
Just wait a second. We're talking
about engaging Caster here.
- I know that.
- You don't know!
When it comes to defending his lair,
he has the largest advantage.
What kind of moron
would go bursting in?
Listen...
In combat, enemy and ally positions
can change by the second.
If you fail to attack the enemy
when you know his location,
...it will be too late for regrets
once you've missed your chance.
What's made you so eager today?
Why should I not be?
My Master has finally contributed
something of worth.
As a Servant,
I must also do my duty,
...and bring back the enemy's head!
Do not be so quick to give up
before we've even begun.
Let us go and see what we find.
It may well work out better
than you imagine.
I was right!
You see?
Everything has worked out!
Unfortunately,
Caster appears to be away.
Is this some kind of water storage system?
Hey, boy...
I think it would be best
if you didn't see this.
What are you talking about?
If Caster isn't here,
...we should at least search for clues
to his whereabouts.
That's as may be, but don't do it.
Boy, this is too much for you.
Shut up.
I warned you, didn't I?
I told you not to look.
Shut up!
Damn it, stop making fun of me.
Damn it...
This is no time for pride, fool.
Your reaction is perfectly natural.
If I saw someone who could
look on this and remain unmoved,
...I'd punch them.
What do you mean,
you'd punch them, you idiot?
Right now, you look just fine!
That's because now is not
the time for emotion.
Because my Master is in mortal peril!
Assassin?
But that's impossible!
Assassin's dead.
We can't afford to be surprised, boy.
H-How?
The "how" of it is irrelevant to us now.
However, one thing is certain...
Anyone who believed in
Assassin's demise has been deceived.
They ran... Didn't they?
Do not let your guard down.
We killed two, and there appeared
to be an additional two.
At this rate, who can say
how many Assassins there truly are.
This is their preferred terrain.
We should withdraw at once.
Should we really leave
this place the way it is?
Perhaps you'd find something
if you were to look, but let it go.
For now, we'll just have to
break what we can.
If nothing else,
it will serve to slow Caster down.
With his hideout in ruins, Caster will
no longer be able to run and hide.
He'll be forced to come out into the open.
Before too long,
...we shall put an end to them.
All right, I get it!
Quit doing that!
Let us be off, boy.
Do not let it trouble you, Kirei.
Indeed, it is unfortunate that
Assassin was exposed to them...
...before we could discern
the nature of Rider's ultimate weapon.
But from this,
...we've found out that Rider's Master
is a mere third-rate mage.
Had they not been discovered...
Other options would have
become available to you?
Yes.
While your plans are
certainly important,
...you must remain refined
and relaxed, in all matters.
Dignity is required, even in battle.
But I never thought
he'd be so boring a person...
We will have another chance to
see Rider's ultimate attack.
Have Assassin continue to monitor Rider,
but to take great care as they do.
Understood, my teacher.
Episode 9:
Master and Servant
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
I used too much mana at once?
I'm certain there's something
I can do to help!
Surely she didn't go to Fuyuki...
Behold the family magic of the Matous.
We're just about to get
the party started.
I can't accomplish
anything like this!
Next Time: Rin's Big Adventure I
can't accomplish anything like this!