Rin.
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
Hey!
You shouldn't gang up on someone
to bully them!
You suck!
You really suck!
What's your problem, Tohsaka?
This doesn't concern you.
In that case, why don't you
do the same thing to me?
Then it will concern me.
Hey.
This is lame!
Here!
You used too much mana at once.
Maintain a calm mind.
In order to control magic,
you must first control your mind.
Lose control, and the mana will
rebound back to your body.
Too much power, or power
in the wrong form,
...will endanger not only you,
but those around you, as well.
Strive to consistently maintain
the proper flow.
That is the Tohsaka family motto.
It means always remaining
reserved and elegant.
You shouldn't let them get away with it
when they try that stuff, Kotone.
If they're in the wrong,
you have to get mad.
You're amazing, Rin. The way you always
speak your mind like that.
It's not amazing.
I think it's normal. It's only natural.
That's right... It's only natural.
Hold out your hand.
Father, teach me more!
How do I make something like this?
Well, that might be difficult
for you right now.
But if you work hard every day,
you'll be able to make it eventually.
After all, you're a daughter of
the Tohsaka family.
Hey, Rin... Can you show me
how to do this part?
Of course. Which part?
Me, too!
- Me, too.
- And me...
This was on page 23
in the textbook.
You just did the math wrong here.
For this problem...
It's just like this example, see?
Kotone?
Have a seat.
I'll help everyone in turn.
Okay!
Do I have to go live
with the Zenjos?
Once the Holy Grail War begins,
it will no longer be safe here in Fuyuki.
I want to help you win
the Grail War...
Rin...
You mustn't cause trouble
for your father.
Are we in the way?
Not at all.
This time, I'll need to make extra
preparations for the battle.
Those preparations include
ensuRin! your safety.
And for me to do that,
you shouldn't stay in Fuyuki.
I'm certain there's something
I can do to help!
That's right...
I just haven't learned how to yet.
So all I need to do is
study on my own.
I-I don't understand
any of this...
What is this? Jeez!
Du, wer die Tür geöffnet hat,
wird Freunde sein.
I have to close it.
Fiir die Aussage, nimm meine Hand,
...wir weden in meinem Zimmer treffen.
It won't move!
Sind deine Hände klein?
Gross? Schlank? Steif?
Rin!
- Jede Hand ist dankbar.
- Are you all right?
Ich will sie erhalten.
I ch schneide sie vorsichtig...
It's still too soon for you
to read this book.
Some things in this world...
...contain their own mana.
This is called a mana compass.
Normally, it doesn't point to anything.
But if there are mana traces
in the area...
Rin, try generating mana in this.
Okay.
See? Like this.
And with that book...
Anything that provokes
a reaction like that...
...is beyond your ability,
so take care.
I'll give this to you.
As an early birthday present.
Th-Thank you, Father!
Once the Holy Grail War ends,
we'll try some real jewel magic.
And then, strange things
began to happen.
They said we have study hall again...
There was another kidnapping
on the news this morning.
In Fuyuki City, the sudden
disappearances of children...
The teachers have been
in a meeting all day.
- They said we won't have fifth period today.
- All right!
But they said we should stay home.
Why?
Another kidnapping...
They said only children
have been kidnapped.
HEY, did you hear?
Apparently, there's no body
inside the coffin.
It was in such bad shape?
It definitely happened
in Fuyuki, right?
U-Uh, my name is Tohsaka,
- ...and I'm in Kotone's class...
- The person you have called is not home.
Please leave your message
after the beep.
Please be safe...
Kotone...
This is Fuyuki at night...
It's completely different
than duRin! the day.
It's really creepy...
What is this?
I've never seen it do this.
Does this mean there are traces
of magic all over?
I have to find Kotone!
Someone out with their kid
this late?
What was that?
Oh, “Q!
That was close... If I'm spotted,
they'll take me home.
You've gotta walk, kid.
Two of them?
He has more kids.
Why?
Wait... Why am I hiding?
I can't accomplish
anything this way!
No one's here?
H-Hey!
Kotone!
Kotone! Kotone!
Something's been done to her?
What do I do?
There has to be something...
What have we here?
Are you lost?
No... Um...
Perfect timing.
We're just about to get
the party started.
We still don't have
enough guests, though.
You wanna help?
The more the merrier, right?
No!
What was that?
Don't run from me.
He's controlling them
with that bracelet?
Ow!
I have to destroy it!
What? So you are gonna help me?
Huh? What?
You used too much mana at once.
I can destroy this!
What?!
Kotone!
Rin
What's going on?
There's no time to cry! Run!
Hey! Wait!
Oh!
Man...
I hope the big guy
won't be too pissed.
Huh?
Where's Rin?
What a relief...
I should start back.
I did it, Father.
What?
Anything that provokes
a reaction like that...
...is beyond your ability, so take care.
Rin...
I can't believe she went to Fuyuki...
Rin!
Rin...
Rin is fine. She's just asleep.
Kariya...
What is this?
What's happening here?
What are you doing here?
Your face...
Behold the family magic
of the Matous.
You offer your flesh,
and your life is slowly devoured.
That is the magic's price.
But Sakura will be fine.
I'll save her
before this happens to her.
Zouken's only desire
is the Grail.
He promised if I win it for him,
he'll release Sakura.
The Grail?
Yeah, so don't worry.
My Servant is the strongest.
He won't lose to anyone.
Hope would be nothing but
cruel torture to Sakura right now.
So since she can't do it herself,
pray in her place.
For my victory.
For Sakura's future.
Kariya, you...
Someday, I'm sure we'll all play
in this park, just like we used to.
And Rin and Sakura will be sisters again,
just like they used to be.
SO,
...you don't need to cry anymore.
Kariya... Do you intend to die?
After you kill Tokiomi?
Mother?
Rin!
I was so worried...
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I'm sorry...
Master Kirei, are you certain
that you wish to allow...
...Tokiomi Tohsaka's wife
and daughter to go free?
It's fine.
Continue monitoRin! Berserker's Master.
Understood.
It wasn't much, but I did
manage to do something.
I guess I'm not a full-fledged mage yet.
I passed out halfway through.
That means I need to work harder.
But that's just for now.
I have plenty of time.
And someday,
I'll fight as a Tohsaka mage.
I'll have to practice really hard
and obey my father,
...so that I'll be ready
when that day comes.
And when the time comes,
...I'll do what I can to the best of
my ability as elegantly as I can.
Episode 10:
Rin's Big Adventure
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
A weak king is even worse
than a figurehead!
Of what worth is a king who fails
to protect the powerless?
We stand to lose nothing.
A Reality Marble?
I shall have to kill you myself.
Your goal was supposed to
be world conquest!