Irisviel.
Are you all right?
They waited for Kiritsugu to leave
before launching a frontal assault.
That lightning, and this frontal assault...
The enemy is likely...
Rider.
Kurikaesu sekai nando te wo nobashitara
In this endlessly repeating world, how many times must I reach out
Hakanai namida wa kuroi kokoro tokasuno?
so that my hopeless tears thaw my black heart?
Mebae dashita omoi ga mune ni hibiita nara
If these freshly-sprouted feelings are echoed in your own heart,
Kimi no tonari de zutto kawarazu mamoru darou
I will forever be by your side, protecting you.
Ochita kibou wo hirotte asu ni tsunaide yukeba
If I pick up the fallen hopes and fasten them to tomorrow,
Karamatta ibitsuna negai datte hodokeru
even my tangled, knotted wishes will come unraveled.
Hikari wo kazashite tamerai wo keshita
Shielding my eyes from the light, I did away with all my hesitation.
Ageta katta no wa mirai de
What I wanted to give you was the future.
Naiteru yoru daita mama nageki wo sakende
As I shouted in grief, holding the teary night close.
Fumi ireta ashi wo tooku no risou ga Sotto iyashite yuku
Far-off hopes soothe my feet that are weary from walking.
Tashika na kizuna wo tsuyoku nigiri
Hold tight to this bond we can count on,
Susumou doko made mo
and let's keep going as far as we can,
Kegare kitta kiseki wo se ni
with this tainted miracle on my back.
Whoa!
Hey, Saber!
Rider?
I came because
I wanted to see your castle.
It's kind of gloomy,
don't you think?
And what's with that armor?
You aren't wearing
your fashionable suit tonight?
Rider, what are you doing here?
Can't you tell?
I've come to drink. What else?
Stop standing there,
and show me around.
Surely you have a garden here
suitable for a banquet.
Really, this castle is too dusty.
The Holy Grail is said to be fated for
the hands of the one most worthy of it.
And the battle here in Fuyuki
will determine who that person is.
If it's simply a means to decide,
...then there's hardly cause for bloodshed.
If all the Heroic Spirits can be
satisfied with our ranking,
...then the matter will settle itself.
Oh?
Then first, you wish to compare
your rank against my own, Rider?
Indeed.
As one who also lays claim
to the title of king,
...you cannot refuse this opportunity.
You might consider this a Grail Dialogue,
rather than a Grail War.
The matter of which among us is
most suited to claim the Grail...
...will become clear as we drink.
That is quite enough nonsense,
...mongrels.
Archer, what is your business here?
Ah, I saw him in town,
...so I figured I might as well invite him.
You're late, Goldie.
Well, I suppose it stands to reason.
You travel by foot, unlike myself.
So you chose to hold a banquet of
kings in this depressing place?
How will you recompense me
for the rudeness of calling me here?
Lighten up.
Here, start with a drink.
What is this cheap swill?
You really thought we could discern
a hierarchy of Heroic Spirits with this?
You don't like it?
This was among the best I found
at the city marketplace.
You can believe it is because
you are ignorant of true drink.
Stupid mongrel.
Behold, and acknowledge your folly.
This is the drink of a king!
A fine treasure indeed.
Magnificent!
My treasury houses only
the finest drink and the finest of swords.
This alone should indicate which
among us is the greatest of kings.
Archer.
Your finest drink is, indeed,
worthy of the finest vessel.
Unfortunately, the Holy Grail
is not a drinking cup.
First, we must hear what wish
you would have the Grail grant.
You are not ruler here, mongrel.
Already, you violate the rules...
...dictating that we must fight for the Grail.
To begin with, the Grail
already belongs to me.
All of this world's treasures,
without exception,
...trace their origin to my treasure house.
Then you once held the Grail?
You would know it by sight?
No.
Do not consider me as
you would some lesser being.
The amount of wealth in my treasury
long ago surpassed my own knowledge.
But that it is a treasure also
means that it belongs to me.
And any who would take it
for themselves...
...is naught but a thief.
Your words are no different than
Caster's insane rants.
It appears he isn't the only Servant
to have gone mad.
Come, let's not go that far...
I believe I've got a clue to
what Goldie's real name is.
So, Archer...
You suggest that if we desire the Grail,
we must get your permission first?
Indeed.
However, there is no reason whatsoever
for me to reward mongrels of your ilk.
Wait a minute...
You're gonna keep it for yourself?
Fool.
My magnanimity is limited to
my vassals and my people.
In which case, Rider, if you were
to swear fealty to me,
...I could lend you a grail or two
whenever you felt the need for one.
Sorry, I'm afraid that's
out of the question!
But, Archer, surely you have no special
interest in the Grail itself, do you?
Of course not.
But I must render my judgment...
...to those who would steal
treasure from me.
It's a matter of principle.
So then, Archer...
On what morals and reasoning
are these principles based?
It is the law.
My law, which I set down
as king.
Perfect.
To live according to one's own law
is the epitome of kingship.
But still, I want the Grail
so badly I can taste it!
It's my style to take what I want.
After all, Iskandar is the
King of Conquerors, is he not?
Right and wrong do not enter into it.
You break the law, and I punish you.
There is no place for discussion.
Which means that
all we have left to us is combat.
So, Archer! Would you like
to finish this off?
There will be plenty of time to
kill one another afterwards.
Of course. Or do you dare
cast aspersions...
...on the drink I did you the honor
of providing you with?
Never! I wouldn't dream of letting
such fine drink go to waste!
King of Conquest...
You agreed that the Grail's rightful
ownership lies with another,
...so will you take it by force?
What makes the Holy Grail
so important to you?
Reincarnation.
Hey, wasn't your goal supposed
to be world conquest-
Idiot.
As if I would leave the conquering
to some mere cup!
Conquering the world is
my dream to make true!
The wish I would ask of the Holy Grail
is but the first step towards that goal.
Mongrel, you would dare challenge me
over something so trivial?
Even if magic lends us form in this world,
ultimately, we remain Servants.
I wish for rebirth,
to live as a flesh and blood man,
...within this world
in which I find myself.
And with nothing but my body,
I shall defy both heaven and earth.
That is the meaning of conquest.
Thus it begins, then proceeds,
and is finished.
Such is the path of my conquest.
Then the matter is settled, Rider.
I shall kill you myself.
Surely I don't have to remind you
of the obvious at this point.
I have every intention of plundering
your storehouse bare, so get ready.
That is hardly fitting of
how a king should be.
Then let us hear what you would say.
I wish for my homeland's salvation.
With the omnipotent wish-granting device,
...I shall avert Britain's fate of destruction.
They're having a drinking party,
of all things?
Shall I continue to leave Archer
to his own devices?
It can't be helped.
After all, when one
is King of Kings,
...it simply won't do to turn
one's back on a question.
Incidentally, Kirei...
How do you judge the relative
strengths of Rider and Archer?
Rider may possess a trump card
that surpasses the Gordius Wheel.
I believe we should
put this to the test.
With Rider and his Master drinking with their
guards down, a better chance to attack...
...will never present itself.
The odds of victory do not matter.
Even if Assassin is defeated,
...as long as he can gauge their relative strengths,
our objective will be accomplished.
We do have the option of launching
an attack right now, Kirei.
I have no objections.
I believe it will take roughly 10 minutes
to summon all of the Assassins.
Fine. Give the order.
It is a large gamble, but even if we fail,
we don't have anything to lose.
Kirei, use a Command Seal
to give Assassin the following order:
"Be victorious, no matter the cost."
Hey, King of Knights.
Did you just say that you would change fate?
Does that mean you wish to change the past?
Indeed.
Even if it is a wish that a miracle alone cannot fulfill,
...if the Holy Grail is truly omnipotent, then surely...
Um, Saber...
Just so I am clear on this...
It was during your time that
this country "Britain" fell?
When it was under your rule?
Indeed. That is why
I cannot allow it.
That is why I regret it.
I want to alter that outcome!
For it was I who was to blame,
and no other!
Archer, what is so amusing?
You call yourself a king, and
are praised by all as such...
And yet you feel "regret"?
How can I not laugh?
Saber.
Surely you do not mean...
...that you would erase the marks that
you yourself have left on history?
I do!
Why should that bother you?
Why do you laugh?
The country that gave me my blade,
to which I devoted my life, was destroyed.
Why should it be strange
for me to find that sad?
Did you hear that, Rider?
Did you hear what this little girl who
calls herself King of Knights said?
"To which I devoted my life..."
Why is that humorous?!
To ensure their country's prosperity, a king
should be willing to make any sacrifice.
No.
The king does not devote himself.
It is the nation and the people
who devote themselves to the king.
Not the reverse.
What?
Those are a tyrant's words!
Just so.
We are heroes because
we are tyrants.
However, Saber,
...if a king regrets his rule
or its end,
...that king is nothing but a fool.
Even worse than a tyrant.
Iskandar, your reign ended
with your heirs slain,
...and your empire dissolved
into three parts.
You have no regrets about that end?
None.
Not if it came to pass by my judgment
and my retainers' sacrifices...
Its destruction was inevitable.
I shall mourn it.
And shed tears over it.
But I shall never regret.
You...
Let alone undo it!
Such an act would be an insult
to all who fought alongside me!
Only warriors can find
glory in destruction!
Of what worth is a king who fails
to protect the powerless?
A just rule, with just laws...
Those are the true duties of a king!
So you, the king, are a slave
to what is right?
That is acceptable.
A king is a martyr to their ideals.
That is not how a person should live.
If I rule the nation as king,
I cannot expect to live as a person.
King of Conquerors,
...you seek the Grail merely
for your own benefit.
You could never understand...
You who became a ruler only to
satisfy your endless greed.
A king without greed is
even worse than a figurehead!
Saber.
You said you would martyr
yourself for your ideals.
In life, you must have been
a pure saint.
A proud and noble figure, certainly.
But who can truly admire
the martyr's thorny path?
Who dreams of such an ending?
A king...
The king must be greedier
than any other.
He must laugh more loudly
and rage for longer.
He must embody the extreme
of all things, good and evil.
That is why his retainers
envy and adore him.
And why the flames of aspiration,
to be as the king is,
...can burn within his people.
Proud king of chivalry...
The righteousness and ideals
you embraced...
...may indeed have saved
your nation and her people once.
However,
...surely you must know
what became of those...
...who were saved by you,
but left to fend for themselves.
What?
You saved them,
but you never led them.
You never showed them
what a king should be.
You abandoned your men
when they lost their way.
Then, alone and untroubled,
...you followed your own
pretty little ideals.
Thus, you are no true king.
You are only a little girl,
...enraptured by a false idol of
the king who serves others,
...but not themselves.
I...
What are you laughing at, Archer?
It is nothing.
I simply thought that your anguished face
was a lovely sight to behold.
It was the face of the virgins who shower me
with flower petals in my bed.
You truly are a woman
after my own heart.
Bastard!
Assassin?
Is this your doing, Golden Boy?
Tokiomi humiliates himself.
This isn't fair! Why are there
so many Assassins?
We are the one, become many.
A Servant who is many and also one.
But a Servant who is one,
with many...
...shadows.
A Servant with multiple personalities
has split into separate bodies for each?
R-Rider, um...
Calm yourself, boy.
Even those rude enough to
interrupt our banquet...
...may yet show us which is
the greatest king.
So you'll invite them to your banquet,
also, King of Conquerors?
Of course. The king's words
are for all to hear.
If they have come to listen,
...it matters not if
they are friend or foe.
Now, don't hold back!
Any who would speak with us,
come forth and take a cup.
This drink is as your blood!
Very well.
As I said, this drink is as your blood.
If you insist on spilling it...
...then so be it.
Saber! Archer!
Here is our banquet's final question.
Does a king stand alone?
The king must indeed be alone!
No, you don't understand at all.
I suppose I'll have to show you...
...exactly what a real king is.
This is...
A Reality Marble?
That's impossible.
A mental image materialized
into the real world?
My armies once rode
across these sands.
The place all the heroes
who stood with me,
...through joy and sorrow,
will never forget.
I can make this world real...
...because it still exists
within our hearts!
Behold my endless armies!
Their bodies destroyed, and their souls
offered to the world as Heroic Spirits.
And still, these legendary heroes
pledge their loyalty to me!
My bond with them is my
greatest treasure,
...my path of kingship!
The ultimate Noble Phantasm
that I, Iskandar, possess.
Ionian Hetairoi!
Each of these is a Servant!
It has been a long time, partner.
A king must live a grander life
than any other's,
...and embody his people's
image of admiration!
Yes!
He who is worthy of all heroes' envy,
...and he who leads their way, is the king!
Therefore, the king is not alone.
For his will equals that of
all his followers combined!
Yes!
Now, then...
Shall we begin, Assassin?
As you can see, what we have
created here is a plain.
Unfortunately, with our superior numbers,
we hold the advantage.
Annihilate them!
That ending wasn't as
much fun as I'd hoped for.
We have said all there is to say.
I suppose that will do for today.
Wait, Rider. I still...
You, keep silent.
Tonight was for a conversation
amongst kings.
But I no longer recognize
you as a king, Saber.
Little girl, wake from your sad dream.
If you don't, you'll someday lose
even that modicum of pride...
...you retain as a Heroic Spirit.
The dream of a king
you spoke of is a curse.
What?
Pay him no heed, Saber.
You are correct.
Follow the path you believe in.
Your pain and sorrow
as you bear...
...a burden of kingship that is
too heavy a weight for any.
It is splendid to look upon.
Keep at it, oh King of Knights.
It is possible you may prove
worthy of still more of my love.
Saber...
I remember.
There was once a knight
who left Camelot,
...claiming that King Arthur didn't
understand how others felt.
Perhaps...
...that sentiment was shared by everyone
who sat at the Round Table.
Episode 11:
Discussing the Grail
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Omoide ni yorisoi nagara kimi wo omoeru nara
All I wish is to love you as I snuggle your memory.
Itsumo minareteru madobe ni utsutta
Your eyes, which I see reflected in the window so often,
Sono hitomi wa ashita wo muite ita
were looking out towards the future.
Aa sakaraenu sadame to shittemo Kowaku nai
Even if I learn that my fate cannot be changed, I will not be afraid.
Kokoro kara shinji te iru
I believe in you from the bottom of my heart.
Shizuka ni utsuri yuku tooi kioku no naka
In my distant, shifting memories,
Kimi to sugoshita akashi wa tashika ni koko ni aru
The proof that we spent time together does exist here.
Afure dasu kimochi wo oshiete kureta kara
Because you told me of your feelings that could not be contained,
Kono sekai ga nakunatte mo watashi wa soko ni iru
even if this world vanishes, I will be with you.
This begins the second stage.
I'm not a normal human.
It is not that simple!
Follow what you seek.
The path is now open to you.
But that is an evil that
must be punished!