If there really is a giant monster up there,
will they give us permission to engage?
If this were a monster movie,
we'd be goners.
We'd just be there for it to kill us
before the Giant of Light shows up.
That isn't funny.
Well, we'll know for sure
soon enough.
It's no use...
It's restoring itself.
Its regenerative power is incredible.
It's all they can do just to keep it
from coming ashore.
I cannot reach Caster like this...
This is amazing...Just amazing!
Seriously amazing, Big Guy!
God is with us...
God is with us!
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
What a complete disaster.
In the Holy Grail War's long history,
...there has never been
a failure such as this.
According to observer reports,
...the Mion River area is
engulfed by a thick fog.
But a large number of bystanders
is beginning to gather.
This is now beyond our
ability to control.
We shall have to request aid
from the Mages Association.
And where is Tokiomi?
My master heads there now,
with Archer in tow.
Kirei...
I will handle the cover-up.
You go and assist Tokiomi.
Understood, Father.
What an utterly hideous
sight to behold...
Mongrels or not, they are still
supposedly famous warriors.
Yet not even together can they
finish that disgusting thing?
How very pathetic...
Do you not agree,
...Tokiomi?
We must eliminate that monster
before further witnesses see it.
In the name of the Tohsaka family...
King, that monster is a destructive pest
that tears apart your gardens.
I implore you to execute it.
That would be a gardener's work.
Or, Tokiomi, do you dare imply...
...that my Noble Phantasm is nothing
more than a gardener's spade?
Not at all!
But as you can see, the others are
unable to handle it themselves.
This is an excellent chance to display
the power wielded by a true hero.
I beg you...
Unbelievable.
We're leaving, Tokiomi.
I cannot bear to look upon that
nauseating thing further.
No...
King of Heroes, please wait!
Tokiomi,
...I have sacrificed four of my
swords and spears for you.
Now that they have touched that thing,
...I no longer even desire their return.
Do not impinge further
on my generosity.
You are the sole hero capable of
defeating that monstrosity.
Given how rapidly it regenerates,
...it must be destroyed
with a single attack!
And King of Heroes,
...the only thing capable of that
is your Sword of Rupture--
You dare?!
You would have me draw my
greatest treasure, Ea, here?
Know your place, Tokiomi!
To speak thus to a king
is punishable by death!
I could use a Command Seal,
...but it would severely damage my
relationship with the King of Heroes.
Father Risei and I devised
this entire plan...
...to restore my lost Command Seal
by eliminating Caster.
Why did it turn out this way?!
Damn it...
What is that?
There's a strange light
at six o'clock, too.
That's no helicopter.
Is it a UFO or something?
Control to Diablo-1.
What is your situation?
My situation...
Um... Well...
I'll drop altitude and get a bit closer!
Wait, Kobayashi!
Get back here, Diabolo-2!
If I can get closer, I should be
able to see what that thing is!
Kobayashi?
Kobayashi!
What is that thing?
It... It ate it.
Control to Diabolo-1!
What the hell is
happening up there?
Report!
Eyes... There are eyes...
Eyes everywhere!
Eyes? What do you
mean by eyes?
Is it going to eat me, too?
Captain Dug“.!
Diabolo-1, engaging!
W-Wait, Ougi!
What's happ--
I'll kill it before it eats me.
I'll avenge Kobayashi...
I'll hit it with everything I have!
Berserker?
What's he doing here?
Fool!
Stay down!
Him again? Why now?
That's...
Oh? The mad dog again?
Interesting...
My King, I shall engage
his Master.
Very well.
Go and play with him.
Good luck, then.
A dog belongs with its
face to the ground.
You dare take to the heavens,
a king's realm?
Do not be arrogant, mongrel!
Such impertinence...
Fascinating.
I've not done anything like
this for a long time...
For a lowly beast,
...you do keep me entertained.
You've certainly changed
for the worse...
...Kariya Matou.
You abandoned magecraft,
but were still drawn to the Grail.
And now, you've returned
looking like that.
Your disgraceful behavior...
...reflects very poorly on the Matous.
Tokiomi Tohsaka, I have
one question for you.
Why did you give Sakura to Zouken?
What?
Should you really be concerned
with that right now?
Answer me, Tokiomi!
There is nothing to say.
I simply wished my daughter
to have a bright future.
What?
Any mage with two children must
face a painful dilemma.
Only one may inherit
the family secrets.
The other must be cast out
to become one of the rabble...
My wife's womb was too bountiful.
Both Rin and Sakura...
...were born with a rare
level of potential.
Both daughters required the
protection provided by a mage clan.
To destroy the possibilities held by one...
...for the sake of the other?
What father would desire
such a tragedy?
One of the rabble...
The mother and two daughters
I saw on that day...
He would simply dismiss
them as rabble?
To fulfill my wish that both their
talents might be developed,
...I had no choice but to
send one away to be adopted.
And so, the Matou family's request
was like a blessing from Heaven.
As a clan that
knows of the Grail,
...their odds of reaching the Root
become that much greater.
A mage is one who is
born with power.
And one who will someday
attain still greater power.
Even before they are
aware of this fate,
...the responsibility lies in their blood.
That is what it means to
be born a mage's child.
If I cannot attain it,
...Rin will.
And even if Rin cannot,
...Sakura will.
She will carry on the
Tohsaka family's wishes.
You...
You'd have them fight?
Sister against sister?
Even should that happen,
...my descendants will be happy.
What?
The glory goes to you if you are the victor.
And if you are not, it goes
to your ancestors' clan...
Could a more joyous battle exist?
You're insane!
It isn't even worth the trouble
of trying to explain it to you.
Not to a man who is blind
to magecraft's nobility,
...let alone a traitor who
turned his back on it.
Shut up!
I'll never forgive you people.
You disgusting mages...
I'll kill you.
Zouken and you, too!
I will kill...
...every last one of you!
You refused to carry
on the Matou line,
...so its magics went to Sakura.
Perhaps I should thank you.
But even so...
...I cannot forgive you, either.
Your weakness, in running from the
responsibility of your blood.
Your baseness, in failing to see
anything wrong in doing so.
Kariya Matou, you are a disgrace
to magecraft.
Having once more
encountered one other,
...what else can I do but kill you?
Shut the hell up...
You inhuman monster!
No.
Taking responsibility for yourself is the
first condition of being a human.
One who cannot do even that...
...is less than human, Kariya.
A dog.
Insects, devour him...
Eat him alive!
Get 'em, Bluebeard!
Crush 'em! Kill 'em!
This whole place is God's toy box!
Saber!
I am in your debt, Saber!
It's time to say goodbye
to boredom...
There's no need to go out of
my way to kill anymore.
I can just sit back and
watch them die.
Crushed...Torn apart...
Smashed...
Eaten!
They'll die, and die, and die!
I'll see all kinds of guts and gore
I've never seen before...
Every day... Every day.
Around the world!
Everywhere!
Never ending! Never even--
It stopped?
What?
Hey, what was that?
Wow, that's so pretty...
I get it...
Yeah, that's why I never noticed.
Sometimes you can't see
what's right in front of you.
What I was looking for...
It was in my own guts...
...this whole time...
Ryunosuke?
I finally found it.
I've been searching
for it forever...
What's wrong with you?
If it was inside me,
why didn't you ever tell me?
You should've just told me...
Ryunosuke...
My Master.
You have died and
left me all alone.
But do not worry, Ryunosuke.
For I, Gilles de Rais,
...shall fulfill my promise to you.
Behold, Ryunosuke!
A gift to see you to
the next world...
The greatest COOL!
I've shot the man we believed
to be Caster's Master.
Appears we were right.
Shall we eliminate our next target...
...while the Servants deal
with the monster?
Wait, Maiya.
That is no mere monster.
It's an immortal creature,
infinitely regenerative.
It will reach the shore
before it vanishes.
If it starts feeding, it's all over.
With a new source of mana,
Caster can sustain his material form.
Then the damage would only spread.
The Holy Grail War itself
may need to be abandoned.
That's correct.
But how do we eliminate
an immortal monster?
Our only option is to
destroy it all at once.
To destroy every single scrap of it,
...completely incinerating it
in a single strike.
Anti-personnel or anti-army
Noble Phantasms won't be enough.
We need an anti-fortress
Noble Phantasm.
And Saber...
...possesses one.
Unfortunately, Lancer's curse
leaves her unable to use it now.
I say...
...that we have them
show us this chivalry...
...that they are so proud of.
Episode 14:
The Mion River Battle
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
This light...
Such a futile effort.
The undefeated king sings aloud the
name of the miracle held in her hands.
It is too painful to gaze upon.
Is he trying to
destroy himself?
We must stop him here!
Next Time: Golden Shine I shall
place my faith in you, Saber.