What do we do, Rider?
What now, mad dog?
Tokiomi...
I'll kill you!
Saber!
This isn't going in our favor.
If only Saber could use
her left hand...
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
Hey, Saber!
We're not getting anywhere
like this!
Withdraw for now!
Don't be stupid!
We must stop him here!
But we've exhausted our options.
Fall back for now.
I have an idea.
Listen, all.
Regardless of our plan,
...we must first gain time.
I shall draw him into
the Ionian Hetairoi.
However, not even the might of all
my elite warriors combined...
...will be able to slay that.
At best, all we can do is stall him
within the Reality Marble.
What then?
No idea.
Huh?
If I take in a thing of
that magnitude,
...the Reality Marble will only
last a few minutes.
Within that time,
you must find a way.
Heroic Spirits,
...I want you to find a
path to victory.
Hey, kid...
You stay here, too.
Hey!
Once I deploy the bounded field,
I won't know what transpires outside.
Kid, should something happen,
focus your mind and call me.
I shall dispatch a messenger.
Saber! Lancer!
I leave the rest to you.
Very well.
Such a futile effort.
Mom!
What is that?
You may as well dive headlong
into that mass of filth,
...mongrel.
After all that raging and
ranting against me,
...but when it comes time to follow through,
this is all you have?
Is he trying to
destroy himself?
Kariya. Consider this
an act of mercy.
Intensive Einascherung.
I-I'll kill you...
Tokiomi!
Zouken...
What should we do?
I know he said he'd
buy us some time,
...but if we don't think of something,
we'll be right back where we started.
Hey, Einzbern...
Don't you have any ideas?
Well, do you?
Well, um...
How does this work?
Iri?
Um, no, I'm...
Wait, who is--
I understand.
You are Rider's Master?
Perfect. I wanted to talk to you, too.
Who are you?
That doesn't matter.
Caster's disappearance
was your Servant's work, yes?
That's right... I guess.
A question, then.
When Rider releases his Reality Marble,
can he put down the contents in a specific area?
To a degree.
Within a hundred meters or so.
It should be possible.
Rider's the one who has control over where
he exits into the outside world.
Very well.
I'll wait for the right moment,
then fire a signal flare.
Send Caster back directly under it.
Can you do that?
I can... I think.
Probably.
One more thing.
I need you to relay a
message to Lancer.
Tell him that Saber's left hand has an
anti-fortress Noble Phantasm.
Huh?
Is something wrong?
Well, there was a
message for you.
Something about Saber's left hand being
an anti-fortress Noble Phantasm...
Is that true, Saber?
Can it destroy Caster's monster
with a single strike?
It can.
However, Lancer...
The weight of my sword is
the weight of my pride.
The wound from my battle with you
is an honor, not a hindrance.
In exchange for my left hand,
I gained Diarmuid Ua Duibhne's aid.
That is worth ten thousand men.
Now, Saber...
I cannot forgive Caster's actions.
He looks favorably upon the despair of the
masses and takes joy in spreading terror.
By the vows I swore as a knight,
...I cannot abide such evil.
Lancer, you mustn't!
Is it Saber who must win this fight?
Is it Lancer?
No, it is neither.
What must triumph here is the
knight's path of chivalry.
Am I wrong,
Heroic Spirit Arturia?
Lancer...
I shall rest my hope of victory
upon your blade, King of Knights.
I shall place my faith in you, Saber.
I accept, Lancer.
And upon my sword,
I swear victory!
That's...
From King Arthur's legend...
Saber!
Berserker?
He's...
You dare turn your
back on me, mongrel?
What insolence!
What?
Saber!
What does Berserker think he's doing?
I regain use of my left
hand, and now this?
Regardless of its own
self-awareness of this fact,
...a soul instinctively
seeks out the superior.
He was the only one you ordered Assassin
to investigate to such a degree...
...that you could understand those
complicated circumstances.
And this was due to your
unconscious interest.
It's still too soon.
What was that tremor?
A sign that Rider's Reality Marble
approaches its limit.
Rider...
I am Mithrenes of the Hetairoi.
I have come as my king's ears.
I want you to tell him
to wait for our signal,
...and then release the bounded field and
dump out Caster at the designated location.
He can do it, right?
It is possible.
But we're nearly out of time.
Within the Reality Marble,
...our forces cannot restrain that
strange monster much longer.
I know!
I know that!
Damn it!
That stupid Berserker.
Can't we do anything about him?
I will go.
Lancer...
I am putting an end to this,
mad warrior!
It's all or nothing...
Archer...
There! Right under that!
As you wish.
Really...
What took so long?
Now, Saber, show me.
I shall judge the true worth of
your Heroic Spirit's radiance.
The light...
It shines.
That sword is the embodiment of the sad,
yet noble, dream of all soldiers,
...past, present, and future, who lie
dying on the field of battle,
...clutched to their hearts
with their last breath.
She carries their will
as her pride,
...bidding them to remain
steadfast in their loyalty.
Now, the undefeated king
sings aloud...
...the name of the miracle
she holds in her hand.
Its name is...
Excalibur!
This light...
That's it, without doubt.
This light is...
This was the light, the blessing
of bliss with Jeanne...
What have...
I...
Did you see that,
King of Conquerors?
That was Saber's radiance.
Even after such a sight,
...do you still refuse to accept her worth?
That light comes from her having taken
all her people's hopes upon herself.
Its brightness is
painful to look upon.
And when you consider that
the one who must bear that burden...
...is but a dreaming little girl...
What I see there is what became
of a girl who was never allowed...
...to admire butterflies or flowers,
or even to fall in love,
...but was cursed by her ideals,
and ended up this way.
It is too painful to gaze upon.
Is that not why she
is so beautiful?
Her dreams were too much for her.
I imagine that, in the end,
they destroyed the dreamer.
The tears of lamentation she
surely shed as she died...
How sweet they must have tasted.
Truly, you and I will never get along,
Babylonian King of Heroes.
Oh? You finally realized that?
Then what will you do, Rider?
Will you let your steel give
shape to your rage?
I'd very much like that...
But I have exerted myself a bit much
to face such a one as you this night.
Of course, should you refuse to
allow me passage,
...I would be forced to fight back.
I don't mind.
I shall allow your retreat,
King of Conquerors.
I shouldn't like to destroy
you at anything less...
...than your full strength.
I suppose that you yourself...
...haven't yet healed from the damage
that black thing inflicted?
I repay provocation with death.
We can decide this next time,
King of Heroes.
And our battle will be
the one that determines...
...the winner of this Grail War.
I wouldn't be so certain.
I have yet to decide whether
only one is worthy to face...
...my ultimate treasure, Rider.
Fool who reaches for dreams
beyond what humans may attain...
Only one in all creation should be
allowed to love her in her destruction.
And that is I, Gilgamesh.
Ephemeral and brilliant one,
fall to my embrace.
Such is my decision.
Episode 15:
Golden Shine
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
I am Diarmuid Ua Duibhne,
first spear of the knights of Fianna!
I am glad that I had the
opportunity to meet you.
Indeed!
I, Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
accept your challenge.
Next Time: The End
of Honor Come, then!
of Honor Here I go!