My apologies for the wait.
Things have been rather
hectic this evening.
It couldn't be helped,
given the situation.
It will be difficult to
cover all that up.
Yes, perhaps...
This is far too much for
the Church to handle by herself.
We are accepting any aid
proffered for this effort.
Now then, Father...
Regarding my request,
what is your decision?
Regarding the reward offered
for the defeat of Caster...
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
Thank goodness...
Now, once I get the Command
Seal for killing Caster,
...Diarmuid and I will be truly connected.
My right hand... It's gone!
My right hand! My right hand!
I need it! Or I cannot
call Diarmuid!
I won't be able to make
him care for me!
My right hand...
My right hand. My right hand.
My right hand! My right hand!
Hand...
My hand...
I have secured Sola-Ui Nuada-Re
Sophia-Ri over in New Town.
I removed the Command Seals
along with her right hand.
Fine.
Get out of there immediately.
Lancer should return any time now.
Roger.
I saved Kariya Matou...
Without doubt, he could
threaten my Master.
There is no excuse.
This is an act of rebellion.
But what is this I am feeling?
It is not regret...
Could I be excited?
It's true that in
the defeat of Caster,
...the Servant Lancer played
an important part,
...as verified by observer reports.
Then I have the right to receive
one of the Command Seals?
About that...
Mr. Kayneth Archibald,
...I am unsure whether it is appropriate
to consider you a Master at this point.
My pact with Lancer
was executed jointly...
...by my fiancée, Sola-Ui, and me.
And is Sola-Ui not the one
currently supplying mana...
...and acting as caretaker
for the Command Seals?
That is true.
I have temporarily given
her the Command Seals.
However, the rights of the
pact still reside with me.
First off,
...the petition submitted to the
Church to be a Master...
...was filed in my name.
Very well.
The rights are yours.
Now, Mr. Kayneth...
Extend your hand.
Take this, and drink from it.
This is my blood, which will be
poured out for you and for many.
The blood of the covenant!
I hope you will continue to fight
a noble battle as a Master.
Yes, of course.
I'm down to a single
Command Seal.
My situation remains dire.
I cannot allow the other Masters an additional seal!
Mistress Sola-Ui!
You complete incompetent!
Useless, bumbling fool!
You fail to protect even
a single woman?
I'm sick of all your talk of chivalry...
I am grievously sorry.
She may have been a mere substitute,
...but you still failed to protect
even your own Master!
What are you good for
as a Servant?
I'm amazed you had the nerve
to return here alone.
I am afraid, my Master,
...that Sola-Ui and I never
entered into a proper pact.
We could not sense
each other's presence.
And so you should have
taken special care!
My Master,
...Mistress Sola-Ui lives yet.
She still supplies me with mana.
Irrelevant!
If you are not properly
her Servant...
...and cannot discern her location,
it doesn't matter!
Sola-Ui, I should never have given
you those Command Seals...
I could not dissuade her.
I share in the responsibility.
I can't believe you have
the nerve to say that.
Don't try fooling me, Lancer.
You were the one who
encouraged Sola-Ui.
Never, Master!
It's just as in the legend...
Are you truly incapable of seeing...
...your lord's fiancée without
attempting to seduce her?
My Master,
...please retract those words.
Oh, have I struck a nerve?
You're only a beast.
You swore eternal loyalty,
...and then gave in to lust!
Kayneth...
why...
Why will you not understand?
I...
I wished only to defend my honor.
To fight in noble battle with you.
Don't speak to me like that,
Servant!
Understand your place.
You're nothing but a ghost,
granted form by magic!
You dare to lecture your Master?
Absurd!
If you are so dissatisfied,
use your precious pride...
...to resist my Command Seal.
You'll never win.
You Servants are mere puppets,
and here is your string.
Kayneth...
Master...
What? You still have something
to say to me?
No, that isn't it.
Something is approaching.
It's just as Kiritsugu said.
There are traces of
a magical barrier.
But it's strange...
It hasn't been properly maintained.
It's already starting to...
...fall apart...
I did not expect you here, Saber.
My...
My ally found this place
and informed me.
They said this was your location.
You would not happen to know
where my Master's betrothed is,
...would you, Saber?
I do not.
What of it?
No. Forget it.
In any event, are you certain
about this, Saber?
You did not come to engage
in idle chit-chat, I'm sure.
After employing that technique
against Caster,
...you must be exhausted.
No more so than the other Servants.
None will be fighting
further tonight.
They will focus on defense.
That is why we needn't worry
about being interrupted.
Dawn nears,
...but I believe this may be the best night
to finish our battle.
What say you, Lancer?
Saber...
The only thing that still
grants my heart peace...
...is your pure fighting spirit.
Her attacks are too weak.
Saber, you...
You will not use your left hand?
Don't get the wrong idea, Lancer.
If I use my left hand here,
...the shame is certain
to dull my blade.
Against your spear,
that would be fatal.
Saber...
Therefore, Diarmuid,
...this is my best strategy...
...to defeat you.
Pride rests in the blade of chivalry!
I...
I am glad that I was given the
opportunity to meet you.
I am first spear of the
knights of Fianna,
...Diarmuid Ua Duibhne.
Here I go!
Splendid!
I, Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
accept your challenge.
Come, then!
Why does he not win?
If he has no certain
path to victory,
...should he not escape
with his Master?
Right now, our highest
priority is to rescue Sola-Ui...
Why can he not
understand even that?
That useless Servant!
Why him, of all people?
This is...
...a Self-Geas Scroll.
A magical item, used by mages
to forge an unbreakable pact.
Binding Spell...
Affected Party: Kiritsugu Emiya.
The Crest of the Emiya family
orders the following.
The pledge is to be obeyed by the Affected Party
upon fulfillment of the terms described herein.
Pledge:
That Kiritsugu, son of Norikata,
fifth heir to the house of Emiya,
...will be forever forbidden
from harming...
...Kayneth El-Melloi Archibald and
Sola-Ui Nuada-Re Sophia-Ri...
...or intending them to come to harm.
Terms...
In principle, the curse of the Geas
cannot be removed by any means.
Even if you forfeit your life,
as long as the Magic Crest exists,
...it will bind your soul,
even in death.
It's true that if I do what's written,
he cannot kill me.
But under these terms, my fight...
...will end here.
The Grail...
And the Archibald family pride...
He asks me to throw it all away?
Sola-Ui...
Use all your remaining Command Seals
to compel your Servant to commit suicide.
The terms have been met.
You want to win...
You want to win so desperately?
You desire the Grail
so desperately?
You have crushed...
You have crushed my sole
remaining wish...
And you...
You feel no shame at all?!
I will never forgive you.
I will never forgive you for this!
You inhuman monsters who have
ruined the honor of a knight,
...let my blood taint your dreams!
May the Grail be cursed!
May the wish it grants
bring disaster!
And when you fall into the pits of hell,
...remember the rage of Diarmuid!
Now the Geas binds you?
Yes, the pact has been sealed.
I can no longer kill you.
I can't, anyway-
Kill me...
Kill me, please...
Sorry.
Our pact forbids me from harming you.
Kiritsugu Emiya...
I finally understand what
a terrible man you are.
I believed that our paths differed,
but we shared a mutual goal.
I was a fool to think this.
Until now,
I placed my faith in Irisviel's words,
...and thus did not doubt you.
But now, I can no longer believe that
your desire for the Grail...
...has anything to do with salvation.
Answer me, Kiritsugu!
What is the true reason
you desire the Grail?
Even should my sword win the Grail,
...if that means I must
yield it to you, I...
Answer her, Kiritsugu.
After all this, you owe her
an explanation.
Come to think of it,
...this is the first time I have shown you
the way I kill, Iri.
If you only eliminate a Master,
...the Servant may enter into
a pact with another party.
So I had to eliminate the Master
and Servant simultaneously.
Kiritsugu,
speak to Saber, not me.
She needs to hear your words.
No.
Honor, glory...
There's no point in
speaking to a killer...
...who extols the virtues
of such things.
You would even insult chivalry
to my face, monster?!
A knight cannot save the world.
Knights call certain methods of
fighting good and others evil,
...acting as if there were some
nobility to the battlefield.
Such illusions, created by
heroes throughout history,
...have led countless young men...
...to their bloody deaths, all for the sake
of this glory and honor.
They are not illusions!
Even the taking of life,
...as a human act,
must have laws and ideals.
Otherwise, every war would
bring hell to this world!
And there you go.
You heard her, Iri.
Our Heroic Spirit considers a battlefield
to be something better than hell.
What a joke.
It's hell itself.
There's no hope to be had on a battlefield.
There is nothing but
unspeakable despair.
Just a crime we call victory,
paid for by the pain of the defeated.
But humanity has never
recognized this truth.
And the reason is that,
in every era,
...dazzling heroes have blinded the
people with their legends,
...and kept them from seeing
the evil of bloodshed.
True human nature has not advanced
a step beyond the Stone Age.
Then, Kiritsugu...
Is the reason you force Saber
to endure such humiliation...
...because of your hatred
for the Heroic Spirits?
Of course not.
Such personal feelings
don't enter into it.
I will win the Holy Grail
and save the world.
And I will wage that war with the
most appropriate weapons at my disposal.
Justice and righteousness
cannot save the world.
I care nothing for such things.
Kiritsugu...
Do you fully understand?
If you do evil
out of hatred for evil,
...that rage and hatred will
merely give rise to new conflict.
Kiritsugu Emiya,
...I do not know what betrayed you,
...or what has caused you
to lose all hope.
But your rage and sorrow...
...are found only in those who
once sought justice.
Kiritsugu, in youth, your truest self wished
to be a hero, did it not?
A hero to save the world.
You believed in that...
You desired it more than anyone.
Or am I wrong?
I will break this endless cycle.
The Grail will make that possible.
I'll ensure that the blood
I spill in Fuyuki...
...is the last blood that
humanity will ever shed.
If that means I must stain my hands
with every evil in the world, I don't care.
If that will save the world, I do it gladly.
Kiritsugu has left, hasn't he?
Irisviel?
Irisviel!
Episode 16:
The End of Honor
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
This cannot be allowed!
An alliance? Now?
Let me tell you the truth
behind the Holy Grail War.
I accept.
Die, to make his dream a reality.
Such a boring ending.
Next Time: The Eighth
Contract Goodbye, Father.