Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
Murdered?!
Impossible...
Why would even the priest
have been killed?
It's unthinkable.
This cannot be allowed!
I'm sure it must also be regrettable for you
to lose the Father in this way.
Yes.
Father Risei was like
a second father to me.
It has been one unexpected
disaster after another...
It might prove necessary to formulate
a plan of some sort at once.
Why did you not tell Tokiomi?
Tell him what?
I pity your father...
He died, believing his son
to be a man of God.
Or rather...
Perhaps that might have
been his salvation?
Does your father's death arouse
no feeling within you at all?
He was killed, after all.
You could at least try
to look a little sad.
It does. I am frustrated
to no end.
Frustrated, eh?
Are you frustrated because you were
unable to kill him yourself?
Saber...
Irisviel, how are you feeling?
It appears I've made you worry.
I'm sorry...
No, as long as you truly are all right,
that is all that matters.
But...
It's okay. It is Maiya's presence
that you are sensing.
From Tohsaka?
Yes. Tokiomi Tohsaka requests
that we present a united front.
An alliance? Now?
Surely Tohsaka is uneasy...
...at the thought of dealing
with Rider and Berserker.
So he has invited us to meet,
assuming that we would be most amenable.
Meaning that, compared to the two other teams,
he believes us the weakest.
Tohsaka said he wishes to meet tonight
at the Fuyuki church.
From the start,
Tokiomi Tohsaka...
...has made elaborate
preparations for this Grail War.
And it's also likely that he secretly controlled
Assassin's Master, Kirei Kotomine.
If Tohsaka exerts some influence
over Kirei Kotomine,
...then I believe we cannot
ignore this offer.
You're right.
Kirei Kotomine...
Keep this in mind, Saber.
If there is anyone in this Grail War who can
defeat Kiritsugu and claim the Holy Grail,
...it is Kirei Kotomine.
We shall accept.
Father?
Father!
Rin, your father says that he
would like to speak with you.
Rin.
Until you reach adulthood, keep
the Mages Association in your debt.
Beyond that, I leave the rest
up to your judgment.
You'll be fine on your own.
One day, the Holy Grail will appear.
It is the Tohsaka family's
duty to claim it.
Above all else, if you wish to be a mage,
that is the path you cannot avoid.
Rin. Take this.
Well, then I'll be going.
You know what to do now, right?
Yes.
I'll see you soon, Father.
First, allow me to thank you
for coming at my behest.
Let me introduce you.
This is Kirei Kotomine, my student.
While we were once
competitors for the Grail,
...all that is now in the past.
He has lost his Servant, and has
yielded his rights as a Master.
This Grail War is heading
toward its conclusion.
The ones remaining are, as anticipated,
the Masters of the three great houses,
...along with one outsider.
Now, what is your appraisal
of the state of the war?
I have no opinion.
We control the most
powerful Servant, Saber,
...so we have no need to await
an opportune time to strike.
We shall simply continue
to win each battle.
I see.
Unfortunately for the Matous, it is my opinion
that they erred in their strategy.
They seemed to have imposed a draining
Servant upon a frail Master,
...thereby hastening
his self-destruction.
Rider is likely to be the victor
in a match between the two.
The Grail must not be allowed
to fall into outside hands.
We two should be able to
agree on that much.
Any alliance is out of the question.
However, if you wish to discuss the order in
which we approach our enemies,
...we may be able to come
to some agreement.
Elaborate.
We can settle things with the Tohsaka team
after we have defeated the other Masters.
We are prepared to agree
to such a proposal.
So a temporary,
conditional ceasefire?
A fair compromise.
We have two conditions.
First, that you share any information you have
concerning Rider and his Master.
Ag reed.
Our second condition is that Kirei Kotomine
be removed from the Holy Grail War.
Kill Kirei?
I am not suggesting that he be killed.
But I insist that,
until this battle is over,
...he be expelled from Fuyuki,
or better yet, from Japan entirely.
Immediately.
Before tomorrow morning.
Would you explain why?
There is bad blood between
the Einzberns and the Executor.
If the Tohsaka team continues
to protect him,
...we will find ourselves unable to trust
you under any circumstances.
To what is she referring?
Kirei.
Well?
How do you like Kiritsugu's present?
It's much more like a horse
than a car is.
This seems to suit me better.
I shall go ahead, then.
I shall scout out the route ahead.
Let us go, as well.
M-Madam?
What's wrong?
Drive, Maiya.
But you--
Tohsaka will realize there
is something amiss...
This isn't unexpected...
It was inevitable.
Honestly, the fact that I've been
able to function...
...for this long as a human
is a miracle.
Does Kiritsugu know of this?
Don't tell Saber.
She has a crucial battle
ahead of her.
I don't want to distract her
with any undue concern.
But Maiya... There is something
I want to speak to you about.
I am a homunculus created
for the Holy Grail War.
You know that, right?
Yes.
Grandfather Acht gave the vessel
an instinct for self-preservation...
...so that it would avoid all danger
and safeguard the Grail to its completion.
He disguised the vessel,
and called it Irisviel.
That is who I am.
But how... Then you are—
Very soon,
I will revert back to what I was.
Next time, I won't even be able to
talk to you like this.
That's why Kiritsugu
gave me Saber's scabbard.
Avalon...
Are you familiar with
its effects?
It halts aging and provides
an infinite healing ability.
Or so I'm told.
Its effects are what has prevented the
hollow shell that is me from collapsing.
Of course, it stops working as soon as
Saber is no longer nearby.
Why tell me this?
Maiya Hisau...
You would never pity me.
You'd accept me.
That's why.
Madam, I...
I have always thought of you
as distant.
That's not true...
Do you understand?
Yes.
Even if it costs me my life,
...Irisviel, I will see
you through to the end.
So please,
...die for Kiritsugu Emiya.
To make his dream a reality.
Thank you.
I wish you had told me of your
history with the Einzberns.
Unfortunately, I am left with no choice.
You must withdraw
from this war,
...Kirei.
Kiritsugu Emiya... Who are you really?
Will I leave this place,
never even learning that?
Still thinking, even now?
Could you truly be
so slow, Kirei?
The Grail beckons to you still.
And you yourself
still long to fight.
For as long as I can remember,
...I have spent my life in
search of a single thing.
I've devoted every moment to it.
Endured great pain for it.
But all of that has
come to naught.
And yet, I sense that the
answer to my question...
...is closer now than it ever has been.
After all that self-reflection,
why in the world do you hesitate?
I have a deep foreboding.
That when I've learned all the answers,
it will result in my destruction.
Understood. Well done.
You've received an exciting
bit of news, I take it?
We've learned the location of the stronghold
where the Einzberns have been hiding.
As I live and breathe, Kirei!
You honestly amaze me...
You were planning to
continue all along!
I did hesitate.
I was even prepared to give up.
But in the end,
it is as you say, King of Heroes.
I know no other way than to
keep asking the question.
What is that?
A gift from my father.
Jn424.
The Gospel of John.
God is spirit.
And those who worship Him must
worship in spirit and in truth.
However, Kirei...
There remains a rather grave problem.
Should you participate in the
Grail War of your own will,
...Tokiomi Tohsaka
becomes your enemy.
In other words, you have entered the
same room as an enemy Servant...
...with no plan to defend yourself.
A dire situation,
would you not agree?
Not at all. I came prepared
with something to trade for my life.
Gilgamesh...
Let me tell you the truth behind the
Holy Grail War that has been kept from you.
Which is?
The ritual held here in Fuyuki...
...is an attempt to open a
passage to the Root,
...by means of the sacrifice of the
souls of seven Heroic Spirits.
The Great Grail is activated by
killing all seven Servants.
Yes, all seven.
You understand?
That's the reason my master has worked so hard
to avoid using his Command Seals.
Because when all
the battles are over,
...he will require them to force his own
Servant to commit suicide.
Then you claim the loyalty Tokiomi
has shown me has all been a lie?
Put another way, my master
is a mage to his very core.
He may worship a Heroic Spirit,
...but he harbors no illusions
about his idols.
Tokiomi...
At last you have shown
some hint of promise.
That boring little man
will finally be able to entertain me.
Now then, what will you do,
King of Heroes?
Knowing what you know now,
will you remain loyal to my master...
...and punish me for rebelling
against him?
A fair question, indeed.
Regardless of his treachery,
Tokiomi still supplies me with mana.
Were I to abandon my Master, it would hamper
my ability to remain materialized.
Oh... Come to think of it, there is a Master
with a Command Seal but no partner.
One searching for a Servant
unbound by contract.
Now that you mention it,
you're right.
But there is a question...
...of whether that man is a worthy Master
in the eyes of the King of Heroes.
He will suffice.
He is a bit stiff, perhaps,
but he has great potential for growth.
He may yet prove a fine source
of entertainment for me.
I've been waiting, Kirei.
I came to have a word with you
before you depart Fuyuki.
I'm still proud to have had
you as my student.
I hope you will maintain
good relations...
...with the Tohsaka family,
as your late father did.
What do you say?
Your words honor me.
Once this Grail War has ended,
...I'd like for you to help
train Rin, Kirei.
It's simple, but in essence,
it's a will.
I thought it prudent to be
prepared for the worst.
It leaves the Tohsaka
family wealth to Rin,
...and names you as her guardian
until she comes of age.
Leave it to me.
I shall do all I can
to look after your daughter.
Thank you, Kirei.
What is this?
It's for you.
A gift from me.
Open it.
An Azoth dagger.
It symbolizes your mastery of
the Tohsaka family magics,
...and marks the end of
your apprenticeship.
You are far too kind to me, sir.
I cannot begin to
express my gratitude,
...my master.
It is I who must thank you.
Kirei Kotomine.
Now I can prepare
for the final battle.
Look at the time.
I'm sorry to have kept you.
I hope I haven't made you
miss your flight.
No.
You needn't worry,
my master.
I never bought a ticket.
Master...
How like my father you are. Even at the
very end, you never understood me.
Such a boring end.
Look at that. Such an idiotic
expression on his face.
He did have a dematerialized
Servant at hand.
It was only natural for him
to lower his guard.
So, you have learned
to jest already.
I shall praise you for your
aptitude at studies.
Well, Kirei?
Do you feel a little better about not having had
the chance to kill your father?
You really have no qualms,
King of Heroes, Gilgamesh?
Not so long as you
continue to amuse me.
Otherwise, Kirei...
Well, you are the one who ought
to question his own resolve.
My will creates your body,
and your sword creates my destiny.
If you heed the Grail's call
and obey my will and reason...
I hereby swear.
Your offering will be my flesh,
Kirei Kotomine.
My new Master.
Now, Kirei.
Let us begin.
Put an end to this farce
in whatever manner you see fit.
And as a reward,
I shall give you the Grail.
Very well, King of Heroes.
May you have your fill of amusement.
Until such time that I find
the answer I seek,
...I shall gladly play the fool.
Episode 17:
The Eighth Contract
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
Kerry, what kind of person do you want to be
when you grow up?
Stop going to that mansion.
What is this?
Decide the rest for yourself.
It's still too early for you.
It's a power that can change the world,
and one day, it will be yours.