Kerry! Kerry!
Hurry UP!
Hurry up! Hurry UP!
Kerry!
Wow! Amazing!
Nah... That was nothing!
Shirley...
Shirley!
Kerry!
Sorry I'm late.
Say, Kerry...
Do you know where this island's
name comes from?
Nope.
Oh, isn't Arimago the
word for "crab"?
Yup.
Long ago, this was a place where they
made offerings to the sea gods.
But one day, a girl who had nothing
to feed her sick mother...
...took some of the food that
had been set out as an offering.
And so the girl was cursed,
transformed into a crab.
That's where it comes from?
What an awful story.
And they say the shrine where
they worshipped those gods...
...stood up in the mountains,
right where your mansion is.
That's why none of the villagers
want to go up there.
They say it's bad luck.
They keep trying to spook me, too, saying that
if I go there too often, I'll be cursed.
You're kidding.
But everyone's nice to me.
Because they don't think of you
as an outsider anymore.
In the village, they treat you
like my little brother.
Oh...
Little brother, huh?
You've really settled in here.
Yeah?
When you first arrived,
everyone used to bully you,
...saying you had a weird name!
That?
You were the first one to use it!
And it was your big idea
to call me Kerry...
Because your name's
really hard to say!
Keri... Keri...
It's Kiritsugu.
Kerytugu!
Not even close...
Oops.
Really?
Okay.
Dad, is that new?
Yes.
This is my hundredth success.
These flowers never wither.
Yes, because I've altered
the flow of time.
They'll never grow beyond this.
But they'll also never wither.
Amazing...
The problem is whether we can get the same
theory to work on humans.
Sorry for the wait!
Shirley, is that a--
Look!
My first success!
Shirley's been watching and learning
while she assists me.
She does seem to have the natural gift
to be a mage.
Oh, come on, you did
most of the work, Professor.
I only did a little,
right at the end.
But it's amazing!
Hey, Dad...
Hmm? What?
Can I also give that a try?
What Shirley did?
That'd be great!
If you had some help,
you could do it!
- Right, Professor?
- No.
Kiritsugu.
It's still too early for you.
This isn't a game.
There are dangers involved.
I only let Shirley try it because I decided she
has the necessary knowledge and experience.
Father Simon,
why won't you understand?
Shirley...
Everyone has the Professor all wrong!
Listen, Shirley...
Stop going to that mansion.
Let's talk inside.
Dad should spend time
with the villagers, too.
Maybe...
Father Simon really
has it in for him.
He keeps lecturing me
all the time.
He says if I keep working there,
I'll get possessed by a demon someday.
Look at this.
He gave me this and told me
to keep it near me at all times.
He says that it's a
powerful talisman.
Aren't you scared of
my dad, Shirley?
Nope.
Sure, magical research
isn't exactly normal.
But the Professor's research and discoveries
are a big deal! They could make history!
I'm not scared of him,
I think he's amazing.
Are you sure you--
It's sharp and really
easy to use.
See you tomorrow.
Shirley, is something wrong?
Making a flower bloom forever...
It really is an amazing magic.
Shirley, you're doing it, too.
The work with flowers
is all I can do.
He can do a lot more.
Medicines he makes could make humans
effectively immortal.
I want him to use his power for
the good of the whole world...
...so everyone will understand
how incredible he is.
He's given up on that.
But, Kerry,
I think you can do it.
Oh, come on.
You're his best student.
If anyone can do that,
it'd be you.
Not me.
I'm not his student.
At best, I'm his assistant.
Running his errands.
Helping out.
I'm not his student.
Far from it.
So even when Father Simon
says bad things about him,
...there's nothing I can say.
Kerry.
You're his heir, without doubt.
Everything he's working on,
he plans for you to continue.
It's just a little too soon.
Hey, come with me.
Kerry, what kind of person do you want
to be when you grow up?
If you take up your dad's work,
what will you use it for?
It's a power that can
change the world.
And one day,
it will be yours.
Yeah, change the world.
You can do it.
I guarantee it.
Well, I...
That's a secret.
Then, when you grow up,
let me see what you can do.
I'll stay with you until then.
Okay?
Wh-Whatever...
Stop it!
Gotcha!
Oh, good morning, Dad.
Kiritsugu, you didn't enter my workshop
last night, did you?
Nope.
You didn't?
Kiritsugu, don't go to
the village today.
Don't leave the house.
What's gotten into him?
Shirley's late...
Hey.
Have you guys seen Shirley?
Shirley?
What happened to you?
Kerry...
Shirley!
I...
I only wanted to prove it worked!
His research...
But...
I guess...
It didn't work...
Kill me.
Use that. Please...
You have to kill me.
Do it now,
before it's too late...
Please!
I can't stop it...
I can't hold it back anymore!
Hurry!
Are you sure it was Shirley?
Kerry, stay here for now.
I'll go inform the village.
Wh-What is this?
Father Simon?
Looks like I'm too late.
W-Wait!
Who are you?
Shouldn't you worry
about yourself first?
Well, if you just sit there,
you'll join them soon enough.
What happened? What's going on?
Who did this?
Why would they burn the village?
Surely you've heard of them...
Vampires.
We call them Dead Apostles.
Dead Apostles?
They drink blood to
increase their numbers.
Nearly everyone on this
island is one now.
So we're cleaning up the mess.
Two groups are down there now,
trying to eliminate them.
One is the Church's Executors.
People who believe beyond the shadow of a doubt
that it's all right to slaughter anyone...
...who defies the will of God.
Of course, they'll show no mercy
to any Dead Apostles they find.
They'll kill anyone they even suspect
of having had their blood sucked.
As for the other, the Mages Association...
Well, they're harder to explain.
But they'd like to keep the
secret of who made...
...such a bizarre thing as the
Dead Apostles all to themselves.
Naturally, since their motto
is "All to Ourselves,"
...they'll kill anyone they suspect
of knowing the secret.
They'll do whatever they can
to cover up what happened.
They're the ones who
torched the village.
Whose side are you on?
I'm something like a salesman
to the Mages Association.
Now, kid...
Answer my question.
I'm looking for a mage who's
been marked for sealing.
A mage...
I guess that word doesn't
mean anything to you.
The first person to become
a Dead Apostle here...
There's a... Think of it as a medium that
makes people turn into Dead Apostles.
A trigger that causes them
to transform.
The bad mage who made it
should be hiding,
...somewhere on this island.
Can you think of
any likely spots?
Oh, Kiritsugu... You're safe.
Thank goodness.
I told you not to go
to the village.
Dad...
Why were you researching Dead Apostles?
Kiritsugu, how did you--
Shirley used the magic
on herself.
Oh...
Well, it's very sad.
But you can't change the past.
This just means that Shirley gave me
my answer sooner than I had expected.
Dad, will you use me like
you used Shirley one day?
Don't be stupid.
A Dead Apostle that can't control
its bloodlust is a failure.
But the Emiya family research
requires unlimited time.
The Root will never be attained
with a mortal body.
It was a time-consuming experiment,
...but it seems to have failed.
I'll have to reconsider
my theory in its entirety.
Kiritsugu, let's save this
matter for another time.
For now, escaping comes first.
It's not too late to escape?
I suspected something like this
might happen,
...so I hid a motorboat
on the south coast.
I'm sorry, Kiritsugu,
...but I don't have time to let
you gather your things.
Come on.
I'll do it.
There's a bounded field
around the forest.
A powerful one.
It'll take time to break through.
But I can get in.
I have to do this.
Kerry/
...what kind of person do you want
to be when you grow up?
I was able to break through that
bounded field fairly easily.
Are you mad?
It was only dumb luck
that you showed up in time.
If this man had escaped, he'd have continued
his Dead Apostles research somewhere else.
That's a crappy reason for
a kid to kill his father.
You're a good person, aren't you?
I'll get you off the island.
You can decide the
rest for yourself.
Do you want to take anything?
Nothing.
Shizuka ni matataku Hoshi tachi no chiriyuku sora
In the sky where stars twinkle quietly,
Todokanu inori ga Ten to chi wo mitashiteta
unheeded prayers fill the heavens and the Earth.
Episode 18: Distant Memories
Todokanu inori ga Ten to chi wo mitashiteta
unheeded prayers fill the heavens and the Earth.
Hosoi eda ni hikaru no wa
What you see shining on that slender branch
Saki wasureta mirai
is a future that forgot to bloom.
Mada nagori oshisouni tsubomi wo otoshita
It sheds its flower buds, as if unwilling to let go.
Hora mou toki wa michite
Look, the time has come.
Minoru kin no kajitsu Sono te de tsumitoru dake de
All you need to do is pluck that ripe, golden fruit
Sekai wa owaru kara
to end the world.
Kegarenu mono toshite furu yuki no shirosa wa
The pure white of the snow, falling
from the sky as something unsullied,
Nukumori wo shireba kiete shimau no
will vanish the instant it knows warmth.
Kirei na yume dake ga anata wo kirisaita
Only beautiful dreams sliced you.
Tsumetai hitomi no yasashisa to shinjitsu
The kindness and truth of cold eyes.
Hageshiku matataku hoshi tachi wa ten ni somuite
Harshly twinkling stars defy the heavens
Adanasu inori ga Kono sora wo otosu
bring down the sky.
After leaving the island, I spent
the next several years...
...with Natalia Kaminski, the woman
who took me away from there.
That meant choosing the
same path as Natalia.
The path of a hunter.