It's you, Kiritsugu.
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
I'm not dreaming, am I?
You really... came...
...to see me again.
Yes, that's right.
Thank you.
The final thing I must do
is return this to you.
From now on, you will be
the one who needs Avalon.
When you begin your final battle,
I'm sure it will aid you.
You know...
I really am happy.
To love... To be loved.
To have a husband and daughter
for nine whole years.
You gave me everything...
All the happiness in the world...
...that was never meant for me.
I'm sorry.
I wanted to show you more
of the outside world.
No... It's enough.
If there is still any happiness
left to experience,
...give it all to Ilya.
To your daughter...
Our beloved Ilya.
Bring Ilya to this country one day.
Show her everything
I didn't have the chance to see.
The cherry trees.
The summer clouds...
I will.
Okay, I'll be back.
Yes. Be careful...
...my love.
Saber is heading to Rider's hideout, right?
Yes. She's on her way.
I'm going to kill Tokiomi Tohsaka.
If Rider and Saber fight, there's a
good chance Archer will also appear.
I'll hit him there.
You continue to watch Iri.
Understood.
Um... Kiritsugu.
You... finally look like you used to.
I don't feel a Servant's presence.
There's no barrier?
What's going on?
Is that good?
Nope. It's awful.
I guess Japanese cuisine
isn't that good after all.
Boy, you walked right by...
...Okonomiyaki Shouki in New Town.
Their modanyaki was a thing of beauty.
Too bad you didn't bring any of that...
If you want to eat there again, recover
enough so you can materialize.
You recognize this spot, right?
This is where I summoned you.
This is the Fuyuki location with the
leylines that suit you best, right?
You should be able to recover
much more quickly here.
I'm staying here all day.
Just sleeping, not doing a thing.
So take as much mana as you want,
as long as you don't kill me.
Maybe you'll be a little
better than now, I guess.
If you'd already figured it out,
you should have said something earlier.
Finding out afterwards that someone's been
on to you the whole time is, well...
It's a bit embarrassing.
You idiot!
You should have just told me!
If you aren't at full strength
when I need you, I'll be the one in danger!
Why didn't you say anything?
I thought maybe I could tough it out
a little longer.
But the fatigue from the river battle
has hit me harder than I expected.
When it's all said and done, your Noble
Phantasm consumes a ton of power.
At first, I didn't notice.
Because it wasn't affecting me, I thought
it was incredibly efficient or something.
Rider, honestly, instead of using mana
that was supposed to come from me,
...you managed to use
your own stored power, didn't you?
And you did it twice...
What's the big idea, doing that?
Well, you know...
When you get right down to it,
as a Servant, I'm a natural soul eater.
If I involve you when I expend
mana at my maximum rate,
...it could put your life at risk.
I'm fine with that...
This is a battle I began.
If I don't shed blood
or make sacrifices,
...and then win at the end of it all,
there's no point.
I just...
I want to prove myself.
That I...
That even someone like me can take what
he wants with his own two hands!
But, kid, that only applies if
the Grail truly exists.
You know, I once did
something similar.
Fought for something that
might not have even existed.
Oceanus.
That's right.
I told them I'd show them Oceanus,
...and they were so swept up by my story
that they followed me without a single doubt.
Many died...
All dreaming of Oceanus
until the very end.
When I gained this era's knowledge,
that hit me really hard.
I'd had no idea the world
was an enclosed circle.
What a bad joke.
But even so, when I saw the map,
I had no choice but to accept it.
I've had my fill of letting people
die for fairy tales.
If the Grail's existence were certain,
...I'd have no objection to
you risking your life.
But unfortunately, it isn't.
Even so...
Even so, I...
I'm your Master!
Boy...
Learned to talk back, have you?
It's true, your Magic Circuits are
more powerful than usual.
If I rest all day,
...I should be ready to go another round
come nightfall!
And?
Another round? What do you
plan to do next?
Hmm... Good question.
Let us begin with Saber.
At this rate, how much will
you recover by tonight?
If I only use the Gordius Wheel for flight,
there shouldn't be a problem.
However...
...I fear I'll be able to employ
my Ionian Hetairoi only one more time.
I see...
We should probably save it
for the fight with Archer.
Then, Rider...
Why do you want to fight Saber?
I must defeat Saber.
No one else.
As a Heroic Spirit,
it is my responsibility.
What's that supposed to mean?
If I don't show that silly girl
the right path, she'll never learn.
That would be too sad
to bear thinking about.
Whatever, have it your way...
Listen, boy, quit keeping yourself
awake and just go to sleep.
Rest is the battle that
you face right now.
I am the shunned.
The scorned.
The despised.
Who are you?
My name is unworthy of praise.
My body unworthy of envy.
I am the shadow cast by
the Heroic Spirit's light.
The darkness born in the
shadow of shining legend.
Thus, do I hate.
Thus, do I resent.
I feed on the lamentation of those
who sink into the darkness...
...and curse those who
shine so brightly.
Her shadow is my shame.
Her honor remains forever unsullied,
...thus am I forever looked down upon.
You are the sacrifice!
Healing won't help me.
I'm going to die soon.
Damn it...
Really, what a sorry sight you are, Kariya...
Don't get the wrong idea.
I'm not blaming you.
Honestly, I never
would have imagined...
...that you'd last this long.
And so, I shall give you the ace
I've kept up my sleeve,
...secreted away for this stage of the game.
Now...
It works quickly, doesn't it?
The worm I just gave you...
...was the first to feed
on Sakura's purity.
How does it feel, Kariya?
For an entire year, it's been
devouring the girl's life energy.
It's a magnificent
mana source.
Now go and fight, Kariya.
Make good use of the life
you've stolen from Sakura.
Use every ounce of
your flesh and bone to acquire the Grail...
If someone such as you
is even capable of it, that is.
Hey, Maiya...
Why do you fight for Kiritsugu?
Because I have nothing else.
I can't even remember
my family or my own name.
Maiya Hisau was the name...
...on the first fake passport
that Kiritsugu made for me.
All I remember is that it was
a terribly poor country.
The wars never ended...
...even though there was no money
to maintain the armies.
But day after day, they continued
to kill one another.
And then, someone had an idea.
Rather than conscript
and train soldiers,
...it was cheaper and faster to
abduct children and arm them.
Maiya, you...
Aim at the enemy and pull the trigger.
That was my sole function.
I threw everything else away.
As a human being, I'm dead inside,
...but the shell continues to move.
Still working like it did before.
That is my life.
But Kiritsugu took me in anyway.
So however he wants
to use me is fine by me.
That is the reason I'm here.
In truth, Madam, it was your passion
that surprised me.
You've been secluded in the castle
where you were born,
...knowing so little of
the outside world.
So I can't imagine...
...why you would fight this hard
for Kiritsugu's dream.
To change a world you've
never really seen.
I...
You're right.
I cannot truly understand
Kiritsugu's ideals.
It's as you say.
I know nothing of the world that
Kiritsugu longs to change.
All my ideals are merely words that
I learned from Kiritsugu.
But don't let him know that.
I've always told him he was
doing the right thing.
I've told him those ideals
were worth giving my life for.
And I've pretended that
I understood him.
Then, Madam, have you
no wish of your own?
A wish?
No, I do have one.
I wish for Kiritsugu and Saber
to win the Holy Grail.
Do you mean the desire of the Einzberns,
attainment of the Third Magic?
No.
What I desire is an end to conflict.
If Kiritsugu's wish comes true,
and fighting everywhere ends,
...the fight for the Grail here in Fuyuki
should be no exception.
I want this fourth battle to
be the final Holy Grail War.
For your daughter?
If Kiritsugu and I fail,
they will use Ilya next.
That is the destiny that an
Einzbern homunculus must bear.
So my wish is to be the last.
If that wish comes true,
...she'll be able to live out her
life as a human being.
Maiya...
What will you do after Kiritsugu
reaches his goal?
I don't expect to survive.
Even if I do, there'd be no
reason for me to exist.
I'm sure it will be that kind of world...
...once Kiritsugu's changed it.
No, that isn't true.
You think so?
You must look for your
real name and family!
Those aren't things
you should forget.
You must learn what they are...
...and etch yourself indelibly
into the memories of others.
So live, Maiya. For me, too.
I'll do my best.
But that isn't until after
the battle ends.
Right now, we must be cautious.
We must stay on guard,
both he and I.
The one who died was... Tokiomi Tohsaka?
Really, you are--
Maiya!
Iri!
By my Command Seal,
I order my puppet...
Saber, return to
the storehouse! Immediately!
Kiritsugu...
This is...
Maiya!
Saber?
Don't speak.
Hurry.
Follow him outside...
Rider took Madam...
But if I leave, you--
I... will be fine.
And Kiritsugu will come soon...
So, hurry.
Maiya,
please hold on until Kiritsugu returns.
I shall bring Irisviel back.
I don't believe it, it really was Rider!
It was Rider...
Yes, I understand.
You mustn't cry.
Save those tears for your wife...
You can't cry here...
You're weak.
So you can't cry yet.
You can't break...
I...
This morning, you finally
looked like your old self.
You can't lose your resolve over this...
Don't worry, Maiya.
Leave the rest to Saber.
Maiya, your task...
...is finished.
Maiya.
Maiya...
Episode 20:
Return of the Assassin
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
Where is Irisviel?
Don't forget!
Tonight, at midnight.
Nothing can stop me!
Don't underestimate me,
King of Conquerors!
Because of him...
If it weren't for that man...
Oh, scary, scary.
Next Time: Knight on Two Wheels
Are you satisfied, Kariya?