Irisviel...
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
Have I lost them?
If I can't see them,
I'll sense them.
A chariot?
I have you, Rider!
Rider, look.
Isn't that her following us?
Well, well, if it isn't Saber.
Saves us the trouble
of searching for her.
Actually... Hey, boy,
are motorcycles normally so fast?
That's a motorcycle?
No, that's impossible.
But with Saber's riding skill...
...that might make it possible.
This will be fun.
Then I'll have to make
this interesting.
We're going down?
Change of plans.
I shall use a race to
settle things with the girl.
Fine, but...
Be careful, okay?
Don't worry.
Nothing in Heaven or on
Earth can stop me!
This is bad...
I'm reaching the machine's limits.
At this rate...
And I'm so close.
Invisible Air!
No way...
She's closing the gap!
She'll catch up to us!
For a mechanical contraption
to go so fast...
Splendid.
But this is a chariot!
It may be a fair race,
but it needn't be polite.
This is what you get
if you want to chase me, Saber!
Excellent!
You really are the proud
King of Knights...
Truly the flower of
the battlefield!
Don't underestimate me,
King of Conquerors!
Rider!
Prepare yourself!
Irisviel isn't here?
No...
That was definitely Rider.
Then, where is Irisviel?
Did you think to trick me
by imitating a Servant?
Rider's master lacks the intel-gathering
skills to have found that place.
Tohsaka could not have
possibly attacked.
By process of elimination,
...only the Matou could
have kidnapped Irisviel.
Answer me.
Where is Irisviel?
I-I don't know!
I don't know anything!
Then where is Kariya Matou?
Kariya?
I don't know where that fool is!
I don't know!
I really don't know anything!
He left this morning with some guy...
...who said he was a judge
from the Church!
Overseer?
Kirei Kotomine...
I did not expect the real
Rider to appear.
A fortuitous development.
Luck certainly favors you on
the battlefield, doesn't it,
...Kariya Matou?
Father,
was this little deception...
...really worth the use of
two Command Seals?
Do not worry, Kariya.
Now, hold out your hand.
As long as you work with me,
...you may use your Command
Seals without hesitation.
Even so...
That transformation ability...
The Berserker class has such
excellent Noble Phantasms.
There are many stories of
them becoming another...
...in pursuit of some heroic deed.
So even with the Command Seal's
control, that is the best result.
Your Servant's fixation on
Saber is impressive.
Enough.
Begone, Berserker.
This woman...
Is she really the Grail's vessel?
More accurately, its contents.
Don't worry, Kariya.
I shall give you the Holy Grail.
But before that,
...there is the other promise
you made to me, Father.
Oh, that?
Everything is arranged.
Come to the Fuyuki church
at midnight tonight.
You will find Tokiomi Tohsaka there.
Don't forget, Kariya.
Tonight at midnight.
And your wish will be fulfilled.
Now, then...
We're alone.
I don't know who you are,
but show yourself.
So, you sensed me.
You are indeed a veteran Executor.
Zouken Matou?
Correct.
Hey, Rider...
We're really going to
attack from here?
From this range?
Straight ahead?
The sword of light we
saw at the river...
...has a delay before activation.
We'll strike then.
Why would you do
something so crazy?
Precisely because it is crazy.
If she loses after all this,
her defeat will be complete.
She may decide to be
my retainer, after all.
You want to win her so badly?
On the battlefield,
she is like a star.
But only as a part of my army
will she truly be able to shine.
Never was he interested in his
opponent's power or wealth.
Without destroying or
degrading them,
...he sought to rule their very souls.
Thus was he the
King of Conquerors.
Very well, Rider...
Win by whatever
means you wish.
Kid, it seems you finally begin
to understand conquest.
Glory lies beyond the horizon!
Let us go...
Via Expugnatio!
Wind!
Excalibur!
What do you want,
Zouken Matou?
I was quite interested to
see what clever trick...
...you'd use to destroy Kariya.
You're willing to let the Matous'
chance at victory dwindle?
In truth, watching him suffer...
I shall never tire of.
Victory for the Matou,
or a miserable end for him?
I'm honestly not sure
which I'd prefer.
You enjoy watching your son suffer so?
I'd thought that you would
have understood.
What?
You give off the same smell as I do.
That of a maggot, attracted by
the rotting meat of Kariya.
Oh, scary, scary.
Inexperienced or not,
you are still a dog of the Church.
I tease you at my own peril, eh?
We shall see each other again,
young one.
By our next meeting,
...see that you allow your true
nature to have ripened...
...such that it may rival my own.
Rider...
Sorry, boy.
I screwed up.
Rider!
Use Ionian Hetairoi!
The chariot is all I'm willing
to expend against Saber.
But still...
She's gone.
A motorcycle, huh?
A magnificent vehicle.
Hey!
Those are your first
words after defeat?
Hey, Rider...
How do we get back to town?
Well...
We'll have to walk.
Yeah, I guess so...
How many more days do I have?
How many more times can I fight?
But I'm still alive now.
I'm still...
Tokiomi Tohsaka!
Did you think you'd
killed me, Tokiomi?
You were wrong.
Until I make you pay,
I'll keep coming back!
Tohsaka...
What?
Kariya?
Aoi?
No! It wasn't me!
This was...
Are you satisfied, Kariya?
Now the Matou
are sure to win the Holy Grail.
I... I...
Why?
Taking Sakura from me
wasn't enough?
Of all the things you
could have done,
...you killed him in front of me?
Why?
He...
It's because of him!
If it weren't for him,
no one would have had to suffer!
You... Sakura...
You could have been happy!
Shut up!
What could you
possibly know of it?
You...
You've never even...
You've never loved anyone
in your entire life!
I had someone I loved.
Warm and kind...
I wanted her to be happier
than anyone else.
For you, I would
throw away my life.
That's why I've endured
this pain until now.
Endured...
Endured, endured, endured, endured,
endured, endured, endured...
Endured it all!
You can't deny all that.
If you do, I'll never forgive you!
A lie, a lie, a lie!
I do have someone...
There is someone I love!
Who did I do this for?
Whose fault is it?!
If I'm going to die,
I may as well...
That was a terrible play.
But not so bad for
a first attempt.
Well, Kirei?
What do you think?
The wine's taste...
It's different than
I remembered.
Then I see that you begin to
understand what it means...
...to expand your horizons.
If it will taste this wonderful,
...then I would dearly love...
...to sample it again.
Episode 21:
Knight on Two Wheels
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
By my Command Seal,
I order you...
Open your eyes, and behold!
Tonight, I shan't hold back.
He must be eliminated at once.
How do he and I differ?
If he doesn't doubt, then what?!
Who am I?