Finally...
Hey, Waver.
Where are you looking?
Over here, over here.
G-Grandpa!
What are you doing?
Enough with the questions,
just come up here.
Let's talk for a while.
Talk?
Why do we have to
talk on the roof?
Grandpa, can't it wait?
Oh, don't be like that.
They really like you, kid.
Listen, they're just
under my spell--
Just go up there.
The old man seems to have
something important to tell you.
Relax, I'll patrol the area
and keep watch.
Don't worry about me.
Worrying isn't the problem...
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
This is the best place...
...to catch the first rays
of the morning sun.
Take a seat.
Here, I even have some coffee.
It'll warm you up.
Grandpa, how long have you
been up here?
When I woke up this morning and checked
in on you, you weren't back yet.
So I thought I'd take the opportunity
to watch the sun come up...
...while I waited for my
grandson to come home.
When you were little,
...we used to come up here
and stargaze all the time.
Do you remember?
Yeah, I guess.
When Martha and I decided
to live in Japan,
...we made sure to build our house
here in the hills of Miyama,
...with a skylight that we could
access the roof through.
We dreamed of sitting
up here on the roof,
...alongside our grandkids,
to watch the stars.
We never thought our wish
would come true, though.
Our real grandchildren
never once came up here.
Whenever I watched the stars,
I was always alone.
Hey, Waver...
You aren't our grandson, are you?
It's so strange, the way Martha and I were
so completely convinced you were.
To be honest, you were a little
too nice to be our grandson...
You aren't mad?
Well, I guess I might have
every right to be.
But lately, Martha's been so happy
and smiling all the time.
I couldn't have imagined
her like that before.
Really, I'm grateful to you two.
Besides, it doesn't seem to me...
...that you moved in with us
because you meant us any harm.
Actually, what do you
think about it?
If you can, I'd like for you
to stay a while longer.
I'm sorry...
But I can't promise that.
I can't even guarantee I'll
make it back here safely.
So you two are risking your lives?
Yes.
Well, I don't know how important
what you're doing is to you...
But when you've had a long life
and look back on it all,
...you realize that
there is nothing...
...that's really worth
risking that life for.
Ryudo Temple
I guess it's been about forty hours
since I last slept...
To win the battle and
summon the Grail,
...one must perform the ritual
at one of the four Fuyuki leylines.
At two of them, the church
and the Tohsaka estate,
...Kirei Kotomine was
nowhere to be found.
Which leaves the other two.
Here at Mt. Enzou,
and the Fuyuki Citizen's Building.
Given the leylines' relative power,
this one is more likely.
Even if he's chosen
the Citizen's Building,
...I can launch a frontal assault there.
If Maiya were still alive,
I would have sent her to secure it.
Once again, I'm alone...
Come to think of it, I never figured her
into my plans from the very beginning.
Since last night, I've been searching
the entire city for Irisviel.
But I have found no sign of her.
I am deeply sorry.
Well, then...
If you have need of me, use the Command
Seal and summon me as before.
Woman.
Can you hear me, woman?
Kirei... Kotomine.
This is where Caster's
Master once hid.
Though it appears that Kiritsugu Emiya
was never able to locate it.
Soon, the Holy Grail War will end.
It's quite likely that I shall be the one
to grant the Einzbern clan's wish.
Are you so unhappy
that it would be me?
There is but one man to whom
I would entrust the Grail.
And it is not you,
Executor.
Kiritsugu Emiya has already
seen right through you.
He recognizes you as his
greatest enemy.
Prepare yourself.
Your words are as the Gospel
to my ears.
Kiritsugu Emiya is
exactly as I imagined him, after all.
How laughable.
You couldn't be any further
from him if you tried!
What?
Even though Kiritsugu can see through you,
the reverse is impossible...
You have none of the things
that he carries in his heart.
Why do you speak of me?
I admit it.
I am an empty man.
However...
How do he and I differ?
Devoting himself to war,
without gain, for all these years...
Senseless slaughter...
Utter recklessness.
Wasted effort!
If he does not doubt as I do,
then what is he?!
Answer me...
What does Kiritsugu Emiya
desire from the Holy Grail?
What prayer would he entrust
to the wish-granting device?
Very well... I'll tell you.
Kiritsugu Emiya's wish...
...is for humanity's salvation.
An end to war and bloodshed.
Forever.
Peace on Earth.
What was that?
You can never understand.
That is the difference
between you.
He has something to believe in.
Conflict is humanity's
intrinsic nature.
To eliminate it would mean...
...humanity's own elimination.
It's futile as an ideal.
It's nonsense that a child
would spout!
And that is why
his only hope is for a miracle.
Many times, he has been forced...
...to sacrifice those he
loves for his beliefs.
Yes...
He is too kind to chase ideals.
He must love,
...even knowing it will mean
losing that love...
I understand...
I understand very well.
So that is Kiritsugu Emiya.
At last, I see it...
My reason for fighting.
Kiritsugu Emiya...
I shall destroy
your ideals right before you.
And the Holy Grail, as well.
Oh, you're up, boy?
I told you to wake me up
at nightfall.
What are you doing?
Sorry, sorry.
But I thought it might be good to
take our time with preparations.
Tonight, there is no
reason to rush.
Why?
I can't say why, exactly...
But it feels like things
will conclude tonight.
The night air seems too still.
Does that mean that fewer
participants remain?
From now on,
only the truly strong remain.
Wh-What was that?
A strange mana surge...
I've felt something similar before.
That pattern...
What is it?
Some kind of code?
Four and seven, in different colors.
"Success" and "victory."
If they're sending up that signal,
does that mean the Grail War is over?
No...
It's in a different direction
than the church.
Then the church didn't
send the message?
In essence, someone is getting ahead
of themselves and claiming victory.
That says, "If you object,
come and get me."
It is a challenge.
It looks like the big showdown
will happen tonight!
I see.
This is it, then...
Quite right!
And now that our
battlefield is known,
...I must ride forth in such a way...
...as to bring honor to
the Rider class!
Come forth...
...my steed!
Now, kid, it may not be as smooth
a ride as my chariot...
What are you waiting for?
Come on.
From this point, only the
truly strong can continue, right?
My Servant...
By his Command Seal,
Waver Velvet orders you!
Rider, fight until you gain victory.
And by my Command Seal,
I further order you!
Rider, win the Holy Grail.
And by my Command Seal,
I further order you!
Rider, take the world for your own.
I will not tolerate failure.
Now, I'm no longer
your Master.
Go... Go wherever.
I don't even want to see you...
Sure, I'll be on my way.
After all those annoying orders,
...surely you are prepared to
see this through to the end.
You total idiot!
Listen...
I have no Command Seals!
I quit being your Master!
Why would you still take me?
I...
Master or not,
you are still my friend.
I-I'm...
You're really okay with me?
I can stay by your side?
After all the battles you and I have
seen together, what are you saying?
Idiot.
Up until now, have you not
faced the same enemies as I?
That means you are my friend!
So hold your head high
and consider yourself...
...my equal.
All right, then...
I shall begin by obeying
your first order.
Boy, open your eyes,
and watch to the end!
Yeah, do it!
Right before my eyes!
He chose the place least
suited to the ritual...
...in order to gain the
initiative in battle.
In other words,
his plan is not to steal the Grail.
But rather to use it as bait,
...to kill me and the other Masters.
That simplifies things.
If he's this incompetent an opponent,
...I'll just eliminate him quickly.
Kirei Kotomine...
You look particularly
ferocious tonight, Kirei.
Now, what will you do?
Do you wish for me
to wait here?
If you unleash your power at close range,
...you may endanger the ceremony itself.
If you want to fight at full strength,
go out and meet them.
Very well.
But what if this place falls
under attack while I'm away?
Would you allow me to use the
Command Seal to save myself?
I shall allow it.
But I do not guarantee
the Grail's safety.
Tonight, I shan't hold back.
That would be the worst outcome,
but if that should happen, it would be fate.
Kirei...
You seem to have found
your reason to fight.
But have you still no prayer
to offer the Grail?
I can think of nothing I want.
Only that I hope that nothing will
interfere with this fight.
Honestly...
As I suspected, the only recourse is to let
the Grail reveal what hides within your heart.
Oh. If it seems as if Saber will arrive
before I can return,
...have Berserker entertain
her for a while.
Understood.
Speaking of Saber,
...what happened to the doll that
was so important to her?
The Holy Grail's vessel is
within her, is it not?
I killed her.
I had no reason to let her live.
Are you crying,
...Mother?
Hey, Mother...
I had a scary dream.
I dreamed I turned into a cup...
And inside me,
...these seven big lumps appeared...
It's okay...
It's okay!
I won't let that happen.
That will never happen
to you, Ilya.
I know that you will be released
from the shackles of fate.
What is this place...
Inside the Holy Grail?
That's not--
Then...
If I'm here...
Who am I?
That's right...
This is inside the Holy Grail.
The omnipotent wish-granting device that
will dispel all the world's sadness,
...and remove all suffering.
I will have the power to
make that happen.
The end...
...is nearly at hand.
Episode 22:
All the Evil in the World
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
Our enemy is the mighty
King of Heroes,
...a worthy opponent!
Let us demonstrate our
path of conquest!
King of Conquerors, I shall show you
the end of your eternal dream.
I, myself, shall show
you the harsh reality.