Rider, look.
Are you scared, boy?
Yeah. I'm scared.
Or maybe this is what you mean
when you say your heart is dancing.
It seems you're starting
to understand.
The enemy is inside?
Berserker?
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
They're going to drink here?
Where is your little chariot
that you are proud of?
Well...
I'm embarrassed to say
that I lost it to Saber.
Did you forget my decision?
I believe I told you that
I would defeat you...
...when you were at full strength.
True, the weapons at my disposal
are somewhat depleted.
But Iskandar tonight is less than perfect,
and thus, is greater than perfection.
So I see.
Indeed, the aura that
is emanating from you...
it is unusually potent.
It appears that you have come before me
believing that you have a chance of victory.
King of Babylonia, a final word.
Our banquet's last question.
I shall allow it. Speak.
Purely hypothetically, were my Ionian Hetairoi
armed with your Gate of Babylon,
...it would create the most
powerful army imaginable.
What of it?
Would you not ally
yourself with me?
Together, the two of us could
conquer the very stars.
You never cease to amuse me.
It has been ages since I laughed so hard at
gibberish spouted by one who is not a fool.
But unfortunately,
...I have had but one comrade,
and he is all I shall ever have.
And there is no need
for two kings.
The lonely path of kingship, eh?
I shall challenge your unwavering
spirit with respect.
Very well.
Show me what you can do,
King of Conquerors.
You are a usurper
worthy of my judgment.
Are you guys actually friends?
I could hardly be unfriendly to him.
He may well be the last
person I ever see.
Don't be stupid...
You can't be killed!
I won't allow it!
Have you forgotten my Command Seal?
You're right...
You're exactly right!
To me, my comrades!
Tonight, we become the
greatest legend in history!
Our enemy is the mighty
King of Heroes, a worthy opponent!
My warriors, let us show
the very first Heroic Spirit...
...our path of conquest!
Come to me, lord of
conquering armies.
Now you will behold the
sight of a true king.
Why are you suffering so much?
Because Berserker...
must fight...
Why?
Because that priest said so.
That priest?
Yeah... He promised me.
That he'd give me the Grail.
If I have the Grail,
I can save you.
You're going to save me?
Yeah, I promised you, remember?
That we'd all play together...
like we used to.
Then... I'll be able to see Mom again, right?
Mom...
NOW!
I barely scratched him?
Can he see it?
He knows the length of my blade...
Could he be some knight
I once knew?
From your skill, I assume you to be a knight
of some renown, and so I ask you this:
If you know me to be
Arturia Pendragon, King of Britain,
...name yourself,
as a knight's pride demands!
Challenging me with your identity concealed
is tantamount to attacking using deceit!
You are...
N-No...
Arondight?
You can't be...
Arthur...
Sir Lancelot...
Why, my friend?
You were esteemed as the greatest of
the Knights of the Round Table! Why, then?
How could you fall so low
as to become Berserker--
Lancelot?
Lancelot...
You saved them,
but you never led them.
Because I never led them...
Enraptured by a false idol of
the king who serves others...
My ideals...
My kingship...
Only a little girl.
Did they drive you to this?!
Arthur!
Lancelot...
To unite dreams beneath
a banner of conquest.
I praise your efforts at least.
But, warriors...
Did you not learn?
That all dreams must disappear
when the dreamer wakes.
Every last one of them.
Therefore, it was inevitable that
I would stand in your way,
...King of Conquerors.
Now, know the end
of your eternal dream.
I, myself, shall show
you harsh reality.
Here it comes!
Now awaken, Ea!
A stage worthy of you
has been set!
Look up and behold...
Enuma Elish!
Hang on, boy!
That...
That sword is the anti-planet
Noble Phantasm that can destroy all creation?
Rider...
Come to think of it,
there is something I must ask you.
Waver Velvet,
...would you like to serve
as my retainer?
You...
You are my king...
I will serve you.
I will devote myself to you.
Please lead me...
Let me dream your dream!
Very well.
As king, my duty is to inspire
others to dream.
And as my retainer, it is your task
to see my dream to the end,
...and to speak of it to
future generations.
Live, Waver.
See all of this to the end.
Live long, and tell everyone.
Of how your king comported himself!
Of the charge of Iskandar!
Now... Let us go, Bucephalus!
Rider!
Glory lies beyond the horizon...
Challenge it because you know
it to be unattainable.
Speak of conquest,
and make it real.
For my men,
who watch behind me!
I swear... It's one strange toy
after another with you, isn't it?
Have you awakened from your dream,
King of Conquerors?
I suppose I have...
My heart danced a good deal...
...during this campaign...
Feel free to challenge me again as many
times as you like, King of Conquerors.
This entire world is my garden
until the end of time.
Thus, I guarantee you this.
It will never bore you.
I am glad to hear it...
Now I see...
It was the beating of my heart...
...that was the sound of
Okeanos' waves...
Child... Are you Rider's Master?
No... I am his retainer...
I see.
But then, child,
if you are truly loyal to him,
...your duty is to avenge
your fallen king.
If I challenge you, I will die.
Of course.
I can't do that.
I was ordered to survive.
Your loyalty is splendid!
Never tarnish it.
He restores my soul. He leads me in paths
of righteousness for His name's sake.
Even though I walk through the
valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil,
...for You are with me;
...Your rod and Your staff--
...they comfort me.
You prepare a table before me in
the presence of my enemies;
...You anoint my head with oil.
My cup overflows.
Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life.
My cup overflows.
Surely goodness and mercy shall
follow me all the days of my life.
Episode 23:
The Sea at the End of the World
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
You would steal the
Holy Grail from me?!
What are you doing, Saber?!
What a difficult person you are...
Impossible!
It longs for its own life!
For its own birth!
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
Next Time: The Last Command
Seal I knew you'd come.