Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Mou daremo nakanai sekai no tame ni
For the sake of a world in which no one will ever cry again,
Akaku kegasareta sora no
My screams and prayers
Doko nimo todokazu kieru sakebi to inori
don't reach anywhere in the red-stained sky.
Nagusame wa sutete ikeru
I can give up consolation and leave this place.
Kirei na tsuki no hikari ga
The pure light of the moon
Hajimari he to shizumi yuku
sinks down towards the beginning,
Sono Kanata he
down ever further.
Tozasare teku hitomi de
With my closing eyes,
Mada tooku he
I reach out once again
Te wo nobasu
far into the distance,
Kimi no nageki wo shinji te
believing in your grief.
Did you hate me...
Did you hate me so much?
Origin rounds.
They cause the target's mana
to go out of control,
...causing their body
to rip itself apart.
What?
Time Alter: Double Accel!
The origin rounds aren't working.
No...
I understand.
He's using Command Seals
as his mana source.
By the time the round
takes effect,
...the Command Seal mana source
has already vanished.
Since he doesn't use his
own Magic Circuits,
...the origin rounds' magic
won't work.
But if I can hit him...
...it'll still be strong enough
to kill him.
Don't think you'll escape next time.
Now that I know you're
moving at double speed,
...I simply need to adjust my timing
to compensate for it.
He's fast!
The depth of your madness...
Is that my fault, as well?
My."
My...
Time Alter: Double Accel!
I'm at a massive disadvantage
at close range.
I've lost my Calico.
My Contender needs reloading.
However...
Avalon...
He has a healing ability that allows him to
instantly regenerate a demolished heart?
Then I'll have to destroy the brain.
But...
I can't use my right arm.
Avalon's healing powers will even
work on self-inflicted wounds...
I have a knife and
two grenades left.
I have twelve blades remaining.
And eight spare Command Seals.
Time Alter: Triple Accel!
Time Alter: Square Accel!
Even so, I will win the Holy Grail.
If I do not,
...there will be nothing I can do
to atone to you.
Even after all of this...
...you would still take up your sword
for such a reason?
What a difficult person you are...
This is...
I knew you'd come.
I had faith that you would
reach this place.
Iri.
This is where your wish
will be granted...
We are inside the Grail you sought.
That is the Grail.
It has yet to take form,
but the vessel is more than filled.
All you need do now is
offer it your prayer.
Only then will it be
able to go outside.
Now, please...
Hurry, give it form.
Kiritsugu, you are worthy
to define its existence.
Who are you?
I am Irisviel.
No...
If the Grail is prepared,
then she is already...
Answer me!
True. I will not deny that
this is a mask.
Unless I use a pre-existing
personality as a shell,
...I cannot communicate with others.
However, the personality of Irisviel that
I recorded is inarguably the real thing.
And so, I have inherited
her last wish.
Are you the will of the Holy Grail?
Yes. That interpretation is not incorrect.
I have a will... A wish.
The will to be born
into the world.
Impossible.
In that case, how does the Grail
intend to grant my wish?
That is something, Kiritsugu,
...that you should know
better than anyone.
What?
You learned how to save the
world a long time ago.
So I will do as you did,
...to carry out your will,
and to answer your prayer.
What are you talking about?
I suppose I have no choice.
The only way is to have you ask
your inner self.
Where am I?
Three hundred on one ship.
Two hundred on another.
What?
Five hundred total
passengers and crew,
...plus Kiritsugu Emiya.
Let's posit that these five hundred and one
are humanity's last survivors.
Giant holes simultaneously open up
in both ships, crippling them.
Kiritsugu alone has the
skills needed to repair a ship.
Now then,
which ship would you fix?
Obviously, the one with three
hundred people.
As soon as you make
that decision,
...the two hundred passengers on
the other ship take you prisoner.
They demand that you
fix their ship first.
So what will you do?
I'd...
Kill all two hundred.
That is correct.
That is what Kiritsugu Emiya would do.
Next, the surviving three hundred
abandon their damaged craft,
...split themselves between two new ships,
and continue their journey.
This time, there are two hundred on one.
One hundred on the other.
But again, holes open in the hulls
of both ships at the same time.
Wait.
The hundred in the
smaller ship take you prisoner,
...demanding that you
fix their ship first.
Now, what will you do?
You already know.
But...
Yes, you made the right decision.
Impossible...
That's impossible!
How can that be the right decision?
Two hundred survived...
But three hundred died
so they could live!
The scales are tipped
the wrong way!
No, your calculations were correct.
You chose to sacrifice the few
to save the many.
Isn't that right, Kiritsugu Emiya?
You have always chosen to kill those
on the lighter side of the scales.
Even if it meant leaving a long
trail of bodies behind you.
If it saved lives, the lives of the saved
must have been worth more.
This is what you wanted
to show me?
Yes. This is your truth.
The answer that lies
within Kiritsugu Emiya.
In short, the course of action that should be taken
by the Grail as an all-powerful wish granter.
No...
This isn't what I want!
I want there to be another way!
That's why I believed that
a miracle was my only hope!
Your wish cannot include
a method you yourself don't know.
If you wish to save the world,
...it must be done in a way
that you comprehend.
Like hell!
How the hell
can you call that a miracle?!
But it is.
The deed that you tried and
failed to do on your own...
...can be accomplished on a scale
beyond the power of any man.
If that is not a miracle, what is?
Dad...
Natalia!
Kiritsugu Emiya,
you truly are Angra Mainyu.
The one worthy to bear
all the evil in the world.
Now, the final question.
Three remain.
Will you save two?
Or choose one?
Welcome home, Kiritsugu!
You're finally back!
You understand now, right?
This is the Holy Grail
granting your prayer.
All you need do now
is to wish for it.
To bring back your wife.
To take back your daughter.
I won't be able to go looking for
chestnuts with you anymore.
It's okay.
I'm happy,
as long as you and Mother are with me.
Thank you...
Daddy loves you, too, Ilya.
If nothing else, I swear
that to be true.
Good bye,
Ilya.
“Ilya!
"Ilya, Ilya, Ilya...
Ilya! Ilya...
Why?! Why would you do this?!
My love, you killed our Ilya!
M-My love...
Wh-Why?
Why do you refuse us?
Refuse us and the Grail?
Six billion people...
I curse you,
...Kiritsugu... Emiya.
Versus two family members...
Angra Mainyu curses you...
I...
Suffer...
...until the day you die.
- I will kill you...
- I will...
And I will save the world.
...never forgive--
What a boring conclusion.
Why did you refuse it?
You saw that, too?
I thought you sacrificed
everything you had...
...to make it this far.
How can you deny the
worth of something...
...you worked so hard to attain?
It's so foolish,
I cannot understand it.
Its cost is greater
than any benefit it offers.
That's all.
That thing is no
omnipotent wish-granter.
Then give it to me!
You may not need it,
but I do!
If it...
If it is given life,
...then it can certainly answer
my every doubt.
It longs for a life of its own!
For its own birth!
Please, don't kill it!
That's...
No, you are so foolish that
I can't understand you.
Irisviel...
You're late, Saber.
I realize that you were enjoying
yourself with your old mad dog,
...but it is imprudent in the extreme
to keep me waiting.
Archer...
Look at that expression,
like that of a ravenous, wild dog.
Get out of the way...
The Holy Grail belongs to me!
Saber, it is when you are delusional
and crawling in the dirt...
...that you are at your most beautiful.
Lay down your blade
and be my wife.
A Grail that grants miracles?
Where is the sense in obsessing
over something so dubious?
Abandon these foolish
ideals and vows of yours.
From now on, seek only me,
and devote yourself to me alone.
If you do,
I swear, as king of all creation,
...that I shall give you every pleasure
the world has to offer.
You would steal the
Holy Grail from me?
For such nonsense?!
I was not asking your opinion.
I am informing you
of my decision!
Now, let us hear your response.
I refuse! I would never--
Shyness has left you
at a loss for words, I see.
That's fine...
You may give the wrong answer
as many times as you like.
If you would learn the
joy of serving me,
...you must first learn pain.
Kiritsugu...
Then you have finally
made your decision.
In the name of Kiritsugu Emiya,
I order you with my Command Seal...
Give me the Holy Grail.
Saber, use your Noble Phantasm...
...to destroy the Grail.
Impossible...
What are you doing, Saber?!
No!
By my third Command Seal,
I order you again...
Why, Kiritsugu?
You, of all people... Why?!
Curse you...
You dare interrupt my
wedding ceremony, mongrel?!
Saber, destroy...
Stop!
...the Grail.
Episode 24:
The Last Command Seal
Doushite sora wa konna ni aoku te
Why is the sky so blue?
Nani mo kanashimi wo shiranu youni
As if it knows nothing of sadness,
Itsumo tamerawazu ashita he to kuzure ochiru
it always caves into tomorrow without hesitation.
Inochi wa tarinai mama umarete kuruno ne
When souls are born, they're lacking something, aren't they?
Kake ochita kokoro ni anata ga furete
You touch my broken heart.
Futari de yuku mirai wa
The future we're heading towards together
Kegare no nai tsuyosa de
with unsullied strength.
Sora wa takaku kaze wa utau
The sky is high and the wind sings.
Yume wo miteta Yorokobi he to
I had a dream to reach joy.
Hito wa itsuka tadori tsukeru
Everyone will reach the goal some day.
Kodomo no hitomi de anata wa shinjita
You believed that with childlike, pure eyes.
Soba ni iruyo
I'm here at your side
Koori tsuita mori wo nuke te
while passing through this frozen forest
Sono hitomi ga sekai no nageki ni
so that your eyes won't be distracted
Mayowanu you ni
by the grief of the world.
I remember that face...
With tears in his eyes,
and joy filling his heart...
It was a man.
The man was grateful to
someone or something.
Next Time: Fate] Zero
“Thank you,“ he said.
Next Time:
Fate I Zero