By my third Command Seal,
I order you again...
Stop!
Saber, destroy the Grail.
How could I hope to know a man
from three commands alone?
I never even knew
the hearts of those...
...who served me
more closely than any others.
Perhaps all this...
...was a punishment meted out to a king
who cannot understand others...
That's...
Impossible...
It's impossible!
Kiritsugu...
What's wrong, Ilyasviel?
I had a scary dream.
A dream...
...where I became a cup...
And inside me,
these seven big lumps appear.
It feels like they'll
tear me apart.
It's really scary.
But I can't run away...
Then I hear Lord Justeaze's voice.
Above my head,
a big black hole opens up.
And then, the world burns.
Kiritsugu looks at it and cries.
Mother, is Kiritsugu okay?
Is he scared and alone?
It's okay.
He's doing his best for you.
He'll make sure our
prayers are realized.
So you'll never have
to be scared again.
Yeah...
That's right.
Kiritsugu always works hard.
He'll finish his important work,
and he'll come home soon.
Hey, Sakura...
Uncle?
I'm here to save you.
It's okay now.
Let's go.
Sakura!
Sakura! Sakura! Sakura!
Kariya...
Aoi.
Thank you, Uncle Kariya!
Thank you...
Daddy Kariya!
Fool...
That's what happens when
you disobey Grandfather.
Where am I?
You're a difficult man
to look after.
Digging you from the rubble
was quite troublesome.
Gilgamesh, what happened?
Who can say...
That mud spit me out.
I imagine it to be a
message from Heaven,
...that I should return
to this age to rule the world.
So you have achieved incarnation?
Infuriatingly enough.
I can't believe we struggled over
that thing as a wish-granter.
This play remained a farce
to the very end.
I was shot...
I have no heartbeat...
Did you somehow heal me,
Gilgamesh?
I couldn't say...
To my eyes,
you do seem dead.
But we were connected
by our pact.
When I regained flesh
within that ooze,
...perhaps you were trapped in some
sort of nonsense of your own.
You're saying it granted me life?
All the other Servants are gone,
...so we are the ones who
have won the Grail.
Kirei, behold the result.
If the Grail truly grants
the Victor's wish...
...Kirei Kotomine,
...what you see is exactly
what you most desired.
What?
What am I?
What manner of evil?
What manner of cruelty?
This is my wish?
This destruction and tragedy?
This is my joy?
Could something so twisted
and corrupt...
...truly have sprung from
Risei Kotomine's seed?
Impossible.
It is impossible!
Did my father sire a cur?
Are you satisfied now, Kirei?
No, not yet.
This isn't enough.
Yes, it is true that my life of questions
has found its answer.
But the problem-solving process
itself was skipped over,
...and I was simply handed
the answer.
How am I to accept this?
The formula that yielded
this strange answer...
...should exist somewhere as
a greater, clearer principle.
No...
It has to.
I must question.
I must search.
I must use the rest of my life...
...to understand it.
You never bore me.
As you like.
Your questions would
slay the very gods.
I, Gilgamesh, shall watch
you seek your answer.
Angra Mainyu...
I will reach it again,
and next time, I will see it to the end.
Its birth.
The proof of its existence.
Kiritsugu Emiya?
I accept your challenge.
What's wrong, Kirei?
Nothing.
I remember the look
on his face...
The tears in his eyes
over finding someone alive.
A man filled with joy,
from the bottom of his heart.
He looked so happy,
...it was as though it had been him,
and not me, who had been saved.
He's alive...
He's alive... He's alive.
And then...
So fervently that, even on
the brink of death,
...I was jealous,
...he said, "Thank you."
That he was glad he'd
found someone.
That by saving even one person,
...he had saved himself.
Episode 25-.
Fate I Zero
And now, our next story.
Huge Explosion in Fuyuki's New Town
The explosion that occurred...
I hope that Alexei make it back
to England safely.
He called me this morning
from Heathrow.
That idiot forgot about
the time difference.
Oh, he called?
I didn't notice.
But it's just like him
to do that.
Hey, Grandpa and Grandma.
I'd like to talk to you
about something...
What is it?
Actually,
I'm thinking of taking some
time off from school.
Of course, I'll talk to Dad
in Toronto about it first.
There's something that I want to spend
my time on more than studies at school.
Oh?
My goodness!
But what brought this on?
You aren't fed up with school
or anything, are you?
No, it's not that.
It's just that in my whole life so far,
I haven't really been interested...
...in anything besides studying.
I'm regretting that a little.
And so...
I'd like to do some traveling.
Oh, my...
Did you hear that, Glen?
Waver just said something
that sounded just like Alexei.
Anyway, there's a lot
I'd have to do first.
And I'll need money
to do it, too.
For starters, I was thinking
of finding a part-time job.
And so...
To make a long story short...
If you wouldn't mind,
...could I stay here until
I get things worked out?
Of course you can!
It will be so wonderful
to keep having you here!
We'll have to celebrate today!
Jeez...
He's just a spirit.
So how can he leave
such a mess behind?
I really did want him
to take me with him...
So basically,
I'm just not there yet.
He never even opened this...
A preorder with a bonus,
original T-shirt.
Does anyone even want
stuff like this?
Idiot...
I know that my
redeemer lives.
And that, in the end, He will
stand upon the Earth.
And after my skin has been
destroyed, yet in my flesh,
...I will see God.
I myself will see Him
with my own eyes.
I, and not another.
How my heart yearns
within me.
Amen.
Rin...
An excellent debut for
the new family head.
Your father would be pleased.
Well done.
You haven't quite grown accustomed
to your Crest, I see.
Does it hurt?
This is nothing.
I'm fine.
Tokiomi's preparations
were flawless.
I imagine that all the magics that the
Tohsaka family has accumulated...
...will pass to you
without incident, Rin.
Why don't you go fetch
your mother?
Yes, I'll do that.
Come on, Mother...
Let's say our last goodbye to Father.
Ah, Rin?
Is it someone's funeral today?
That's right.
Father died.
Oh, dear...
Then I should take out
Tokiomi's black suit.
Oh, Rin...
Help Sakura get changed.
What should I do?
I have to get ready, too.
Dear, your necktie
isn't on straight.
You need to look good.
After all, you're Sakura
and Rin's father.
I'll be leaving Japan
again for a while.
Do you have any
immediate concerns?
No! I don't need your help
for anything!
We will next meet
in six months.
At that time, I will conduct the
second Crest transplantation.
Take care that you are in
peak physical condition.
I know what to do!
You don't need to tell me!
Rin...
You are now the Tohsaka family head
both in name and reality.
To commemorate this day,
I'd like to offer you a gift.
An Azoth dagger.
When my master accepted
the results of my training,
...he gave this to me.
Now you should have it.
This was my father's...
I'm here...
...again.
Everyone...
Lancelot...
Because I could not stop myself
from loving Guinevere,
...I was never able to
forgive myself.
But, King Arthur...
You never spoke of my sins.
You never sought atonement.
You simply continued
to stand before us...
...in your righteousness.
But I desired judgment
at your hands...
Had your anger judged me,
I might not have fallen...
...onto the path of madness
in my quest to atone.
I'm sorry... I'm sorry.
I...
I am unworthy.
But this much I can
say with certainty,
King Arthur...
One day, I will claim
the Holy Grail.
You were the greatest
of all kings...
All who served you...
It was not I...
...felt the same way.
...who should have been king.
After that,
I visited the Einzberns many times.
But as I had not returned
with the Grail,
...Jubstacheit never opened
the forest's barrier.
I never saw Ilya again.
However...
Ilya would be the final person
I would lose.
My life was meant to
be one solely of loss.
But everyone is still here,
just like when we met.
I adopted Shirou,
the boy I saved that day.
- Five Years Later -
Hey.
Hey, Pops...
If you're gonna sleep,
do it in your bed.
Right...
I'm fine.
When I was little,
I wanted to be a hero.
What?
You wanted to be?
Did you give up?
Yeah. Unfortunately...
Becoming a hero
has an expiration date.
When you grow up,
it's hard to call yourself one.
I wish I had realized
that sooner.
I see.
Then I guess you'll
never be one, huh?
No...
No, I never will.
It really is a nice moon tonight.
Fine.
Since you can't do it,
...I'll be one for you.
You're an adult now,
so you can't do it anymore.
But I still can.
Leave it to me...
Your dream.
All right.
I'll do that.
I can rest easy now.
Kerry, what kind of adult do you want
to be when you grow up?
Well,
...I want to be a hero.
Ato ichido dake kiseki wa okoru darou
A miracle is sure to happen just one more time.
Yasashii koe de egaku yuganda mirai
The twisted future described with your gentle voice.
Kimi o erande Tatta futari no yorokobi o sagaseta nara
If I can choose you and search for happiness for us alone,
Donna tsumetai honoo ni mi o yakarete mo
we could be burned by the coldest flames
Hohoemi no chikaku
and still be smiling.
Kono sekai o Sunda mizu no naka he kaeshitai
I want to send this world back into the clear waters.
Kanashimi dake kese wa shinai
We cannot erase only sadness.
Sonna hito no kokoro no kotowari sae
I'll cut through such reasoning of the human heart
Kono te de kirisaite
with my own hands.
Down to zero we go
Kirei na tsuki no hikari wa
The beautiful moonlight
Tada shizuka ni Hajimari he kuchite yuku yo
is rotting away quietly towards the beginning.
Tozasareta akogare wa
The admiration locked inside
Mada tooku he Yami no naka
is still far away and in the darkness.
All those days I lived with you.
Yasashii uta
A gentle song.