Edited at https://subtitletools.com
In the shadows that keep expanding, we exchange revolutionary vows.
Hirogaru yami no naka kawashiatta kakumei no chigiri
I won't let anyone get in my way
Dareni mo jama saseru wake ni wa ikanai kara
The recent past tells me of the future. My ideals become my dreams.
kajitsu ga tsugeta mirai. Yume, visou ni kaeru
The ending that everyone desires.
Daremo ga nozonda owari wo...
In the shadows that keep expanding, we exchange revolutionary vows.
Hirogaru yami no naka kawashiatta kakumei no chigiri
I won't let anyone get in my way
Dareni mo jama saseru wake ni wa ikanai
Itsuka boku ga misete ageru hikari no kagayaku sekai wo
Someday I'll show you a world that shines in the light.
Light-kun... is the first friend I've ever had.
Misa?
Yes?
Can you ask Rem to kill L?
Rem, I want to be loved by Light.
I'll be happy.
Okay...
I'll kill L.
L is going to die... just like that?
Gamble
So, when do you want him killed?
If you take me to him, I'll kill him instantly.
The earlier, the better.
It could even be tomorrow.
Then again, it may be a little careless to decide straight away.
Tonight, I'll think carefully about when and how we should kill him, and I'll give you my answer after that.
I understand.
Listen. No matter what happens, don't kill until I give the signal.
No matter what happens!
Sure, I can promise you that... with regard to L...
Misa, give me your cell phone number.
You're rather slow on the uptake!
Give me yours too.
No, I can't give you mine.
Why?!
You can't do that when you're part of a couple!
I already told you, I'm being marked by the police.
These days, they have the ability to bug specific telephone lines.
Oh! In that case, have this!
Misa will give you one of hers!
After I started to use each for a different purpose, I ended up with three!
It's a good idea.
Yours should probably be fine.
Yay! I'll give you a love call every day!
And send you lots of texts!
No, I'll be leaving the phone switched off.
I'll call you only when necessary, and ensure that information is kept to a minimum.
No way... when will you call me?
Probably tomorrow.
Regardless of whether we go ahead with killing L or not, I'll give you a call.
Yay! Tomorrow?!
Doesn't sound like the call is going to be very romantic, but if we can talk love afterwards, I don't mind!
Anyway, Misa, you'd better go home now.
Oh, what?! It's only 7 pm!
The time for lovers has only just begun!
We can go grab something to eat together, and follow that by watching the sun set, and then it'll be time to get serious!
Misa.
Okay?
For today, go home.
...Okay.
Also, when you talk to Rem outside, make sure no one is around, and do so quietly.
I do the same with Ryuk.
Okay...
Thank you for having me...
Misa-san! Please come again tomorrow!
I was pretty surprised when you just kissed her out of nowhere.
It's necessary to ensure that Misa falls utterly in love with me.
Oh...
More importantly, I need to decide whether or not to kill L tomorrow.
Since Ryuuga's identity as L isn't publicly known, I've got to be prepared for the fact that if he dies, I will be strongly suspected of being Kira.
Aah, I see.
I thought that since you declared yourselves to be friends, you might be having second thoughts about killing him.
"Friends"?
I just went along with what he said.
From the beginning I've said, "if he wants friendship, I'll take it".
For Yagami Light, Ryuuga is merely a friend for appearance's sake.
L is Kira's enemy.
That's right. L is my enemy.
Since he's revealed himself to me as L, I'll have to kill him...
If I make it an "accidental death", hardly anyone will suspect that I'm Kira, and even if they do, there'll be no proof.
I can only imagine what will happen after L dies... this is now a gamble.
Tomorrow, L... or rather Ryuuzaki or Ryuuga, will be your last.
Hair.
Crumbs from snacks.
Yagami-san?
If I die in the next few days, your son is Kira.
Hair again.
What did you just say, Ryuuzaki?!
That's right! Where's this suddenly coming from?
I'll arrange it so that you can use Watari as you please.
The rest will be up to you.
Ryuuzaki! You said that the majority of your suspicions had already been dismissed!
How deeply do you really suspect my son?!
I'm not sure I really understand what I truly think myself.
Nothing like this has ever happened before...
If Kira and the second kira have indeed made contact... I'm in a dire pinch.
Thus, right now, I'm probably incapable of calmly analyzing myself.
I could be doing this solely because I have no other suspects.
Nevertheless, if I am killed now, please conclude that your son is Kira.
I'll have to make another surprise attack, but it can't be helped... this is now a gamble.
That's not true, I'm just pretty sharp.
What's wrong?
Ah! Yagami-kun... hi.
Takada-san, I'd like to speak to him alone for a bit.
I'll see you later.
Huh? Okay...
Sure this is okay? What about her?
Never mind that. You said you were "scared of showing your face in public", are you okay?
Yagami-kun, I realized I'd be fine as long as you're not Kira.
Outside, you're the only one who knows I'm L.
That's why, if I'm killed within the next few days... you are Kira. I've informed everyone at Headquarters of that fact.
You!
You said yourself that it's lonely without me around, so I thought I'd come in for a change of scenery.
As long as I don't die, university is fun.
Yeah, when you're not around, there's no one I can talk to at my level. It's boring.
And thus the talented Takada-san?
Well, something like that.
Will it really be safe to kill him today?
No, by non-chalantly turning up like this, he's just trying to break my will to kill him.
He's probably trying to warn me off.
This is just what he wants to happen...
Shall we grab some cake from the cafeteria?
Yeah, I got no lectures next period.
That's good.
I wonder if they have shortcake?
Don't know, I can't remember.
Light! There you are!
I had a shoot nearby, so I thought I'd drop by!
Misa... you idiot!
Light, one of your friends?
Wow, he's wonderfully unique, isn't he...
No wait... I've won!
Misa can see Ryuuga's real name!
I'm Light's girlfriend, Amane Misa. Nice to meet you.
I'm Ryuuga Hideki.
Huh? Ryuuga Hideki?
Yeah, he's got the same name as the idol. Funny, huh?
But... that's different from the name I can see...
Ryuuga, this time, your decision to come out has worked against y--!
What's he laughing about?!
Don't tell me, he's realized?!
But if he thinks there's a possibility that she's the second Kira, surely he wouldn't be able to laugh like that...
Yagami-kun...
I'm very jealous.
I've been a fan of Misa's since the August edition of "Eighteen".
Yay! Really?! I'm happy!
That girl, it's Misa-Misa, isn't it?!
You're right! It is Misa-Misa!
Eh?! Misa-Misa?!
Eh?! Really?!
I always seem to get noticed when there's lots of young people around!
Where?! Wow!
Wow! Really?!
I buy your stuff every month!
Please keep up the good work!
Thanks, I'll try my best.
What's going on here?
No! Someone just touched my butt!
What nerve! To take advantage of all this confusion to do something like that!
I'll find the culprit!
Ryuuga-san, you're so funny!
I wanna feel too.
Dumb-ass...
I want to find out L's real name from Misa as soon as possible, but with all these people around...
Misa! It's time to go.
Do you want to be late, again?
Sorry, Yoshii.
Let's go.
No matter.
Even if Misa leaves, all I need to do is make one phone call to find out.
Bye Light! See you after work!
Well then, shall we go, Yagami-kun?
Yeah.
You go ahead, I need to go to the toilet.
Really? Okay then.
It's over.
It's been all sorts of fun, L.
I'm so glad I was able to find out your real name and kill you myself.
Yes, hello?
What do you mean, "Hello"?
It looks like someone dropped this phone amid all the confusion just now.
At that time... he...
Hello?
That's Misa's phone. I'll return it to her.
Really? Okay, got it.
Ryuuga, you may think you've outwitted me, but Misa has another cell phone.
Once I ring that...
This time it's my cell phone.
Yes?
Ah, is that right. We've done it, then.
Understood.
This is probably both good and bad news for you.
We've apprehended Amane Misa on suspicion of being the second Kira.
Since when has he suspected Misa?!
I can't believe she was caught so fast...
When the second Kira sent the video tapes from Amane's room, they left a great deal of evidence, such as hairs and clothing fibres, stuck to packing tape used to seal the envelopes.
We believe that announcing she's under suspicion of being the second Kira would cause public chaos,
so we're saying she's gone to be questioned about the charges held against her manager for drug possession.
However, I doubt the public will find that out.
I was too naive.
Those videos... I should have ensure I destroyed the evidence.
In the end, by being around me, rather than hiding, Ryuuga managed to protect himself, and get right to the heart of the case...
This gamble... I've...
I've...
No!
It's not over yet.
The fight has just begun, L.
Watari, has she said anything yet?
No, not a word.
Bring a visual of her up.
Are you sure?
Yes, hurry up.
R-Ryuuzaki... what the hell is this?!
She's been apprehended on suspicion of being the second Kira.
It's only natural to take these precautions.
It's true that there was enough evidence in Amane's room to assure us that she's the second Kira...
Yes, there's no doubt.
Now, we need a confession of how she kill people, if she knows Kira, and if she knows who Kira is.
Watari, as long as you're careful, I won't mind if you use slightly dubious methods.
Get her to spit it out.
Okay.
And, Yagami-san, please prepare yourself for the fact that I'll be bringing Light-kun in for questioning regarding Kira.
Ryuuzaki! Amane has said something.
Hurry and bring up a visual.
Finally! After three days.
I can't stand it anymore...
Kill me.
Kill me! Hurry up and kill me.
I thought it might have been too much for a girl who's only around twenty.
This must be her limit.
Amane Misa, can you hear me?
I can hear you.
Please... hurry up and kill me.
Does that mean that you admit you are the second Kira?
No. I don't know anything about the second Kira...
I can't take this anymore... I'd rather die.
Come on! Hurry up and kill me!
I know you could kill me in an instant if you wanted to!
Misa... you don't mean...
That's right, kill me...
...you want me to kill you?
Yes, kill me.
I can't endure this anymore, kill me.
If I kill you, I'll kill Yagami Light too.
This is all his faul--
No! No!
Kill me.
Misa... you're really willing to die for him?
That's enough! If you won't kill me I--
Oh no!
Watari! Don't let her bite her tongue!
Surely, she's not being manipulated by Kira just before she dies?
Hey Rem, what do you want all of a sudden?
Yagami Light, even though I offered to help Misa escape, she refused.
It's probably because she realized that she would be seen as having special powers, which would cause you trouble...
And when she realized she was reaching the limits of her mentality, she began to ask for me to kill her.
All this, because she wants to be loved by you.
Even though she begged me to, there's no way I could kill Misa.
I couldn't bear to watch her suffer like that.
There's only one way to save her.
Forfeiting ownership of the Death Note?
That's right.
Once you forfeit ownership of a Death Note, all the memories you have of it disappears completely.
She would forget about all the people she's killed, and the fact that Yagami Light is Kira.
So, there would be no danger of her giving away your secret.
Also, she would no longer be able to see Ryuk or myself.
A few hours earlier
Misa, this means that you'll forget everything you know about Shinigami.
It's okay.
The human you love is Yagami Light. Those feelings alone will remain.
That is why you should give up ownership of your Death Note and entrust everything to Yagami Light.
Misa is no longer the owner of a Death Note.
Good work, Rem.
I was just thinking that that was our sole option.
If Misa has no memory of the Death Note, it's possible that she can be released.
Yagami Light, I knew that this would be the best option for you, which is why I suggested it to Misa.
If you don't save Misa, I will kill you.
I understand, Rem.
I've got a fair idea of what L might do from here, and I have a plan.
This is goodbye, Ryuk.
Huh?
To be continued
Darenimo mirenai yume wo mita
I've had dreams that no one else could have.
Iranai mono wa subete suteta
I've thrown away everything that I don't need.
Those feelings I can't rid remain in my heart.
Yuzurenai omoi kono mune ni yadoshite
Even though I'm stuck between ideals and reality,
Mada real to ideal no hazama ni ite
and my legs are bound by the shackles of sacrifice.
Gesei no kase ni, ashi wo toraretemo
If I can hold back these overwhelming urges,
Afureru shoudou osaekireba
Tsuyoku motomeru kokora ga arukara
I still have a soul that yearns for more.
Itsuwari, Osore, Kyoshoku, Urei
Lies, fear, pretension, grief.
Samazama na negative ni
I'm not so weak,
Torawareru hodo yowaku wa nai
that I'll become lost in these negative feelings.
A trickster that doesn't know loneliness.
Kodoku mo shiranu trickster
Preview
Right now, I know I'm in a bad situation, but meaningless pride like that... I discard it!
Next time
Decision