Edited at https://subtitletools.com
We've always been this to free all the pain
Banzai, you're so useful!
Benri benri banzai
ningen
Human!
Benri benri banzai
Banzai, you're so useful!
ningen
Human!
Hora BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
Hey! You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
Human!
Ningen
Hora BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
Hey! You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
Human!
Ningen
What's up? So much ground for concern; the guilt never fades.
WHAT'S UP
fuanzai ippai hanzai kienai towa ni
What's up? So much ground for concern!
WHAT'S UP
fuanzai ippai
urami ni wana, dare daun
Who fell down the trap of resentment?
What's up? So much ground for concern; the guild never fades.
WHAT'S UP
fuanzai ippai hanzai kienai towa ni
What's up? So much ground for concern!
WHAT'S UP
fuanzai ippai
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
WHAT'S UP PEOPLE?!
Huh?! W-What's happening?!
Everyone, the Shiniga--
Reincarnation
Go on! Kill me!
We lied about this being a live worldwide broadcast.
This announcement is currently being broadcast across the Kanto region of Japan.
Your first victim was, in fact, the Phantom Killer in Shinjuku.
In addition, that incident was only reported within Japan.
We've just heard that the culprit was found dead in the nursery!
Yes, it looks like the culprit is dead!
Just those pieces of information were enough for me to figure it out.
It means that you are in Japan, and that that criminal was your first "experiment".
The Investigative Headquarters for Countermeasures Against Kira
Kira is able to access confidential police files.
There are 141 people within the police who have access to information regarding Kira.
But within the 141 people or people close to them... Kira will definitely be among them.
FBI investigation into those connected to the Japanese Police Force.
On the 14th of December, twelve FBI agents entered Japan.
On the 19th of December,
Kira is evidently using prisoners as test subjects in order to study how they could manipulate the victims' movements before death.
Don't move!
From this we can deduct that to kill the FBI agents, Kira found it necessary to experiment to see how far they could manipulate someone's death.
Everyone, get down!
Consequently, Kira must be someone that was under investigation by the FBI between the 14th and the 19th.
An important witness:
Misora Naomi
Ray Penber's fiancée?
Misora Naomi...
I see... the girl who worked for me on that case... in Japan...
Apparently she was with Penber.
She might have discovered something...
So, does this mean Kira beat me to it?
Yagami Light
Everyone. From now on, we'll only be investigating those people who were under surveillance by Ray Penber.
The subjects of our investigation will be Deputy Kitamura and his family, and Chief Yagami and his family.
I'd also like to be able to set up cameras and bugging devices in both households.
Ryuuzaki, don't tell me... you actually suspect my son?!
Oh, I definitely suspect him, alright.
Contact with Yagami Light
I'm L.
Relax, Yagami.
Although Kira hates to lose, the majority of people would want to win in a match, whether they're Kira or not.
See. I knew you'd want to win.
I suspect that you may be Kira, Yagami-kun.
Me, Kira?
Ryuuga... is there any way that I can prove to you that I'm not Kira?
It'll be alright.
If you aren't Kira, I'll find out sooner or later.
Murder cases
involving a TV channel
co-operating with Kira
Four days ago, the director on duty received these four tapes.
Our ratings will rise by 60.. no, 70% at least!
...further predictions to provide proof that they are Kira, but also a message to the people of the world:
I am Kira.
The anchorman, Hibima Kazuhiko, will die of a heart attack at exactly 6 o'clock.
We've got to stop this broadcast, or there'll be trouble!
Idiots!
Ukita-san!
If Kira doesn't have a name, they shouldn't be able to kill!
Having watched this, it seems that the probability of Kira being able to kill someone solely by knowing their face isn't zero.
Police! Stop the broadcast!
The probability of this Kira being a fake is extremely high.
No, a "second Kira" is probably a better description.
Yagami-san, would it be okay if we asked your son to help us in the investigation?
Yagami Light summoned
to the Investigative Headquarters
If nothing else, there's a high probability that this is not the same Kira that we've been dealing with previously.
The same as L... I mean, that's exactly the same theory as Ryuuzaki!
When we meet, we can confirm our identities by showing each other our Shinigami.
What?!
If they're using a code that only those with a Shinigami's power would understand, then I won't be able to break it.
But... we'll need to ensure that we keep a close surveillance on all the locations mentioned.
I need you to observe Light-kun carefully during those two days as well.
If, by any chance he really is Kira, the second Kira may attempt to approach him in some way.
And Yagami-san... have Mogi-san keep a close eye on Light-kun's movements.
Light!
The arrest of Amane Misa on suspicion of being the second Kira
Light! There you are!
I'm Light's girlfriend, Amane Misa.
Pleased to meet you!
I'm Ryuuga Hideki.
Huh? Ryuuga Hideki?
This is probably both good and bad news for you...
We've apprehended Amane Misa on suspicion of being the second Kira.
When the second Kira sent the video tapes from Amane's room,
they left a great deal of evidence, such as hairs and clothing fibres stuck to packing tape used to seal the envelopes.
Amane Misa's detention
R-Ryuuzaki... what the hell is this?!
Come on! Hurry up and kill me!
I know you could kill me in an instant if you wanted to!
Does that mean that you admit you are the second Kira?
No! I don't know anything about the second Kira!
The voluntary detention of Yagami Light
Ryuuzaki, it's as I said on the phone... I might be Kira.
You're saying "I might be Kira"...
It's an act.
It's not that you "might be" Kira; you are Kira.
Light-kun, are you okay?
Yeah.
I can't say that I look too good at the moment... but such meaningless pride...
I discard it.
Ryuuzaki! I know I chose to be imprisoned and go through with this, but I've just realized, I am not Kira!
Hurry up and let me out of here!
What's going on?!
Two weeks' worth of criminals were taken out in one shot yesterday!
I have no idea what's going on...
Release of the two
It seems like all three of them are reaching their limits.
Ryuuzaki, why do you continue to detain Light-kun?! It's already been fifty days!
I'm going to kill you here and then I'll kill myself.
What are you saying, father?! Don't be stupid!
Stop it! Dad! You're crazy!!
It's better to run!
It's too late, Light.
Stop it, father! I'm not Kira!!
Light... we're both murderers; see you in hell.
Father!
Stop!!
It was a very realistic performance.
As promised, I'll end their imprisonment.
Yagami Light, summoned again under
the pretext of helping with the investigation
Also Light-kun, as promised, I'm prepared to make a pact with you; that is, you'll be with me 24/7 assisting me with this investigation.
Yotsuba
These are deaths that have benefited Yotsuba.
If you dig a little deeper, there have been thirteen incidents over the last three months.
The infiltration of Yotsuba
Is Kira a part of Yotsuba? Is Kira merely using Yotsuba?
I've got no idea which it is, but we can assume that Kira is behind this.
It's time that we investigate Yotsuba thoroughly.
Please, think ahead carefully before you act, and don't do anything rash.
Don't just act on your own judgments.
I-I'm Matsui Tarou, a manager at Yoshida Productions.
How would you like to hire our star, Amane Misa, for your commercials?
Ryuuzaki, can you see me?
The eight that are here were in a meeting together, planning who to have Kira murder.
If Matsuda-san dies now, it will confirm the suspicions surrounding Yotsuba.
Is there really no way to save me?
Matsuda, you idiot!
The conclusion that
Higuchi Kyousuke is Kira
Go for it, Misa-Misa!!
I'll go and prepare the celebrations for when you land this commercial!
Misa's dream is to become Kira's wife!
That's because Misa is... the second Kira.
Well, since I'm Kira, you'd better marry me, Misa-chan!
So, as you can all hear... Higuchi is Kira!
Higuchi's capture
What are you planning?
I'm going to use Sakura TV to trap Higuchi.
You mean Dokkiri TV?!
Higuchi, this looks bad. Turn on your TV.
And one of those is Kira, is that right?
Yes, and I have plenty of proof!
It's him! Why is he still alive?
Higuchi's status confirmed. I'm in pursuit.
We're going after him!
You in the Porsche! Stop!
Pull over to the side! Stop the car!
Rem, it's time to do the deal.
"Deal"?
You were speeding. Let's see your license.
Ah, alright then.
He managed to shake off the cop! He's getting away!
This is the Traffic Riot Police--
Everyone! I believe it will be too dangerous to allow Higuchi to act any further!
We're going ahead with his capture.
However, Higuchi is now able to kill just by looking at someone's face, similar to the second Kira.
We'll be making the arrest under that assumption!
It ends here.
Stay back! No one come near!
Higuchi captured
Higuchi, how were you killing people?
You probably won't believe me, but if you write the name of a person whose face you know in that notebook, that person will die.
I found it in his bag.
What's wrong, Yagami-san?
M-Monster!
A Shinigami...
More than one notebook exists.
It's not over yet...
The Notebook of Death,
and the analysis of its rules
"How to use"...
"The human whose name is written in this note shall die."
And this final sentence...
"From the moment a new user writes a name into this notebook, they must continue to write names, each within 13 days of the last; otherwise, the user will die."
Yagami Light and Amane Misa are still alive...
13 days... this is the only thing...
Ryuuzaki has been dead for ten days now; seems like we've managed to avoid being killed.
We've managed to find a little about Watari's true identity, but we've found nothing about Ryuuzaki.
However, Watari turned out to be an incredible inventor, didn't he?
"He established orphanages all over the world using the fortune he made from his patents."
He was a great man! A great man.
However, with L and Watari gone, we can't continue our investigations from here. It's tough.
Light? How's it going?
We should be able to remove and take most of the system with us by tonight.
It doesn't feel good doing this though, it's like being a thief.
I've managed to create a voice identical to the one Ryuuzaki was using;
we'll be able to make it seem like he's still alive, and we can control the world's police forces just as before.
However, I don't know who'll take L's place or where... or what we're supposed to do with this murderer's notebook.
What are you talking about, Light-kun? The only one who can take on the role of L is you.
If Ryuuzaki died as a result of provoking Kira, it's not exactly a tempting position.
Besides, it means we're deceiving the entire world.
I understand how you feel, Light-kun, but besides you, there's no one else.
He's right. Even L said, "Light-kun would be able to succeed me".
So easy... just as I predicted, without Ryuuzaki around, it's so easy.
Fine, I'll do it.
But unlike Ryuuzaki, I won't be using any dangerous methods such as challenging Kira in order to gain hints.
As long as you're all okay with that...
Yes. It's probably better to err on the side of caution.
Ryuuzaki was probably a little too confrontational.
In that case, I can manage with just this PC and my own, so it'll be possible for me to act as L from my own room at home.
I'll act as Watari as well.
But it's going to be rather difficult with my mother and sister around.
It'd be useful if I could rent a single room somewhere.
I'll give you an allowance to live on your own. No one will find that odd.
Yeah, you're right. Well, from now on, Light-kun's room will be the new investigative headquarters.
Now all that's left is to decide what to do with the murderer's notebook.
We won't need to think too hard about that either.
We just need to keep it in an unknown location. So have one of us five, someone we trust will never use it, hide it somewhere.
Chief, please do it.
The Chief can definitely do it. He's full of righteousness.
Me? Okay then.
Let's avenge Ryuuzaki!
Kira is still on the loose. We must catch them!
Well, why don't we hold a party to celebrate Light-kun becoming the second L?
Light! This is our first date in a while, you could at least try to look a little happier!
Misa.
Let's live together.
R-Really?
Yeah, I've already rented an apartment.
Yay! We're going to live together!
Misa wins!!
Wins?
Over Kiyomi, Mari, Yuri and so on...
It's okay, Light. I understood that you were just using them to deceive L.
You won't be seeing them anymore, will you?
Yeah, I won't.
So, you've completely settled the score with L, eh?
Yeah.
Guess I won't have much fun to look forward to then.
That's not true at all, Ryuk.
From here on... I'm going to show you the reincarnation of a new world.
Papa?
Papa?!
The reconstruction of Yotsuba begins now.
Y-Yes, let's do our best.
Hey? Namikawa?!
S-Surely not...
April 2012: Yagami Light, aged 23, joins the National Police Force.
Summer 2012: The rate of Kira's judgment increases even more rapidly.
The world becomes split into two groups: those that scream in fear at Kira, and those that secretly cheer him on.
Little by little, those voices in support of Kira begin to surface.
Eventually, entire countries begin to declare their acceptance of Kira's work,
and the world continues to head toward a dark age, where Kira is law.
What's up, Roger?
L... has died.
To be continued
This one page of everlasting depression;
Towa ni utsu kono ichi peeji
hakanai senpou sono meni
a fleeting tactic in your eyes.
Aigan sezumo hou ni aku tsunagou rou he
Let's intertwine evil with law, pass no plea and go to jail.
Nooto ni moudoku bonnou ni osore idaku
Deadly poison within the Note harbors fears of carnal desires.
Oouso no mousou ni yodare ga taema naku
Incessant drool at false fantasies;
sabaki hanzai toukatsu to hozaku
judgment; never-ending talk of uniting crime.
Who would know of a path to salvation?
Dare ga dakaisaku nodo wakaru?
Menzai no waarudo
World of acquittal,
seisai no waado
words of retribution!
Eru netsu masani "desu paireetsu"
This fire I feel, I truly am a Death pirate!
Redeem the game of law!
Aganau houritsu geemu
Despair the Billy,
Zetsubou za birii
here are the morals!
iza rinri
Come, relentless eraser rain.
Saa tomerarenai eraser rain
Zetsubou za birii
Despair the Billy,
iza rinri
here are the morals!
Saa tomerarenai eraser rain
Come, relentless eraser rain.
tomerarenai eraser rain
relentless eraser rain.
Preview
L's death... who... where... did they hear this from?
Is this a joke?!
But... what is this... presence?
Next Time
Abduction