Edited at https://subtitletools.com
We've always been this to free all the pain
Banzai, you're so useful!
Benri benri banzai
ningen
Human!
Banzai, you're so useful!
Benri benri banzai
ningen
Human!
Hora BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
Hey! You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
Ningen
Human!
Hora BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
Hey! You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
Human!
Ningen
What's up? So much ground for concern; the guilt never fades.
WHAT'S UP
fuanzai ippai hanzai kienai towa ni
What's up? So much ground for concern!
fuanzai ippai
urami ni wana, dare daun
Who fell down the trap of resentment?
WHAT'S UP
What's up? So much ground for concern; the guild never fades.
fuanzai ippai hanzai kienai towa ni
WHAT'S UP
What's up? So much ground for concern!
fuanzai ippai
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
WHAT'S UP PEOPLE?!
Every now and again one should go out into the sunlight.
What am I... supposed to do now?
Father
Ryuk.
Sidoh! What are you doing here?
Hey, quit following me!
Give me my notebook back.
I thought that might be it...
Erm... actually, it's gotten a little complicated... and even I don't know where it is at the moment.
That's so irresponsible!
You still following me?
Then gimme the notebook back!
I don't know where it is!
You want it, you find it.
Wammy's House is not just any orphanage.
It's like a special institute; they gathered the brightest children there with the aim of raising the second L, in other words, L's successor.
L's successor?
Out of all of them, a young boy named Near stood out as the top student.
Near... is he N?
And the young boy that N mentioned, Mello, was apparently the closest to Near in terms of abilities.
Near is L's successor... there's no doubt about it.
He's the "N" that's controlling the SPK.
No... Mello must have been aiming to become L's successor as well,
in which case, it's highly likely that he'll do whatever it takes to get his hands on the notebook before Near does.
This "Mello" that N was talking about... He doesn't merely "suspect" him, there's no mistaking that he's behind this.
Here are sketches of the two.
No photos were left of either of them.
L's successor... am I fighting L still?
In any case, the first thing I need to do is locate the mafia group that Mello's with.
I had Misa look through a list of currently wanted mafia members, and point him out to me using her Shinigami eyes.
I've found one! Someone whose lifespan I can't see!
Number 105. He's listed as "Jack Neylon", but his real name is Kal Snydar.
Using the Death Note, I manipulated Snydar into sending a sealed letter with the whereabouts of their organization.
It should arrive soon...
Light! The letter has arrived!
They're in LA!
I did it! I've completely outplayed both of them.
With both the notebook and Misa's eyes in my possession, I really am invincible.
Light... Misa was able to help again, wasn't she?
Yeah. I love you, Misa.
Stare...
Now, all that remains is to test to which extent we can manipulate people with this notebook.
I'd like them all to be able to see me and talk to me at least...
The current owner, Snydar... I'll start by getting him to touch the notebook.
I guess there's no choice...
Whee... plonk.
What the fuck? The notebook just jumped of its own accord...
It's a notebook that can kill people. It'd hardly be surprising if it turned out to be alive.
B-Boss!! The guy in the weird, dirty costume... is he a new recruit?!
I'm not a recruit, I'm a Shinigami.
Shinigami?
For me to be visible to the others, just have them touch the notebook.
A-Apparently, if you touch the notebook you'll be able to see it.
Everyone! I need you to touch the notebook!
I'm not going crazy!!
Alright then.
Everyone, try touching the notebook!
What the hell?!
I never saw anything the last time I touched it!
Boss! Should we kill it?!
It's no use. Humans can't kill me.
Looks like this Shinigami really exists, and is telling the truth...
Ryuk, as of now, I'm relinquishing ownership of this notebook.
I want you to accompany whoever becomes the next owner.
What the hell?! You're giving up your ownership?
But if you do that, won't you lose your memory?
Let me have your notebook.
As long as I do this, even if I relinquish the ownership of my notebook, I won't lose my memories.
I'll cut out pages when you need them.
From now on, you'll have to play the part of Kira. Can you do that?
Of course... but what are you planning to do?
I'm just getting to that...
We can't afford to make any mistakes.
This "chocolate" stuff is really good!
Hey, what you just said, is it really true?
"If the person using the note fails to continously write names of people to be killed within 13 days of each other, then the user will die."
and "If you make this note unusable by tearing it up or burning it, all the humans who have touched the note till then will die."
Are these two rules really fake?
Yeah, they're completely false.
A Shinigami probably wrote that as a joke before giving it to a human.
We can check whether the "13 days" rule is true or not by having someone test it.
The problem here is whether or not Kira has used this notebook before, and if they have, whether they know these rules are fake.
If they do know, then they could use these rules... especially this "13 days" rule... it could be used to prove someones innocence.
Sidoh! Keep watch outside.
You'll be useful, as humans won't be able to see you.
Keep watch outside. Got it?
What's with this guy? For a human, he sure is... scary!
This is Yagami.
This is Kira.
What did you say?!
Kira?
The notebook that was in the hands of the Japanese investigation has been stolen by criminals, right?
Kira? If you're really Kira, prove it!
Proof? Now that the notebook has fallen into other hands, committing an announced murder will no longer prove that I am Kira.
However, you should shortly receive proof that I am Kira.
I'm sending you my notebook.
W-What do you mean?!
With the notebook I'm giving you, you'll be able to see a person's name merely by looking at them. Do you understand?
Li-st-en care-fully...
On November 10th at 23:59,
all mafia members that I've been able to identify from information taken from the FBI and other organizations will die.
This has already been written in the notebook, and cannot be changed.
I already know the location of their hideout, and I'll pass that along with the notebook.
In other words, that moment, the 10th of November at 23:59, will be your greatest chance to retrieve your notebook.
What should we do?
If the mafia die on day X as Kira said, it would definitely be a big chance for us.
I'm uncomfortable with following Kira's plan, but it's a good idea.
Exactly.
But, all we actually know is when the mafia will die...
Ide-san, you say that, but you must already have realized...
we're being asked to do the deal for the eyes of a Shinigami and ensure we kill them.
I'll do the deal.
N-No way! If anyone's going to do the deal, it should be me!
I was the one who handed the notebook over in the first place.
Because of that, I've even thought about ending my own life.
I'll use the notebook to kill those criminals, and then after 13 days, I'll die myself.
If father ends up writing the names in the notebook, then...
10th November 23:47
Everyone, are you all prepared?
Yes.
Very well. Deputy Chief Yagami, go ahead and exchange your eyes with the Shinigami.
Ryuk, do it.
As you wish.
Deputy Chief Yagami, can you see the names and lifespans of the criminals in the photos I passed you?
Yes! I can see them.
When those names disappear, that's your signal.
Charge!!
Looks like Kira has gotten involved.
They've already gotten this far... we haven't perfected our plans yet...
Damn it! Sidoh, what are you doing?!
Just shut up and watch, Sidoh.
As long as you don't meddle in this, you'll get your notebook back.
Roy! Skiar!
The notebook is under Rodd.
Bring it up to the monitor room!
Freeze!
L, two of the mafia members have been captured and the notebook safely retrieved!
We're coming back.
No... it's not over.
We haven't found anyone that fits the description of Mello yet.
He's definitely hiding somewhere in this building.
We've already made it this far. We'll need to search for him slowly and calmly.
An explosion?!
Don't move. I've sealed off both exits with that one blast.
That was merely a threat... next, I'll blow the whole hideout.
Follow my orders...
This is Mello?
So, it's you again, Yagami.
I should have killed you the first time.
I never imagined I would be doing a deal for the notebook with you a second time.
M-I-H-A-E-L K-E-E-H-L
Your real name is Mihael Keehl.
Oh, fuck.
How?!
Yes! I did it!
Give it up, Mello. If you come along quietly, we won't kill you.
W-Why are you saying such idiotic things?!
Just write his name in the notebook and kill him!
If I write your name in this notebook, you'll die.
Move your hands away from the switch and raise them in the air.
Yagami...
Don't move! All I need to write now is your family name.
It'll take less than a second.
Idiot! Just write it! Write it down now!!
I'm sorry, I honestly never had any intention of killing you.
Yagami... I bet you've never killed anyone before.
Gunshots?!
What was that?!
Jose! The notebook!
Damn you! Let go... of the notebook!!
You... bastard!
Deputy Chief!
Mello! Put your hands up!
Matsuda? Are you alright?
No, I'm not...
Well, you look alright to me.
L! There's no sign of Mello!
Shit! He got away?!
That's why I said to kill him sooner!
Father? Father?! I'm begging you! Please don't die!
Light...
Father!!
I--
I'm so glad...
You're glad? Father?
Light...
I still... have the eyes of a Shinigami.
According to the Shinigami, Ryuk, I can't see the lifespan of anyone who owns a Death Note.
Light... you aren't Kira...
I'm so happy.
Of course he's not. I can't believe you're still saying things like that.
Father, don't speak more than necessary...
That's important too, but right now, there's something even more important!
Like writing Mello's name into the notebook...
I-I'm sorry... in the end, I couldn't kill him.
Would it be strange if I say "It's not too late" now?
No, I guess it'll depend on how I phrase it.
In this situation, it's not unnatural to be confused and upset.
Father! Use the last of your strength and write that bastards name down!
Do you really want to go down beaten?!
Father?!
Light...
I'm sorry.
Father?!
Father!
Father!!
Don't die! You fool!!
So you're the Shinigami who came to retrieve this notebook.
Yes.
Even if it's for the sake of the Kira investigation, we only need one notebook.
I'm returning this one.
"People who use this notebook will become unhappy", huh?
Well, Souichirou never actually used it, but he died believing his son wasn't Kira, so I guess he was happy.
To be continued
Towa ni utsu kono ichi peeji
This one page of everlasting depression;
a fleeting tactic in your eyes.
hakanai senpou sono meni
Aigan sezumo hou ni aku tsunagou rou he
Let's intertwine evil with law, pass no plea and go to jail.
Deadly poison within the Note harbors fears of carnal desires.
Nooto ni moudoku bonnou ni osore idaku
Incessant drool at false fantasies;
Oouso no mousou ni yodare ga taema naku
sabaki hanzai toukatsu to hozaku
judgment; never-ending talk of uniting crime.
Dare ga dakaisaku nodo wakaru?
Who would know of a path to salvation?
Menzai no waarudo
World of acquittal,
seisai no waado
words of retribution!
This fire I feel, I truly am a Death pirate!
Eru netsu masani "desu paireetsu"
Redeem the game of law!
Aganau houritsu geemu
Despair the Billy,
Zetsubou za birii
iza rinri
here are the morals!
Saa tomerarenai eraser rain
Come, relentless eraser rain.
Zetsubou za birii
Despair the Billy,
iza rinri
here are the morals!
Come, relentless eraser rain.
Saa tomerarenai eraser rain
tomerarenai eraser rain
relentless eraser rain.
Preview
If Kira is caught, then Kira is Evil.
If Kira takes control of the world, then Kira is Justice.
Henceforth, things will accelerate and the world will gradually turn toward Kira.
Kira will definitely become Justice.
Next Time
Justice