Edited at https://subtitletools.com
In the shadows that keep expanding, we exchange revolutionary vows.
Hirogaru yami no naka kawashiatta kakumei no chigiri
I won't let anyone get in my way
Dareni mo jama saseru wake ni wa ikanai kara
The recent past tells me of the future. My ideals become my dreams.
kajitsu ga tsugeta mirai. Yume, visou ni kaeru
The ending that everyone desires.
Daremo ga nozonda owari wo...
In the shadows that keep expanding, we exchange revolutionary vows.
Hirogaru yami no naka kawashiatta kakumei no chigiri
I won't let anyone get in my way
Dareni mo jama saseru wake ni wa ikanai
Itsuka boku ga misete ageru hikari no kagayaku sekai wo
Someday I'll show you a world that shines in the light.
Matsuda! This isn't child's play! Don't be flippant!
Understood...
This is about the Kira investigation! Will you take it seriously?!
S-Sorry...
Matsuda!!
I mean, Matsuda-san, please stop.
"Matsuda"?
I don't want to be a dead weight around here.
R-Ryuuzaki, is there anything else I can do? Other than being a manager?
Then, can you bring me another cup of coffee?
I too... want to play a bigger role in this!
Matsuda
I love you...
So, please, don't tell me that you're leaving.
I want to be by your side forever.
Director!
Please, Misa has a boyfriend, so love scenes are no good!
Huh?! W-Wait...
What are you saying all of a sudden?!
We can just pretend to kiss.
If you say things like that, we'll never get this movie finished!
I said no, and I mean no!
The Yotsuba Group's Tokyo Headquarters.
Today is Friday!
All the deaths which benefit Yotsuba happen towards the end of the week.
I don't want to be a dead weight around here.
There was always something amazing about Mogi-san.
Matsuda! This isn't child's play!
Will you take it seriously?!
Well, Matsuda-san is a bit of an airhead by nature.
Bring me another cup of coffee.
Matsuda!!
Misa's pet name for Matsuda is Matsu.
Matsu! Hey, Matsu!!
He seems to have gone off somewhere.
Huh?!
In that case, let's try starting with the names on this list.
Understood.
If it was possible to kill someone by merely knowing their name and face, would I try to kill criminals?
I do believe there are people in this world that are better off dead...
but I wouldn't take it upon myself and become a murderer to make the world a better place.
No, I'm thinking about this too much.
There's no way I'd forget about killing so many people--
What's the matter?
Why are you staring at me?
Are you annoyed that I'm the only one with cake to eat?
No, it's nothing like that.
Here.
I'm not envious.
Ryuuzaki.
What's up, Watari?
The detective Erald Coil has been commissioned to "reveal L's identity".
Erald Coil, the famous detective said to be second only to L.
Who would commission this?
We've determined that the commission came from Kida Masahiko, the Planning Director of the Yotsuba Group's Tokyo Headquarters.
So, it is Yotsuba's work!
Yotsuba has got to be working with Kira.
They want L's identity, so that they can kill L.
This is bad. We're already understaffed, and now we have this Coil to worry about.
It's fine.
The detective known as Erald Coil is me.
The three most famous detectives in this world at the moment... L, Coil and Deneuve... are all me.
A lot of people who try to find me fall for this.
If you keep this secret, this strawberry is yours.
Impressive as always, Ryuuzaki.
It might be better to try and blend in and get out of here.
No! Then me coming here would mean nothing.
Should I wait for everyone to go before searching the building?
But what if I get caught?
Maybe it's better if I leave...
Jeez, tonight again? I'm really not in the mood for this...
At least it's the weekend; if we had these drawn out secret meetings on a Monday, it'd be hard for me to bring myself to work.
Secret meetings?!
Bingo!
The nineteenth floor.
I've come this far...
I'm going to do this!
Okay, I've got to get close to this guy? Leave it to me.
So, you want me to hack the surveillance cameras and security system at Yotsuba Group's Tokyo Headquarters?
Yes.
It's safe to assume that there's definitely a connection between Kira and the Yotsuba Group.
First, we need to investigate Yotsuba, and determine exactly who, and how many, have this power.
Most importantly, we must ensure that the Yotsuba Group doesn't discover that we're investigating them.
Just consider that if you're caught, our chance of catching Kira will disappear then and there.
Damn it, I can't hear this clearly...
If I could just overhear one important thing...
He's just in our way... we should kill him and let our share prices rise...
They just said "kill"!
Kira-sama is really...
"Kira"?! They said "Kira"! They said it!
They're getting Kira to kill someone?
Yes! I heard it!!
They're definitely connected to Kira. I did it! What an achievement!!
Who the hell are you?!
Please, think ahead carefully before you act, and don't do anything rash.
Ryuuzaki.
What is it, Watari?
We've received a distress signal from Matsuda-san's belt.
Where from?
Well, it seems to be originating from Yotsuba Group's Tokyo Headquarters.
I-I'm Matsui Tarou, a manager at Yoshida Productions.
How would you like to hire our number one recommended, multi-talented star, Amane Misa, for your commercials?
Please, just forget everything I've just said.
We need to rethink our plan.
Matsuda, you idiot...
Yoshida Productions... Matsui Tarou...
He doesn't seem to have anything suspicious on him.
I doubt he's an industrial spy.
Yes... erm, I hope you will consider Misa-Misa...
These two are most likely keeping an eye on me, while the rest of them are in the meeting room, deciding how to dispose of me.
I'm as good as dead...
I wonder if they've received my distress signal?
I wonder if Ryuuzaki will bother to try and save me?
I wonder what's going to happen to me...
It's alright, you can answer that.
Just don't mention that you're here.
Also, hold the phone away from your ear so that we can listen in.
O-Okay.
Hello?
Yo, Matsui!
Ryuuzaki!!
It's Asahi, long time no talk.
Hey, Asahi, how's it going?
Doesn't sound like you're outside... you at home?
Err, yeah...
You alone?
Yeah, I'm alone. What's up?
He's not with Amane Misa, Matsuda is alone.
Fancy going out for a drink?
What? Now? Sorry, not tonight...
What, don't tell me your finances are in a pinch again?
"Pinch"?
Yeah, they're in quite a "pinch" at the moment. You got me!
Matsuda is in quite a pinch.
Never mind, another time then. See ya.
S-So, what do you think of Misa-Misa? I'm sure she'll be an asset to your company.
If you're serious about promoting her, shouldn't you have brought her here?
Are you really her manager?
Well, she's currently shooting a movie nearby, I'll call her over as soon as she's done.
Please consider using Misa-Misa as your image in your commercials.
For now, I've got to keep stalling!
Misa's phone is going straight to the answering machine.
I'll send a message telling her to call us.
What should we do, Ryuuzaki?
Let's see, if Matsuda-san dies now, it'll confirm the Yotsuba Group's guilt.
For the moment, let's just see what unfolds.
What shall we do?
It all depends on whether or not he overheard our discussion.
The possibility's there. There's no other choice than to kill him.
But is he really here merely to promote a "talent"? Surely he's not from the police?
That's impossible. The Japanese police should have abandoned the Kira investigation by now.
It doesn't matter who he is, we've got to kill him.
It's true that she might actually be a good image for us.
Don't you agree?!
Her shoot should finish soon, so please wait.
Jeez, I'm so tired...
Yay, a message from Light.
He must be worried about me, since it's so late.
Misa.
Light! I'm sorry, but I've been working all this time. I'm done now!
Misa, you're not with Matsuda-san then?
He's such a disgrace. He just abandoned Misa!
My work cell phone is ringing...
Huh? It's Matsu.
Matsuda-san is calling Misa.
Ask Misa-san to enable us to hear.
Misa-Misa, as soon as filming finishes, I need you to head over to the Yotsuba Group's Tokyo Headquarters.
You could get the chance to appear in their commercials.
Currently, I'm in the middle of negotiating a deal for you.
Oh, really?! That's amazing, Matsu! So that's what you were doing!
Misa will give it everything she got!
Okay, take a taxi, and you'll be here in no time.
Yagami-kun, we may be able to save Matsuda-san, but we will need Misa-san's help.
She'll listen to you.
Hi, I'm Misa-Misa!
Misa doesn't do nudes, but underwear or swimsuits are fine!
Pleased to meet you!
Hmm, she's ridiculously cute in the flesh...
Surely that's not the issue right now...
Matsu, the production company gave the go-ahead for a special reception especially for Yotsuba-san.
Huh? Special?
Good evening! Pleased to meet you!
Tonight, the girls from our production team would like to provide you all with a special reception!
Oi, I think we're starting to go off on a tangent here...
It can't be helped; for now, we've got to stay close to that manager.
So, we may as well enjoy ourselves.
Ryuuzaki and the others should be able to see us in here.
We might be saved.
Okay, drink up! Drink up!
This has got to be heaven!
Misa-san... she's not bad at this, is she?
Okay then...
I'm just going to the toilet.
Ryuuzaki, can you see me?
Yes.
I'm sorry, I--
Never mind about that now.
Right. The eight that are here were in a meeting together, planning who to have Kira murder.
I heard them clearly.
Without a doubt, it's them.
Are you absolutely sure?
If it's true, they'll be aiming to kill you.
I thought as much. Is there really no way to save me?
Luckily, you're still alive, so there's a chance that we can save you.
But to do that... you've got to die before you're killed.
Huh?!
Understand? Listen carefully...
What?!
No way...
That's stupid...
Say, Nagano-san...
In other words...
Really?!
Our company is still expanding...
Oh, I agree...
What's going on?!
Man, I'm so drunk...
I feel so good!
Hey, everyone! Are you all having fun? You should be!
Now everyone, this is what you've all been waiting for! It's Matsui Tarou Showtime!
Hey, what the hell do you think you're doing?
Yay! Go for it, Matsui-san!
Woo-aah!
Hey! That's dangerous! You're drunk!
It's fine, I do this all the time...
Cut it out!
That's dangerous, you idiot!!
I'm... fine...
H-He fell!!
This is bad...
Oh, no! I heard a huge bang and came out to see what happened...
119! 119!
119 is the emergency telephone number in Japan
God... what an awful role to play...
Leave this to us, gentlemen. Hurry up and get out of here!
Y-You sure?
We'll be fine. Please, keep me in mind for the commercial.
Hurry! If the paparazzi catch us, it'll be troublesome.
What, what's going on?! A jumper?!
Well, at least he died in front of us.
I know we're understaffed, but I can't believe I got dragged into this.
Matsuda, you idiot...
Amane Misa's manager, dead...
Yes?
Is this the Planning Director at Yotsuba Group's Tokyo Headquarters, Kida Masahiko?
Ah, that is correct. Who is this?
The name's Erald Coil.
I'd like your advice on a certain issue.
An advance of $2 million, and $8 million for a successful completion? Is he serious?!
On top of that, he's demanded $2 million for his silence if we don't go ahead with it.
Buying his silence, huh? It's best to assume that he already knows something.
This is getting too dangerous! I want out.
I've got no clue to which one of you is Kira, but I don't want to get too deep in this and end up being arrested!
Hatori... you're going to be dead tomorrow.
Wait, that was just a joke!
I'm in! I'll do this properly!
So, what're we gonna do? Even if Coil knows something, he's still willing to take it on.
As long as we give him the money, he's on our side. That's all there is to it.
We've got to keep a shrewd guy like him on our side.
You're right; it doesn't matter how much we've got to pay.
Yeah, that's right! Buy him off!
Okay, this contract with Coil, any objections?
No objections.
L, you listening?
What a disappointment. The security levels here are terrible.
All they've got is a contract with some security firm... not even any measures to detect bugging devices.
I-It's been a week since I infiltrated that place.
Somehow everything seems to be going brilliantly!
It's time...
Someone out of this lot is... Kira.
In that case, let's begin the meeting.
But there's only seven of them, instead of eight...
To be continued
Darenimo mirenai yume wo mita
I've had dreams that no one else could have.
Iranai mono wa subete suteta
I've thrown away everything that I don't need.
Yuzurenai omoi kono mune ni yadoshite
Those feelings I can't rid remain in my heart.
Even though I'm stuck between ideals and reality,
Mada real to ideal no hazama ni ite
and my legs are bound by the shackles of sacrifice.
Gesei no kase ni, ashi wo toraretemo
If I can hold back these overwhelming urges,
Afureru shoudou osaekireba
I still have a soul that yearns for more.
Tsuyoku motomeru kokora ga arukara
Itsuwari, Osore, Kyoshoku, Urei
Lies, fear, pretension, grief.
I'm not so weak,
Samazama na negative ni
that I'll become lost in these negative feelings.
Torawareru hodo yowaku wa nai
A trickster that doesn't know loneliness.
Kodoku mo shiranu trickster
Preview
Ryuuzaki! do you truly believe that after catching the current Kira, I'd go on to become Kira... A murderer?
Ryuuzaki... do you truly believe that after catching the current Kira, I'd go on to become Kira... A murderer?
Do you really see me as that kind of human being?!
Next Time
Makeshift