Edited at https://subtitletools.com
In the shadows that keep expanding, we exchange revolutionary vows.
Hirogaru yami no naka kawashiatta kakumei no chigiri
I won't let anyone get in my way
Dareni mo jama saseru wake ni wa ikanai kara
The recent past tells me of the future. My ideals become my dreams.
kajitsu ga tsugeta mirai. Yume, visou ni kaeru
The ending that everyone desires.
Daremo ga nozonda owari wo...
In the shadows that keep expanding, we exchange revolutionary vows.
Hirogaru yami no naka kawashiatta kakumei no chigiri
I won't let anyone get in my way
Dareni mo jama saseru wake ni wa ikanai
Itsuka boku ga misete ageru hikari no kagayaku sekai wo
Someday I'll show you a world that shines in the light.
Execution
I want you to continue disposing of criminals in this manner.
Once this is over, you can do whatever you want with this notebook.
That's the deal.
If everything goes according to Yagami Light's plan, this should save Misa...
This is a good deal for both you and me, don't you agree?
As you might say, "it's good business", right?
Imprisonment: Day Fifty
Yagami-san, you okay there?
You know, there's no need for you to continue doing this.
It's been more than a month since criminals began to be killed by Kira again.
I'm convinced my son is not Kira.
Now all that remains, Ryuuzaki, is for you to realize this too.
When I leave here, it will be with my son.
The Chief is so stubborn...
Light-kun, are you okay?
I'm okay... but Ryuuzaki... ever since my imprisonment, criminals have stopped dying...
there's a good chance that Kira or someone knows about my current predicament, it might be worth investigating alo--
No.
The reason they've stopped dying is because you are Kira.
That's not true!
I am not Kira!
How many times do I have to tell you this?!
If you're Kira you would know that criminals are being killed, yet I can't see this in you.
Ryuuzaki is pretty harsh. I can't believe he's not told Light-kun that criminals are still being murdered.
Amane.
Yes?
You don't look so good. Are you okay?
What? Are you stupid or something?
If Misa was fine after so many weeks of this, she'd be some kind of weirdo...
I guess you're right.
Hurry up and release me.
I want to see Light... Light... Light... Light...
It seems like all three of them are reaching their limits.
Ryuuzaki, why do you continue to detain Light-kun?!
You should release him.
That way the Chief will be free as well.
Despite neither Amane nor Light-kun receiving information about them, criminals continue to be killed.
Doesn't this tell you enough?!
No.
The only thing I've been able to establish is Amane's extraordinary love for Yagami Light.
Ryuuzaki... sorry, but personally,
I think you're only doing this because you don't want to accept that your "Light-kun is Kira" theory is wrong.
Oh, so you do think that after all...
It's as Light-kun said. Kira killed Lind L. Tailor and those FBI agents.
If they were able to kill without the need to acquire information, there would have been no need to kill Tailor or the FBI.
No matter how much they were investigated, they would never have been caught!
"Kira does not kill more than it's necessary to."
You said so yourself!
Oh, I see. If they could kill people under those conditions,
they could have left the FBI agents alone because they would pose no threat.
Fifty days have already passed.
There's no point in carrying on with this anymore.
Instead, we should be focusing on capturing the real Kira.
I understand...
Yagami-san?
What is it?
Could I get you to return to Headquarters?
I'd like everyone to hear my verdict on this matter.
I'd like you, Yagami-san, as Light-kun's father, to be the first.
Fine...
Three days later
I never imagined you would be such an old man, Stalker-san.
I'm not a stalker, I'm a detective.
Detective?!
I remember now!
At the beginning, they mentioned something about "suspicion of being the second Kira"!
They were actually serious about that?!
Surely not... the police would never tie me up like a maniac.
Besides, if you're releasing me, isn't it a little odd to keep my hands and feet cuffed?
Silence.
Light!!
Misa.
Light! I wanted to see you so much!
Father, what's going on?
Huh? Father?!
Oh no! Misa called Light's dad a stalker and lots of other rude things!
Pleased to meet you! I'm Amane Misa.
I'm going out with Li--
Take them away, Chief.
What's wrong? Hurry up and get in.
I guess this means we're no longer under suspicion and finally free.
No.
I'm going to be taking you two to the execution chamber.
I volunteered to escort you to a top-secret execution chamber in an underground facility.
Execution chamber?!
What?!
What are you saying?! Father?!
You're joking, right, dad?!
L has concluded that Yagami Light is Kira and Amane Misa is the second Kira,
and if we dispose of both of you, the "Kira killings" will end.
The "Kira killings" should have stopped already...
No, they're still taking place.
Still taking place?! That's not what they told me...
It was most likely an investigative technique L was using in order to get you to confess.
But that's not the point...
L's proposal of killing both of you, thereby stopping the "Kira killings",
was quickly accepted by all the heads of the United Nations and the Government.
Kira will be executed in secret, away from the public eye.
T-That's stupid! Father! I am not Kira!!
That's right, dad!
What are you thinking?! He's you own son!
It wasn't my decision, it was L's decision.
He's solved all sorts of impossible problems in the past, and he's yet to be proved wrong.
Father... you're believing L over me?
L has even said that if the murders don't stop, he will take full responsibility for it, and pay with his life.
L, what are you thinking?!
It's true that given all the evidence acquired up till now, the conclusion seems inevitable... but there's been a mistake!
L, how did he come to such a conclusion?
There's something wrong here... this isn't like L at all.
Up until now, he's always been able to offer solid proof when he solves a case... is he going to end it all just like this?
We've arrived.
Where are we?
What are you planning to do, bringing us to such a remote area?
Dad! Is it possible that you're planning to release us?!
Yes, no matter what we do here, no one will see it.
I deliberately brought both of you here instead of the execution chamber.
Light... I'm going to kill you here, and then I'll kill myself.
What are you saying, father?! Don't be stupid!
Stop it! Dad! You're crazy!!
You're going to kill your own child and then yourself?!
If you want to die, then just die by yourself!
If you go through with this, then you're no different from Kira!
No, I'm different from Kira.
I have responsibilities, both as a parent, and also as the Chief of Police.
Father, it's exactly as Misa says!
Even if we die here, they still won't know the truth!
If that's the case, it's better to run!
It's too late, Light.
Whatever path you choose, you will be executed, and if that's the case, at least it will be by my hand.
Stop it, father! I'm not Kira!!
If I die here, it'll be exactly what Kira wants! Don't you see that?!
Amane, my son and I will die here, but I have no reason to kill you.
The police will probably find this car soon, and then you can be executed at the formal execution chamber.
Light... we're both murderers; see you in hell!
Father!!
Stop!!
Light... we're both murderers; see you in hell!
Father!!
...a blank?
Thank god...
What do you mean, "Thank god"? What are you doing, father?
Both of you, forgive me.
This was the sole method of freeing you.
But, believe me, I only did this because I truly believe that you are not Kira.
Were you watching that, Ryuuzaki?
I did exactly like you asked, and as you can see, I'm still alive.
Yes, it was a very realistic performance.
If Amane was truly the second Kira and could kill purely by looking at someone,
I'm sure we can assume she would have killed Yagami-san before he shot Light-kun.
And if Light-kun was Kira, the way I have imagined Kira to be, they would kill even a parent if necessary.
However, in Light-kun's case, I can't dismiss the possibility that he may have figured out that it was an act at some point.
But, as promised, I'll end their imprisonment.
And also as promised... Amane Misa, although you may insist that those tapes are occult videos,
due to your confession that you sent them, and other points of evidence,
you will remain under surveillance until Kira is caught, and everything is resolved.
What's up with that? Are you still suspicious of me?!
Well, you can return to your everyday life. Isn't that enough?
As long as you're innocent, all surveillance means, is that you'll be protected by the police.
Oh, really? Well, since Misa isn't the second Kira, she just has to think of it as having a bodyguard!
Also, Light-kun, as promised, I'm prepared to make a pact with you;
that is, you'll be with me 24/7 assisting me with this investigation.
I understand, Ryuuzaki. Together we'll catch Kira.
Yes, I'll be counting on you.
Is it really necessary to go this far, Ryuuzaki?
You know, I'm not doing this because I want to.
Eh? This is what you meant by being with each other 24/7?!
You're both guys, it's kinda creepy...
So, you lean that way, Ryuuzaki-san?
Look, I said I'm not doing this because I want to.
But Light is Misa's Light after all, and if you're around 24 hours a day, when is Misa supposed to go on dates?
Unavoidably, when you go on a date, it'll be the three of us together.
What?! Does that mean we have to kiss and stuff in front of you?!
I didn't say you had to.
But I will have to maintain surveillance.
What's with that?! You're a pervert after all!!
Light-kun, please get Misa-san to shut up.
Misa, stop being selfish over this.
Given that they can prove you sent those tapes in, you should be thankful for being released.
Huh? Even you are saying this?
Misa is your girlfriend! Don't you believe in your own girlfriend?
You say that you're my girlfriend... but you've just been chasing me around saying that you fell in love with me at first sight...
So, when I said, "I love you", you just took advantage of that to kiss me?
Jerk! Jerk! Jerk! Je-erk!!
Regarding you "falling in love at first sight", that happened on the 22nd of May in Aoyama, right, Misa-san?
Yes?
On that day, why did you go to Aoyama?
What clothes were you wearing?
Look, I just went on a whim. How many times do you want me to say this?
I honestly can't remember how I was feeling, or what I was wearing that day.
Is it that wrong of Misa to hang around Aoyama without a reason?
So, when you returned home from Aoyama, you knew Light-kun's name, someone you had just fallen in love with at first sight...
Yes.
Yet, you have no idea as to how you knew his name?
Yes. That's right.
So, what if Light-kun is Kira? Then what would you think?
Eh? If Light is Kira?
Yes.
That'd be amazing.
Misa has always been really grateful to Kira for passing judgement on the murderer that killed Misa's parents.
If Light was Kira, I'd love him even more!
Although, I couldn't possibly love you more than I do now.
We're talking about Kira here... "I'd love him even more", don't you think that's scary?
We're talking about if Light was Kira, right? That wouldn't be scary at all!
I'm a Kira supporter, so I would try to think up ways to help him, rather than be afraid.
You may get in his way, but I doubt that you'd be able to help him...
With this being the case, it's unmistakable that the second Kira is Misa-san, but...
it seems so obvious. Somehow I don't want to believe it.
You'd be correct not to believe it. 'Cause Misa is not Kira!
Anyway, we'll be placing you under surveillance.
When you want to go out, please contact us in this room by using the private line.
We've paid your agency so that from now on, whether it's at work or during your own personal time,
Matsuda-san can accompany you as your manager, Manager Matsui, at all times.
Hi, I'm Matsui. Yahoo!
The police have yet to be informed, so please ensure that you don't reveal this.
I don't want this old man as my manager.
No way! What's so unsatisfactory about me, Misa-Misa?!
Talk of homos? Dates? Kisses? "Misa-Misa"?! Will you all kindly behave yourselves?!
This is about the Kira investigation! Will you take it seriously?!
S-Sorry...
No... I'm sorry, I know you're taking this seriously.
Come on, Amane, go to your own room.
Aaww...
Don't you "aaww" me.
Light! Even if it's got to be the three of us, let's go on a date, okay?
Light-kun, are you serious about Amane?
Erm, no. It's like I said before, it's kind of one-sided...
Well, could you please act as if you're serious about her?
Given the incident with the video tapes, it's clear that she has some sort of connection with the second Kira.
Also, it's clear that she loves you.
Are you telling me to get close to her so that we can find out about the second Kira?
Yes. I think you would be able to manage that.
Having you draw out the beginnings of an answer from Amane, was one of the main reasons I released both of you.
Ryuuzaki... even if it's for the sake of solving the Kira investigation,
there's no way I can bring myself to use a girl's emotions like that.
I'm sorry, but please to try understand this.
For me, walking all over someone's goodwill is one of the worst things you can ever do, it's something that I can't forgive.
There's definitely something strange going on... I can only imagine that somehow, his personality changed.
Is it even possible to just act like this?
I can only assume that not only was Amane Misa being manipulated by Kira, but so was Yagami Light.
What's wrong, Ryuuzaki?
Oh, nothing. You're right, Light-kun.
However, it'd help me a lot if you could ensure that she doesn't reveal anything about this investigation, given its secrecy.
Ryuuzaki, is it possible to change this system of moving hotels every few days?
Yes, I've been thinking about doing so since the start.
So, from the moment I met Yagami-san and the others, and decided to take this case, I commenced construction.
It'll be completed in a few days.
This is it.
Twenty-three floors high with two basement levels.
It's constructed in such a way that you can't observe the roof from the outside, and there are two helicopters housed within it.
Incredible!
As much as possible, I'd like everyone to live here.
Even if we choose to increase the number of people on the investigation, it can accommodate at least 60.
Surely Misa-san won't complain if we give her an entire floor.
At any rate, this is amazing! To have gone this far...
In fact, Ryuuzaki, where did you get the money for this?
I'll do whatever it takes to solve this case, that's what it means.
You didn't actually answer the question...
Yeah, you're right.
Of course, for being a mass murderer, and for what he's put my father and me through, I can't let Kira get away with this.
I'll do whatever it takes to solve this.
Well, if you'll "do whatever it takes", why don't you get close to Misa-san and try t--
No, not that. That's going against my honor.
Is that so? It's a pity...
Oh, nothing. I'm just getting really psyched about this.
Ryuuzaki, Yagami-san, Light-kun, let's ensure that we catch Kira, no matter what.
Umm.. you didn't mention my name?
Looks like everyone is here.
Well, let's begin the meeting.
In order to further our company's activities and make Yotsuba the greatest enterprise in the world...
who do we need to kill?
Having someone killed every week is pretty serious.
But why has Kira moved from solely passing judgment on criminals to undertaking assassinations?
Takahashi, don't tell me you have yet to realize it?
It's because this will benefit Kira, of course.
Benefit Kira?
Are you telling me that Kira has become an assassin, Higuchi?
If I were you, I'd shut it more.
If you're too stupid, you could get killed.
All eight of us here are still young,
but it's rumored that all of us are capable of going for the company presidency in the near future.
In reality, since we started these meetings, out salaries have multiplied to several times the salary of a regular employee.
It just seems really strange to me that Kira would give their backing to a single enterprise.
However I think about it, it can only mean that out of the eight of us, one of us is... Kira.
Ooi Takeshi
Takahashi Eiichi
Kida Masahiko
Higuchi Kyosuke
Namikawa Reiji
Shimura Suguru
Misou Shino
Hatori Arayoshi
Getting back on topic, does anyone have any suggestions?
Who should we kill for our own profit?
Humans truly are... such ugly creatures...
To be continued
Darenimo mirenai yume wo mita
I've had dreams that no one else could have.
I've thrown away everything that I don't need.
Iranai mono wa subete suteta
Those feelings I can't rid remain in my heart.
Yuzurenai omoi kono mune ni yadoshite
Even though I'm stuck between ideals and reality,
Mada real to ideal no hazama ni ite
and my legs are bound by the shackles of sacrifice.
Gesei no kase ni, ashi wo toraretemo
If I can hold back these overwhelming urges,
Afureru shoudou osaekireba
Tsuyoku motomeru kokora ga arukara
I still have a soul that yearns for more.
Lies, fear, pretension, grief.
Itsuwari, Osore, Kyoshoku, Urei
I'm not so weak,
Samazama na negative ni
Torawareru hodo yowaku wa nai
that I'll become lost in these negative feelings.
Kodoku mo shiranu trickster
A trickster that doesn't know loneliness.
Preview
This is no good... the way you're talking, it sounds like you won't be satisfied unless I really am Kira.
Don't fuck with me, Ryuuzaki!
Next Time
Ally