Edited at https://subtitletools.com
We've always been this to free all the pain
Banzai, you're so useful!
Benri benri banzai
Human!
ningen
Benri benri banzai
Banzai, you're so useful!
ningen
Human!
Hey! You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
Hora BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
Ningen
Human!
Hora BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
Hey! You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
You gonna piss me off, make me tremble with rage?
BIRIBIRI ikarasu ka?
Human!
Ningen
WHAT'S UP
What's up? So much ground for concern; the guilt never fades.
fuanzai ippai hanzai kienai towa ni
WHAT'S UP
What's up? So much ground for concern!
fuanzai ippai
Who fell down the trap of resentment?
urami ni wana, dare daun
WHAT'S UP
What's up? So much ground for concern; the guild never fades.
fuanzai ippai hanzai kienai towa ni
WHAT'S UP
What's up? So much ground for concern!
fuanzai ippai
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
A-A human... human fucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Ningen SUCKER!
Human sucker!
Aa ningen... ningen FUCKER!
A-A human... human fucker!
HEY HEY!
Human sucker!
Ningen SUCKER!
WHAT'S UP PEOPLE?!
What's the matter, Ryuuzaki?
What is it?
Silence
The corner of a page in this murderer's notebook appears to have been torn off.
Would a person still die if their name was written on the torn-off part?
Who knows? I've never used it that way, so I wouldn't know.
So, is it true that Shinigami only eat apples?
That's not true.
But a Shinigami's internal organs are retrogressive.
No, in fact, they've evolved such that we no longer need to eat.
Yagami-kun.
You've finally been freed, and yet you never leave this place.
Even when Misa-san comes to see you, you only chat for a few minutes.
When I said that you're free to take your romance outside now, I meant it.
The Kira case is far from over.
Right now, I'm hardly in the mood for romance.
Or are you saying that you've got a problem with me always being here?
No...
Right now, I'm not in a position where I can judge criminals.
Misa, I want you to judge them.
Misa... let's build a new world, together.
ki o tsukete
Take care,
kamisama wa miteru
God is watching you.
In the dark streets of the night
kurai yomichi wa
please hold his hand.
te o tsunaide kudasai
Even if I'm on my own far away,
hitori de tooku ni ite mo
itsumo mitsukedashite kureru
he will always find me.
shitteru koto wa zenbu oshiete kureru
He tells me all I know,
watashi ga oboete nakute mo
and even if I forget,
he tells me time and time again.
nando demo oshiete kureru
demo zenbu wakatte shimattara dou sureba ii no...
But what will I do once I've learned everything?
What's the meaning of this?!
There are more criminals being killed?!
Yesterday alone, there was 16...
All of them were broadcast as criminals after Higuchi's death.
It's just one after the other...
I guess this means that Higuchi wasn't Kira after all...
No. We know for a fact that until Higuchi was captured, he was the one judging criminals.
So, you're saying that yet another Kira has made an appearance?
Why?!
Damn you, Kira!
Kira... now?
What's going on?
I don't believe this...
Misa is the only possibility!
This began the instant Amane was freed.
Ryuuzaki, I can't believe you're still saying that.
Misa has nothing to do with this.
If we're talking about "the instant" this started, that was when Higuchi died.
That's true.
Well, in any case, if there is someone out there using a second notebook...
We'll definitely catch that person.
The Shinigami said she didn't know, but if it's possible to kill someone using paper torn out from the notebook... it's not impossible.
But once someone writes a name in this notebook, they need to write another name within 13 days or they'll die.
Yagami Light and Amane Misa are still alive...
13 days... this is the only...
But Ryuuzaki, even if we manage to catch the person who's writing names in the notebook,
will you actually be able to charge them of mass murder and get a conviction?
Of course! They wrote a lot of people's names in the notebook knowing that those people would die as a result!
If we can't make the notebook public knowledge like that, we should obliterate them!
Obliteration isn't the calmest solution to the problem.
I guess the higher-ups will opt for a solution similar to that though.
If we can prove the murders resulted from the notebook, it'll be the death penalty, or at the very least, life imprisonment.
That's more or less how it goes.
What are you thinking, Yagami Light?!
If Misa gets caught, then you'll--
So, that's it! This guy is unbelievable!
Yagami Light is certain that I'll save Misa's life.
In this situation, the only way to save Misa is to write Ryuuzaki's real name in my own notebook.
And if I kill Ryuuzaki... I'll undeniably have interfered with Misa's lifespan, and will also die.
This is all set up for the benefit of Yagami Light!
So, what will you do, Rem?
Despite the fact that you're a Shinigami, I know you're into Misa.
There's no way you'll stand by and let Misa die after her lifespan has just been halved again.
Think of Misa's happiness.
What are you doing out here, Ryuuzaki?
What are you doing, Ryuuzaki?
Ah, it's nothing worth mentioning.
The sound of bells...
Bells?
Yes, the bells sound incredibly noisy today.
I don't hear anything.
Oh, really?
They've been ringing incessantly today; I can't stop thinking about it.
Maybe there's a wedding at a church, or maybe...
What are you talking about, Ryuuzaki?
Stop talking nonsense. Let's go inside.
Sorry. Everything I say is made up on the spot, so please don't believe a word of it.
You're right, Ryuuzaki. The majority of what you say isn't true.
If I took it all seriously, there'd be no end to it.
I know that better than anyone else.
That's true, Light-kun.
But... the same applies to you.
What do you mean?
Have you ever uttered a single completely true thing since you were born?
What are you talking about, Ryuuzaki?
Certainly I lie every now and then, but surely no one can be truthful throughout their entire life?
People aren't that perfect.
Everyone lies.
But even so, I've made a point of not telling lies that will hurt others.
That's my answer.
I thought you'd say that.
Let's go back inside. We're both soaked.
Yeah.
Wow. That was quite an ordeal, wasn't it?
It's all your fault for being out in that downpour.
True. I'm sorry.
What are you doing, Ryuuzaki?!
I thought I'd help. You seem to be drying yourself with quite some fervor.
It's fine. You don't have to do something like that.
I'll throw in a massage?
At least allow me to atone for this. I'm not at all bad at it, you know.
Do as you please.
Okay.
Hey.
You'll get used to it quickly.
You're still wet.
Sorry...
Sad, isn't it?
Huh?
It's nearly time to say farewell.
Yes? Understood, I'll be there straight away.
Shall we go then, Light-kun?
Seems like things have gone well.
Ryuuzaki, what's the meaning of this?!
You've got permission from a ruined country to use the notebook in an execution?!
Watari, good job.
No problem.
Please begin the arrangements to transport the notebook at once.
Yes.
Ryuuzaki! What's going on?!
We're going to test the notebook for real.
This is absurd! There's no need to do this now.
We already know that the power of the notebook is real.
Besides, who is going to write the name?
Once you do, you have to write in it every 13 days for the rest of your life!
The person who will write the name in the notebook... will be someone who's already been sentenced to die within 13 days.
We'll do a probationary deal, saying that if they're alive after 13 days, they'll be removed from death row.
But... people's lives--
It's just a little further!
If we manage to clarify this, it'll take us straight to the solution.
Huh?! W-What's happening?! A power cut?
Watari?
Watari?!
Deletion of data? What's happening?
I instructed Watari to delete all the data if something were to happen to him.
"If something were to happen to him"?
Don't tell me...
Where's the Shinigami?
Now that you mention it... I can't see her.
She's not here!
What does this mean?
Everyone, the Shiniga--
Ryuuzaki!! What's wrong?!
Oi, Ryuuzaki? What's the matter? Get a hold of yourself!
What?!
What happened?!
Calm down, Light!
We're going to be killed!
Watari, Ryuuzaki... and now us!
Fuck! Where's that Shinigami?! Show yourself!!
L-Light...
You must know something about this! Show yourself!
We should look as well.
Mogi, we'll leave the rest to you.
Understood.
Everyone! Get over here!
W-What the hell is this?!
Sand?
What's going on?
Whatever it is, whatever's going on here... I will avenge Ryuuzaki's death.
Solving this case is the only way to bid him farewell.
For Watari, and the other victims too... for everyone.
Light...
That's right, Light-kun.
B-But we'll be killed! Isn't that what this has been about?
Matsuda-san, if you're scared of being killed, then I suggest you leave.
This team is composed of men willing to give their lives.
Erm, well, I guess you're right... but don't say it how Ryuuzaki would, Light-kun.
All my obstacles have been removed.
I am the god of a new world.
To be continued
This one page of everlasting depression;
Towa ni utsu kono ichi peeji
a fleeting tactic in your eyes.
hakanai senpou sono meni
Let's intertwine evil with law, pass no plea and go to jail.
Aigan sezumo hou ni aku tsunagou rou he
Nooto ni moudoku bonnou ni osore idaku
Deadly poison within the Note harbors fears of carnal desires.
Oouso no mousou ni yodare ga taema naku
Incessant drool at false fantasies;
judgment; never-ending talk of uniting crime.
sabaki hanzai toukatsu to hozaku
Dare ga dakaisaku nodo wakaru?
Who would know of a path to salvation?
World of acquittal,
Menzai no waarudo
seisai no waado
words of retribution!
Eru netsu masani "desu paireetsu"
This fire I feel, I truly am a Death pirate!
Aganau houritsu geemu
Redeem the game of law!
Despair the Billy,
Zetsubou za birii
iza rinri
here are the morals!
Come, relentless eraser rain.
Saa tomerarenai eraser rain
Zetsubou za birii
Despair the Billy,
iza rinri
here are the morals!
Come, relentless eraser rain.
Saa tomerarenai eraser rain
tomerarenai eraser rain
relentless eraser rain.
Preview
Ryuuzaki... Watari... Rem... all my obstacles have been removed.
I am the god of a new world.
Next Time
Reincarnation