Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Doing things that bring attention to myself...
That is what I, Yoshikage Kira, hate the most.
And to think that I'm experiencing this
humiliation in front of total strangers...
To think that the invincible auto-pilot
Heart Attack would get caught...
Damn... I have to undo this spell somehow...
Hey, mister. You okay?
You sick or something?
Want me to call your mommy?
It's nothing. Get lost.
Hey, hey, hey, did you hear that?
You seeing some sweet dreams during the
day after drinking too much, mister?
Is it fun? Does it feel good?
Grasp
That's a nice suit you've got on.
We've been fired and don't have any money.
We can't even get any bitches.
Seeing guys like you piss me off.
At least try to defend yourself.
Hey, mister. Your shoelaces are untied.
I'll tie them for you.
A square knot! That's super nice of you!
H-Hey, what's wrong?
Deadly Queen's first bomb.
It turns anything it touches into a bomb.
Th-The doctor! Call the doctor!
What a terrible day.
Get me a doctor!
I just want to live a quiet life,
and yet I had to deal with those
two pieces of trash today...
Diamond is Unbreakable
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 24     Heart Attack, Part 2
Hey, Josuke.
What the heck happened at Centipede Shoes?
I don't really know, but it wasn't good.
Hurry! It'll take about five minutes.
There are cracks in it.
That means the actual Stand's
been damaged, too, right?
Please don't go too far away from me.
My range is five meters.
Act 3's is five meters.
We have matured.
We're even more powerful now.
It can't be helped that my
range is shorter than Act 2's.
5 Meters
If you move more than five meters from me,
Gravity
the weight on that thing will disappear.
It'll stop struggling and regain its vigor,
and rush toward us like a dog in heat.
On the other hand, the closer you get to it,
the heavier I can make it.
What would you like to do?
N-No... This distance is plenty.
I hope Josuke gets here soon.
Apparently, a gym will be opening
near Budogaoka High School soon.
I was really considering
getting a membership.
I have to gain more stamina.
But I wonder if I'll be
lifting the same dumbbells
who've been playing with their dicks
after not bathing for a week,
or getting in the same pool with them.
It took me three minutes to get here.
I felt my lack of stamina the most
when I tried to cross at the crosswalk.
By the way, who's going to show up here?
You called someone for help, didn't you?
Josuke Higashikata and Okuyasu
Nijimura live the closest.
It'll take them about five minutes,
so two minutes to go?
You're their friend, aren't you?
H-H...
Yukako Yamagishi and the woman
who runs Salon Cinderella are also
what you call Stand users, aren't they?
You wouldn't actually call
a lady for help, would you?
H-He's...
I left my jacket with the button behind.
I'll go get it later...
After I'm done with you.
H-He's... right in front of me!
This man...
The one who killed all those people
over all those years...
And Reimi and Shigechi...
Let him have it, Act 3!
Dogyuun
Deadly Queen!
Why does he have two Stands?
I thought a user could only have one Stand!
Heart Attack is a tracer bomb that was
launched from Deadly Queen's left hand.
That's why the damage
is only in my left hand.
Warning, Sir Koichi.
You have just left my range of five meters.
The bomb Stand's weight will disappear.
S-h-i-t. I'll have to attack
it with 3 Freeze again.
I see... Range, eh?
Who would you like me to hit?
The actual murderer,
or that shitty bomb Stand?
3 Freeze cannot make two
things heavy at once.
Even if we make the user heavier,
the bomb Stand is on
auto-pilot, so it won't stop.
Even if we make the bomb heavier,
the user will come after me.
Which will it be?
Please hurry and give me orders.
Which one are you going to attack?
S-Stop the bomb!
3 Freeze!
Ker-bam-bam
It appears that, no matter who you attacked,
you were still fated to lose.
However, to think that Heart Attack,
which I thought had no weak points,
would be completely useless...
I had to pay some expenses at the café,
then ended up in a scuffle with some
hooligans. I feel like I've been had.
This is the first time
I've ever felt so cornered.
I even feel a slight sense of defeat.
Goodness. I must show you some respect.
You're rather impressive.
By the way, do you have any pocket tissues?
A handkerchief would work, too.
Hm? I've shown you some respect.
The least you can do is talk to me.
I don't... have any.
Then, here. Use mine.
A lot of blood is coming from your nose, right?
It's just so you can wipe that off.
I'm about to beat you to death.
I have a little over a minute
before your friends get here.
Otherwise, I just won't be satisfied after
having to face such humiliation in public.
Now, now, stop screaming
in such a weird way.
I endured the same pain you feel now
as I was heading over here, but I didn't scream.
You're a boy, aren't you?
You should take after me.
See? You need some tissues now, don't you?
I'll wipe it for you.
They say your brain slows down
when your nose is stuffed up.
But you know, I was on the ground
a little while ago, too, just like you.
I'll blow you away with
Deadly Queen in another minute.
Until then, you need to be like
me and just endure the pain.
You need to be like me!
Y-Your name...
is Yoshikage Kira...
Yoshikage Kira is your real name...
My driver's license!
When did you take it out of my wallet?
You little brat...
You said you paid some expenses
at the café earlier, right?
That's when I had an idea.
So what?
What do you gain from knowing my name?
You're about to be erased.
Yeah, you're about to kill me.
But even I was able to figure out your name.
You're not that big a deal.
You might get away for now,
but how do you feel?
A little brat like me managed
to find out what your name was.
I'll say it again.
A little brat found you out!
You're a complete idiot!
I'll be looking forward to
seeing you in the next world!
You bastard!
Damn it! What is this sense of defeat?!
Re
Rev
Rever
Reverb
Reverb A
Reverb Ac
Reverb Act
Reverb Act 3
Ko
Koichi
Koichi Hiro
Koichi Hirose
What an infuriating little brat.
I still have a minute before
Josuke and Okuyasu show up.
And I was trying to beat the crap
out of him to calm myself down.
He's got his socks on inside-out.
Doesn't that bug him?
Ugh, it sure bugs me!
Not that way, Okuyasu!
But Centipede Shoes is this way.
If we go this way, we'll get
there in a minute! Hurry up!
Wear them properly.
Now I can finally relax.
And now I can blow you to kingdom come!
Deadly Queen!
The tip of this finger can
turn anything into a bomb.
I guess, in your case, I'll make
your student badge a bomb.
The first bomb!
Koichi, you were winning against
that man psychologically.
What?!
Well, this is a surprise.
I never thought you'd be able
to stand with those wounds...
However, you would have been much
better off if you had stayed down.
I can almost see the view behind
you through your wounds.
That's a nice watch.
But I'll break it so you can never
see the time on it again...
By that, I mean I'll break your face.
You seem like quite an interesting fellow.
I'd love to learn your name,
as well as various other things,
but I must take my leave.
I only have twenty seconds left.
I don't have time for idle chit-chat.
Your Stand just now was very weak.
I was easily able to catch it, like a pop-up.
Do you really think you can defeat
my Deadly Queen with so little power?
Smash
Wh—
H-He's fast...
Wh-What's with this speed?
Upon closer inspection...
Good grief, what an ugly watch.
But you won't have to worry
about that anymore...
Because your face is going to end up
even uglier.
What is this Stand?
It's so fast, it's like it stopped time!
Koichi, if it weren't for you,
I would have been dead.
You did well fighting all by yourself.
You have my respect, Koichi.
You've matured.
Hey, Koichi!
Koichi!
Wh-What the heck happened here?
K-Koichi! Jotaro!
Be careful, Okuyasu.
What the heck happened?! Jotaro! Koichi!
Calm down. I need to find out
if Koichi is alive or not.
If he's alive, I can fix his
wounds with Shining Diamond.
Yes! Jotaro is alive! Just barely, though.
K-Koichi's alive, too.
But he's not breathing!
Hurry! Hurry up and fix him, Josuke!
Hey, he's not waking up at all!
But I've already fixed him up.
This is awful... Josuke and Okuyasu are here.
He's hurt really bad!
It's gonna take a while for
him to regain consciousness.
What a day... I've never had
such an awful day in my life.
I have always been able to
get through any dilemma...
I'm going to get away, no matter what.
What are you doing?
Hey, he's awake.
Hey, don't try anything funny.
Turn this way slowly. Show us your face!
Be careful! Don't go to Centipede Shoes!
There's going to be some crazy explosion!
The owner just suddenly came flying out!
Those two, too!
An explosion?
H-Hey, calm down. Were you caught in the blast?
I'm just an office employee.
But now I'm going to die...
Look at all this blood.
I-It hurts!
H-Hey, calm down. It's all right now.
I'll patch you up.
Where did you get hurt?
I think one of my ribs might
have punctured my lung.
H-Hurry up and fix me, please!
Hurry?
Oh? No matter how you look at me,
I just look like a high school student,
so why would you ask me to fix you?
I have trouble just getting
into pachinko parlors,
yet I look like some doctor who
graduated from med school to you?
You totally fell for it.
You saw my Shining Diamond, didn't you?
Crap... I got too impatient.
Which means you're the enemy.
This was a draw.
Th-This guy's the murderer?!
I guess this means I've lost.
Yes, the one you're all looking for is me.
My face has been seen,
my Stand has been seen,
and my name has been discovered.
It appears I won't be able to
sleep peacefully anymore...
But only tonight!
Deadly Queen!
What the hell are you doing?!
Exactly what it looks like. I cut it off.
I-It hurts... It's so painful,
and I'm bleeding a lot.
I'm even crying.
But winning or losing means nothing to me.
I'm going to survive.
I'm going to survive in peace.
I have to live with the fate of being
unable to fight the urge to kill people,
but I will live happily!
Heart Attack, you are free!
I leave the rest to you.
Protect me.
What the hell is that wimpy-looking thing?
Josuke, that's a bomb Stand
that goes after body heat!
And it won't break!
It's going to explode in reaction
to your body temperature!
It won't break?
Break?
You've got it backwards. I fixed it.
If that guy left it behind...
This is a pretty gross idea, but that
hand is heading toward the murderer.
Let's go after it!
Yeah!
You're not getting away that easily, dumbass!
H-Hey, look at that...
Now I'll be able to sleep peacefully...
K-Kira? Why is your face all bloody?
Hello, everyone. Is it
already time to head home?
I'm in a hurry, so I'll be seeing you.
The murderer's name is Yoshikage Kira.
His address is Morioh Kotodai 1-128.
He's 33 years old.
His Stand is a short-ranged
bomb Stand, Deadly Queen!
Hey, where is that guy headed?
It doesn't matter where
he's headed. He's finished!
He's in this building.
Hey, wait... This is...
Salon Cinderella!
What's he doing here?!
A-Aya! Are you here?
Dr. Aya Tsuji!
A-Aya's...
Aya's...
What is this? What the hell is this?!
He's dead... Why is Yoshikage Kira dead?
Aya!
Th-This is...
What the hell happened?
Wait! That man isn't Yoshikage Kira!
He has his left hand!
Huh?
He d-doesn't have a face!
What?!
He's missing his fingerprints on his
right hand, too. Who is this guy?
Guy...
He's wearing the same suit...
He brought in that guy,
and killed him in front of me.
He's too terrifying...
He made me switch his face using Cinderella.
And his hair and fingerprints, by force...
So he's someone else now?
Yes...
H-His face...
Shining Diamond!
H-His...
Josuke, don't touch her! Get away from there!
His face...
Aya!
On the other side of that door!
You're not getting away, damn it!
Th-This is...
I-It's time for everyone to go home...
S-So many...
Wh-Which one is he?
Which one is Yoshikage Kira?!
Yoshikage Kira, you coward! Show yourself!
He managed to get away.
He's not going to be quivering, or hiding.
He's not even going to leave Morioh.
He's going to live his life in
this town, like he always has.
Aya Tsuji: dead.
Aya Tsuji: Dead
Yoshikage Kira Changes His Face, Name, and Address,
Becoming a Different Person
Yoshikage Kira changes his face, name,
and address, becoming a different person.
Episode 25
Heart Father