Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hello, Kawajiri residence.
July 16th (Fri)  7:57 AM
Huh? No, it's not.
I see. Well done, Hayato.
You protected me from that nuisance, Rohan.
I'm telling you that you
have the wrong number.
Goodbye.
Now, then...
They had the wrong number.
I guess I'll head to work so I can make
my precious family happy.
But first, do you mind if
I give you a goodbye kiss?
Huh?
What are you doing?! My precious teapot...
Why would you do that?!
I never know what you're thinking!
You never even answer me! Why?!
Honestly...
Mom, he's not human.
If I say anything about him to anyone,
they'll be blown away,
and the morning will reset.
If we just keep letting him do what he wants,
it might not happen now, but he'll
eventually kill me and my mom.
R-Rohan Kishibe...
There was someone other than
Kira who had abilities.
I have to do something about Rohan Kishibe.
The only one who can save me
and my mom and defeat Kira
is someone with abilities like Rohan Kishibe!
Th-There he is. It's Rohan.
If I meet Rohan, he'll be
blown away and die...
And then I'll repeat the same morning again.
I have to tell Rohan about
him without meeting him.
I'm going to change fate!
Flip
Wh-What is this?!
[Warning]
You mustn't read any further.
It's Rohan's ability that he
used one me the last morning!
Damn it.
I was hiding from Rohan this time!
Rohan didn't even see me!
Once fate has happened,
it can't be changed...
Hayato.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
July 16th (Fri)  8:27 AM
Episode 36      Bites the Dust, Part 2
Ugh, the forecast didn't
say it was going to rain!
You seem to be under the impression that
you purposely broke the teapot,
but that is incorrect.
Whatever broke last morning
will break again, no matter what.
It'll happen because it's meant to be.
That is what fate is.
If you were turned into a book last morning,
you'll turn into a book, no matter what.
This is why Deadly Queen
Bites the Dust is invincible.
It erases my identity and returns
everything else to what it was.
That means I get to observe Rohan
exploding before I head to work.
At 8:27 AM,
lightning struck
above the Pepsi sign.
It rained.
I can't let Rohan die!
I have to save Rohan!
Ah, Rohan Kishibe.
Watch carefully.
He has no idea why he's dying right now.
I wonder if he's thinking about how he
won't be able to draw his manga anymore.
R-Rohan...
N-No!
Hayato, the very fact that you
met Rohan will disappear,
and the morning will continue on.
If I undo Bites the Dust right now,
Rohan's death will just become
fact and not repeat again...
But for now, I won't undo it.
A few of his friends should
also be showing up, after all.
You're going to automatically
defeat them for me, as well.
Just like a landmine.
But Bites the Dust won't cause you any harm,
so you should relax and enjoy
your fun life as a young boy.
Well, I have to head to the station.
Make sure you study hard.
It's all my fault. It's because he met me...
Rohan Kishibe was killed because he met me!
Can't I do anything to defeat him?
Um... Can I ask you something?
Do you know what time it is?
My watch doesn't seem to be working right.
Hello? Are you listening?
It's 8:33...
Huh? Haven't I seen you somewhere before?
Where was it?
Do you know who I am?
No...
Huh... I guess I was imagining it.
Sorry for saying something weird.
8:33... Thanks!
Jotaro! It really is past 8:30.
Strange, though... I wonder
where Rohan-sensei went.
Th-They're Rohan Kishibe's friends!
They were supposed to meet up!
He left the car door wide open
and the key in the ignition.
They probably have the same abilities...
Th-They also came to ask
me about Yoshikage Kira.
That's not like Rohan-sensei...
Crap! If they find out
that I'm Hayato Kawajiri
That's Rohan-sensei's earring.
and ask me about my dad...
Sorry about that.
I overslept and was late
meeting up with my friends.
Huh? I've seen you before... Where was it?
Ah, Josuke and Okuyasu.
Yo.
Yo, Koichi. Good morning, Jotaro.
What, so Rohan's the only
one who's not here yet?
A-And two more...
When he said his friends
were going to show up...
We won't know where Hayato Kawajiri's
house is if he's not here.
He must have been talking about them!
I just remembered I accidentally
grabbed onto this.
Here you go. Your hat.
Th-Thanks...
That angle...
It's that angle. I'm sure
I've seen him before...
Where was it? I know I've seen him...
Koichi. Look at the name on his backpack.
Huh?
Hayato Kawajiri
Hayato Kawajiri?!
What?!
I-I've been found out!
Wake up
Lightning strikes the Pepsi sign
Kira leaves the house
The weather report begins
Hayato meets Rohan
Rohan Kishibe dies from explosion
July 16th (Fri)  8:34 AM
Hayato Kawajiri...
What are you doing here?
Is it a coincidence?
D-Does this have to do with
Rohan-sensei not being here?
If these four start asking me about my dad...
They're all going to be blown away!
N-No! Don't ask me any questions...
If you guys die, too,
who's going to defeat him?
Even if I have to deceive them...
I can't let these people die, no matter what!
I want to ask you about this photo...
I want to know why you were
recording a video in this photo.
Why were you recording your da—
M-My nose is bleeding!
I need to go to the clinic!
My nose is gushing blood!
I-I... Bye!
Hold it.
Your nose is bleeding? Let me see.
Here. What happened?
I have to go. Excuse me.
You don't need to go to a clinic.
Your nose isn't bleeding.
Huh?
Huh?!
My name is Josuke Higashikata.
He's a relative of mine, Jotaro Kujo.
The one with the scary face
over there is Okuyasu Nijimura.
And the friendly-looking
guy there is Koichi Hirose.
You go to Budogaoka Elementary, don't you?
Then you won't be late just yet.
We just have some questions...
about this picture.
If it's nothing, then that's fine.
W-Well, it is something!
Don't ask me any questions!
You can't ask me any questions!
Is the person in this picture
your da—
No! Don't say any more!
I-It's no use...
Now they're going to ask even more questions.
What do you mean by "Don't say anymore"?
One after another...
What are we not supposed to say?
I can't stop it anymore!
Are you talking about your dad?
They're going to explode!
They're all going to explode!
You suddenly shouted, "No!"
"Don't say any more"?
But we didn't ask you anything yet.
Could it be...
that even asking you a
question is a bad idea?
They're going to explode...
Explode... Explode...
I know...
I-If I die, no one else will have to die!
Since I'm the bomb, I just need to die!
If I die, I'm sure these people will be
able to defeat him and save my mom!
Come on, ask him about
Kosaku Kawajiri already.
Wait, Josuke. Something's wrong.
What are you crouching down for?
I-It won't go through...
For some reason, the box cutter
won't go into my throat!
That's...
That Stand...
I'd never forget it after seeing it once!
Deadly Queen!
To be more precise,
its Deadly Queen's third bomb, Bites the Dust.
It's already too late to attack.
If you're seeing me, that means
I'm already inside your eyes.
It doesn't matter how many of you
there are, because all at once...
You tried to find out my identity!
What, you're already awake?
I'm glad you replied for once when I
called you, but there's no need to yell.
Breakfast is ready, so come on.
I couldn't stop it...
Those four got attacked, too.
It's no use... No matter how hard I try,
in an hour, fate is going to
eliminate those four, too...
I can't even kill myself.
My dying would be troublesome to him,
so Bites the Dust must be
automatically protecting me.
He's too strong...
Yoshikage Kira is too much of a monster.
Either he has to die, or he has to undo
Bites the Dust for whatever reason,
or those four are going to die for sure.
Either he has to die, or he
has to undo Bites the Dust...
I always thought there was no
way I could ever kill someone.
There was no way an 11-year-old boy
like me could kill a monster like that.
But there is one way!
A way for an 11-year-old
like me to kill him...
Just one.
And it's sleeping quietly in the dark
attic like a gun resting in an armory.
For the first time in my life, I was praying
to God from the bottom of my heart.
"Lord, please let me kill this man somehow."
I was right.
This cat-like plant starts moving
when sunlight hits it,
and then attacks by shooting air bullets.
And even with just this little bit of light
in the room, it's so destructive.
This behavior...
I'll utilize this behavior
and attack him with an
air bullet at point blank range.
Point blank range...
But when and how am I supposed to do that?
I can't do it in or near the house.
Mom's here.
That's it... My hat!
He'll come to put the hat on my head.
That'll be point blank range!
My chance will be when he
comes into range behind me.
That's when I have to do it!
What? No way! We're on the air already?
Er, um... It's now 7:55...
Dad was saying that he wanted
another cup of coffee.
Hello?
No, you've got the wrong number.
This isn't the Sakurai residence.
Here you go, darling. Thanks for waiting.
Here's your fresh cup of coffee.
Right...
It's a lovely morning.
I guess it wouldn't hurt to have
another cup before I go to work.
Fate doesn't change with
Bites the Dust, right?
Something that's been destroyed once will be
destroyed, no matter how much I fight it.
You said that, didn't you?
My precious tea set!
Serves you right!
All right, Mom, I'm heading to school!
I'll be there for you.
I'll protect you forever, Mom!
I can't believe it.
I really never have any idea
what he's thinking... But...
Maybe he's not so bad after all.
Oh, it's fine. I'll clean that up.
There's nothing we can
do now that it's broken.
More importantly, did you get burnt?
No... I'm fine.
He's not here yet...
H-He's not here... He's not here yet.
S-Something's wrong. He should have
already been here by now...
Why isn't he here?
Ugh, the forecast didn't
say it was going to rain!
I-It's starting to rain!
Did fate change because I
left the house before him?
No, that can't be!
If he's coming to put the hat on my head,
he should definitely come up from behind me.
L-Lightning struck the Pepsi sign!
Calm down. Calm down! There
are still two minutes left!
There's more than two minutes before
Rohan Kishibe is automatically blown away.
I need to believe in fate—
H-He's already by that tree...
He's already right there!
What a lovely morning.
But Hayato was acting strangely...
What was that?
It's just a hunch,
but something was strange...
It appears that we've repeated this morning
three... no, four times now.
I-Is he just that intuitive?
But there's no more time!
I'll just have to attack him from here.
D-Did he figure out that
I have the cat plant,
and that's why he's not coming near me?
No... He's too close if he knows that.
But I have to completely
defeat him in one shot.
If I miss, Rohan will explode,
and then he'll undo Bites the Dust
after the other four are eliminated.
If that happens, he's going to win!
There's no time! Damn it...
Just one more step to the left!
If he just steps out from
behind that filthy tree,
I can attack!
What?! H-He's hidden himself even more!
The look in Hayato's eyes
when he left the house...
He looked determined about something.
It's the same look that the loathsome
Koichi Hirose and shitbag Josuke have.
My hunch is telling me to
carefully observe him...
Though there really isn't
much that Hayato can do...
It's too late!
Once it's a few seconds past 8:29,
the attack on Rohan Kishibe will start!
That brat is shaking.
Those eyes look like a despaired
mouse drowning in a cesspool.
I guess I was just imagining
his determination.
Those are definitely the eyes of a loser.
He moved!
I came to bring the hat you forgot, Hayato.
If there is a God, I thank you!
I thank the fate that got this murderer
to move from behind that tree!
I feel a fighting spirit burning within me!
Take this, Yoshikage Kira!
What?!
Y-Yes!
I hit him dead-on! I... I did it!
Hayato Kawajiri's not coming...
I guess he must've taken
a different route to school.
This is the end, you murderer!
Wh-Wh-What?!
Lately...
Impossible!
With my nails growing so quickly...
I got to thinking about how
unlucky I've been lately.
But inside my pocket...
It seems like, since last night,
luck is coming around to my side.
Remember when Mom's precious
tea cup broke this morning?
When the coffee spilled onto
my wrist, I was burned,
so I removed my watch and
put it in my chest pocket.
What unbelievable luck!
If that coffee hadn't spilled this morning...
How... How is that possible? I...
I... I failed!
I-It's almost time!
Episode 37
Shining D (Diamond) is Unbreakable, Part 1