Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I met that boring man
when I was going to community college.
He went to a pretty upper-rank
college in the area,
and my friends were envious
because he was quiet and cool,
so I went out with him to feel superior.
We had a child.
I see. Because it's three times the
speed, the picture quality's...
Hey, Hayato. No "hello" for your mother?
Hi.
My husband's not a bad man.
It's not as if he drinks a lot,
and even though he doesn't earn much,
he always goes to work.
Kosaku Kawajiri
Shinobu
Hayato
But...
I'm a woman who married
without ever knowing love.
Hmph. He's home.
He only knows the words
"food," "bath," and "sleep."
That boring man...
I'm home.
Where's dinner?
Oh, you're home? I didn't even notice.
I was really busy today,
so that's all there is.
But it's your favorite, isn't it?
Ramen
Land
Is he mad?
If you have the guts to
get mad, then get mad.
I'm sure you're just going to eat your
dinner silently as usual, though.
Good evening! This is Morioh Radio,
brought to you again today by
your neighbor, Kai Harada.
What are you doing?
How's your evening going so far?
Here's a perfect song to end the day...
Episode 25     Heart Father
Fifteen minutes by car from Morioh Station...
His house was in the villa and resort area.
Morioh Station
Yoshikage Kira's House
Rather, it was Yoshikage Kira's house
when that was still who he was.
Kira
He has now gained a new face,
family registry, job,
and a different place to call home.
I'm sure he'll never try
to come near here again.
There aren't any corpses
in the fridge, are there?
But we had to search the place.
Because now that he's someone else,
the only clues we could possibly
find on him would be in this house.
Is that his album?
That totally looks like him.
Third Grade Summer
Summer Camp
7-25-1974
Yoshikage Kira...
Born in Morioh Town on January 30th, 1966.
His height is 175 centimeters,
weight is 65 kilograms,
and his blood type is A.
He was born to parents of advanced age.
His father, Yoshihiro, died of
illness when Yoshikage was 21,
and his mother died of old age not long after.
In 1988, he graduated from
D Academy's Department of Literature.
That same year, he started working for
S City's Kame Yu department store.
He transferred to the Morioh branch in 1993.
No previous criminal record. No record
of getting married. No close friends.
No girlfriend. No surgeries.
It's impossible to find him using
fingerprints, teeth, or surgery scars.
That's all rather vague information.
Look. These trophies and awards...
High School Music Recital
Violin
3rd Place
Yoshikage Kira
They're all third place.
Middle School Track Meet
200 Meter Hurdles
3rd Place
Yoshikage Kira
He definitely wasn't the school hero.
Award
Grade School
Writing Contest
Overall 3rd Place
And it's hard to tell what he was good at.
Sports? Music? Writing?
Even in this photo, he's positioned
so he doesn't stand out.
No one envied him or ridiculed him...
He's a man who doesn't show his
strengths or weaknesses to anyone.
Which means...
Of course, all this was deliberate.
He was hiding his high intellect and abilities.
He knew that was the best
way to stay out of trouble.
I came here hoping we could possibly
find one of his hobbies, but...
Hobbies? Come to think of it,
he seems to have kept several jars in a drawer.
See?
It looks like some sort of scrapings in them.
And what are these numbers?
"1983"... Maybe it's the year.
They have a faint smell.
What do you think they are?
They appear to be nail clippings.
Huh?
Wh-Whose nails are they?!
Th-They couldn't be...
No, they're his own nails.
They're not from his victims.
He's kept very meticulous data in his notebook.
Data? You mean the numbers on the jars?
Does that mean he's been
collecting them since 1983?
For the last fifteen years?
Thumb | Index Finger | Middle Finger | Ring Finger | Pinky
Gah! He recorded every
finger! He's so detailed!
[Years that my nails grew more than 30cm]
Right Hand Measurements
Does this mean that in 1983, his thumbnail on
his right hand grew 31.5 centimeters?
1983 was the year Reimi Sugimoto was killed.
The records begin in that year.
He probably reached the point
where he couldn't contain his
murderous instincts any longer.
Whoa! He's got his toenail
lengths on the next page!
I guess we've discovered the odd hobby
of a man who tried to convince
others that he was boring.
Look.
Years that my nails grow more than 30 cm
I'm on a roll!!
No one can stop me.
This data is fortune-telling.
Jewish merchants observe
the movement of sunspots
to determine how well
their businesses would do.
It appears Yoshikage Kira
used the length of his nails
to determine the condition he was in...
Whether he was in condition to kill, of course.
1999!
As of June, they've already grown
more than 20 centimeters this year!
He's insane, that sick bastard!
But this isn't a clue we can use to track him.
There might be something else.
Does this mean someone
else is in this house?
It would appear so.
Josuke, stay on your toes.
Does that mean he's working
with someone else?
No... That's not possible.
Crimes can be traced from
interactions with others.
A partner could possibly rat him out.
He's not the type to trust anyone.
This is...
Jotaro, look at that camera.
I-It's his father... Kira's father!
He's in the picture, right behind us!
But...
This is not good. This is so not good.
Does that mean he's a ghost?
Yeah. Considering the case of Reimi Sugimoto,
it's possible that his father
also couldn't pass on
to the next world and is stuck
here as a soul's energy.
Look at his expression.
He looks like he wants us to get the hell out.
Number Withheld   Public
Are you trying to scare us
with your ghost energy?
But this is all the more reason we can't leave.
Hurry up and answer the phone, you slowpoke!
I'm making it ring!
You think I look like I want you to leave?
It's the opposite, you moron!
My face is saying that I'm never
letting you leave this house!
Anyone who goes after my son must die.
You bastard! You know
about your son's crimes?
Hey, is something wrong?
What's all the racket?
Where are you hiding?
Get out here, you geezer ghost!
Ghost?!
Josuke, he's not hiding.
Huh?
It appears Kira's father has
been present from the start.
Look.
Boom
Wha... When did he...
He's moving around in the picture.
He's calling us from inside the picture.
He probably threw the receiver
from within this picture, too.
I'll kill you...
I'll kill anyone who goes
after my precious son!
Josuke!
We can attack ghosts with our Stands!
Rohan-sensei used his Heaven's Door
to read Reimi's memories!
Bastard!
Take this!
What?!
D-Damn!
Any damage to the photograph
will come back to us!
Hurry up and fix it, Josuke!
We're going to blow to pieces!
Josuke! Jotaro!
That power... I see!
You two have
the same kind of power that my son has!
Okuyasu, you're up!
Use The Hand to cut just
the old man out of the picture!
Gotcha! Leave it to me, Josuke!
Huh?
O-Okuyasu?
Wh-What the?!
Why did I run straight into the window?
M-My hands are coming out
all the way over there!
I can't come past this point!
That's...
A-A wall!
There's a wall here that we can't see!
It won't break! I-It can't be!
You finally figured it out?
That's the frame of the photo!
It may look like you're in the
room, but you're actually not.
I'm a ghost that lives within a photograph...
I can control the dimension of
any photograph that I appear in.
Because I can trap the energy of others'
souls in photos, using the camera!
That is my power!
That room is inside the picture!
If you damage the photo,
your soul's energy will be hurt,
and the damage will come
back to you, as well!
Inside the picture?
But it's right in front of me!
If you're as dumb as you look,
you don't need to think about it too hard.
After I kill these two, I'll trap
the two of you and slice you up!
J-Josuke! Jotaro!
I'll kill you...
You bastard! Stop, damn it!
Jotaro, what are you doing?
Do something with your
invincible Star Platinum!
Josuke... I'm giving up.
Huh?
It appears impossible to stop
the old geezer's attacks.
If all the damage is just
going to come back to us,
then even if I stop time with Star Platinum,
we won't be able to do anything.
When something's useless, I give up.
What did you say, Jotaro?
What the hell are you talking about?!
I'll kill you!
Your heads went flying!
A-A knife...
What?!
I can't touch it! J-Jotaro!
I've given up on stopping the geezer,
but...
Wha?
If he controls any photograph he's in,
then maybe all we have to do is take a
picture of him by himself, so he's alone.
What?!
To think you've evaded my attack... Damn it!
Josuke, say something to him.
Something cool. Let him have it!
Y-You didn't scare me at all, you idiot!
The
The Ha
The Han
The Hand
Oku
Okuyasu
Okuyasu Niji
Okuyasu Nijimura
Damn you!
You guys are clearly used to fighting.
You must have fought against
people with the same kind
of power as my son many, many times!
He can get out, since he's a ghost.
We need to make sure you
stay in there and keep quiet.
There's something in this house that will
cause him a lot of trouble if we find it.
That's why you attacked us.
I get it.
So if you fold him in half, there's no exit.
He can't run away.
Okuyasu, Koichi, you two search this room.
We'll search the right side.
I can't protect my son now! Damn it!
If that falls into their hands...
Still, what thing that might cause
trouble for him should we look for?
I'm not thinking too much about it.
If Kira's old man there turns pale,
it's a good sign.
I-I can't breathe...
I-It's too cramped...
Please, just a little is fine.
Just open the tiniest of holes
in the tape and let me breathe...
Y-You really can't breathe?
Hey, Koichi, he's just acting.
He's trying to get you to
open a hole so he can escape.
Y-You may not believe me,
b-but I really can't breathe!
I'm claustrophobic, so I
understand how that feels...
Oh, quit whining. You want us
to open up a hole that bad?
Fine, then. I'll open up plenty for you...
With tacks, that is.
Wh-What are you doing?!
Damn it! Let me out of here,
you stupid little brat!
Now you've shown your true colors.
I won't be removing those tacks.
Tacks? I can't see, but I appear
to be on the post right now.
I've got a great idea!
Your tacks helped me come up with
a trump card to get out of here!
It's easy! It's all thanks to you!
Well, see ya!
Wha...
Hey, you bastard...
What was that sound? What did you do?
Say something, damn it!
O-Okuyasu, this isn't good!
I think he might have run away!
Jotaro! H-He got away!
I-It's my fault. H-He used
the tacks and did something!
You've been fooled, you moron!
Looks like I've won the battle of wits.
What?!
Th-This is...
What's this doing here?
It can't be!
It's the bow and arrow...
But we retrieved them...
The bow and arrow should be in safekeeping
at the Speedwagon Foundation...
Is there another set?
Josuke, be careful! Kira's father escaped!
What?!
This arrow drew Deadly Queen out of Yoshikage!
The arrow is the important part!
I'll never let you have it!
R-Reverb, Koichi! Use Act 1 to go after it!
I-It's too far away!
Seriously?
The thing that Kira's father didn't want
us to find was the bow and arrow!
D-Damn it! It's all my fault!
No, Okuyasu. He was just a stronger opponent.
You can tell that Kira is definitely his son.
We've lost to that family's determination
to never give up, and to survive, no matter what.
As long as they don't get
this arrow, that's good enough.
I'm going to use this to
make more enemies for you!
The bow and arrow, huh... I see.
I thought there might be more than one set.
Now I know exactly how DIO and the others
were able to gather so many Stand
users in such a short amount of time.
They created more of them around the world
with a number of those bows and arrows.
I'm assuming Kira's father got this set
from an old woman named Enyaba,
and eventually, Okuyasu's brother, Keicho,
also got hold of one, and came to this town.
Because Stand users attract
other Stand users, apparently.
Yoshikage, where are you right now?
You never could help but kill women,
even when you were a boy.
But if that's what brings you
happiness, I'll protect you.
Because...
You're my one and only son.
Kosaku Kawajiri
Shinobu
Hayato
What's gotten into you?
You're actually cooking?
I-I mean, I didn't know you even knew how.
Two plates? This one's for me?
You're telling me to eat your cooking?
How stupid are you?
Hey! Cut your nails later!
And didn't you cut them last night?
They must grow fast...
Oh... Th-This is actually really good...
H
He
Hea
Hear
Heart
Heart F
Heart Fa
Heart Fat
Heart Fath
Heart Fathe
Heart Father
Yoshi
Yoshihiro
Yoshihiro Ki
Yoshihiro Kira
Kitty!
Why?
Were you crying all night at the top of
that tree because you couldn't get in?
Hey! What gives you the right to
shut the window near the tree?!
I've told you day after day not to shut it!
What's wrong, kitty?
Why are you so worked up?
Cats hate water.
I'm sorry about that.
I shut the window without thinking.
I won't do it again.
Something's wrong. He's changed somehow.
He started cooking out
of the blue last night,
and he's using an actual blade rather
than an electric razor to shave.
Blades always give him razor burn...
Hey, you haven't paid your
rent from last month.
It's now 260,000 yen including this month's.
Pay up right now!
Rent?
You heard him. Hurry up and
bring it from the safe.
Safe?
Hurry! You're the only one who
knows the combination to the safe!
Hey, what are you...
Thank you for coming so
early in the morning, sir.
But I seem to be a bit
short on cash right now.
Huh?
Quit screwing around!
You got in over your head when
you tried to rent my wonderful house
with your lousy income, you peon!
You need to learn to live within your means!
Um, we'll get it right away—
No. Please don't get the wrong idea.
When I said I was a bit short, look.
I meant that I only had a
little over 500,000 yen.
I'll only be able to pay for this month,
last month, and the next
two months in advance.
Will that suffice?
Y-Yes, that's plenty.
Thank you very much.
Pleasure doing business with you!
Y-You...
You must have stolen that
money from the landlord.
I don't know how you did it,
but you stole it from his bag, didn't you?
I'm sure in most cases,
people would fear him and
think that he's just a low-life...
But my husband's actions...
him stealing that...
For the first time,
after years of living with him,
I think he's so romantic...
Episode 26
Janken Boy Is Coming!