Edited at https://subtitletools.com
All of Kosaku Kawajiri's shoes
are a bit big for my own feet.
I need to switch them with
shoes that fit me, before they
start to suspect something.
Hayato.
Aren't you going to say goodbye?
Have a good day.
Darling!
Something terrifying
happened in the basement!
It was so scary! I thought I was going to die!
It might have been scary,
but it gave me an excuse
to dive into the arms
of the one I love so much.
Like that, and that, and that!
You see... There's a cat I've never
seen before in the basement!
A cat?
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 30     Cats Love Yoshikage Kira
So the reason it was really scary...
I went down to the basement
because I ran out of mineral water.
And you know how much I love cats, right?
So I was like, "Oh, it's a British Blue."
It had perfect proportions,
and golden eyes contrasting with
its velvet-like, blue-gray fur.
Where did you come in from?
You cute little kitty...
Oh, dear. It's being defensive.
It must have come in from there.
But I can't let it stay down here forever.
It might pee on the potato
sack it's sitting on,
and it might even have fleas.
It's okay to get closer if you
don't make eye contact, right?
Oh, right. I just need to let it
know that I'm not its enemy.
See? My belly's up, which
means I'm being submissive.
Let's be friends.
Why am I trying to humor a cat?
If you don't get out of here,
I'll hit you with this!
You hear? I'll throw it!
Darn it!
Why, you!
It was clinging to the ceiling
like some kind of bug!
A-And what really creeped me out was
that the cat had a hole in its throat.
A hole about as big as a one-yen coin!
And then, from the hole, I heard...
Mreow
A hole?
Could it be a hole from the arrow?
I just frantically waved
the broom around and ran.
Please, could you go check it out?
It was really creepy.
It had a hole... right?
Hey... Is it gone? Did it run away?
No... It's dead.
Huh? What are you talking about?
W-Wait...
One of the shards went right into its throat.
Wait a minute! I was just—
It was an accident.
It's no one's fault. It was just bad luck.
It's not your fault.
It's no one's fault.
Apparently it had a hole in its throat, but...
Now there's no way to tell if
it was a Stand user or not.
No, I'm sure it wasn't...
Good morning, Morioh.
Isn't it a refreshing morning,
now that the rain's stopped?
I just saw a rainbow in the sky
before I came into the studio.
Is it still out there?
"Where am I, mrowr?
What am I doing here?
Meow, meow," he thought.
"Two days go, someone
attacked me with an arrow,
and I survived that, but..."
"M-My body's different from usual!
It's shaped funny! It's all wrong!
Why can't I move from here?"
he thought, bewildered.
Where did he bury it?
I'm so sorry, kitty. Please rest in peace.
"Who's this human lady?
I get a bad feeling from her," he thought.
"The broom! That's it! Now I remember!
This woman...
That's right! A whole bunch of glass
stabbed me, and I couldn't move!
The reason I'm like this now
is because of this woman!"
he thought angrily.
He was perplexed.
"What? Something came out.
When I got angry at that woman,
something just came out."
My toenail? Wh-Why?!
Is it a curse? C-Could it be that cat?!
He lived by his desire and instinct,
so he understood this power,
as well as how to use it.
That's... a Stand user!
Why is this thing growing from
where I buried the cat yesterday?
Just what is this thing?
What did it do to that sparrow?
I couldn't see an actual Stand.
The most important thing is whether
that thing is an enemy or not.
Is it an enemy who wishes
to harm me, or is it...
I should probably kill it, just in case.
It fell asleep after eating.
Is it a plant or an animal?
It'd be easy to kill it,
but it might be worth
watching for a while.
The way it turned around because
it thought it was being called
is almost like a cat, as well...
The fact that it can't resist trying
to smell me is also like a cat.
It looks like it might be okay to pet it.
The way it's purring creepily
as it's about to fall asleep
is also, indeed, like a cat.
But I'm still not sure if it has
any hostility toward me or not.
Let's find out.
Hmm... It's angry,
but this confirms that it doesn't
have any hostility toward me.
This is definitely the cat that
I buried here yesterday.
So it really did have a hole
in its throat from the arrow!
D-Darling?
The woman!
That place scares me.
That's where my toenail came off...
This cat attacked her because
it had a grudge against her!
If she found out about this thing...
That rumor might eventually reach
Jotaro Kujo and the others!
That would definitely be bad news!
That's where you buried the cat, right?
It seems like it's cursed,
so I'm really scared...
I didn't bury it here.
Go back into the house.
You're lying!
You're lying out of consideration
for me, aren't you?
Crap! This cat means me harm, after all!
I still don't know what kind
of Stand ability it has,
but I'm going to get rid of it.
Deadly Queen!
I feel bad for you, but I'm going
to blow you up with this.
First bomb, switch on!
What?!
Impossible! There's no way it can be a dud!
Is it because of this thing?
Is this thing's ability
keeping it from exploding?
Huh? Is that a plant?
Th-That plant is moving!
I told you to go back into the house!
Huh?
Shinobu!
The moment Deadly Queen's bomb moved
away from that thing, it went off!
Could this thing's ability be...
The plant that was a cat
until yesterday thought,
"I'm going to kill that woman!"
I can't allow you to attack her anymore.
I'm going to have to make you disappear.
"Then I'll just have to kill this man
who's getting in my way, too!"
The only time the bomb doesn't explode
is when there's no air around it.
This plant instinctively knew
just how it should kill him.
Could its Stand ability be the
ability to control air freely?
It's coming!
I can't see it, but it released something again.
Deadly Queen!
It is releasing something. It's air!
It's releasing bubbles of air!
You damn cat! I'll crush you!
I can't touch it!
It's like I'm stepping on an invisible balloon!
It really is controlling the air.
What?
Th-That thing...
I can't see it, but I'm sure it
released an air bubble again.
This isn't good... Something isn't right!
What?
The cactus!
Sh-Shinobu!
What is this? Was I,
Yoshikage Kira, just relieved
at the fact that the cactus
needles didn't pierce her eyes?
What is this feeling?
Am I actually worried about someone else?
No!
I'm just worried that if this
woman dies, Jotaro Kujo
will find out about this house!
That's the only reason I was
relieved that she was okay.
That's all it is...
That attack won't work anymore.
Even though I may not be able to see it,
now that I know the mystery behind it...
It's just an ability that allows you
to blow and spread air bubbles.
You are no longer a match for Deadly Queen.
What?!
Th-This thing just...
put an air bubble into my veins!
It's rising higher and higher into my body!
I'm not that knowledgeable
in medicine, but I've heard
that if you inject more than 10cc
of air into a human being's veins,
it can block the vein and lead to death.
This is definitely more than 10cc!
Shit!
It's no use! This is bad...
I have no choice... I have to do it.
Deadly Queen!
I underestimated that thing.
Its ability to freely control the air...
It's a terrifying ability.
Wh-What should I do?
It's coming! It's going to attack again!
What should I do?
That was close...
For now, I guess I'll let this go.
I'll let this go.
S
St
Str
Stra
Stray
Stray C
Stray Ca
Stray Cat
A
A Plant
A Plant That
Was
Was Once
A Plant That
Was Once a
Was Once a Cat
He told me yesterday that he buried
that cat's corpse far away.
The cat's curse, as he said,
was just an illusion my mind
came up with out of fear.
I suddenly fainted in front of him...
It was so embarrassing.
But...
He took care of me, even though
it made him late to work.
I was so happy.
It felt like our hearts were connected.
That was the happiest morning of my life.
Well? Is it good?
That Hayato...
He left without saying goodbye again.
Was that brat observing me?
Oh, darling!
That's my plate.
You don't like shiitake mushrooms,
so I took them out of yours...
When did you start liking them?
You've already eaten more than half of it.
But I'm happy to see you
gobbling down my cooking.
I guess you realized that you only
thought you didn't like them, huh?
Yes.
All right, I'm going.
Have a good day, darling.
Jeez... I wanted him to
give me a goodbye kiss.
But we're understanding
each other's feelings.
I'll seduce him soon enough.
He was using a shoehorn
to put on his shoes.
I'm sure he put on the 25.5cm sized shoes.
Having two different sizes of shoes is weird.
It's also weird that Mom and
Dad are getting along lately.
He was even gobbling up the shiitake
mushrooms that he hates.
This is weird, too.
Why was he writing his own name over and over?
And last night...
No matter how many times
I see it, that's potting soil.
And I think the other thing
he has is a bag of cat food.
And then he goes inside his closet...
They're all wearing hats.
Do they have to wear those for school?
Something doesn't feel right...
The attic?
Wh-What is that bizarrely shaped thing?
It's too dark for me to see it clearly.
There it is. It's that bag.
Huh?
Wha—
I-It's moving!
It's not a plant... Those are eyes!
It has eyeballs, and it's looking this way!
Could that cat food be for this thing?
Oh, darling.
What's the matter?
Did you forget something?
Oh, is the thing you forgot
my goodbye kiss?
No...
Aww...
Then what is it? Shall I get it for you?
No, I'll get it.
Why is he back?
Crap!
Huh?!
What?! Th-This thing...
Something I can't see that's inflated,
like some kind of air bubble,
has my arms and neck pinned down!
He's coming up! C-Crap!
The attic! I knew it! That brat...
I-It attacked me when I
tried to shut the window?
Does this thing need sunlight to move?
I-I know! If they're air bubbles...
Yes! So it was the sunlight.
That noise...
Did Stray Cat wear itself out trying to
get the cat food from the shelf using air?
I thought it would stay calm if
there was no sunlight hitting it,
but I guess a tiny bit of light was coming in.
Still...
I thought that maybe Hayato
had gotten in here,
but it appears that it was, thankfully,
just my imagination.
If that brat knew the truth about me,
I would have had to kill him.
He has Dad's face,
but that's not my dad. Who...
Wh-Who the hell is he?!
Episode 31
July 15th (Thurs), Part 1