Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hey, apparently Koichi's
family doesn't know, either.
They were talking about
possibly calling the police.
So he is missing. And since
Yukako isn't here, either...
I sort of feel responsible.
You don't think he's dead, do you?
Nah, I doubt she's gone that far yet.
She must be keeping him somewhere.
We need to find him, and fast.
This might end up being
a life or death situation.
It won't open!
This is awful!
Q.
What year did Columbus
discover the new continent?
The answer is the lock's combination.
It was also a movie title, wasn't it?
But it looked really long,
so I didn't watch it.
I've almost got it...
1, 4, 0, 0...
Um...
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 9  Yukako Yamagishi Falls in Love, Part 2
I washed your underwear and
your pajama pants for you.
What's wrong?
I won't know if you don't say anything.
I-I'm a first-year in high school...
This is just the worst.
This goes beyond being embarrassed.
I feel like an awful human being.
Please, stop this already.
You hate me now, don't you?
You think I'm pathetic, don't you?
Just let me go home already.
What could you possibly like
about me, after I peed my pants?
Oh, you poor thing, Koichi.
I must be tormenting your heart.
I'm a bad girl.
Nothing I say does any good!
I-I can feel tears starting to well up...
First I wet my pants, and now
I'm getting wet with tears?
But Koichi...
After saying that you're
an awful human being,
I can see something shining, something
invigorating, deep in your eyes.
Like you still have a trump
card hidden up your sleeve.
That's what I like about you.
I would love to see what that is.
And if it belongs to someone you love,
there's nothing wrong with
even poop or snot, right?
It's strange that you'd even worry.
I felt true bliss while I was washing your pants.
Look!
I'm working on a chair that has
electricity running through it.
I'll make sure it's done by dinner study time.
I'm thinking about making Italian for dinner.
I should go buy some olive oil.
Look forward to it.
H-Help me!
She's just getting worse!
I have to hurry and escape,
o-or she's seriously going to kill me!
But...
How am I going to escape?
Koichi's got Reverb, though.
With that thing, he can still call for
help even if he's being gagged, right?
But Reverb's range is about 50 meters.
He might've been taken to a place
where no one else lives nearby.
There are tons of places like that.
Wait!
She said she was going
to buy some olive oil.
But I can't imagine her going out
shopping in this situation.
Is she going to order by phone, then?
Could it be...
There it is! A pay phone!
48 meters! Yes!
It's just within my range!
Reverb is a sound Stand!
Now I can signal Josuke for help.
I don't have any 10 yen coins!
I was wearing pajamas
when I was brought here.
Should I dial 110?
But that woman might
actually kill the police.
I'm just going to have to
contact Josuke somehow!
You were wondering if there was
a pay phone nearby, weren't you?
Y-Yukako...
I know exactly what you're thinking.
You heard me say that I was
going to get some olive oil,
so there must be a pay phone nearby.
But even if you were to get to it,
you don't have any 10 yen coins.
That's what you were thinking, right?
I-Is there a pay phone?
Hmph. Playing dumb, I see.
You should abandon the idea
of trying to call someone.
You wont be able to set
foot outside of this house.
Just in case, I'm going to go destroy
the 110 button on the phone.
Is there anything that you'd like?
N-No, not really...
Wh-What is wrong with her?!
I guess it's no use... I can't contact anyone...
Beep
Boop
What are these letters?
There's suddenly sound
coming from my hand...
It's calling somewhere!
I haven't even dialed the phone number yet.
Hello? This is Higashikata.
It connected!
As long as the call sounds go through,
calls on those phones will be connected.
Hello, is this Koichi?
Hey! It's me, Josuke!
Koichi, where are you?
What? I can hear the sound of waves...
Koichi, you...
You have a power like I do, don't you?
Yes! Now Josuke will definitely come here!
It'll only take 15 to 20 minutes by car.
I just have to survive until then!
N-No matter what!
The sound of waves... A pay phone...
The place Koichi is...
It's gotta be here!
Koichi.
Koichi!
She's coming back!
I-I've got no choice but to fight!
Open the door, Koichi.
Wh-Why don't you just break the door down?
If Josuke sees a broken door,
he'll definitely think something's wrong.
I'm very happy right now.
I'm so happy that you have
powers like I do, Koichi.
Though it pisses me off that
you were hiding that from me.
But I'm still very happy.
Because the most important thing for
a man and a woman living together
is love, and having the same
goals and values, right?
We have something in common
that no one else has.
We have the ultimate compatibility.
So please, Koichi...
Open the door.
I told you to open the door.
Hurry up and open the door!
I hate you
I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
Th-The ultimate compatibility?!
I hate you! I hate you! I hate you!
I hate you! I hate you!
Can't you tell how much
I don't want to be here?!
That sound won't go away until you cry,
apologize, and give up on me.
What is this? I don't hear any of this.
I hate you—
Huh?!
Th-This is...
nothing like that time with Tamami.
Her delusions are way too strong!
I had no idea sh-she'd be this stubborn...
I finally found out that we've
been bound by the one
and only red thread in this world.
Some people never find it at all.
Don't you understand how wonderful that is?
Koichi...
I was going to try to make you into a fine man,
but now things are different.
I won't let you leave this house
until you fall in love with me.
I will make you love me!
Or else...
I might just kill you.
I can't let her in here, no matter what...
I need to attack her with
Reverb one more time!
If I try harder, I'll be able to
produce a louder sound than before.
Reverb!
Something's wrong with Reverb...
It's not moving!
D-Did it die?
Did my Stand die of utter despair?
Reverb is dead!
Re
Rev
Rever
Reverb
Ko
Koichi
Koichi Hiro
Koichi Hirose
N-No! M-My...
My Reverb isn't moving at all!
Stands use mental ability to move.
I pushed it too far, and then it
got too worked up and died!
My Reverb...
What?!
Wh-What is that?
It's called a "Stand"?
What is that Stand?
This shoe cabinet is in my way!
I-I'm going to be killed!
If she comes in the door and catches me,
then sooner or later, I'll be killed!
Open up, Koichi!
Don't come through that door!
If only that door would blow her far away...
It's gone! It's just an empty shell.
Where did you put it?
Huh?
I'm asking what happened
to the thing inside that!
Huh?!
Th...
That's...
Wh-What is this? My Reverb
i-isn't dead!
Did it emerge from its old
shell into a new form?
What is this?
The design's only changed
a little, and it shrank.
Just changing its shape
won't make any difference!
I-It's fast!
Wh-What is
this wind?!
Bam
Sh-She got blown away!
I'm not sure how, but she just got
blown away by something like wind!
Wh-What just...
happened to me?
Reverb's letters are on the door...
Fwoosh
Because she touched the door with
these words on it, they became real.
Fwoosh
The sensation of "Fwoosh"
actually blew her away.
Earlier, I wished this door would blow her away...
I guess I was unknowingly controlling it.
This is the new Reverb!
Reverb Act 2!
Koichi...
Teioh
It's those two...
If it's a place near the sea with
a lot of uninhabited houses,
it has to be this area with all the villas.
But there are, like, dozens of villas around here.
We can't tell which one it is.
We have to find the pay phone!
Koichi called us from one.
Let's find the pay phone first and
then look at the houses near it.
Yeah.
Cute little Koichi belongs to me.
I won't let anyone else have him.
You probably shouldn't come any closer, Yukako.
I can tell for myself
that you can't beat my Reverb Act 2's abilities.
You won't be able to keep me here.
My left eyelid is starting to twitch.
Ever since I was little,
my orbicularis oculi muscle would
start twitching when I got worked up,
and I'd start to feel a bit violent.
Don't you get up on your high horse just because
you've obtained a slightly different ability!
I'm going to have to get violent now!
Hot!
H-How dare you?!
My hand got burnt! You little shit!
When you said you were going to get violent,
did you mean how you're talking right now?
How dare you do this to me?!
You're just a baby chick!
You belong to me!
You belong to me, but you dare defy me?!
Even though you belong to me?!
Reverb Act 2!
I missed?
Hey, Josuke.
I heard it.
That was the sound of something breaking.
Hey, I think it's that house.
T-To think that her hair
would grow this much...
Her mental ability is too strong.
Mental ability that's completely
black and vindictive...
Was yours called Reverb?
Now that I know what it does,
it's not impressive at all.
I just need to make sure I don't
touch those letters, right?
By the way, I'll ask you one more time...
You love me, right?
Just try to say that you don't love me.
I'll rip you and this house
apart right here, right now.
If you die, you'll be mine forever,
because you'll live on in my
heart as a memory forever.
Hurry up and answer me!
I'm in this mess right now because
you wouldn't understand when I told you.
I've been telling you that I don't like you
all this time.
I'll kill you, Koichi!
Dogon
I've also already told you
that you won't be able to catch me.
You've touched the letters
that will blow you away.
Those letters are on me,
the one you called a little shit.
Her hair turned white!
She's not dead, is she?
She's alive!
Even though she's crazy and downright nasty,
I suppose I should be happy about this.
I wasn't able to catch you...
But I figured out that all I need
to do is destroy your Stand!
Impudent brat!
Dumbass!
I-I can't believe you can still attack...
Your mental ability is insane!
Shut up!
How dare you, you little pissy-pants?!
How dare you do this to me?!
My precious hair turned white,
you limp-dicked bastard!
I loved you!
But I can't forgive you for
doing this to my beautiful hair!
I don't care who you are! I won't
forgive you if you harm my beauty!
I'm gonna rip off this pissy-pants' little dick
and pull out his organs along with it!
S-Stop...
Shut up!
You're gonna end up like
that, too, aren't you?!
What? What was that noise just now?
Let go of my Reverb and grab hold of something.
The cliff is going to crumble.
When Reverb heard the sound of your heart,
it also heard the sound
of the ground cracking.
Hah! Don't make up shit just
because you think it'll save you!
I have to let go of this thing
and grab on to something!
Damn it!
I-I don't have... time!
Boingy-Boing
It crumbled, just like I said, right?
But you don't understand
anything I say, do you?
You mean you had written it there already?
When I was trying to rip Reverb apart...
You put those letters on
that rock beneath the cliff?
You mean that while I was
trying to kill Koichi,
he was already trying to
think of how to save me?
I-I've lost completely.
No, I lost the moment I first saw Koichi.
Hey, Koichi! Are you alive?
Are you all right, Koichi?!
Josuke! Okuyasu!
Took you long enough to get here! Jeez!
B-But I love him even more now.
I don't care if he completely ignores me.
I'm happy just thinking
about you, Koichi!
Hey, look over there! Is that Yukako?
Her hair's gone completely white!
Whoa, you're right.
But isn't that chick smiling like
she couldn't be any happier?
And she's looking right this way.
Huh?!
You're right. That's creepy as hell.
Let's get outta here!
Save me, Josuke!
Don't depend on me!
Well, I'll be damned.
Did you see that, Masaji?
I ain't drunk, Gramps!
Morioh Landmark 2
Cape Boingy-Boing
Directions: Ask one of the local fishermen, "Where's Cape Boingy-Boing?"
They will kindly take you there by boat.
Boingy-Boing Cape.
It seems it grew famous due to a rumor
that some fishermen saw a
young girl try to kill herself,
only for a rock in the cape to go
"boingy-boing" and gently fling her back.
Hirose!
You worked really hard on this exam.
You can do it if you try.
English Exam        Answer Sheet
Test 3        Koichi Hirose
I don't...
know how I should feel about this.
Episode 10
Let's Go Eat Some Italian Food