Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Just like a sickness that continues to
progress without any visible symptoms,
there was someone hiding
in our town of Morioh,
committing murders somewhere in the town.
And it seems like no one's even realized
that these murders are taking place.
It's such shocking and chilling information.
But there is currently no
way of finding that murderer.
We don't even know how many Stand
users currently live in Morioh.
And rather than worry about a huge problem
that presents no visible symptoms,
people are worried about what
they should have for dinner,
because that's what's right in front of us.
Kameyu
Bank No.
Deposit Amount
Transaction No.
Window No.
Balance
Branch No.
I only have 285 yen left in my savings!
But I had 20,000 yen in there!
Twelve yen?!
I was weak!
My 20,000 yen that I was saving up to
buy those kewl brand-name shoes...
I can't even remember what I used the money on.
This is all that damn old man's fault!
Because he used my card to buy
130,000 yen worth of baby crap!
I made the old man pay me
back the 130,000 later,
but then I felt like spending a little
here and there wouldn't hurt,
and totally lost track of my spending.
I wonder if I tucked away a thousand yen
somewhere and just forgot about it.
A cockroach!
I guess banks could have them, too.
A S-Stand?
I found one yen.
Y-You bastard!
I-It's a Stand!
A new Stand has appeared!
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 18    Shigechi's Harvest, Part 1
Where the hell is it heading?
There's another one!
Damn it! Who the hell are you?!
I'll kill you!
Okuyasu!
Oh, Josuke!
Look! It's an enemy Stand. I'm gonna kill it!
There're two of them!
Yeah. There was one at the
bank, so I followed it here.
How did it attack you?
Actually, it didn't attack me.
I was buying Calpis Water,
and it suddenly came out from
under the vending machine.
What? It didn't attack you?
But you just said you were going to kill it.
It scared the crap out of me,
and I spilled the Calpis Water
all over my uniform.
Damn it! Give me back my money!
Found it!
Hey, another one just joined in...
Found it. Found it.
What the... What the hell are these guys?
There's a ton of them gathering up!
Okuyasu, they're just like
your brother Keicho's Stand.
But...
Since they're ignoring us, they're
a totally different kind of creepy.
Yeah...
Be careful! The user's probably nearby.
Boom
It's...
It's money!
Come to think of it, it picked up a 1 yen coin
underneath a machine at the bank.
They're only 1 yen and 10 yen
coins, but they're all real!
Well done, you guys.
Many a little makes a mickle.
I think that's about five thousand yen.
As long as I have you guys, Harvest,
I'll never have to worry about money.
Hey, that's the user?
He's talking to his Stand...
Yeah... He seems to have
become a Stand user because
of the bow and arrow, but it doesn't
look like he's trying to attack us.
Grin!
You guys...
You can see my Harvest?
Hey, you can see them, right?!
Yeah, it's called a Stand.
I'm Josuke Higashikata.
This is Okuyasu Nijimura.
Friends! I've never had any before!
My name is Shigekiyo Yangu.
I'm a second-year at Budogaoka Middle School.
I weigh 110 kilograms,
and my Papa and Mama call me "Shigechi."
"Shige-chan" turned into "Shigechi."
My turtle I have at home is named Gonta.
The other day, I was wondering
if the 41 yen, 62 yen,
and 150 yen stamps all tasted different,
so I was licking them all,
and Mama yelled at me.
This is a picture of my Mama,
who yelled at me.
A picture...
Wow, your mom's actually kinda hot.
How strange.
U-Um...
So, you call these things "Harvest"?
Did they really gather up all this?
Yup. From ditches and underneath
vending machines and things...
But I'm not a thief.
The officer at the police box said that
I didn't have to turn in any
change under a hundred yen.
I hate bad things!
That's not a bad thing at all!
Actually, I think you're doing
something great for society.
Though it's not much,
you're putting all of the forgotten
change back into the Japanese economy.
That's a great thing.
Really? I'm great?
Hey, do you think I'm a great person?
It's what you'd call a blind spot for ideas.
No one would do all this to get money.
I'm jealous... You're smart.
D-Did you just call me smart?
N-No one's ever told me that before.
I've picked up about 120,000 yen, but...
120,000?!
B-But that makes me even happier!
A t-total of 120,000?!
Aren't I a good boy?
J-Just here in Morioh?
Ayup! I don't go outside of Morioh.
I might get lost and someone might kidnap me.
120,000... And I only have 12 yen.
Okuyasu...
Is something wrong with your left foot?
Whoa, what?!
There are three 50 yen coins on the ground!
Do they belong to you, Shigekiyo?
I didn't even notice...
Talk about stingy...
Hey, I'll give you guys half of this.
Huh?!
You're my friends, right?
We have the same kind of power.
R-Really?!
Lucky us!
N-No... Wait a sec.
Look, you shouldn't give other
people money or things so easily.
Then I'll give it to you in a hard way.
I'll give it all to you. We're friends, right?
Hey, why are you just
hardening your expression?
H-Hey...
Let me talk to him alone for a sec, Shigechi.
Hey, Josuke! Stop acting
like a goody-two-shoes.
If he says he's going to give it to us,
we should just take it, dumbass!
My pride won't let me do that. Not Josuke.
I'll take anything anyone wants to
give me other than a virus! Got it?!
Calm down! I totally understand
what you're saying!
Stop crying!
But...
I'm actually really broke right now, too.
And so I just thought of a nice idea
that can make everyone happy.
Huh? An idea to make everyone happy?
Leave it to me.
Ha
Har
Harv
Harve
Harves
Harvest
Shige
Shigekiyo
Shigekiyo Ya
Shigekiyo Yan
Shigekiyo Yangu
To All the Good Kids
Let's All Play Nice
Morioh Town
Hey, Shigekiyo. Can I call you "Shigechi"?
Sure.
Shigechi, we can't take this.
What you tried to do just now
is the same as trying to
buy friendship with money.
Huh? B-But that's not what I meant!
I believe that friendship is
something that grows between
people through a common bond.
I was just...
I know. I totally get how you feel.
We're all Stand user buddies.
And so...
Why don't we do a little business
and strike up a friendship?
Business?
Yeah. A business using all three of our powers.
Right here?
That's your elbow. No, business.
Basically, I think you're at your
limit for picking up lost change.
So I have an idea for how
we can use your Harvest
to make even more money.
Huh?
An idea that'll make us more money
than Harvest picking up change?
It's not a bad thing, and it
won't cause anyone trouble.
S-So what's the idea?
That's where the business comes in!
Give Okuyasu and me half of
what we make for the idea fee.
You'll take the other half, Shigechi.
The three of us are going to work
together to pull off a huge project,
and we can all become happy.
O-Okay! That's fine, but wh-what should I do?
You know what this is, right?
Kameyu
A b-blue stamp!
Yeah! When you shop at one of Eastern
Japan's biggest department store chains,
Kameyu, you get one sticker
for every 100 yen you spend.
I think there are a lot of people who
don't collect these and just throw them away.
There are these, too.
A voucher from a stationery shop,
Meiwado, worth 20 yen.
yen
Meiwado Stationery Shop
Product Voucher
Oscar
A coupon from CD Shop Oscar,
where you can trade in ten for
2,000 yen worth of merchandise.
The cleaners, the toy shop Märchen Kids...
Nagasaki
Cleaners
Yotsuba Electronics
Service Card
And this is a card from
Yotsuba Electronics.
Now, this is the important part.
At Kameyu, for example,
you can get cash back for these.
Ah, a-are you... I got it, Josuke!
I know what you're thinking!
Let's go, you guys!
Rumble
With only one or two,
they'd just be scraps of paper...
But if Harvest happened to pick up
the thousands and ten thousands
that are thrown away around town...
Found it.
Inside this trash can!
Inside that trash can!
Found it. Found it.
Found it.
Found it. Found it. Found it.
Th-They just keep piling up one after another!
Wh-What an amazing Stand!
That's awesome, Shigechi!
I got complimented again.
We'll fix the ripped pieces of
paper with Shining Diamond.
Yes! Do we have tens of thousands now?
No, it's definitely over 100,000 by now.
Yes!
Grab
We're an invincible trio!
Let's go get our money!
But, Josuke, you sure are something.
After you went on about pride and junk...
Well, in this case,
everyone's happy, so it's fine.
F-Friendship is great...
O-Okuyasu, J-Josuke, I wonder if it'll be okay.
Will it turn into money that easily?
Calm down, Shigechi. Believe in Josuke.
That's Okuyasu and...
I wonder who that is.
Okuyasu—
Josuke! H-How did it go?
Were you able to get the money?
Did they tell you to piss off?
I wasn't able to get cash back
at the CD shop or the toy store.
But I can exchange the coupons for about
40,000 yen worth of CDs or video games.
I'm not asking about that!
What about Kameyu?
Were you able to get cash
back for the Kameyu stickers?
Actually, something kind of
unexpected happened.
S-Something unexpected?
It unexpectedly turned into 61,500 yen!
Here you go! It's real, Shigechi!
I-It's real!
It's right in front of my eyes! It's like a dream!
That's awesome, Shigechi!
Your Stand, Harvest, is really amazing!
Y-You really think it's amazing?
Hey... P-People don't really
compliment me much...
Do you really think I'm amazing?
Hey, have a little more confidence, Shigechi.
This is something that only you can do.
Okuyasu... Josuke...
Straighten.
Hey, girl. I got a fat stack!
Wanna go have some fun?
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Oh, yeah. Here, Josuke, Okuyasu.
Here's your share, 10,000 yen.
Shigechi, what is this?
We've got friendship, right?
We're friends, right?
Yeah, we are.
So that's a token of our friendship.
Hey, wait...
This isn't what we promised, is it?
You said okay to us getting half,
and you getting the other.
Half of 61,500 yen is 30,750 exactly.
R-Really? Did I say that?
What?
N-N-Not to mention...
It w-was my H-Harvest's job
to collect all of those.
I did it all!
Y-You two were just talking and did nothing.
And, if Josuke hadn't come up with the idea,
you never would have thought
of gathering up all those!
I would have eventually thought of it!
I'm an awesome guy!
Er... No, no... You never would have
thought of it with that pea brain of yours!
Hey, stop, Okuyasu.
Come here, fall back a sec.
This is just great.
Apparently he was fine with a few thousand,
but once it went over ten thousand,
he's much more hesitant to pay up.
I don't think he means anything bad by it,
but since he's got the mind of a kid,
no matter what we say,
he's gonna feel like we tricked him.
We should be the adults here and let it be.
We got 10,000 yen out of it,
so let's call that good.
I guess if you're okay with it, I won't argue...
But this just pisses me off so much!
Are you sure he's not taking advantage of us?
No, Okuyasu, there's no point
in fighting right now.
We just need to teach Shigechi how
adults actually make agreements.
Oh, so you can make more money?
You smug bastard...
But that's what I love about you.
All right, thanks. We'll gladly take this.
Okuyasu.
Are you thirsty?
Is there anything you want to drink? I'll buy.
You're going to buy it for me?
Then... I want some Calpis Water.
Then drink some.
Ah! Hey! Why are you throwing those away?
They're just worthless junk tickets,
like for the year-end lottery.
I told Shigechi to pick them up along
with everything else earlier.
You mean the losing New Year's Lottery tickets?
How do you know it's a losing ticket?
No one would throw away a
winning ticket, dumbass.
There are lots of people who forget
to confirm the numbers and
never get their prizes!
If this wins, I'm gonna take half of it.
Promise me, damn it.
Sure. Half is fine.
But if you win a sheet of stamps, I don't want it.
Exciting
Winning Numbers
List
You really like those cheap,
annoying ways of gambling.
Ah, that's no good... How about this one?
I wonder if we're allowed
to claim prizes from the
lottery if we're in high school.
Lottery?
It should be fine as long as you
have your ID and name stamp.
SG Group 121314...
Group
Payout Period
From 1/20/1999
To 6/21/1999
Nope, this one's not a winner.
I thought there might be a chance, but...
Hm?
Group
3rd
SG Group 121314... Um...
Hey, maybe, just maybe, if I won...
Do I have to take it to the police?
You idiot. There's no reason to take it there.
Harvest just picked them up
after people threw them away.
And you should only worry about that
when you're bragging after you win.
Good luck with that.
What? SG Group 121314?!
From 1/20/1999
To 6/21/1999
Payout Period
Group
SG Group 121314?!
SG Group 121314!
Winning Numbers
List
Hey, what are you yelling for?
Prize    5 Million Yen
5 Million Yen
5,000,000!
There's no doubt about it! I won!
What?! You better not be
messing around, damn it!
5 Million Yen
Yes! It's a dream come true! A fantasy!
There's no other experience like this!
Wait, wait, wait, wait!
Calm down, Okuyasu.
Let's confirm it one more time.
SG Group 121314, prize 5,000,000 yen.
There's no doubt about it!
It's too good to be true, but it's true!
And it's a lottery ticket
that was thrown away,
so it would've just gone
into the incinerator.
There's still a few days before it expires.
Even if they ask us annoying questions
when we go to cash it at the bank,
we can just proudly say that we bought it!
You got that?
Heck yeah, I do!
Which means it's our 5,000,000 yen!
I wonder what I should buy.
First, I gotta get some kewl Italian shoes!
Then I'll buy a high-end
suit with a sexy silhouette,
and go all-out at Tonio's shop
and eat the most expensive food!
I also want to go overseas somewhere!
I'm gonna put it in savings!
Man, talk about a boring life!
M-My Harvest is the one that picked that up...
Five million... Th-There's no
way I'm giving up half of it.
Episode 19
Shigechi's Harvest, Part 2