Edited at https://subtitletools.com
There's nothing in there.
Both pockets are empty.
Other than this piece of paper...
The scent is no longer in the pocket...
Could it be...
It's just a plain, white piece of paper.
What?!
Blam
J-Josuke!
July 15th (Thurs)  12:42 PM
Swip
Now you've done it!
You should really be more careful.
I told you that the floor up
here was burnt, too, didn't I?
I don't see anything out of the ordinary.
It's a perfectly fine back...
I-It's over... I'm finished...
I don't know why,
but I have this fear that if
someone sees it, it's all over!
H-Hey...
I'm already finished!
C-Calm down.
I'm sorry.
I just couldn't hold back my curiosity...
What?!
That's a Stand attack!
There's a Stand on his back?!
If there is, then even if I read
him with Heaven's Door...
I see. No wonder there was nothing written.
This architect had already been
attacked before he came here.
This architect was a victim
of the enemy Stand that's
going to attack me.
Carry me on your back.
It's here! The enemy Stand is here!
Carry me on your back. Okay?
Carry me on your back.
On your back... Carry me on your back, okay?
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
July 15th (Thurs)  1:39 PM
These are all the people missing
from Morioh, including runaways.
Episode 33    July 15th (Thurs), Part 3
These are all from after Kira disappeared,
so there aren't that many.
So there's a possibility that Kira's
victims might be among them.
I'm not sure about that,
but the possibility exists.
What's important is to not
miss any of his movements.
If a guy holding his breath makes
even the slightest movement,
there will be some kind of change.
*Address, contact information
available on a separate sheet.
Sex: Female
Age: 29
S City M Community College First-year.
Family includes father, mother,
younger sister, and younger brother.
Ran away from home after an argument
with her father in July, and moved in
with her boyfriend, Satoru Nakae.
A missing persons report was filed
the 6th of the same month.
She keeps in contact with her mother.
Dating Minako Okura.
A third-year at T University.
22 years old.
No matter what.
July 15th (Thurs)  12:55 PM
Carry me on your back, okay?
Carry me on your back.
Heaven's Door!
Carry me on your back, okay?
Carry me on your back.
What?! I-It can't be...
Has it possessed my back?
Did it transfer to me because
I saw the architect's back?
Damn it!
Burn the pictures...
Hey, burn the pictures.
Pictures?
Burn them, okay? Burn away those pictures...
What are you talking about?
The pictures I took...
Could it be there's one among them
that might get us closer to Yoshikage Kira,
and you're here to get rid of it?
Just burn all of them, okay?
Burn them away, okay?
Shut up!
Heaven's Door!
Let's see...
If I read about who you are
and write in some orders...
Ow!
What?!
I'm a Stand that was born when
Masazo Kinoto's back was
pierced with an arrow...
Cheap Trap.
But my user now is you, Rohan Kishibe.
You're my user now.
Wha?!
Do you get it?
It basically means that you're
using a Stand to attack yourself.
You get that? Okay?
I'm a Stand with a will of my own.
Even though Masazo Kinoto created me,
he couldn't become a Stand user
that could actually control me.
He could only hear my whispers,
and had only the fear that he mustn't
let anyone see his back, okay?
Do you get it? Okay? Do you get it?
Do you get it? Okay?
My ability is to just whisper to people.
Okay? If you get it, burn the pictures.
You bastard... Get away from me!
Damn it! Why, you...
How do I get you off of me?!
That's easy. You just have
to show someone else.
If you show someone your back...
Okay? I'll go away and transfer over there.
You just have to show someone.
Hello, Rohan-sensei!
I always read your manga.
Next time, could you draw a nude?
A nude girl!
Bye!
Burn the pictures, okay?
July 15th (Thurs)  12:47 PM
Josuke!
H-He wasn't shot.
Y-You asshole!
Shining Diamond, eh?
Well, looks like it's just as I heard,
and a bullet from a gun won't do much...
That was scary, right?
Bite it, Josuke Higashikata.
Bite your lower lip.
Are you gonna bite it?!
Bite it! Come on, just bite it
and show me your sign!
So this is his Stand?
Pretty crappy-looking Stand,
just like the old man in the picture!
Not going to bite it yet, I see...
Looks like he's covering up his fear with anger.
I guess I have no choice.
I'll have to show myself.
You've got some nerve, you asshole!
This is it... This creepiness.
He's been hiding all this time,
so why is he coming out now?
He showed up on purpose.
He showed up on purpose
so you would attack him!
He's dangerous... He's too dangerous, Josuke!
True... My Stand's ability
might be a crappy one.
But if I were to explain my ability to you...
I can make various things
into paper and file them away,
and it's extremely useful.
And this paper is Koichi Hirose.
You bastard... So that's
where you were hiding Koichi!
That's Koichi's scent.
He didn't have something of Koichi's...
He had Koichi himself!
He's alive, of course, because my
Stand ability is a crappy one.
I don't have the power or
ability to kill someone.
Though that's not the case if someone
rips it up, like I did just now.
I'll let you off the hook with just an ass-kicking
if you bring Koichi back here right now.
Just try and get him...
If you can.
Koichi Hirose
Koichi!
Because my Stand ability is a crappy one.
I don't have the power or
ability to kill someone.
Though that's not the case
if someone rips it up.
That's the trap!
If it were me, I wouldn't
go after that paper.
Josuke, ignore it.
You bit it! You finally bit it!
Misterioso was waiting for this
moment, Josuke Higashikata!
It was waiting for the moment you bit your lip!
You bastard...
You showed your sign of fear!
No matter how you resist,
once you've shown your fear,
you're powerless before Misterioso.
Thud
I feel bad for Josuke,
but I'm glad I didn't help him.
If I had helped him, that guy
would have probably
gotten rid of me first, since I can find scents.
Do you understand now that there's no power
in the world that can stop Misterioso?
Wh-What?
That metal rod is fixed...
He's trying to use that power to get out.
That paper there
is probably not the paper
that Koichi's trapped in.
I knew it was just bait with the name
"Koichi Hirose" written on it.
That's because the only reason you
were confident enough to show yourself
was because you were holding
Koichi as a hostage,
and it's because he's alive
that you can threaten me.
I knew that piece of paper was a trap...
It was, wasn't it?
But the reason I still tried
to save that piece of paper
was because there was still a
possibility that it was Koichi.
If there's even a 1% chance that it's Koichi,
then my only choice is to try to save him!
Misterioso, you win.
Looks like this is as far as
Shining Diamond's powers go.
However, let me just warn you of one thing...
If you turn me into paper,
you should immediately rip
me up and get rid of me.
If I'm able to come back
from this, I will kill you!
L-Look at you, talking big...
You weren't a big deal at all.
Koichi Hirose
Yuya Fungami, huh?
Not helping out Josuke was
a very smart thing to do.
I could have gotten rid of you easily.
Your sign of fear is to poke at
your chin with your fingers.
But the old man in the picture
didn't tell me to get rid of you,
so I guess you get to stay alive.
That's the smart thing to do.
Want to hear something
interesting about this paper?
Anyone can take out what's
inside if they open it.
It's a very simple thing to do, but it's
quite hard for someone who's in fear.
To Morioh Grand Hotel.
All right! We got rid of
Koichi Hirose and Josuke Higashikata!
Right about now,
Rohan Kishibe should also be...
July 15th (Thurs)  2:21 PM
Which is it?
Which picture has something
to do with Yoshikage Kira?
Which picture is the old man in
the photo trying to get rid of?
Burn them, okay? Burn them.
It's no use...
Right now, there aren't enough clues.
So let's burn the pictures, okay?
Shut up! You're annoying!
Damn it! I have to let them know...
I have to let someone know about this thing.
Mis
Miste
Misterio
Misterioso
Teru
Terunosu
Terunosuke
Terunosuke Miya
Terunosuke Miyamoto
July 15th (Thurs)  1:20 PM
Er, that was Morioh Grand Hotel, right?
Yeah, that's right.
Are you spending the night?
No, there's a lot there, so...
A lot there, indeed...
No...
You won't be going to Morioh Grand Hotel.
Josuke, you bastard!
Trying to play it cool...
If, just if, as stupid as this is,
if the one turned into paper
was one of my girls who
makes me smile every day...
If it was any one of my girls,
I would have done the same thing!
Letting you or Yoshikage Kira live
in this town would be totally uncool.
Hand over Koichi!
What you're doing right now
isn't the smart thing to do.
So you're saying that you want to fight me?
You're saying that you're going
to make Kira's dad your enemy?
Very well!
63, 64, 65 kilometers...
Though it lacks power, my Highway
Go Go will never stop its pursuit.
The taxi stopped...
Even though it's not at the hotel yet.
No one's gotten out of the taxi yet.
His scent is emanating
strongly from the car...
But where is he? Where is he hiding?
The scent of this paper...
There's no doubt about it!
This paper smells like Koichi and Josuke!
Wait, Highway Go Go!
Don't open the door just yet.
That bastard is underestimating me.
This must be another trap.
So he's trying to lure me in, huh?
Very well, I accept!
I said I would do it!
He's after my fear.
How is he going to try to scare me?
I need to find that out.
What? What is this piece
of paper stuck in the door?
Underestimating me again. This scent...
This piece of paper is the trap.
I figured out what kind of trap it is.
Open the door, Highway Go Go.
Foom
To think he can turn flames into paper, too...
But I saw through the trap!
Josuke, Koichi, I'll save the two of you!
But I smell something other
than Josuke and Koichi...
This looks dangerous to
just go ahead and open.
What is this?
A scent I've never smelled
before is moving around.
It's faint, but it's moving
inside the paper...
What?!
Crap! Highway Go Go!
Wh-What is this liquid?
I-Is it some kind of chemical?
Damn it, it's one thing after another...
W-Wait...
I smell iron from inside there.
C-Calm down. What he's after is my fear.
If he manages to scare me, he wins.
Iron...
What is it? A machine?
Damn it!
I have no choice but to open it!
Koichi Hirose
Josuke Higashikata
Josuke! Koichi!
Th-That's an electrical current.
He's even got electricity inside the paper!
The smell of machinery that I could
smell from this paper was...
A...
A shredder!
It won't turn off!
Josuke and Koichi are getting sucked in!
Damn it! Highway Go Go!
I-It's no use.
Highway Go Go's powers can't
destroy this thing to stop it!
Josuke! Koichi!
You finally touched it, Yuya Fungami.
You finally got scared
and touched your chin...
You look pathetic.
It was so easy to scare you, Yuya Fungami!
There's no one that Misterioso
can't turn into paper!
No matter who it is, it can do it easily!
Easy? That's why it's so great!
It turns anyone into paper instantly...
That's why it's great!
I lost. You really freaked me out.
But I'll gladly declare my defeat.
Because, now that I'm a
thin piece of paper,
I can stick my hand inside the shredder!
What did you just pull out?!
Don't you dare open up that piece of paper!
I'll gladly turn into a piece of paper.
Josuke Higashikata
Koichi Hirose
Yuya Fungami... You're...
actually sorta cool, after all.
Josuke Higashikata... Koichi Hirose...
S-Stay back, Josuke! Look at this paper!
I-I'll rip it!
Yuya Fungami is in this piece of paper!
Act 3! 3 Freeze!
S-So heavy...
Let's see, what was it?
There was something that I was
supposed to remember about you...
Oh, that's right. I remember.
I said that I would kill you.
That's right... I definitely said that.
I said I would never forgive
guys like you, right?
Guys like you
who take hostages and try to
threaten people emotionally...
W-Wait a minute!
I just liked observing other
people getting scared!
I just recently got this Stand, so I got cocky.
I-I apologize. I feel really bad.
There's something I realized
after watching you...
Huh?
You have a habit of closing one eye
when you get scared, don't you?
That's a habit, right?
But...
When you're even more scared, you close both.
You like observing? Then keep doing it.
Quietly and calmly keep observing.
I-I'm a book...
The Misterioso boy, Terunosuke Miyamoto,
became a book and is thus unable to fight.
Josuke didn't read the contents of the book,
but the book is at Morioh Library.
If you give the staff the title "Misterioso,"
they'll bring it for you,
though you can't take it home.
When reading this book, you sometimes
feel like you can hear a voice.
Well, that's that.
Morioh
Library
Or probably not at all.
Maybe this means that we're
getting closer to Yoshikage Kira.
Though we don't know anything.
Curses... Those resilient bastards!
July 15th (Thurs)  4:10 PM
It's no use calling for help.
Hurry up and burn the pictures, okay?
July 15th (Thurs)  4:30 PM
All right, I'm heading out for a bit.
Where are you going?
To find out what he's
going to do even quicker,
I'll check out the surroundings
of the missing people listed here.
People cannot escape the fate
into which they were born.
He'll definitely make his move.
July 15th (Thurs)  4:52 PM
I'm going to film it...
I'll film the proof that Dad isn't Dad.
No matter what.
Episode 34
July 15th (Thurs), Part 4