Edited at https://subtitletools.com
So that guy, Hazamada, says
he doesn't know anything
about the electric bastard
that killed my big bro?
Yeah. He said he's only ever
talked to him on the phone.
And you believed him, Josuke?
Did you torture him?
If Hazamada actually knew who that guy was,
he would probably have
already come to silence him.
R-Right... Just like my big bro.
Yeah. Seeing as how Hazamada is alive,
that proves he really doesn't know.
But Hazamada did say this...
Stand users, for some reason, seem to
be unknowingly drawn to one another,
even if they don't know each other.
They say that you're bound to
the person that you're going
to marry by the red string of fate, right?
It's sort of like that.
You just end up eventually meeting them.
They might be an enemy, a friend,
the guy who steps on your foot on the bus,
or someone who just moved in next door.
You just don't know.
Morioh's not very big...
I don't know how many Stand
users are in this town right now,
but no matter how they try to hide,
they'll eventually show themselves.
He knows that's going to happen eventually.
He wants you to disappear.
Damn it.
What a coward.
He needs to attack us already!
But that also means that he's cautious.
When guys like that attack,
it's probably only when they're
certain they're going to win.
Oh?
Hey, that's Koichi.
Why's he trying to act all cool, drinking tea?
Hey, Ko—
What?!
A... A girl?!
Diamond is Unbreakable
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Episode 8  Yukako Yamagishi Falls in Love, Part 1
Koichi, was me asking
you to come here, um...
a bother?
Huh? No, it's not a bother...
But I was wondering what you needed.
Wow, so Koichi's with a girl...
That chick's in my class!
Her name is Yukako Yamagishi.
All right! Let's get a bit closer!
If you wanted to see my
notes on some homework,
my grades aren't that good,
and my handwriting's messy.
If it's money, I can probably
manage about 1,000 yen...
Or did you want me to switch
weekly duties with you?
That's not what this is about.
Huh? It's not? Then what is it?
If you need someone to take
in a kitten or a puppy,
we've already got a dumb
dog named Police at home.
Koichi!
I'm just going to come out and say it.
Koichi...
I'm in love with you, Koichi.
Huh?
What?!
U-Um... Uh, um... Wh-What?!
You're the only thing I think
about all day, Koichi.
I've been so afraid to
express these feelings...
But if I don't, I feel like
my chest is going to burst.
I don't mind if you hate me.
I just thought I'd be brave and tell you.
Wh-What is going on? Did someone
just confess her love to me?!
To me?!
I can't believe it, but she
did just say that, right?
I-I'm so happy...
Why is it Koichi? You can't
be serious! Come on!
Even I've never had anyone tell me that!
You don't have to cry about it.
But seriously? I'm surprised, Koichi...
I'm sure that you must have
a girlfriend, Koichi...
Huh? I-I don't...
But, um... Are you making fun of me?
I'm serious!
Koichi, your face has gotten sharper lately.
You look like a man with
courage and conviction.
But you're also so cute when you smile.
Yeah, she's definitely got a point.
My face is pretty sharp too, isn't it?
I think the best thing
about a man is his future.
And Koichi, your future is shining.
Wh-When you speak that highly of me...
I'm sure you must hate girls
like me that aren't cute.
Huh? Not cute? That's not true...
Damn it, she is cute!
Just say yes already!
That bastard has all the luck!
Do you hate me?
Huh? Uh, n-no, I don't, but...
Then do you love me?
Huh? Wait a sec... It's just that, um...
So you do hate me...
Huh? That's not it!
It's just, when you ask me that so suddenly—
Which is it?! Do you love me or don't you?!
Just answer me already!
I've already told you so much!
I spilled my coffee! This is all your fault!
Um... I just got all worked up...
I-I'm sorry. I'm just...
By the way, you will come
see me again, right?
Y-You know... I feel like a
balloon that's been deflated.
All my jealousy just flew away somewhere.
Y-Yeah...
Let's just pretend we never saw anything.
Yeah.
What's wrong with this cola?!
Th-Th-There's so much... hair in it!
Stand users are drawn to one another...
Nah, it couldn't be.
Chemistry Lab
It's me, Koichi.
Y-Yukako!
What are you doing?
Um, as you can see,
it's my turn to clean the lab.
Fourth period was chemistry lab.
Ah...
Koichi...
I said some weird things yesterday.
Would you just forget all that?
I get that way when I think too hard.
It's so embarrassing.
People are supposed to be more broad-minded.
Uh, r-right...
It was a little surprising,
b-but I didn't think anything of it...
Will you still be friends with me?
O-Of course! I would be honored, yes!
Thank goodness.
I was so worried about
what I'd do if you hated me,
I couldn't sleep all night.
That's a bit dramatic.
And to make it up to you... Here.
I was up until this morning
knitting this for you, Koichi.
Thank goodness! It's a perfect fit!
I knew your height and chest size, but
I was worried how it would fit your shoulders.
Charm
I made you a good luck charm, too...
In hopes that you'll find a wonderful love.
I also prepared lunch so we
could eat it together...
I bought this shrimp at the
fish market this morning.
You can't find this freshness at a store.
See this flounder meuniere?
I personally took out all of the
bones, one by one, with tweezers.
Here. Say, "Ah."
Ahh...
There's one thing I know now...
Yukako Yamagishi, to be completely
honest, is extremely strange!
Ahh...
I have to hurry up and turn her down!
B-But if I eat this, it'll be like saying yes...
Ahh!
But if I refuse it, she'll probably get mad.
What should I do?!
Hirose!
Why are you wasting time?
You need to hurry up and throw this
garbage away before class starts.
I-I'm saved!
R-Right! Right!
I-I'd better go throw it away.
Ugh, you're useless.
Here, give me that.
I'll hold half of it for you.
Huh? N-No, I'd feel bad...
Just give it to me!
I'm the class rep, so I'm
the one who'll get yelled at.
Jeez!
S-Sorry...
Hey, you.
Would you stop bothering Koichi?
Koichi? You mean Koichi Hirose?
I haven't the slightest idea
what you're talking about.
I know what you're doing.
The stench of a homewrecker is all over you.
Homewrecker?! What are you talking about?
Listen well. If you ever
come close to Koichi again,
I'll make sure you regret it.
Just one second.
I tried to be classy about this, but...
Koichi Hirose?
I couldn't care less about him!
You have no right to tell me what
the hell I can or can't do!
Dumbass!
Ow!
What was that?
What the hell is her problem?!
She's not right in the head.
She actually likes Hirose?
Hmph. Hilarious. I'll tell the whole school!
Huh?
What is that?
Something's hot... Something's wrong.
Something's not right...
It's insanely hot...
W-Water!
S-Someone! I need w-wa...
Hey, Josuke...
Looks like Yukako Yamagishi
really was a Stand user.
Her Stand has hair that moves.
Yeah. But it doesn't seem like she's
an enemy, or going to attack Koichi.
By the way, Okuyasu, what are
you gonna do about her hair?
I can't fix something after
your The Hand takes it away.
She can't complain. I saved her
from getting burnt to a crisp.
Sorry, but I'm not a beautician.
Re
Rev
Rever
Reverb
Ko
Koichi
Koichi Hiro
Koichi Hirose
What am I gonna do?
Year 1    English Exam    Answer Sheet
Quiz 2     Koichi Hirose
This is my English test from earlier.
I'm worrying so much about Yukako,
I can't concentrate on anything else.
Even I did better! I only got 32 points, though.
To be honest, I was a little happy at first.
I'd never had a girl tell me she loved me before.
I get that. I totally get that!
So much it hurts!
But I'm the one who let it come to this
by not being up-front with her.
I'm thinking about telling her straight
that I don't like her or anything,
so she needs to leave me alone.
That's not a good idea, Koichi.
If you say that, you're only going to add
fuel to the flames of Yukako's passion.
You'll piss her off.
Y-You think so?
Of course! Listen.
Convincing Yukako Yamagishi not to use
her Stand of hair for evil will have to wait.
Right now, we have to figure out
how to make her not hate you.
But how?
No matter how strongly she feels about you,
if she gets an idea in her head that you're
a disenchanting, horrible, boring guy,
everything will be happily ever after, right?
Y-Yeah...
So you've just got to act that
way on purpose in front of her.
Yeah, that totally makes sense!
You're so smart, Josuke.
Thanks!
But hearing that from you doesn't
make me feel better.
I wonder what I need to do to
make Yukako think I'm terrible.
Well, most girls aren't into
bad hygiene or mama's boys.
I-I don't want her to think I'm a mama's boy!
She might get mad at my
mom and put her in danger!
Then it's bad hygiene for you!
Starting today, no more baths.
Huh?!
Yeah, and don't brush your teeth
or change your underwear.
How about getting some lice
or spiders in your hair?
Having smelly socks is pretty bad.
Maybe you should fart everywhere.
Yeah, she'll totally hate that!
Stop messing around! I'm serious about this!
I'm being serious, too!
You need a snotty nose and some drool, too.
What?!
If you don't want to do that,
then you need to become a guy
who seems like he doesn't have a future.
You need to make her give up on you.
We'll help you out. All right?
Okay...
What? Koichi Hirose did that? Unbelievable!
He was really shoplifting? That's awful.
Yeah! Koichi said so himself.
He was talking about it like he was proud of it.
You know what else?
Koichi never keeps his promises.
I lent him money, and he never paid me back.
He cheats on his tests
and steals girls' underwear.
He's got no future. He's gonna
bring about his own downfall.
I'm gonna stop hanging out with him.
I'll cut ties with him, too.
Man, that girl is intense.
Now as long as Koichi confirms he
did all of this stuff by tomorrow,
she'll give up.
Josuke, Okuyasu...
I hope they did a good job with all that stuff.
I hope she actually gives up on me.
What is that?
My eyes are closed... Is this a dream?
A woman?
I-It's Yukako!
I can't believe this. She's even
showing up in my dreams...
I can't rest at all!
It appears that your friends don't
think too highly of you, Koichi.
But don't worry. You have me.
I'll properly discipline you and
make you into a fine man.
You have something that other men don't.
You must live up to that potential.
J-Josuke! This totally backfired!
Where am I?
Koichi, are you hungry?
Breakfast will be ready shortly.
O-Okay...
She has that hair Stand...
I'm going to have to wait for a chance to run.
That's my only hope!
Th-There's something I want to ask you.
Yes?
Your hair last night... Wh-What was that?
Did that startle you?
Of course. I guess anyone who
suddenly saw that would be.
Around February of this year,
someone shot an arrow through my chest.
No, that might have been a dream.
When I woke up, my wound was healed,
and I was able to do that...
Keicho Nijimura!
D-Do you know anyone else who
can do anything like that?
No.
She hasn't realized that I'm a Stand user!
Now, have a seat. You're a growing boy.
If you don't get proper nourishment,
you can't become a fine man for me.
I-I just need to play along with her for now.
Wow, this looks delicious! I'm digging in!
You're not eating just yet, Koichi.
Koichi Hirose
English Exam    Answer Sheet
You got a 16 on your English exam.
Even if a man is more than just
his brains, this is just awful.
I've decided to have you study while you eat.
Understand?
I'm going to give you some questions.
You'll choose the correct
answer from boxes A, B, and C,
and you'll eat what's inside your chosen box.
W-Wait a sec...
You're going to do this!
While you live in this house, everything
we do must be for your betterment!
Right?
Here's your question.
Prince often sings the lyric "funky music."
What does that mean in Japanese?
Wild Music
A: Wild music.
B: Primitive music.
Primitive Music
C: Fantasy music.
Fantasy Music
I-If I disobey, I'll be in trouble...
B-But I have no idea what the answer is.
I have a feeling it's A,
but B and C also sound right.
Whatever, I'll just pick one.
I think it's B...
Squee! You're right!
I'm so happy! This box contains boiled eggs!
I'll peel them for you.
You want some salt, right?
By the way, if you had chosen box A,
I would have had you eat this eraser.
Wild Music
Huh?!
Box C contained soap.
Wh-What?!
Next, you'll be able to eat
bacon and eggs. Do your best.
Question:  How is "contrast" (taisho)
written in Japanese?
Is it taisho A, taisho B, or taisho C?
Taisho
Sh-She's serious...
If I choose the wrong box, she'll definitely
make me eat what's in there...
Come on, hurry up and answer!
The food will get cold.
U-Um, uh...
What am I going to do? This is ridiculous...
I-I think it's C...
Koichi, you just chose your answer by
watching the look on my face, didn't you?
Huh?!
So the rumors about you being someone
who's sneaky and shoplifts and
cheats on his tests is true!
As punishment, I'll have
you eat both A and B.
A is English vocabulary corn flakes.
B is asparagus wrapped in pages
from an English dictionary.
I'm going to make sure
you learn while you eat!
Here!
Open your mouth! I'll feed it to you.
What's the matter? Eat!
No way! You expect me to put up
with this?! I can't take it anymore!
I'm outta here!
I-I'm being pulled! By my scalp!
Th-There's moving hair mixed in!
That's right. I had planted a few hundred
strands of my hair in your scalp.
Koichi,
you may come to hate me.
But once you leave this house,
you'll see a much better man in the mirror,
and I know you'll thank me.
You'll realize that you need
a woman like me in your life.
You won't be able to live
without Yukako Yamagishi.
And just so you know, until you
finish eating plates A and B,
you won't be getting the next dish.
This is some company president's holiday villa.
No one will come here until summer.
S-Summer?!
Even then,
it doesn't matter if anyone comes...
Because love is invincible.
H-Help me!
Episode 9
Yukako Yamagishi Falls in Love, Part 2