Edited at https://subtitletools.com
The old woman in Egypt, Enyaba, told me
to shoot the arrow at those it desires.
They will become allies.
Those shot with the arrow
will be able to bring out just one
special power hidden in their heats.
I believe she called them Stands.
Jotaro Kujo and the others...
If there are others in Morioh
who are after my Yoshikage,
then I need to make more
Stand users, more allies.
Now, arrow! Who do you want?
Choose! Choose them!
Pull
A telephone pole?
How is the telephone pole relev—
Could it be... you want that child?
Are you saying that child will be my ally?
V-Very well.
I just have to shoot that child, right?
Diamond is Unbreakable
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Episode 26      Janken Boy Is Coming!
Well, if it isn't the manga artist, Rohan Kishibe.
Good morning, Mr. Joestar.
What are you shooting here?
I was sneaking some photos of
businessmen heading to work.
If Yoshikage Kira switched places
with someone at Salon Cinderella,
he should be going to work every
day, just like that person did.
Going to work...
Knowing he's a man between
the ages of 25 and 35
who's around 175 centimeters
tall and an office worker
narrows it down quite a bit.
I see...
But you can't be sure that he uses the station.
He might drive to work in a car.
That is possible.
But he only changed his face.
I don't think it's possible to change
completely into someone else.
I'm pretty sure that the family of
one of these men is already
starting to think he's acting bizarre.
What worries me is that,
if the family finds Kira out,
there's a possibility Kira will
get rid of that family.
I'm not trying to preach justice or anything,
but I just want to find
Kira before that happens.
Hey!
Mister, would you play janken with me?
Janken...
Hey, come on. It wouldn't
hurt to play, would it?
What's with this kid?
Janken...
There's always at least one
weirdo at any station.
Anyway, if you find any clues,
please let me know, Mr. Joestar.
And you make sure you don't meddle
in anything dangerous alone.
Hey, Mister. You're the
manga artist guy, right?
Didn't your series take a break not long ago?
I read Shonen Jump weekly.
So come on. It wouldn't
hurt to play janken with me.
What's with you? Beat it!
I wanna play janken. Come on, please?
What's with this kid? He has a hole in his cheek!
I-It's deep.
Hey, come on! Hey, hey!
Does it go all the way into his mouth?
No hard feelings if you lose.
If we tie, we play again.
If you shoot too late, you lose.
Got it? Ready, and...
Janken...
This brat is being oddly persistent.
Is he a Stand user?
Ready, and... Janken...
Heaven's Door!
Hmph.
Let's see...
His name is Ken Oyanagi, and he's eleven.
There's nothing about a Stand written here...
And it says the hole in his cheek was
from falling off a telephone pole.
Loves "janken."
Really wants to play "janken."
Plays "scissors" first.
It looks like this kid really wants to play janken.
It's stupid, but...
Hey, guys. Are you getting in or not?
Would you mind waiting about 30 seconds?
Here we go.
Yeah, all right. You just
want me to play, right?
Janken... hoi!
Well, see ya.
I... I lost...
I guess that's enough work for today.
Yo, Rohan-sensei.
Are you done with work already?
Why don't you sit down and chat for a bit?
It's the shitbag Josuke, the idiot Okuyasu...
And the moody Yukako.
All people with whom I have
nothing to talk about.
Sorry, but I'm still working. Some other time.
I see...
Hey, what are you doing? That's my seat.
You haven't sat down yet, have you?
This seat was empty, so I sat down.
Whoops.
What's with you? Why do you keep bugging me?
Let's use janken to decide
who gets the seat. Okay?
Again?!
No! I sat here first!
This seat belongs to me!
Sir...
Hang on...
Rohan-sensei, just let him have it.
He's just a kid.
Don't make him cry.
That's pretty immature of you.
Why don't you sit next to him?
Shut up! All of you, shut you mouths!
Fine! I'll play janken!
Janken's what you want, right?
That's the spirit! H-Here we go!
Janken... hoi!
Oh? Y-Yes, I won!
Take that!
I've never been so happy to
win at janken in my life.
So immature...
No, winning against a brat
is the best feeling there is.
D-Damn it!
I can use this as reference material.
Who knew a book on such a minor
subject was being sold in Morioh?
7,500 yen, huh...
Do I have that much on me?
Excuse me, can I get this book?
Why, you little...
Wanna decide with janken?
Fine!
Here we go! Janken...
Rock!
Stop messing around!
I won. See?
I finally won!
One win, two losses!
What the hell is this?!
Wh—
What?!
I-Impossible! Th-The hole...
Could he be a Stand user?!
What?!
S-So cool!
I didn't know something
so cool would come out!
Beautiful and magnificent
energy is flowing into me!
I'm feeling better!
H-Heaven's Door!
Make this kid into a book!
Open
Cannot attack Rohan Kishibe.
This kid...
seemed to be bringing out his
own Stand for the first time.
Could he be on his way to becoming a Stand user?
Hmph. "I want to beat the crap
out of Rohan with janken," huh?
"Janken is not about probability.
It's all mental, dependent on
how much you want to win.
Beating Rohan at janken means
you've beaten him mentally.
Rohan Kishibe is only 20 years old,
and he's already facing the world alone.
Not to mention, he's awed
many people with his works.
If I beat the crap out of someone so widely
admired, it means I'd surpass them.
I want to grow up to be someone
people admire, just like Rohan."
So this kid really is on his way
to becoming a Stand user!
He must have only just been hit by the arrow.
"Ability... When I beat my opponent
in janken, their energy becomes mine.
However, we have to play five times.
If I don't win three times, I can't take all of it."
Play five times?
Cannot attack Rohan Kishibe.
attack Rohan Kishibe.
Can attack Rohan Kishibe.
Wh-What?
That's so cool. So this
ability is called a "Stand"?
You may have thought you got away,
but I've already absorbed
one third of your Stand.
I-Its right arm is missing!
I can move one third of Heaven's Door!
I won't let you read my mind anymore.
You brat...
If I win two more times,
all of your ability will be mine!
You brat! Who do you think you are?!
You had some nerve to hit
me with your fist earlier.
That's payback, you moron!
It appears that in order to get
Heaven's Door's right arm back,
I'll have to win at janken...
Very well.
Good!
Match 2
Match 5
5 Matches
Match 4
Match 1
Match 3
He
Heav
Heaven
Heaven's
Heaven's Do
Heaven's Doo
Heaven's Door
Ro
Rohan
Rohan Kishi
Rohan Kishibe
Do you understand the situation you're in?
You can't lose again.
Do you understand that you're cornered?
Now that I know you're a Stand user,
I won't hold back anymore!
As soon as I get back my right arm,
I'm going to knock you out.
You know that, don't you?
Are you trying to pressure me?
All right, let's do this.
No, we're not doing that yet.
Since I just won using paper,
I would usually go with rock or scissors next,
but I think that might be childish.
But you don't seem that
simple-minded, Rohan-sensei,
so I was thinking about turning that
around and going with paper.
All right, I've got it.
Here we go!
Janken... hoi!
What?!
I did it! I forced my hand against
Rohan mentally, and won with paper!
5 Matches
Ken
Rohan
Now I've got two wins and two losses.
Now, then...
I took your lower half.
If you're tired, should we
head over to the bench?
No, there's no need.
When you win, it's best to be
looking down on your opponent just like this.
I've got two wins and two losses,
which means we're both on the edge.
But you know, I really don't feel
like I'm going to lose now.
After I lost twice at first,
I won twice in a row.
You're the opposite, Rohan-sensei.
You've lost twice in a row.
You're currently on the
downhill slope in this match!
This is amazing!
No wonder the arrow picked this kid!
If this kid is able to obtain
Rohan Kishibe's ability
to read minds, we'll be invincible!
It'll help out my Yoshikage.
You brat...
It seems you've gotten better
at pressuring your opponent.
It's the truth that you've lost twice in a row.
The truth, huh... Indeed.
In that case, let me give
you a dose of truth, as well.
In our next match, you will
definitely not use paper.
I'm not so sure about that.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hold it.
I used rock twice in a row and lost.
Which means that rock is the
unluckiest choice for me.
Am I wrong?
It's only natural that I wouldn't be able
to use the unlucky rock a third time.
Since you said I was on a downhill slope,
you won't be able to use paper.
If you use paper, it's like admitting
that I am actually not going downhill.
I'll force my hand and beat you!
Let's go, Rohan Kishibe!
It's on!
Jan...
...ken...
...hoi!
After all that pressure, he still used paper.
His mental strength is remarkable.
There's no way I'll lose!
I definitely still have the
upper hand in this match!
I'll use paper four times in a row!
I'm gonna force my hand!
All right! Rock! I'll get the
unlucky rock on my side!
One more...
Th-The strength in my knees...
What? He's using a different
form than before!
The only one Rohan hasn't
used yet is scissors...
Crap... Going with paper again is dangerous!
Crap!
I guess rock wasn't unlucky after all!
Damn that Rohan!
Th-That's...
Hey, Mister!
Hey, Rohan-sensei. Those two are
probably Stand users, too, right?
They are, right? I can feel it.
Let's test my luck.
If I'm out of luck,
those two will come over here.
If I'm protected by strong luck,
they definitely won't come over here.
Hey, that's Rohan.
Hey! Hey!
I really hate that guy.
Let's just smile and walk away.
Hmm... Well, hmm...
Menacing
That child...
I do believe he's...
a fan of his.
See you later.
See ya.
It looks like strong luck is
on my side, Rohan-sensei.
I feel like there's no way I can lose right now,
because I'm protected by strong luck!
Right now, I feel like I could
survive Russian roulette
with five out of six bullets in the chamber!
Crash
It's a shower of glass!
Now, let's have our final match
to see who'll win, Rohan-sensei!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and get into your janken pose.
You're the one who needs to
hurry up and get started.
I'm going to go with this.
Stop messing around.
No, I'm dead serious.
You said you were going to surpass me,
but since I've lived nine years longer
than you, I'll let you in on something...
It's not very hard to make others lose.
The most difficult thing is...
Listen carefully, now...
The most difficult thing is
to surpass yourself!
I'm now going to surpass my own luck!
Let's go, Rohan!
It's on!
Janken hoi!
Yes! How's that, Rohan Kishibe?!
Wh-What?
What?!
Huh?
Wh-What the?
Why is my hand shaped as rock?!
Now I have three wins and two losses.
You have the unlucky rock.
Strong luck came to me a moment ago,
along with Joseph Joestar.
The Invisible Baby.
Huh?!
Will save Rohan when he's in danger.
Will become invisible and make the kid's hand into "rock."
You only relied on your strong
luck, and I changed my luck.
That's what it means to surpass yourself.
Boom
Now, then. I'm going to knock
you out now, as I promised.
I'll write,
"You'll never be able to win at janken again.
Your Stand will be destroyed."
Sh-Shut up!
Stay away from me, Rohan!
O-Otherwise, this baby's gonna...
Do you understand what you're doing?
Hmph! Right now, our match
is a verbal argument!
You haven't really won against me!
You won because you cheated, you coward!
Let the baby go.
Fight me one more time!
Then I won't do anything to this baby.
And I'm telling you to let the baby go.
I'll fight you.
I'll make you lose! Janken, hoi! Hoi! Hoi!
I-I-I can't win!
D-Damn it! I made you into a
Stand user and you still lost!
See ya!
You won't die.
I'm just going to destroy your Stand.
If...
If I have to obey what you write...
If I'm going to be mentally controlled by you...
I'd rather die like this!
Take that, Rohan Kishibe!
Pfft
Nice. I like you, kid.
I feel moved when I see people who are...
Dash
dramatic like you!
Wha?!
Y-You'll be run over, too!
You think so?
What the? Th-The wind!
Whoa, what the hell is this picture?!
I-I can't see in front of me!
I-It avoided us and drove by?
Y-You could have died, too,
but you did that for me...
Was it strong luck?
You've become quite impressive
in such a short time.
I won't knock you out.
However, don't use that
Stand for evil anymore.
I carelessly bumped into it, damn it!
I lost. I've completely lost.
Hey, Rohan!
D-Did you see the baby?
She's missing, Sensei!
N-No, it might be that we just can't see her.
C-Crap...
She's gone.
Hey, where are you?
I'll just pretend I don't know
and look with them...
Wh-Where did you go? Where are you?
Janken Kid. Real name: Ken Oyanagi.
Hey!
Stand name: Boys Man Man.
Unable to fight.
For some reason, the hole
in his cheek is still there.
Episode 27
I'm an Alien