Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 3  The Nijimura Brothers, Part 1
Yeah. The issue with Angelo's been resolved.
But I won't be coming back for a while.
That other photo we've been investigating...
Send it over, too.
Yeah, the one that the Speedwagon
Foundation found in Egypt ten years ago.
I think I might finally know what it means.
Please.
Yeah, thanks to him.
Josuke! I killed your grandpa,
but you have no right to kill me!
If you kill me, you'll end up
a cursed soul, just like me!
Don't go telling people what
they can and can't do.
M-M-My right hand! My hand!
No one's going to execute you.
Not me, and not Jotaro, either.
You're not going to be executed,
and you're not going back to jail.
Josuke, I'll leave the rest to you.
Wh-What do you plan to do
with me, you bastards?!
Repent for eternity, Angelo!
For all of those you killed,
including my Gramps!
Damn it...
Don't you dare get cocky!
I'm sure he'll kill you both for me.
What? "He"?
That's right. The one wearing a school uniform,
who gave me this power.
What?
It can't be...
Are you saying someone can
willingly give another a Stand?
Are you scared?
Huh? How is that supposed to scare us?
No... Angelo's not a Stand user by birth.
It was a mystery how he
obtained his Stand powers.
But if there is actually a person
who can give others Stands...
Terrifying, isn't it?
Want me to tell you?
It was last year, so 1998,
on a night about a month
before my execution.
I couldn't sleep that night...
I was just staring blankly
up at the ceiling of my cell.
It was a completely silent night.
But then...
I should've been the only one in that dark cell,
but he was there.
The guy in the school uniform.
H-Hey! How long have you been there?!
Where'd you come from?!
Wha...
It was a very old bow and arrow.
It looked like it was centuries old.
Wh-What are you doing?
I was so scared, I could almost
feel my balls shriveling up.
But before I even had a chance to scream...
You're alive. Congratulations.
That means you've got the aptitude.
If you didn't, you'd be dead.
You've just obtained a talent.
No... It's more accurate to say
it was pulled from your mind.
The worse the villain, the more they have...
This talent that the man
named Dio called a "Stand."
Dio?
Did you say Dio?
Jotaro? Is something...
What?!
You fools!
It looks like you were so busy
listening to my story that you
forgot about my Aqua Necklace!
Angelo, you bastard!
Josuke! Hurry up and get me out of this rock!
It would appear that...
I didn't have enough rage in my heart for you.
What are you doing? Stop messing
with your stupid hair!
I'm gonna kill this brat!
Let me out right now!
What did you say...
Don't be rash, Josuke!
...about my hair?
Y-You know... If you kill me,
the guy in the school uniform won't let it slide!
He lives in this town, too!
What? Josuke, wait!
Ker-Blam
Yeah... I just didn't have enough rage earlier.
I needed to do a great job of burying
that asshole into the rock, like this.
Good grief.
I wanted to get a bit more out of him.
Huh? You actually believe
the crap he was saying?
It wasn't crap. He said Dio's name.
Who is that, anyway?
He's a man that the Joestar family has
been fighting for over a hundred years.
My friends and I fought Dio and defeated him.
But there was one thing
that I didn't understand.
Back in 1987, why did the man
called Dio suddenly acquire a Stand?
Could the same person
have made him a Stand user?
Yeah... The guy in the school
uniform might be our new enemy.
Or perhaps it's the bow and arrow he had.
If that's somewhere in this city...
Then it's hard to believe that
Angelo's the only danger here.
Good grief...
Morioh City Report
It's just like Jotaro said.
There's no doubt that the worst thing
imaginable is hiding in this city.
An extremely terrible danger
is coming to this city...
No, it's already begun.
Since the beginning of this year, 1999,
81 people have disappeared in Morioh City.
Abductions & Kidnapping Cases
Of that number, 45 of them
were young boys and girls.
Even if some were runaways,
Have You Seen This Person?
that's still seven to eight times greater
than Japan's national average per city.
That number is extreme.
Not to mention...
Ryohei Higashikata Dead
(Morioh Police Officer)
Josuke's grandfather...
Koichi, you're even studying after school?
Let's go home.
Oh, right.
Thank goodness. Josuke
seems to be feeling better.
Yo, Angelo.
Uh... Huh? Hey, was this rock always here?
Yeah, but it didn't look like this at first.
At first?
Well, whatever. Yo, Angelo...
By the way, what happened to Jotaro?
Oh, he said he had something
he wanted to look into.
He's staying at the Grand Hotel.
Does it have to do with this city?
I'm sure it does.
I see.
The danger this city faces...
Huh? Josuke?
No one's lived in this house for
about three or four years, right?
Yeah. It's so run-down that
there's no way it'd sell.
It should be torn down and rebuilt.
No, someone's living here.
Maybe someone moved in?
There was someone in the window just now.
Huh? Nah, that can't be.
My house is over there, right?
I'd know right away if someone moved in.
Besides, realtors are always checking
to make sure homeless people don't crash there.
Now that you mention it, that's true.
How strange. I wonder if I actually saw a ghost...
H-Hey, don't say stuff like that.
Ghosts are scary! And we're
right in front of my house.
Stop gawking at my house, little brat.
Billion
Say something!
Koichi!
Hey! What the hell do you think you're doing?
What? That's my line.
You two are in front of my house...
Morioh City Landmark 1
The Angelo Stone
How to get there: A minute's
walk from Morioh City
Johzenji Street Bus Stop #3.
The Angelo Stone
is known as a landmark,
and a place where lovers meet.
It's admired by
the people of the city,
despite its creepy appearance.
Give it a rest.
If you're the newspaper guy,
I already told you we don't want it.
Who is it?!
My father just died of a stroke,
and we're still busy with
everything that follows.
Could you come back another time?
Y-You're...
Jo...
Joseph!
You finally came back, Joseph!
I was waiting for you this whole time!
I've been so sad and lonely since my dad died.
I can't believe you showed up
at a time like this, Joseph!
I love you, I love you, I love you,
I love you, I love you, I love you!
I hate to disappoint you,
but I'm not Joseph Joestar.
Huh?
Take a good look. No wrinkles.
Oh... Now that you mention it...
You're pretty young!
Good grief...
I'm Joseph's grandson. My name's Jotaro Kujo.
O-Oh, really?
Ask Josuke for the rest of the details.
I hate annoying conversations.
I'm here to see Josuke. Is he here?
I'm asking you where Josuke is.
Huh? Oh! Josuke hasn't come
home from school... yet.
I see... Then I'll be back tonight.
Huh?
You're leaving already?
Oh, yeah...
About your father...
Huh?
It's a shame.
If Joseph Joestar had come to this city,
he would have protected you as best
he could from the dangers to come.
But he's old now.
I can't let him come here.
I'm here in his place.
I just can't feel at ease.
The bow and arrow that
Angelo was talking about...
In documents the Speedwagon Foundation
obtained regarding the witch, Enyaba...
She's holding the bow and arrow.
They give ordinary people the power of a Stand.
Damn, that's unbelievable...
No Trespassing
Are you insane?
Let him go.
No Trespassing
My father bought this house.
Don't go digging around here.
Never do it again!
I'm not talking about that.
I'm telling you to let go of him, bastard.
If you don't let him go now,
I'm gonna get pissed off.
Come on, now. "Bastard" is a bit much, ain't it?
Calling someone you just met a bastard
right in front of their house...
Do you even know how to talk to people?
Well, I know how to shut that mouth of yours.
Stab
What?!
Bro?!
Do you wanna know why
I shot him with the arrow?
Because that guy is Josuke Higashikata.
Oh, really? He is?
Since he defeated Angelo,
that means he's a Stand user
who'll be trouble for us, too.
A Stand user?! You two are Stand users?!
Okuyasu! Make Josuke Higashikata disappear!
Koichi...
Hmph! I was hoping I could
make him into a Stand user
that I could use like the others,
but I guess that's not happening.
He's gonna die.
M-Move!
I can still heal his wounds
with my Shining Diamond!
No!
Josuke Higashikata! I, Okuyasu
Nijimura, will make you disappear
with my The Hand!
Here we go!
If you don't move, I'm seriously
going to mess up your face.
You're pretty fast.
Hey, Okuyasu.
Using a Stand is the same as
driving a car or riding a bike.
Dipshits with no skill or guts
will get scared and maneuver like crap,
no matter what kind of
monster machine they ride.
Bro...
Please don't say things
that'll piss me off too much.
This bastard's much faster than I thought.
We're not messing around here, Okuyasu!
The Stand that you acquired, The Hand,
gives me chills just thinking about it.
You'd better be serious when you use it.
Make sure you kill Josuke Higashikata,
who defeated Angelo, no matter what!
He's bound to get in our way.
I know—
Ah! I was talking!
Th-That's not fair!
You're pretty stupid, aren't you?
What? Why?!
Why do you think tha—
I told you to move.
Koichi!
Thank goodness. You're still alive.
Then I can still save...
That's it! You're gonna pay for that!
I told you to move!
Get any closer and you'll really piss me off!
Take your best shot, if you can!
He's got way too much
confidence in his right hand.
This isn't good.
I've got a really bad feeling
about that right hand of his...
Let go of my right hand, you little shit!
Yeah, it's his right hand!
Swoop
Why, you...
Don't you dare run away, Josuke!
Don't abandon your friend like that!
There's something up with
that right hand of yours.
Something's telling me it's not safe.
Think about that after you're dead!
Here I go!
Koichi... Just hang on a little longer...
No  passing
What's with that gate?
Something's wrong with it...
No... passing?
Stop walking backwards, you dumbass.
You're getting farther away from your buddy.
Come a bit closer!
That's it... The "tres" is missing.
I bet your Stand's right hand
scraped it off, right?
It has the power to scrape
away its surroundings.
No  passing
That's right, Josuke Higashikata!
Whatever this right hand
grabs gets scraped away.
And the parts that don't get scraped away...
close together, so it looks like nothing changed.
As for the part that gets scraped away...
Even I don't know where it ends up!
I can do this to guys who try to run away, too.
I scrape away the space between us! And then...
See? You came right to me.
You could call it teleporting!
This is the power of the Stand
even my bro fears, The Hand!
You can't run away anymore,
Josuke!
No matter where you go, you're...
always...
within my reach!
So weak!
You really beat Angelo like this?
I guess you just don't get that it's no use.
You're the one who's stupid!
Now die, Josuke!
You really are stupid, aren't you?
Why?!
Smack
Crash
Kaboom
That was close. Okuyasu Nijimura, huh?
That's a pretty great and terrifying Stand.
I'll be in trouble if he wakes
up and tries to attack.
I guess I should strangle him a bit,
just to make sure he stays knocked out.
It'll put the feeling of defeat in his soul, too.
One, and...
K-Koichi's...
That's enough, you bastard!
This arrow is very precious.
It's the only one there is.
It's my precious objective.
I just have to retrieve it.
According to Angelo's story,
it's this bow and arrow that
unleashed Dio's Stand powers.
There's no doubt about it.
That unleashed The World...
And after Enyaba died,
someone obtained the bow and arrow,
and is creating more Stand users in Morioh City.
I've got to hurry and destroy
that bow and arrow...
To make sure a villain more evil than Dio
doesn't appear with a Stand
more powerful than The World.
Episode 4
The Nijimura Brothers, Part 2