Edited at https://subtitletools.com
My plan is already finished.
What?!
Okuyasu's big bro was a pretty great danger.
Koichi, let's get the heck out of this house.
Huh?
Wh-What about the bow and
arrow that sh-shot me?
The bow and arrow?
Looks like Okuyasu's big
bro hid them somewhere.
Are we going to look for them?
Y-Yeah...
You know, I could swear they
mentioned having a dad around.
I took some pretty major damage,
so let's just leave for today.
W-We can't!
I-I'm alive because you healed
my wounds for me, but...
If someone else is shot with
that bow and arrow again,
they might actually die!
Here in this town!
S-Stay here. I-I'll go look for them myself!
N-Not to mention, I don't think
their dad is here right now.
I-If he was, I'm s-sure he would
have shown himself by now.
He's a lot braver than he looks.
He can be tough when it counts...
Or maybe just reckless.
But right now, we should really
hurry up and get out of this house.
Hey...
Wh-What? D-Don't try to stop me.
I won't.
Let's hurry up, snap that
bow and arrow in half,
and get the hell outta here together,
Koichi.
Jojo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 5  The Nijimura Brothers, Part 3
They have an attic. Maybe the
bow and arrow are up here.
Th-There they are!
The bow and arrow!
They're hanging on the far wall!
Hey, I think this was a bad idea.
There's something in there.
Is something chained up in there?
I-Is it a dog?
Those sounds can't be from a human...
I-It sounds like an animal.
No, I'm scared! What should we do?!
What should we do?
It was you who insisted on going!
Yeah, but...
We're just gonna have to do this.
Listen up, Koichi.
You're gonna kick in the door as hard
as you can on the count of three.
We're gonna scare it.
Then, I'm gonna run over and
snap the bow and arrow in half.
Got it?
Yeah.
Here we go.
One...
Two...
Three!
Grab
What the hell is that?!
Koichi!
Help!
That hand doesn't belong to a Stand. It's real!
That's a real body!
H-Help me!
Bleh...
I didn't mean to chop it off...
Wh-What the heck is that creature?
I can't believe that thing's
been living near my house...
Bleh...
Looks like you finally saw the
thing you weren't supposed to see.
You bastard...
That thing right there... is our dad.
My dad needs these.
Th-The bow and arrow...
I want to find a Stand user for my dad's sake.
That's why I can't let anyone else
have this bow and arrow or destroy them,
no matter what!
Is it some kind of disease?
Disease? No.
My dad's perfectly healthy,
and he's got an appetite.
But he just keeps moaning, and he
doesn't recognize me as his son.
So you were looking for a
Stand user to fix your dad.
Fix?
You gonna fix him for me?
That's not it, either.
It's the opposite.
I'm looking for a Stand user who'll kill my dad.
Dad won't die, no matter what.
Whether you smash his head in,
or grind up his body, or rip
things off, nothing works!
I just want to let him die normally.
I swore when I was a kid that I'd do
anything to make that happen.
And to do that, I need this bow and arrow.
Otherwise, my dad will probably
live like this forever.
Because my dad had some
guy named Dio's cells
implanted in his head,
so he ended up like this!
Dio? Did you just say Dio?
That's the guy Jotaro talked about.
Let me tell you a bit about the past,
Josuke Higashikata.
After all, you're not completely uninvolved.
Everything happened eleven
years ago, in 1988.
At the time, I was seven,
and Okuyasu was four.
We lived in Tokyo.
The world was carefree,
thanks to the bubble economy,
but at the time, my dad had no luck.
Our mom died of an illness,
the business that my dad
was running went under,
Luxury Houses
Nijimura Land
and he was in massive debt.
He would hit us for no reason all the time.
Our dad was a total loser.
But then, suddenly,
money started rolling in to my dad.
Even jewels and precious
metals, too, sometimes.
He wasn't even really working.
I found out later when I did some research
that my dad had apparently
already sold his soul to Dio.
He became one of his minions
in exchange for money.
It seems that Dio was looking for anyone
with Stand potential back then.
Somehow, he found out that
my dad had the potential,
though I have no idea now
what his Stand was like.
But one day... Even though it was ten
years ago, I still remember it vividly.
When I got home from school, around 2:00 PM...
Okuyasu!
Did Dad hit you again? That scum!
N-No!
Huh?
Dio...
Dio's dead...
That has to be why!
Dad?
Dad, let's call an ambulance.
It's no use! This isn't an illness!
The flesh bud has gone berserk!
I'm done for!
Dad!
About a year after that, he became
a glob of flesh that can't even tell
that we're his sons anymore.
Dio would implant his own cells into
the heads of those he couldn't trust,
and order them around when
he wanted to control them.
Dad had one of those flesh buds
implanted in his head.
I spent ten years researching everything.
About Stands, about Jotaro...
Then I found out about the
old woman named Enyaba,
and obtained the bow and arrow.
But as I learned all of this,
I also had to accept that
my dad would never recover.
Because Dio's immortal cells
had become one with him.
This is all he does, all day long.
Every single day...
Day after day, for ten years,
he uselessly scratches
around that box of junk.
If I take the box away from him,
he just cries for days.
It pisses me off.
Watching him just makes me
hate the idea of living.
How many times have I told
you not to make a mess?
He can be obedient if I discipline him,
but he never stops digging
around in that box!
Bleh...
Hey! You're the one who needs to stop!
He's your dad!
Yeah, that's right.
He's my father by blood.
But right now, he's as much
my father as he's not.
He's a man who sold his soul to Dio,
and got what he deserved.
Yet, on the other hand,
do you know how it feels, not being able
to finish him off because he's your dad?
That's exactly why I want him to die normally.
Once he's finally dead,
my life can actually begin!
Damn it! I told you to stop that!
It pisses me off!
Hey!
That's enough!
I can't let you have this bow and arrow.
No matter what!
Don't get the wrong idea!
I'll worry about the bow and arrow later.
Right now, that box has my attention!
Dogyaa
Do
Th-The box?
gyaa
I saw him grabbing at some paper scraps,
so I was curious about what it was.
I see now.
A family photo...
S-So there was a reason.
There was a reason for the
behavior he repeated for ten years.
He was looking for the photo
of his sons at the time.
He might not understand
what's going on right now,
but deep down inside,
he still has his memories!
Memories of the past!
The
The Ha
The Han
The Hand
Oku
Okuyasu
Okuyasu Niji
Okuyasu Nijimura
Instead of looking for a Stand to kill him,
if you'll try to find one that can cure him,
I don't mind helping you out.
But hand over that bow and arrow.
I'm gonna snap them in half.
You planning to run?
Big Bro, let's stop this.
Okuyasu!
Come on, let's stop all of this, okay?
You were still here?
Dad might get cured, right?
Even if his body doesn't go back to normal,
maybe his mind and his memories
will go back to how he used to be.
Right?
Okuyasu! What do you think you're holding?
Big Bro...
Out of the way, Okuyasu!
I can't turn back anymore,
no matter what happens!
I've already killed so many people in
this city with this bow and arrow!
Besides, I don't even think of you
as my little brother anymore.
Since you're not my little brother,
I can kill you without hesitation!
B-Big Bro...
You guys...
Do you have any relatives
here besides your dad?
Relatives? There's only the three of us.
Th-That's...
It came out of the electrical outlet...
Okuyasu! Stop spacing out, you dumbass!
Big Bro!
I'm taking this bow and
arrow, Keicho Nijimura!
I, who got shot by this bow and arrow,
and had my Stand ability awakened!
You think...
someone like you can handle
this bow and arrow?
Keicho Nijimura!
You said Stands depend on
one's mentality, didn't you?
Well, I've grown!
How else do you think my Stand,
Chili Pepper, grew this much?
Worse Company!
Shut up!
Th-That's...
Electricity!
Okuyasu's big brother is being
turned into electricity,
along with the bow and arrow!
Big Bro!
Don't touch me!
You'll be dragged in, too!
Big Bro...
D-Damn it! It's taking the bow and arrow!
Okuyasu...
You were always holding me back!
Big Bro!
Josuke!
I could have sworn I just saw
someone who looked like
the user looking in through that window.
Do you know anything about
that Stand we just saw, Okuyasu?
N-No. My big bro found a lot of
Stand users I didn't know about.
J-Josuke! Th-That's...
Okuyasu...
My big bro... deserved to end up like that.
There's no way he could
have lived a decent life.
That was his fate.
But you know...
In the end, my big bro...
In the very end, my big bro
defended me, didn't he?
Josuke, you saw it, right?
Yeah. I definitely saw it.
Your big bro defended you.
Is this Jotaro Kujo?
I don't recognize your voice.
Who are you?
That doesn't matter.
Jotaro Kujo, I'm asking
you to leave Morioh City.
I don't think I'll listen to someone
I don't know suddenly telling me to leave.
Would you leave, no questions asked,
if you were in my shoes?
I'm the one who has the bow and arrow.
I got it after I killed Keicho Nijimura.
I don't mind killing you either,
Jotaro, but I hear that
you have the ability to stop
time for a second or two.
You sound like a tough opponent,
so I thought I'd give you
a call and warn you first.
Are you also Stand user?
What do you plan to do
with the bow and arrow?
I don't plan on giving you any trouble.
And as long as Josuke Higashikata
doesn't try anything,
Unavailable Number  Public Phone
I won't do anything to him, either.
I just received this Stand ability.
I just want to have a little fun.
I'm fed up with my annoying life of
entrance exams and getting a job.
Are you a student?
What difference does that make?!
Listen! If you overstay
your welcome in my city,
I'm gonna kill you and Josuke, too! Got it?!
How many other Stand users are in this city?
Good grief...
Keicho Nijimura was buried
in Kunimi Peak Cemetery,
which is west of Morioh City.
The stolen bow and arrow remain missing.
Nijimura Family
Okuyasu Nijimura decided to settle down
with his father in Morioh City for a while.
And...
Josuke, would you get that?
Yes?
Hey, Josuke! Let's go to school.
Huh?
I'll be going to the same school
as you starting today.
Even so, you don't have to come and get me.
We're not in grade school.
Man, I had no idea your house was,
like, right in front of mine!
Yeah, you could call that a shocking truth...
Come on. Let's hurry up and go.
Oh, is that a friend of yours, Josuke?
Hi! I'm Okuyasu Nijimura!
Come on in and have a cup of coffee
while he finishes getting ready.
Really? Thank you very much!
Your mom is totally hot.
Pardon the intrusion!
This is just great... and heavy...
Episode 6
Koichi Hirose  (Reverb)