Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Today was another exhausting day.
I just want to hurry home so I can relax.
K-Koichi...
Hazamada...
Hey, how are you doing?
Th-Thanks for everything the other day.
Um, are you all healed up now?
Kinda. I was released from
the hospital two days ago.
Where's that bastard—
I mean, where's Josuke?
He already went home.
Apparently, he found an
invisible baby yesterday,
and there was a big fuss
over finding her mother.
Is she a Stand user?
Apparently.
The baby has only warmed up to
Josuke's father, Mr. Joestar,
and if he's not around, she turns
everything around her invisible.
So is Mr. Joestar going to be
in town for a while, then?
Probably.
I see. By the way, Koichi,
do you like to read manga?
Manga? Oh, I guess about as much as anyone.
Have you heard of Rohan Kishibe,
who draws Pink Dark Boy?
Pink Dark Boy? Of course!
I'm a huge fan!
Yeah? You like it?
I guess you'd call it "horror suspense."
There are some pretty gross scenes,
but the thrills that seem to close in on you
and the realistic characters
are great, aren't they?
Right, right!
Did you know that Rohan Kishibe
actually lives in Morioh?
Huh?!
What?! He lives in Morioh?!
No way! You can't be serious! Really?!
I couldn't believe it, either!
But I happened to overhear
some realtors talking.
I know it seems unbelievable, but it's true!
Hey, want to go see if we
can get some autographs?
Morioh Station
Rohan Kishibe's House
Yes! Of course I'll go!
Looks like we think alike!
Really?
Kishibe
Over there!
I think that might be his studio.
The light's on!
You're right...
I wonder if he has any other family.
I heard he lives alone.
He debuted at sixteen, and now he's twenty.
Twenty?! He's so young!
So he became a pro at my age.
There's no point in snooping around, Koichi.
Try ringing the doorbell.
M-Me?
Oh, come on! I'm ordering
you, as an older student.
I tend to get pretty nervous.
What? That's not fair...
Episode 14  Let's Go to the Manga Artist's House, Part 1
That face!
Rohan Kishibe!
He looks just like his picture
in the New Year's deluxe edition!
Uh, I mean... Rohan-sensei!
H-Huh?
Who are you two?
What are you doing? Playing a prank?
N-No! We would never!
Um, we're students at Budogaoka High School.
W-We're fans of yours, Sensei.
Fans? Of mine? You're readers?
So my address has gotten out.
N-No, um... I just happened to overhear it.
So, I know this is sudden,
but it would make us really happy
if we could get your autograph.
Fans of mine, eh?
That's good.
We might be on the same wavelength, then.
Huh?
Nothing, never mind. Pardon.
An autograph or two is no problem at all.
Yes! I guess it's a good thing we came.
I know.
Since you're here, would you
like a tour of my studio?
Huh?
You'll let us go into your studio?!
I'm already done with my work for
the day, so if you two would like...
Of course!
Then...
Pardon the intrusion!
Come in.
Wow!
Wow! Raw 4-color manuscript!
This is amazing! It has so much more impact!
I-I'm so moved! I-I-I'm so glad that we came!
How long have you been working in Morioh?
I moved here three months ago.
My family home is in S City,
but I lived here for a time when I was a child.
Tokyo is very convenient,
but it's pretty chaotic.
The environment is nowhere near
as calm as it is in Morioh,
and I can't work there.
Not to mention,
with the fax machines and
copiers we have these days,
I have a system where, given four hours,
I can send in a complete manuscript.
You could say there's no point in living in
the city now, other than for pointless status.
Um... So what do you do
for assistants or staff?
I don't have any. I draw it all by myself.
Huh? All by yourself?!
You draw 19 pages of such
elaborate art in just one week?!
I can draw them in four days.
Five if there are color pages.
What?!
On the remaining days, I have
fun going on trips and such.
I don't really like dealing with people,
and that's why I chose to be a manga artist.
If I had an assistant,
it'd be harder for me to work.
That's so amazing... Wow.
You're a genius!
Pardon me for a moment.
Whoa, a s-spider!
We really are out in the burbs.
There are a lot of bugs and spiders.
Um... Sensei?
I see... So this spider is
an Araneus ventricosus...
It can be found in houses and
mountainous regions all across Japan.
Though it is an orb-weaver,
there are some that make webs day and night.
By the way,
do you two know what it takes
to draw an interesting manga?
Reality!
Reality is the energy that breathes
life into a piece of work,
and reality itself is entertainment.
People often think that manga are
drawn from imagination and fantasy,
but that's not actually true!
For me, drawing something
that I've experienced,
or something that has moved me,
is what makes it interesting!
For example, in the city, people would just
be grossed out by this spider and kill it.
As a manga artist, you need to
know how its legs are connected,
where the eyes are, and how to tell
the difference between a male
and a female in order to be able to draw it.
Apparently a spider's webbing hardens
when it's exposed to the air,
but you have to know what
hole it comes from,
and what its innards look like.
When a spider's belly is cut upon,
how does it suffer before it dies?
You have to know these things
for the sake of reality.
That's so cruel!
Cruel?!
An amateur brat like you is
criticizing me, Rohan Kishibe?!
N-No! I wasn't criticizing at all! I'm sorry!
I should have a taste, too.
Manga artists are really strange people,
just as the world perceives them!
Very nice! That agonized expression...
Perfect example of how one looks when puking!
I should sketch it.
R-Really?
Now it looks fake.
Forget it. I won't sketch it.
It won't be of any use.
I-I'm sorry.
Autographs, wasn't it?
I'll go get a signing pen from the kitchen,
and bring out some tea, as well.
Oh, you don't have to...
But that's amazing! I had no idea...
Pink Dark Boy must be so amazing
because of how far he goes to
figure out all kinds of things...
Um, Hazamada...
I know we just got here, but, um...
Maybe we should go home.
Huh? Go home? You want to go home? Why?
This is a lot of fun!
I don't really have a reason, but...
I guess you could call it a hunch.
Though I'm not usually that perceptive...
I just suddenly got the feeling that
Rohan-sensei is a bit dangerous.
Dangerous?
Do you mean that he might be a Stand user?
No! Nothing like that. Just, um...
Just because Rohan-sensei's a bit unusual,
I don't think you should just
assume that he's a Stand user.
I'm not assuming that he is...
I just said I have a bad feeling.
Besides, if Rohan-sensei
actually is a Stand user,
wouldn't that be great for us?
That means I have something in common
with a famous manga artist.
But, all right.
If you have a bad feeling,
we can go home for today.
We can always come again.
But!
Only after I've looked at this
thing that caught my eye.
Thing? What thing?
Jeez, you're dense, Koichi!
On top of the desk, next to the phone.
Look carefully.
Oh! C-Could this be...
Yup! He said he just finished working, right?
I've been eyeing that carefully.
A manuscript for Pink Dark Boy
that's just been finished?!
Does that mean no one else
has even seen it yet?!
Once I get a glimpse of this, we can go home.
We should get permission first.
Koichi, you don't know manga artists at all.
These manuscripts, before
they've gone to the printers,
are a closely-guarded trade secret!
There's no way he'd let us outsiders read a
manuscript that hasn't even
been checked by the editor yet!
I'll have a look, then put it right back.
That's an even worse idea!
It's fine! It's not like it can hurt anything.
Huh?
What is this feeling?
It's always a thrilling manga, but is
this the impact of a raw manuscript?
I'm getting goosebumps!
It's so good!
Hurry up and turn the page, Hazamada.
I'm so moved!
It appears
that my manuscript was compatible
with you two after all.
I thought you would read it.
And only those who are the first to read
my manuscript, and are compatible...
H-Hazamada...
K-Koichi...
...will have their hearts opened
by my ability, Heaven's Door!
A-Ability?!
My hand!
K-Koichi! What's going on?!
Morioh Landmark 5
Manga Artist Rohan Kishibe's House
Get off at the Morioh Kotodai 2-chome
bus stop and walk 1 minute.
Area: A mansion situated on 103 tsubo of land.
7LDK plus an attic.
If you actually go, he'll pretend to be out.
There are a lot of things
recorded in the human body.
Everything from the moment you were born.
In order to read that, I will
turn you both into books.
Books that have your lives written in them.
Help!
You read the manga too, didn't you?
It's happening to me, too!
Hazamada!
This will cause you no actual
harm, so don't worry.
Wh-What are you trying to do?!
I told you earlier that for manga, the author's
sense of reality is important, right?
Which means reading about your lives and
experiences will offer me realistic ideas.
You can't get this from interviews!
You're going to tell me 100% realistically,
as if I had experienced it myself.
Koichi Hirose. Born March 28th, 1984,
at 6:27 AM at Red Cross Hospital in S City.
You were born premature at 2325 grams,
and spent a week in an incubator.
You're from a family of four,
and your older sister's name is Ayana...
I see...
It appears that your grade school and
middle school days were pretty ordinary,
and your personality is very honest.
That's very commendable.
You...
What is this ability that you have?! Reverb?
Someone other than me has an ability like this?!
You, too?
"Stand users!" This is...
Everything from April of 1999 on is amazing!
You've only had amazing
experiences ever since!
Josuke Higashikata, Jotaro Kujo,
Yukako Yamagishi, Okuyasu
Nijimura, Tamami Kobayashi...
I can't believe it...
This is amazing! It's so entertaining!
I just discovered the best material a manga
artist could hope for, Koichi Hirose!
Shining Diamond,
Star Platinum,
The Hand, Love Deluxe, et cetera, et cetera!
Wh-What do you plan on doing with us?!
I'm going to take your memories
so I can use them as material for my manga!
Reverb!
Please stop attacking us
with your Stand immediately!
Otherwise...
Are you going to have Reverb
Act 2 attack me with sound?
Yes! Please release me from your Stand!
I won't hold back!
I know. It's written on your 11th page.
You're far more timid than most people
and taken rather lightly by others,
but when it's necessary, you have
courage that can overpower your fear.
Truly magnificent!
I'm very impressed with you!
I'm sure my readers will
like your personality, too.
I'm not bluffing! I'm really
going to attack you!
Oh, shut up...
And just try it!
Reverb Act 2!
Crash
Huh? I-I missed?!
Did you accidentally miss
or did you miss on purpose?
Your control is way off!
Then how about this?!
Crash
Where are you attacking?!
Koichi, sadly for you, I have
put a safety lock on Reverb.
Huh?
You are now unable to attack me.
Safety lock?
Look... I've already written it into
your 11th page, right here.
I can not attack the manga
artist, Rohan Kishibe
I can not
attack the
manga
artist,
Rohan
Kishibe.
c
an
n
ot
can not
This is Heaven's Door's ability.
It lets me read people's experiences
via words and pictures,
and it also allows me to
write into your memories.
You will now never be able to harm
me in any way, shape, or form.
Wh-What?!
But that's all I'm going to mess with.
If I write in any more,
it'll make your life fake,
so it wouldn't benefit my work at all.
Let's see... I guess I'll
have a look at Hazamada, too.
Sensei! You are a genius! I admire you!
Huh... I see.
Let's see...
You sometimes feel relief after you've
picked on things weaker than yourself,
like kittens and small birds.
You want to force yourself on Junko from 3-E,
but you're too cowardly, so you can't.
Your balls often get sweaty,
and when you're adjusting them during class,
nothing gives you a greater thrill than
the thought that someone might see you.
You're an awful man.
There's no way my readers would like
you if I wrote you into my manga.
You're useless.
No fair! There's no hope for me!
Why?
Why are you doing this?
Even without reading about my experiences,
you're an amazing manga artist!
The world knows that!
You're living in this amazing
house at the age of twenty!
You're doing much better
than most people your age!
And yet, why do you need my memories?!
Do you think that I,
Rohan Kishibe, draw manga
for the sake of money and attention?!
I'm drawing manga so people will read it!
So someone will read it!
That's the only reason!
It's a very simple reason, but I
don't care about anything else!
So that people will read it,
I look for realistic material every day!
Listen well. Whenever I finish
a manuscript, I feel amazing.
Everyone feels great after
finishing work, don't they?
But that feeling only lasts for an instant.
It's only a little while,
because I start thinking that no one's
going to read my completed manga,
and my insecurities start to grow.
Then I get even more insecure
because, maybe next week,
no one's going to read it, and
then I might not know what
to draw anymore, and I might not
feel like doing anything anymore.
These feelings have been reoccurring
over and over since I was sixteen.
Until three months ago,
when someone shot me with an arrow,
and I gained the ability of Heaven's Door.
Keicho Nijimura...
Yes, that was also written in you.
I'm sure you two don't understand
the feeling of having found
the best material to use
for drawing a masterpiece!
But this is it, right now!
It's the best!
Koichi, I'm going to make your reality mine!
See, Koichi? Wasn't Rohan-sensei a great guy?
Aren't you glad we went?
Yeah! It was so much fun!
To Hirose
Rohan Kishibe
Not only did he give us
these great autographs,
he even served us tea and cookies.
I'd love to go again.
Yeah. Let's definitely go again.
Well, I'm heading this way, so...
He really was a great guy.
You'll never speak of this, Koichi.
Huh?!
Wh-Why?!
How did I lose 20 kilograms?
But I don't look any different!
It reads five kilograms...
The scale's not broken.
Th-This is impossible!
Th-This has to be the work
of an enemy Stand user!
Otherwise, there's no way
I'd lose 20 kilograms!
But who...
I need to talk to Josuke about this.
What's the matter, Ko?
Huh?
Me? U-Uh...
Wait... What was it?
What are you talking about? Weirdo.
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing. My little brother's
wandering around in his underwear.
What was it?
I could have sworn I thought about
something really important just now.
Well, if I forgot about it,
it can't be that important.
Man, my shoes and bag sure feel heavy today.
Huh?
Th-This house...
Why?
I somehow ended up walking to
Rohan-sensei's house without realizing it.
The door's open...
I'd like to stop by and thank him for yesterday,
but then I'd be late for school.
It's probably a bad idea.
He might actually still be asleep
since he's a manga artist.
I really shouldn't just barge into his house.
It's really not a good idea...
Hey, did you see that, Okuyasu?
Yeah...
We followed Koichi because
he was heading in the
opposite direction of the school,
but what the heck is he doing?
Whose house is that?
I have my doubts, but it's
not some chick, is it?
Rohan-sensei...
He's working so frantically.
But I wonder what it is...
I can't shake the feeling that
being here is actually terrifying.
What is it?
I'm glad you came.
I've been waiting for you.
You're right on time.
Episode 15
Let's Go to the Manga Artist's House, Part 2