Edited at https://subtitletools.com
This is Morioh City Radio,
and our next segment is
"Help Me, Midnight Discussions!"
Our first letter is from
"Forever 21, Pretty Baby."
"Listen to this, Kai.
I was late meeting someone
because of that thing again.
Yeah, the one by the station!
The railroad crossing that
never lets you through.
Ugh, it just goes ding, ding, ding, ding,
ding, ding... It just needs to shut up!"
Now, calm down, Pretty Baby.
Oh...
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
See ya.
Seriously?
Episode 7  Toshikazu Hazamada (Show Off)
There are Stand users besides us at this school?
Yeah. He's Toshikazu Hazamada,
a student in class 3-C.
This Hazamada guy apparently got into
an argument over something silly with a
friend right around the start of spring.
One of them had insulted the other's
favorite idol or anime or something.
That night, surprisingly, the friend
he got into the argument with
gouged out his own left eye
with a mechanical pencil.
Isn't that insane?
Apparently Hazamada's friend
said this at the hospital:
"Next thing I knew, I was staring at my left eye,
which I'd gouged out, with my right eye."
So you're saying that this guy gouged out
his left eye using some kind of a Stand?
Could be, but maybe not.
Normal people can't see Stands.
Something about this is really fishy.
What'd you say?!
Josuke, you've got no right to criticize me.
I've got a real job now, y'know!
Huh? You've got a job?
Yes, Master Koichi! I found myself a
little job that involves financing.
Financing?
You don't mean you became a loan shark, do you?
Well... It's a very reputable
establishment, though!
Still, though, we can't just ignore this.
Wait up, Josuke!
M-Master Koichi!
Are you going, too?
Just leave it to that idiot Josuke.
There's something scary going on in my town.
If Morioh City is in danger,
that means my parents, my sister,
and everyone else important to me
will have to face that danger.
So even if it's scary, I gotta do something!
Wh...
What a tough thing to say.
Nothing less from the man I've chosen to admire!
But...
I'll be heading home now!
Be safe, Master Koichi!
Yeah, totally.
Looks like he's not in the classroom.
But if that Hazamada guy really
did gouge out his friend's eye
and can still blend into normal school life...
He must be one creepy guy.
Hazamada
H-Hey, Josuke!
I'm gonna check out his locker.
Watch my back, Koichi.
Tell me first before you break it!
For starters... His bag is still here.
So he's still at school. Be careful.
R-Right.
So he's in the tennis club and likes manga.
Still, this guy's got way too much stuff.
I don't think the bow and arrow
would be in here, but...
What's this wooden thing?
A Sta—
N-No... This is a physical object.
Is this one of those dolls they sell
at art stores for sketching?
It scared me...
Huh?!
What? Why?!
It turned into me when I touched it.
But now we know for sure...
Hazamada is a Stand user!
This is just great. You've got
some nerve, turning into me!
You've heard of Perman, right?
I-It talked! It sounds and talks just like him!
You know the copy robot from Perman?
Isn't that thing convenient?
Don't you think it'd be great to have one around?
Hey, Koichi. What is he talking about?
What the hell is Perman?
You haven't heard of Perman?!
I can't believe it.
And you call yourself Japanese?
Shut up! I'm the one asking the questions here!
M-My arm!
Josuke!
But mine is a copy doll that replicates
people I don't want around.
Once it copies you, you'll
mimic all of its movements.
Which means it's not a puppet,
but a puppet master!
K-Koichi! Move!
Crunch
Koichi!
And one rag's been hung out to dry.
Oh, but I'm not the one who did it.
The one who did it was you, his friend.
Stuff like this
pisses me off more than anything.
When you don't do anything yourself,
but use others to do things for you.
That makes me want to kick
your ass like nothing else!
That's just great. Tee-hee!
Looks like you're out of range.
If you can't move from that spot,
your Stand can't get any closer, either.
Which means if I maintain this distance,
Josuke, you stand no chance against me!
This Stand's name is Show Off.
By possessing a doll,
it has gained a physical form...
Which means even normal people can see it.
Hazamada! You bastard!
My goal is to beat the shit out of Jotaro Kujo
and run him out of this city.
He's got some nerve!
An outsider, coming here and
trying to dig up dirt on us...
But I heard that his Star Platinum
can stop time for a second or two.
There's no one in our group that
stands a chance against him.
That is, no one besides my Show Off,
now that it's copied you, Josuke!
I'll have to knock you out now.
The genuine article would just be in the way.
Squish!
Crushed, huh? That's a satisfying sound.
As long as you didn't cut the nerve,
you'll be able to see again...
If you're lucky.
Looks like he's gonna be out for a while.
That was super easy.
Hey! Pick up my bag.
We're gonna go straight after Jotaro.
Easy enough.
I'm pretty sure the hotel that
Jotaro's staying at is...
Squish!
Uh...
The Morioh Grand Hotel.
Yeah, that's the one.
K-Koichi!
Koichi!
J-Josuke, are you okay?
Th-Thanks... But man,
you've really got some guts.
Even though you're hurt, you managed
to use your Stand to trick him.
What are you talking about?
That's only because,
as soon as I got hit, you fixed my
broken bones with Shining Diamond.
And, uh...
I'd appreciate it if you could fix the
injuries I got from breaking down
the door and window right after that, too.
R-Right!
Hello, this is the Morioh Grand Hotel.
Oh, uh, could you put me through
to Jotaro Kujo in Room 324?
Certainly.
Ugh! We have to hurry up and
tell Jotaro about that Stand!
Thank you for waiting.
The line for Room 324 is currently in use.
Please wait until the
current call is completed.
The line's in use?
What?!
Of course! It must've been the copy!
It called him before I did!
Are you certain, Josuke?
There's another Stand user at your school?
Yup! I'll tell you the details at Morioh Station.
Please come to the station plaza.
You should be able to get
there in fifteen minutes.
All right. In front of the
station in fifteen minutes.
Too easy.
I-It's no use! He's not answering.
He must have left the room.
They must have lured him out
to meet them somewhere!
Damn it! We're just gonna
have to go after the copy!
I really couldn't tell the difference
between you and the copy.
Yeah. What really creeped me out
wasn't when I saw its face.
It was the fingers.
You see your fingers more often
every day than your face, right?
I could tell that it had copied me
right down to my fingerprints.
Oh!
Josuke, you're early.
Where's Master Koichi?
H-Hazamada?!
What are you doing here?
Tamami Kobayashi?
You don't know why we're together?
N-No, I don't...
No idea at all?
No idea! Why?!
Then...
Good!
Hurry, please.
We've got to hurry and
catch up with Hazamada,
or Jotaro's gonna be in trouble!
Sh
Show
Show O
Show Off
Toshi
Toshikazu
Toshikazu Haza
Toshikazu Hazamada
9 Mi
9 Minu
9 Minutes
9 Minutes Le
9 Minutes Left
9 Minutes Left Un
9 Minutes Left Until
9 Minutes Left Until the
9 Minutes Left Until the Me
9 Minutes Left Until the Meet
9 Minutes Left Until the Meeting
There'll be trouble if Jotaro meets the copy!
It'll definitely be bad!
Yeah.
I don't know what we should do,
but we need to catch up!
Bye-bye, Josuke!
See you tomorrow!
Bye!
Josuke!
Bye, Josuke!
Why the hell are you the
only one they say goodbye to?
I've never had anyone say that to me.
All the girls in this school are ugly, anyhow.
Josuke...
Hey, read this.
B-Bye.
Why the hell did you accept that?
Rip this stupid thing up!
Damn it... What the hell is the
difference between you and me?
Why does that even matter?
Wha...
You don't have any time to waste, do you?
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?!
Ow!
You scraped your hand? That was dumb.
I'm made of wood, remember?
Shut up! Get away from me!
Damn it, I'm getting pissed off.
It's my own Stand, but this happens every time.
The other day, I had it copy my crush, Junko,
but I got pissed off because it
kept doing things to piss me off,
so I never even got anywhere.
Doesn't anyone in this world have
a decent personality? Damn it!
That stupid Josuke!
I'll hurry up and take care of Jotaro first,
then I'll crush him to bits!
I can't wait!
My bike!
It's dirty.
Damn it, that dumbass! I'll kill him!
Hey, it's not like he meant it. And he'll hear you.
Like I care! That's exactly why I said it.
Wobbling around like that...
Man, he looks like a dying cricket.
That's a good metaphor! I like it!
Yeah? It was a good description, huh?
Huh? What?
Hold him, Show Off.
I'll carve him up myself.
Wh-What are you doing?
You don't have to worry about that.
I'm just going to make sure
that you'll never be able
to open your mouth again.
S-Stop!
A shard of glass?
J-Josuke Higashikata?!
Why... And the shrimp, too?
Hazamada!
We finally caught up with you, asshole!
But did you already forget?
When you come face to face with
Show Off, you become a puppet, Josuke!
Control him, Show Off!
Don't be so sure about that.
Wha... That shape...
I didn't throw that shard to hit you.
I threw it so I could put it
back in its original form!
Swoosh
M-My right hand!
It turned back into wood!
This isn't good, Hazamada!
Calm down!
Just pretend you have
your hand in your pocket!
No one will notice!
The real problem is
that Jotaro should arrive at the station soon!
I'm shocked that Josuke was safe,
but let's give up on beating him right now!
H-Hazamada! Wait for me!
I see...
So they're meeting him in front of the station.
J-Josuke, we have no time to waste!
The way they went is the fastest
way to get to the station!
And that's why I've got you, Koichi.
Looks like Josuke's not here yet.
Can you see Josuke anywhere?
Nope.
If I see any sign of him,
I'll just take control of him.
Don't worry!
Ding Ding Ding Ding
Hazamada! A train's coming through.
The railroad crossing that
never lets you through!
We'll have to wait a minute or two...
All right. We'll go through the station building.
No Crossing
Emergency
Stop
Button
Even if he catches up with us,
the train will stall Josuke!
Just one more minute!
I'll head over to the meeting spot first!
I won!
Huh?
That's Josuke!
Wh-What happened to the train?!
Why's the crossing open?!
Hazamada, look!
Wh-What the hell is that Stand?!
Ding Ding Ding Ding
That was great! You see?
That's why I said I've got you.
Ah! There he is!
J-Jotaro! It's me, Josuke!
Hey.
We made it in time!
We got Hazamada good, didn't we, Josuke?
Did something happen?
A copy?
A Stand that copied you
down to your fingerprints?
That's right!
There would have been trouble
if he'd gotten here before me.
But now we can relax.
That copy bastard is missing
his right hand, so it'll be easy.
I blew off his right hand.
Use that to tell us apart.
All right.
They should get here at any moment.
Huh? Why do I have this thing?
Why did I get a pen out of Jotaro's pocket?
I-I can't move!
My arm just stopped moving on its own.
O-On the other side of the glass...
Th-That's...
Josuke Higashikata...
You're gonna stab Jotaro in the head
with that pen and kill him instantly.
After all, if his death isn't instant,
your Shining Diamond will just fix him.
Josuke! This is your fault
for getting outta line!
I was just gonna halfway kill Jotaro
to chase him out of town.
But now you're the one who'll kill Jotaro!
It'll be all your fault!
Now! Let him have it, Show Off!
J-Jotaro...
You bastard!
Something wrong, Josuke?
Huh? No...
Looks like those guys finally found Hazamada.
You little shit!
You were just across the pedestrian bridge
at the station, just like that Josuke said.
He's a great guy.
He treated our wounds, and I'm not
even sure how, but they're all better!
I'll make sure I pay you back in full for earlier.
Let's take a little trip behind the restroom.
That Stand is pretty
terrifying if it catches you.
Well, I guess I'll break this doll now.
It'll make me feel better.
Meanwhile, unknown to anyone else,
Tamami was admitted to the hospital.
What a fool!
Well, you have my condolences.
Episode 8
Yukako Yamagishi Falls In Love, Part 1