Edited at https://subtitletools.com
There it is... The old man's ship.
Right on time.
It's about twenty minutes away.
I-Is Mr. Joseph Joestar the only passenger?
Yeah.
The entire crew is from
the Speedwagon Foundation.
The Stand Chili Pepper can only
move where there's electricity,
but I'm sure he'll do everything possible to get
over the water and onto the old man's ship.
If he gets there before we do, we lose.
The old man will be killed.
Jotaro!
We've finished checking the boat.
He's not in the battery.
All clear. We can take off.
Josuke, the only ones going to the
old man's boat are me and Okuyasu.
Huh?
You and Koichi will stay behind at the harbor.
Stay behind?! Josuke and me?
Why?
Josuke, Chili Pepper's user is hiding
somewhere in this harbor, watching us.
He's waiting for us to make our move,
so he can confirm the boat's position.
But my guess is that he won't be using a boat.
All he needs is something with a battery
that's faster than a motorboat.
Morioh Harbor
Lighthouse
Just like he did with the bike,
he'll have Chili Pepper fly over
in something that has a battery.
Fly? You mean it's actually
going to fly through the air?
Yeah.
I'm guessing Chili Pepper is
stealing a remote control model plane
from the model shop right now.
A remote control model plane?!
That could work!
Even model planes can travel over 100 kph!
That's faster than this motorboat.
And because Chili Pepper is controlling it,
he can keep going as long as
the battery and fuel last!
The controller signal's range won't matter!
So Josuke, if you spot something flying,
look for his user here at this harbor.
Koichi's Reverb has a range of 50 meters.
He can help find him.
If he makes his move before we do,
the old man is finished.
You need to protect your father
from on-shore. Got it, Josuke?
Yeah, I get it. We don't have
even a second to spare.
JoJo's Bizarre Adventure
Diamond is Unbreakable
Episode 12  Chili Pepper, Part 2
Do your best, Okuyasu.
Thanks, Koichi.
We'll arrive at Morioh Port in about
twenty minutes, Mr. Joestar.
I see. Um...
Do you know where my cane is?
Huh? It's right in front of you.
Ahh...
My father, huh...
Josuke? Is something the matter?
Being told that some guy I've never
met is my father is just kinda...
You know...
Well, it's different if his life's in danger.
I won't be able to sleep well unless
I do my best to protect him.
Besides, I'm sure my mom
will bawl her eyes out if he dies.
Damn it! It must have been Jotaro.
If he had you two stay behind to find my user...
Then he completely saw through my
plan to use a remote control plane!
Chili Pepper!
Yeah!
Jotaro Kujo is a smart man.
Yeah, he's the one person
I don't want finding me.
This Spitfire remote control plane
can get to Joseph Joestar
in a mere five minutes.
On the other hand, a motorboat will
take about eight to ten minutes.
Which means if I take care of
you two in about three minutes,
I'll have plenty of time to get past them.
Y-You're Chili Pepper's user?
The name's Akira Otoishi, nineteen years old.
Oh, and don't mind the guitar.
My dream is to one day
be an ultra super guitarist,
like Jimi Hendrix and Jeff Beck,
who lives hard and passionately!
So I keep it with me all the time.
In the near future,
I'm going to take my guitar
and knock out people around the world!
Oh, yeah.
I never even thought that the user
would show himself on his own.
That must mean he's confident that
he can kill both me and Josuke!
Yeeees
I'll only use my pinky finger
against your Shining Diamond,
just like I did with Okuyasu earlier.
Stay back, Koichi.
Here we go, Josuke Higashikata!
One sec.
Huh?
If you're going to use only your pinky,
then I'm gonna make some rules, too.
Rules? Don't get cocky!
Someone like you doesn't need any rules!
How dare you do that, you bastard?!
Well, you said I didn't need any rules.
Didn't you say something about taking
care of me with just your pinky?
So what are you going to do,
Otoishi, my senpai?
I'm going to kill you.
You already said that earlier!
Stop saying the same thing
over and over, you dumbass!
This agony and pain...
What am I supposed to take it out on?
This rage...
Who do I proclaim it to?!
He's amazing...
Right-Hand Tapping
I'm going to kill
your mommas, too!
I was able to fully express my heart!
I was able to express the ultimate rage.
Just try it, Otoishi!
Wh-What? The user just...
I can understand his Stand
moving at amazing speeds,
but the user himself was actually
able to move behind me?
Th-That's not it, Josuke!
I saw what happened from here.
It wasn't Otoishi that moved...
It was you!
You were moved!
What?
Chili Pepper came out and
turned Shining Diamond
180 degrees at incredible speed!
You're facing the ocean, aren't you?
Chili Pepper came out?
Koichi! I haven't seen Chili Pepper at all!
He's underneath the ground!
See all the drainage grates around you?
His upper body came up from there just now!
There must be electrical wires
running all over under there!
I'm strong when I reflect on my actions.
Behind you to your right! There it is!
Now it's behind you!
It keeps running back into
the electrical wires!
And at light speed!
Jotaro's the only one who
can keep up, after all!
You don't have time to dig up the asphalt
and cut all the wires underground,
Josuke Higashikata.
And the more big holes
you make in the ground...
The more places I can pop up from!
Josuke! To your right!
In front of you!
Behind you!
No, wait! Um...
It's like insanely hard whack-a-mole!
He's moving too fast for me
to tell where he'll come from!
You should really stop relying on guesswork!
Josuke...
And I still have two minutes left...
That's plenty of time to finish you.
Koichi, watch where Chili Pepper
comes from and tell me.
I can't tell because I'm too close!
I-I can't tell, either!
Every time I think he's out, he goes back in!
Watch carefully, Koichi.
You should be able to tell
what I'm thinking by now.
Huh? What you're thinking?
I-It's all squishy!
The asphalt's been turned into coal tar...
And the grates are covered by
the oil film from the coal tar!
I got it!
When he hit the ground earlier,
he turned the asphalt's base into
something else when he fixed it!
Which means...
Behind you, to your left!
Gurb
Yeah! Bull's eye!
Bull's eye? That's great.
Do I get a prize
if I keep hitting him?
Chi
Chili
Chili Pe
Chili Pep
Chili Pepper
Akira
Akira Oto
Akira Otoishi
It's the boat! I can see the Traffic!
W-We're almost there!
Don't let your guard down yet.
Huh?
Wh-What the hell is that?
Josuke! Koichi!
I-It's so bright!
It seems that I wasn't taking you
seriously enough, Josuke Higashikata.
I have to give up these foolish thoughts,
don't you think?
I'm concentrating all of Morioh's
electricity on my Chili Pepper.
The reason I didn't do so before
is because the electricity of this whole
area, which is my power source,
would be drained to zero for a while!
But I don't care anymore!
After I defeat you two, I just need to
fly over there using the RC plane's battery
and kill Joseph!
I-I can't see!
You bastard...
J-Josuke actually got overpowered!
Josuke!
Do you see?
All of this town's electricity is on my side!
I'll be sure to tack the
cost of all the electricity
I just used onto your meter.
This is the end, Josuke!
A t-tire?!
By the time you realize it,
it's probably too late.
You blew up that tire on purpose, didn't you?
So you could fix it and trap my
Stand inside the tire's rubber!
That's right! Tire rubber is an insulator,
so it doesn't conduct electricity!
Chili Pepper won't be
able to use electricity!
Damn it!
Yes! Now we just have to wait for Jotaro...
Just kidding.
Huh?
You were going to insulate
me with tire rubber?
It might have worked if it
were about a meter thick!
Don't make me laugh!
As if this flimsy rubber
could have done anything!
You dumbass!
Bomu
You've lost, Josuke!
Great. You would have been much better off
if you didn't have the power
to break through that tire.
Th-The air from inside the tire!
It was completely full?!
N-Not the ocean! The ocean is very bad!
O-Oh, yeah...
Salt water conducts electricity.
Since the ocean's so vast, the electricity
will spread out in every direction!
I'm sorry! Please!
Pull me out of here!
You said something about reflecting
on your foolish thoughts,
but it seems that it's your
entire character that's foolish.
I-I'm dispersing...
His Stand's been split up! Which means...
H-He's dead?
Jotaro!
We defeated the user!
We defeated Chili Pepper's user!
Well done. That's a relief.
So this guy is Josuke's dad...
His body's huge, but he's
a rickety-looking geezer.
You there,
what's your name?
I-It's Okuyasu.
Okuyasu?
I'm Josuke's neighbor,
and I'm also a Stand user.
Huh?
A Stand user.
A S-t-a-n-d u-s-e-r!
Ah, you can't stand losers?
I'm a Stand user!
Oh, I see! So you're a Stand user.
Must be rough.
By the way, Osomatsu,
I can't seem to find my cane.
Do you know where it is?
Ah!
Sorry about that. It's right in my hand.
Is this geezer okay?
Mr. Joestar.
I've come to carry your luggage.
By the way, Osomatsu, I have a question.
Has Josuke...
Since I didn't even know he was born and
left him alone these past sixteen years,
has he said anything about me?
I can't say that he's said much about that.
I see. So he hasn't...
Yay! It's finally here!
Look, Josuke!
Yeah, that's good, I guess.
To be honest,
I'm sort of hoping he just goes back home.
Josuke...
Well, I mean, I'm glad
he wasn't killed by Otoishi,
and things ended happily ever after.
But you know...
I've never even met this guy before.
I can't really see him as my parent.
I'm sure it's just going to be
awkward for the both of us.
Not that I have a grudge
against him or anything.
But I have to think about
what my mom'll think, too.
Don't you think so, Koichi?
O-Oh, no...
Josuke, there's trouble!
Th-The body!
Jotaro, there's trouble!
Akira Otoishi's body disappeared!
He's still
alive!
There's trouble! The enemy
has boarded the boat!
It appears that Akira Otoishi was not dead!
Seriously?
Take Mr. Joestar...
Who are you?
Huh? Did you say something?
No, he...
I'm the one who said it!
He's not a part of the Speedwagon Foundation!
Wha...
What?!
He's the enemy!
Seriously? You bastard!
Please wait!
I'm the one who told you about the enemy!
Would any enemy actually do that?!
He's the real enemy!
You've got a point.
I'm the one who pointed out the enemy first!
He came to tell you that so
you'd let down your guard!
Th-That's also a good point...
Wh-Which one's the enemy?
He is!
D'oh!
I have to choose again?
Damn it.
This is what I get for relying
on my Big Bro so much...
Okuyasu's easy to deal with.
Jotaro hasn't seen my face yet.
If I can just kill Joseph...
I'm gonna escape!
I'm gonna get the hell out of here!
Chili Pepper!
Huh? What's that about a chilly pigeon?
Rumble
I'll kill you!
I figured out
who it is!
It's you!
Don't think you can fool
Okuyasu Nijimura twice!
H-How did you figure it out?
You wanna know?
How...
I was gonna punch both of you!
I'm not very smart, you know.
Watch...
your step. You're gonna fall into the ocean.
S-Sorry.
If only I had my cane,
I'd be able to get down myself,
but it broke a moment ago...
G-Guess I don't have a choice.
Hold on to my hand.
I just had a great idea!
Why not have Shining Diamond fix the cane?
Y-You idiot! What are you saying?
You're so stupid, Okuyasu.
Huh? Why?
Things are better if he
doesn't fix it this time.
Huh? Why?
Why is that?
Now if we just
retrieve the bow and arrow, it'll all be over,
including the threat to this town.
Episode 13
We Picked Up Something Crazy!