Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I am Worm, a Shadow Beast.
Which group do you belong to?
We're bodyguards for
the Nostrade Family.
I see.
It seems that you can use Nen,
but don't bother.
These aren't ordinary thugs.
To them, taking lives is like breathing.
Y-You could say they're
professional killers.
And a pro knows his trade best of all.
Rabid Dog.
I'm Leech.
I-I'm Porcupine.
We Shadow Beasts will see to them.
Buildup x To A x Fierce Battle
After the Phantom Troupe's
raid on the auction,
Uvogin has single-handedly
annihilated the Mafia pursuit.
Now, they watch the arrival
of the secret weapon dispatched
by the Mafia's Ten Dons,
the Shadow Beasts.
Man...
Not one of them put up much of a fight.
Uvo!
Yeah?
Here they come.
Hey, don't interfere.
I still haven't gotten to enjoy myself.
Jeez...
Let Uvo handle it.
Care for a round, Feitan?
He's going to fight the
Shadow Beasts by himself?
The Shadow Beasts, huh?
Where did you hide the merchandise?
What happened to all the
guards and guests?
We killed them.
So where's the merchandise?
If you don't answer me...
That stung.
Now you can't escape...
Make your choice.
Do you want to die
underground, at my hands?
Or on the surface, at the
hands of the other three?
Idiot.
Here he goes.
Uvo's getting serious...
Four.
You're the one
who can't escape!
Big Bang Impact:
Fist of Destruction
I-I don't believe it!
I've never seen a Nen user
of this caliber before.
That's...
A spider tattoo.
Then he's...
Spider...
Poor chap.
Not much left of him.
Uvo's Big Bang Impact
packs a powerful punch.
Honestly...
He's just throwing a straight right,
with a little added Nen.
Eight.
Nine.
Ten.
Okay, who's dying next?
The Phantom Troupe, huh?
He sounds pretty confident.
You're the one who will die next!
Fool.
Nice...
I like reckless opponents.
But you're still going to die!
I can manipulate my body hair at will.
I can even turn it into hard spikes, yup.
You throw a strong punch,
but it's meaningless if
you can't connect, yup.
They managed to damage
Uvogin's iron skin with nothing
but body hair and teeth.
Must be skilled Nen users.
I'm impressed.
Thirteen.
No way!
Sorry.
Want a hand, Uvo?
Keep out of this!
Damn it...
It's futile.
You can't shake off thousands of spikes
once they've penetrated your skin, yup.
Then I'll use you as my fist!
Since I can manipulate it at will,
I can relax certain sections of
my body hair as necessary, yup.
We've got Muscles on the ropes.
That's bull.
You're damned tough.
Did it finally kick in?
My fangs secrete a tranquilizer
that's meant to instantly incapacitate you...
Bastard...
Everything from the neck up is unaffected,
so you can still feel pain and fear.
So sit back and enjoy.
If he were using a lethal poison,
this fight would be over.
I'm sure he likes to torture opponents.
I keep numerous leeches
of all sizes within me...
They'll enter your body
through your wounds,
and deposit their eggs in your bladder.
These spotted leeches are
a gift from me to you.
You're totally disgusting!
Most people die from the
excruciating pain
of hundreds of millions of leeches
as they hatch inside their bodies.
Yuck.
I thought that uglier usually
meant better-tasting.
Why are you surprised?
You aren't the only one
who can use his teeth.
Everything from my neck up
is all I need to defeat you.
They're going to lose...
The Shadow Beasts will lose.
Defeat us?
Heh.
You can't bite me when I'm
all the way over here.
A bullet?
No...
It's a fragment of Leech's
skull that he bit off!
He's going to do the same to me?
But it won't work...
My body hair will repel
any projectile, yup.
Huh?
You can't repel sound projectiles, can you?
Oh, you can't hear me anymore?
He used sound to defeat
a Shadow Beast.
They're all crazy...
You idiot!
Give us a warning first!
What if our eardrums had burst?
Sorry about that!
But that would've given my plan away.
Besides, you guys had plenty
of time to cover your ears
before the sound reached you.
That's true.
Wait, Kurapika!
What are you doing?
Shouldn't that be obvious?
I'm going to capture him.
It's impossible!
You saw what he's capable of!
You're going to get yourself killed!
Kurapika!
I really don't care.
I hear tremendous rage and hatred.
He's completely lost control.
Kurapika!
He will definitely get himself killed.
I cannot leave him in this state.
Stop, Kurapika!
Wild Flower.
The perfect song to relax you.
Has everyone calmed down?
Let's cool our heads,
and devise a plan together.
Y-Yeah...
What kind of abilities do the
other members possess?
I bet they're all ridiculously strong...
Melody...
Hmm?
Thank you.
I've cooled down now.
However, I still must capture them.
Leader,
I can make this happen.
What?
Let me go.
After witnessing that
incredible show of strength,
you still believe you can defeat him?
Of course.
I understand.
Bring the car, so we can
leave at a moment's notice.
R-Right.
Shizuku!
Would you suck the poison and
leeches from my body?
Your vacuum will do the trick.
Blinky can suck out poison,
but nothing alive.
What?
Then what am I supposed to do?
Let me see.
This is a spotted leech...
It takes one day to migrate to the bladder,
before laying its eggs and dying.
So?
The eggs will hatch shortly after,
exiting through your urinary tract.
It will cause enough pain to kill you.
Hey, don't joke around...
However, they require a specific
ammonia level to hatch.
If there isn't enough,
the eggs don't hatch, and they
can be excreted harmlessly.
So, until this time tomorrow,
you should drink beer non-stop,
and be sure to urinate frequently!
Don't scare me like that...
Shizuku, can you take care of the poison?
Yes.
Someone go to the city
and get lots of beer.
I'll go.
Make sure they're ice-cold!
Don't get too greedy!
Okay, get that poison out of me.
Huh?
Did you see that?
Yeah.
Those chains came from nowhere,
to wrap around his body.
Is it a new Shadow Beast?
Uvo can't move because of the tranquilizer,
and the leeches are still inside him.
Then that's that...
Let's go and save him.
Good grief.
He's so much trouble.
I have a trace for now.
I used In to conceal the thread.
So as long as they don't use
Gyo to spot the needle,
I can follow them anywhere.
Okay, let's find them
before they notice it.
This is our chance to finish the
remaining Shadow Beasts.
Franklin, we're counting on you
to bring back lots of beer.
Man, the chase sounds more fun...
Let's go!
Indeed.
The spiders...
We'd need all the remaining members
just to stand a chance...
Understood.
Chains...
Hey, driver...
You think these chains can hold me?
If you don't kill me now,
you'll regret it later.
Shut up.
Don't you understand?
This is a golden opportunity.
Stop wasting time, and just...
I told you to shut up!
Kurapika, watch...
Watch the road!
How can he be this strong?
Even if my body weren't paralyzed,
I'd still be having trouble...
He's put enough Nen into these chains
to keep a master Enhancer in check?
Chain Jail.
Chain Jail:
The Restraining Middle Finger
This power can only be used on the spiders...
A power to capture and
restrain the Phantom Troupe.
I've sworn to use this ability
for no other purpose.
I've applied the condition that,
should I use this technique
on one who is not a spider,
I will die on the spot.
A self-imposed restriction.
A self-imposed restriction,
and a covenant with myself.
A self-imposed restriction.
A covenant with myself.
The proof of my resolve.
Look out, Kurapika...
The risk is high.
Watch the road!
But the stronger my resolve,
the stronger my Nen!
Kurapika has captured a member
of the Phantom Troupe, his sworn enemies.
Armed with resolve and the
willingness to risk his life,
an intense battle is about to begin.
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Coming up, we have Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
It's Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Today, we introduce the Shadow Beasts.
A fighting force formed
by the Ten Dons.
A fighting force serving the Mafia community's
There are ten members,
Ten Dons.
So who are they?
all named after
animals and insects.
Owl, Worm, Rabid Dog, Porcupine...
And Leech—
Next time: Restraint x And x Vow!
Killua, don't run in the hallway.
Limbatics counts as walking.
Promise to follow the rules!