Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Shroud
Ten.
The ability to build up a shroud of Nen aura.
You can make your body harder,
and considerably slow the effects of aging.
Null
Zetsu.
A technique that nullifies your Nen aura.
It is effective for concealing your presence,
and recovering from extreme fatigue.
Enhance
Ren.
A technique to create an
especially strong Nen aura.
This ability is crucial for increasing your power.
Act
Hatsu.
The release of your Nen aura,
after boosting via Ren.
These four elements are known
as the four major principles,
Four Major Principles
and are critical to the mastery of Nen.
Gon,
we need to learn more about Nen.
Yeah!
An x Empty x Threat
After two months, during which Gon
was forbidden to practice Nen,
Wing has summoned Gon
and Killua to see him.
Gon-kun. Killua-kun.
Starting today, you'll train with Zushi.
Gon-kun, I'm pleased
that you kept your word.
It's thanks to your promise thread.
A few times, I almost gave in.
But when I looked at the thread,
I was able to control myself.
That's because I added some Nen to help you.
Huh? Really?
No, I was lying.
Huh?
But how could you tell that he kept his word?
He could have been practicing in secret.
Because the promise thread remained intact.
Gon-kun, it's been a while,
but would you try using Ten ?
It's okay?
Yes.
Crap, do I remember how to do this?
It's been so long.
Can I still pull it off?
Zushi, what do you think?
I-It's amazing!
His aura is flowing all around him!
Soft and calm...
But it's very strong!
I did it!
Whew...
I was worried that I might
have forgotten how.
Once you've learned the technique,
you can't forget it.
However, to become a master,
you'll have to train hard.
But it felt easier than before,
despite not having been practicing Ten.
That's because
you were training your spirit each day.
Now, look at your left hand.
Huh?
It snapped!
By applying my own Nen,
I tied the thread such that
if you broke your promise and used Nen,
it would snap.
That's actually possible?
Hey, Wing-san...
Did you watch Kastro and Hisoka's match?
Yes, I did.
What was the ability that Hisoka used?
Could we send loose limbs flying around?
Hmm, that's a difficult question.
Gon-kun, have you seen the fight on video?
No, not yet.
Then I'll explain while we watch.
Can you see the threads of aura
extending from his left hand?
Threads of aura?
Yes.
Do you see them?
N-Nope.
I can't see a thing.
Same here.
Are there really threads of aura
coming from Hisoka's left hand?
Yes, Hisoka is using a technique
that makes his aura difficult to perceive.
Null
It's a high-level application of Zetsu, known as In.
Hide
When you use In,
even the strongest opponents will
find it hard to see your aura.
The most effective counter to this technique
Enhance
is to focus the aura created by Ren
into your eyes, a technique called Gyo.
Focus
The method Gon-kun used
in his fight with Gido
might work, as well.
However, you couldn't take offensive action,
so ultimately, you'd throw your life away.
Right.
My assignment for you two
is to practice Ren until you
can see through Hisoka's In.
Eh?
Uh, master?
What should I do?
Zushi,
you should already be strong
enough to see past his In.
I should?
Show them your Ren.
O-Osu!
Ren!
It's so strong.
It doesn't have a much greater magnitude,
but it's very dense.
Then direct that aura into your eyes.
Osu!
Gyo!
So, can you see the aura that emanates
from Hisoka's body?
Yes.
And how many threads are there?
Twelve...
No, I think it's thirteen.
Not quite.
But you were close.
I could really see them!
You're making excellent progress, Zushi.
O-Osu...
Thank you very much.
By channeling all your power through Gyo,
you achieved a level where you
could see through Hisoka's In.
But with enough training,
you'll be able to use Gyo while fighting.
Do you understand?
First, practice Ren,
and master the Ren application known as Gyo.
Then you'll discover the true nature
of Hisoka's ability.
And will you be able to use that same ability?
My answer is both yes and no.
Regardless of what Hisoka's precise power is,
so long as it uses Nen, you can learn it.
However,
Nen powers depend on the
particular individual.
Each of us possesses different
specialties and preferences.
Thus, Nen differs for each person.
If you're serious about mastering Nen,
you shouldn't merely copy others' abilities.
It's important that you first identify
your own strengths.
Strengths...
You've only just begun to develop.
You haven't settled on one form yet.
Initially, try to grow as much as you can.
That is the purpose of this training.
Train hard,
play hard, and enjoy life.
Osu!
The final day of Killua-kun's
window to fight is June 9th,
and Gon-kun's is the 10th, correct?
I'd like you both to register for your final day.
In the meantime, you'll train.
You must learn Gyo
before it's time for your battle.
Osu!
Your Ren was impressive, Zushi.
You moved way ahead while I was resting.
No, I still have a long path before me.
Hey, let's practice what we just learned.
Yeah, then let's go to your room, Gon.
Okay.
Killua... Zushi.
Osu!
We have company.
You guys don't know when to quit.
That's why no one likes you.
Oh, don't be so harsh.
Tell me when you're going to fight,
because I'd love to be your opponent.
I guess they specialize in hunting newbies.
They want to rack up wins
by beating us up.
We're getting desperate...
Because our deadline is nearing.
Come on, let's fight.
I'll even demonstrate my power
right now.
I'm fighting on June 10th.
Hey, Gon!
That won't work.
My deadline is May 29th.
Fight on that day.
Who cares about your deadline, moron?
Let's go.
Gon-chan...
You and I will fight.
I guarantee it.
Gon, ignore him.
What will you do?
I'll force him to fight me.
Visualize the energy building in your body.
Power gathers in each cell, and grows.
Then you force that power
out!
I'm getting used to this.
Learning when to shroud the
boosted aura with Ten
was a little tricky.
A-A little?
They pick it up too fast!
But our auras still aren't as strong as Zushi's.
Guess we should practice more.
N-No, that's enough!
Learning when to rest is part of training.
Let's call it a day.
Really? I can still—
No!
If they pass me in half a day,
I'll lose all my motivation...
Oh...
Well, it's okay.
We'll practice more tomorrow.
Yeah.
See you tomorrow.
Bye.
Okay, then...
I can't...
I can't move!
I can't talk or breathe...
What's going on?
Oops.
Please...
Forget it.
I figured you were up to something.
But you don't need dirty tricks
to make me fight you.
When do you want to fight?
Don't worry.
I'll let you win.
I'll even give you each a win.
Is that good enough?
After I get my win off you,
I'm going to fight Gon-chan.
If you want to fight Gon,
you'll have to follow his schedule.
He'll be more than happy to fight you.
I can promise you that.
Okay.
If you two are willing to fight,
we don't need to bother with this.
Let's go register together.
Once that's done, I'll return the boy unharmed.
Yeah, yeah. Sure...
But only this once.
May 29th...
Okay, happy now?
Yes,
we'll return him.
Oh, just to reiterate, it's a one-time deal.
If you break your promise...
Eh... Whatever.
Forget it.
What? You got me curious.
What will happen if we break our promise?
No point in telling you now.
Just keep your word.
Hello? Is this Gon-kun?
I'm sure you'll understand what this means.
As long as you don't tell anyone,
and you follow my instructions,
the three of you will be able to
train as usual tomorrow.
Zushi...
How did it go with Gon-chan?
Perfect.
He's registered for the 30th.
That's two wins.
Too easy.
Not killing people is pretty hard.
Clean living's tough...
Come on down! We have tickets!
These are fresh off the press...
Gon versus Sadaso!
And here's Killua versus Sadaso...
If you don't buy now, you'll regret it!
Pops.
Yep?
Does Sadaso have only one arm?
Yeah, the one-armed fighter,
with the mask-like face.
If he catches you with his
invisible left arm, you're finished.
They call him the newbie crusher...
That bastard.
Huh? Killua?
Gon, you were here?
Y-Yeah...
Killua-kun,
I believe you helped Zushi last night.
Thank you.
You feeling all right?
Yeah, I'm fine.
I was probably tired.
Sorry to worry you!
Oh, Wing-san...
Can we watch that video again?
I've learned how to use Gyo.
Really?
Fifteen threads, right?
Thirteen for the cards, one for the scarf,
and a well hidden one that
leads to the arm he tossed.
Continue.
Hisoka is...
Hisoka's aura appears
to expand and contract.
Or does it
attract certain objects, similar to a magnet?
Why else would his arm reattach?
Or fly into his opponent's chin?
It's probably the former.
His aura is elastic, like rubber.
That would explain most of his tricks.
He's on a completely different level!
Very good... You pass.
But I am surprised...
I didn't expect you both to learn Gyo overnight.
Gon?
Uh-huh,
but I still couldn't figure out Hisoka's power.
So, Killua-kun,
since you finished your assignment,
I assume you want to fight, yes?
O-Oh, I wasn't trying to
beat you to the punch.
I just got an itch to fight.
Yeah, I get it.
Gon, they must have threatened you.
Actually, I've already chosen my day to fight.
May 29th.
Mine's May 30th.
That's fine.
I underestimated how fast you could learn.
Spend the remaining days practicing Ten and Ren.
Be sure you get plenty
of practice, rest, and sleep.
Osu!
Killua...
They must have threatened you.
Now I'm mad...
Yeah, but my biggest concern
was the master, and he agreed.
But I'm worried they'll use Zushi again.
It'll be okay.
You don't need to worry.
Today, I'll beat Killua-chan for my sixth win.
Tomorrow, I'll beat Gon-chan
for my seventh win.
Then I just need to find three more chumps.
And I'll be a Floor Master.
I'll get all the wealth and glory to
set me up for the rest of my life.
Move, and I will kill you...
Use Nen, and I will kill you.
Make a sound, and I will kill you.
If you understand, slowly close your eyes.
Do you know what happens
if you break your word?
If you know, slowly open your eyes.
Look at me in the mirror, and listen carefully.
Never show your filthy face to us again.
That's a promise.
Time has run out for Sadaso!
Killua wins by default!
Damn, I want my money back!
Killua opens the battle
against the persistent trio
with a win by default.
Thanks to their inborn talent,
Gon and Killua are learning Nen
at incredible speeds.
Now they will start the real battle
at Heavens Arena.
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Coming up, we have Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
It's Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Today, we introduce Sadaso.
A Heavens Arena
200s-class warrior.
He underwent the traditional greeting
with Gido and Riehlvelt.
Alters his Nen to form
an invisible left arm.
Yeah?
His invisible left arm is made of Nen.
Oh.
Yeah?
Next time: Power x To x Avenge!
Power, yeah?
Avenge, yeah?
Yeah? Yeah? Yeah?