Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I can no longer think of him...
as a target to destroy.
He acknowledged our efforts.
He wasn't a bad guy.
In that case, I no longer have...
any reason to defeat him.
The King...
The soldiers are not important.
If the King waves his baton, the soldiers
will become demons if necessary.
Pose x And x Name
This is an area used for testing weapons of war.
We won't need to restrain ourselves.
Why do you fight?
You have no chance of defeating me.
Why rush to your death?
You presume to know I cannot win?
You know nothing about me.
If you judge me by my appearance,
you'll get burned.
You have it backwards.
You don't seem like some ordinary man
who can't read the state of the battle.
I was born to rule this world.
Originally, you humans were as
no more than livestock to me.
But I have changed my mind.
I learned that there are a few
humans worth keeping alive.
Like that woman.
I sense that you are worthy, as well.
If you back down now,
I am willing to spare your life.
You'll only spare my life, yes?
Given my position,
I can't accept that offer.
Meanwhile...
In exchange for his agreement to stay still,
Pouf was pressing Pitou to explain
just what had happened.
Pitou complied with Pouf's request, telling
him what happened after the attack.
In other words, everything since
they'd been separated.
Pitou made it a point to include
details that Gon did not know,
to ensure that Gon's attention would
be focused on the explanation.
Pitou deliberately did not mention
how the King had held Komugi
because Pitou did not know how to
describe the events accurately.
There was no significant change in Gon.
However...
Pitou knew the plan had succeeded
when Gon's eyes wavered briefly.
The King...
left with the enemy of his own
volition, by that doorway.
There is no need for us to go.
I see.
He went south.
I understand.
A fine play, Pitou.
Then we should await the King's return here.
To maintain only my outward appearance,
I only need one-seventh of my flies.
The other six-sevenths
will go to the King!
You fight with the resolve to lose?
I do not understand.
You fight for the human race?
If so, then know that my actions
are, in fact, for their benefit.
For example, in human society,
lands are divided by national borders,
much like territorial marking.
On the right side of the border,
children may starve to death.
While on the left, scum who do nothing
have everything they need.
Absolute madness.
I shall crush that madness...
And create a world so fair,
the very concept of inequality will be forgotten!
I concede that
I will initially use power and terror
to accomplish my objective.
But I will only do so to the extent
necessary to maintain order.
I have learned what power
is meant to be used for.
To protect the weak,
who deserve to live.
Power is not meant to be used
to torment the defeated!
This could be a problem...
I shall not fight you.
I agreed to leave the palace
so we could have a free, open discussion.
He's wavering...
Come closer.
Wavering between Ant and human.
And he hasn't realized
that those two sides are incompatible.
And neither one
is dominant yet.
But regardless of which side he falls to,
the outcome won't change.
We're counting on you.
You have a single mission.
The immediate extermination
of these dangerous creatures.
There have already been many casualties.
We will use any means necessary.
Will that be acceptable?
Naturally, we have no intention of
telling the experts how to proceed.
We simply desire
those dangerous creatures
eradicated as swiftly as possible.
Understood.
So their goal is to eradicate the Ants,
leaving the Hunters Association
to take the blame.
I must make this fast...
Before my heart is swayed.
King...
We are both in difficult positions.
100-Type Guanyin Bodhisattva
100-Type Guanyin Bodhisattva!
First Hand
First Hand!
That's...
I can't sense anyone else fighting.
Does that mean I'm the only one left?
Youpi!
Pouf!
You've changed a lot since I last saw you.
I could say the same to you.
I had to escape without alerting the enemy.
And if I move all my dispersed particles
at once, it's too conspicuous.
So I must go slowly.
I'm sure you're feeling impatient,
but please spare me a moment.
I need to tell you what's happening.
Well, I suppose you have your own concerns...
You've grown up.
And there you have it.
I have no conclusive proof
that the change in Pitou will
actually benefit the King...
Through his own experiences,
Youpi could understand Pitou's behavior.
Youpi...
What do you think we should do?
This was a test.
Which made it very clear to Youpi
that Pouf was fearful of the subtle changes
Pitou and Youpi had undergone.
A foolish question.
We must go
to the King at once!
And that's all there is to it... Right?
His response was entirely sincere.
Indeed.
He was concerned only with
leaving as soon as possible.
Because Youpi was feeling the same fear.
I'm sure that was a direct hit...
He's tough!
A good attack.
I could not anticipate it.
Are you satisfied now?
He still wants me to sit with him?
I shall not repeat myself.
Third Hand
Third Hand!
I can no longer back down!
Are you really so eager to die?
From the King's perspective,
the wrath that was unleashed
was no stronger than that
of a child throwing a fit.
Yet it was violent enough to induce
Netero to more than double the distance
between the King and him.
It was an insult likened to laughing off
Netero's declaration that
he would not back down.
Come on...
You will only influence me by using words.
Damned newborn brat.
If it were that simple,
I wouldn't have to do this!
Wait...
By using...
words?
King...
Would you like to know your name?
How would you know my name?
My subordinates were present at the
moment of your mother's passing.
She uttered your name with her dying breath.
And my subordinates may have died
fighting your Royal Guard by now.
Interested in fighting me now?
If you can force me to admit defeat,
I will tell you your name.
Force you to admit defeat
without killing you?
So, similar to a bishop and rook handicap...
No matter.
I shall checkmate you shortly.
The real battle between Netero
and the King has begun.
Next time: Centipede x And x Memory.
Hey, what do you want to be in your next life?
Uh, what do you want to be?
In my next life, I want to be me,
and meet you again.
Stupid!