Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Please help save Gon!
Use your heads!
If you have an idea, take action!
If there's something I can do, tell me.
I'll do anything!
Defeat x And x Reunion
The results of the eighth chairman election
were promptly counted by Beans.
Now, please take a look at the result of
the eighth election for the 13th chairman!
Wow!
Eighth Election for the 13th Chairman
1) Leorio 282 (44.4%)
2) Pariston 250
3) Mizaistom 58
4) Cheadle 16
Turnout: 95.4%
This puts Leorio in first place!
For the first time, Pariston hasn't
finished in first place...
However, the first place vote-getter, Leorio,
received only 44.4% of the vote.
That was below the 50% requirement,
which means we'll finally have a run-off
between the top two vote-getters.
Are they serious about this?
Then I'm gonna do whatever the hell I want.
Oh, it's Brother.
Morning.
Did you sleep well?
Uh-huh.
Where are we?
The hospital.
My friend is here, sleeping. He's very sick.
I want to help get him
on his feet again.
You want Something to take over.
Boo! Just when I was able to spend time with you!
Don't worry.
Like I told you...
We'll be together from now on.
And that's a promise.
Please help me.
I knew it.
Killua is the one person who doesn't
have to follow the rules.
Though I'll have to check
whether it's specific to Killua or something
that happens after a wish is used to heal.
Okay, I'll do it.
Either way, the power to destroy and fix
can become a powerful tool
if the user can be tamed.
His utter lack of humanity and wicked ambition
deviate even from the path of an assassin.
How tragic...
When he was being controlled, he suffered less.
Alluka is only awake when Something is asleep.
She spends less time as Alluka than one would think.
The time after Something's requests
aren't met and people die,
until Something makes the next level-1 request...
Or the time when request-making is paused
after someone leaves Something
before her three requests are complete...
Or the time after Something fixes and falls asleep,
until someone else makes a wish
to Alluka and has it granted...
Making this the last wish and never
wishing to Something again
would be the best thing that could happen.
Hand... Hand...
Please,
Something...
Please heal Gon!
'Kay.
Such incredible power...
What's happening inside?
Who's doing this?
What is this?
I've never felt anything like this before.
Are you serious? Are you serious?
Then I'm going to do whatever I want.
Magnificent.
I want this.
This...
belongs to me.
Then let me ask the two remaining candidates
if they have anything they want to say.
If not, we will proceed with the final vote.
It's futile.
It doesn't matter what you have to say.
Well, I have a feeling that
this election is already over,
but I would like to ask Leorio-san a question.
Can you answer this question for me again?
What will you do if you become chairman?
Leorio-san, can you please
give us your answer again?
What will you do if you become chairman?
Save Gon!
And I'll make all of you help me!
That's all.
This would have been the perfect time,
but I'm not God.
In that case, do you have any
plans for shuffling personnel
or restructuring the organization?
Of course not!
I don't even know why I'm
standing here right now!
Naturally...
Those are all the questions I have.
It's futile, Pariston.
Everyone was aware of those answers
when they voted for Leorio.
His supporters applauded because they
have every intention of backing him!
Do you have any questions for me?
No! Let's just get this over with!
I understand.
Then I move for an emergency council.
Huh?
Er, what are you saying?
An emergency council.
In accordance with the Eighth
and Ninth Hunter Commandments,
I move for a vote of confidence.
The topic will be a revision of the Hunter
Commandments and the Hunter Exam.
First, I propose that we abolish the
current Hunter Exam system.
If you agree, please vote "yea."
If you disagree, please vote "nay."
Hold it right there!
During the Zodiac council, we decided
the Ten Commandments weren't to be touched!
That isn't relevant right now!
No.
You're wrong, stupid tiger!
You're absolutely right.
The council reached an 11-1 majority decision.
I was the only one in favor of
revising the Ten Commandments.
If Cheadle-san or Mizaistom-san were
standing on the stage now,
I would have deferred to the council and
kept my mouth shut until the election ended.
But both of them are out of the running.
And Leorio-san has stated that he
has no plan for the Association!
This is the only time
I can express my opinion as vice chairman,
and not as a member of the Zodiacs.
Don't you understand, Kanzai-san?
This is the only chance I will ever get!
Of course, I could use the Eighth Commandment
to override the council's decision
and force the matter to a vote.
But I wanted to avoid that.
The Zodiacs are something precious
that the former chairman left us.
Hey, if you say something stupid,
he'll pay you back ten times over.
Honestly, part of me wishes to let this
matter die without making waves.
However, the late Teradein-san and
Bushidora-san made an excellent point.
The Third and Fourth Commandments
are suffering gravely as a result
of the current exam process!
He doesn't want to win.
He doesn't want to lose, either.
You're right...
He's a spiteful person!
He doesn't care about winning or losing,
so with nothing to gain or lose, he can
always stay dispassionate and calm,
while he manipulates others and plays the rules
against us in the worst way possible.
May I say something?
Yes, what is it?
If Leorio wins, I volunteer to serve as an advisor.
I promise to conduct a comprehensive review of
the Ten Commandments and
Hunter Exam at that point.
I won't let you grab any of the Teradein votes!
I'll counter every point you've made!
To everyone who's voting for
the potential Leorio shows,
but who's concerned about
how he will serve initially,
I will quell those concerns, even if it
requires me to leave the Zodiacs.
Hey, hey, hey!
I have no idea what you people are talking about.
But I'm in a hurry to save Gon
as quickly as possible!
Leorio!
Gon!
Damn!
You had me so worried!
Leorio!
I'm so glad!
So glad!
Did I l look that bad?
Bad doesn't even begin to describe it!
Leorio, stop.
He's healed now. Isn't that enough?
Yeah, you're right.
Everyone was worried about you.
Thank you... Thank you.
He got us.
Pariston wanted Leorio to be his final opponent!
Leorio no longer has the motive or
support to become chairman.
You become chairman!
Leorio, you can't tell Gon that Killua healed him.
Who's the bald guy?
Huh? Why not?
You can't tell him!
For Killua's sake, promise not to tell him.
O-Okay, got it.
Pariston, when?
When did you predict that this would happen?
Huh?
No, no...
I don't have the ability to predict anything.
This was pure coincidence.
Please tell me. I want to know.
It hurts to admit this, but I've been defeated.
It was when Ging-san said he
would run for chairman...
What?
After he said he would run,
I asked a question to provoke him.
And he responded that Gon-kun wouldn't die, right?
Go visit him.
He isn't going to die.
In that moment,
I could see the scene that
just transpired before us.
Well, I anticipated Ging-san
and I would stand on stage,
and Ging-san would ultimately win.
At least, in my vision.
First, since Ging-san said Gon-kun wouldn't die,
I knew that meant there was a way to heal him.
And that if he became part of the
election, I would never win.
Do you understand?
That was the moment I was defeated.
But Ging-san gave up on the election,
then Leorio-san arrived, and hit him.
When he stood on stage
and talked about his friends risking
their lives to save Gon-kun,
I finally saw the complete picture.
I was assured of my victory a moment ago,
when I felt that immense power.
I could sense that Gon-kun's friends had saved him.
All that remained was to delay
the vote until he arrived.
Oh, I'll retract the earlier motion,
so there's nothing for you to worry about.
That was all the information you had?
You put your trust in someone
you'd never met before?!
I trust Ging-san as an enemy.
And these are the friends that
Ging-san trusted to save his son.
I trust them.
Why wouldn't I?
Run for chairman!
I'll vote for you!
Get on stage and say something!
Speech! Speech!
Man, I don't know what to do.
Ging?
This is bad.
But, well, this was always gonna happen...
Gon has finally caught sight of Ging's back.
What will he say to him?
Next time: Chairman x And x Release.