Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Facing the palace, each of the three exits
is progressively closer to the throne room.
Okay, we're all agreed.
We'll all use the closest exit,
and bust in from beside the central stairway.
Confusion x And x Expectation
This seemed like a good idea
since Leol-sama praised me so much,
but dispelling Nen is hard.
And the stronger the Nen,
the bigger my stomach gets.
This was a bad idea.
To a girl, there's nothing
worse than losing your figure.
I should ask Leol-sama for a larger reward!
Right, Shidore?
Having a peon that understands
speech is useful, but...
You really need to talk more.
You have permission to shoot her on sight!
As a foreigner, she can't blend
in with the other citizens!
Damn! Damn that woman!
What does she want?
Hey!
How many times have I told you
not to use your cell phone here?
The radio waves irritate my ears,
and it gives me a headache!
Plus, I can hear what you're saying.
Next time I catch you, I'll snap your
phone and your arm in half.
W-Well... There are urgent matters
that must be dealt with.
I need to use my phone.
It's so urgent that you find
the woman who ran away?
I can find her for you.
R-Really?
My nose happens to be very sharp...
If you have something she wore, I can track her.
The Royal Guard appreciates the work you do,
and I respect you, as well!
So, a little give-and-take will benefit us both here.
O-Okay!
Hold on, and I'll bring you something.
I will become the King behind the scenes.
To accomplish that, I must be friendly
with Bizeff, not with the King.
Welfin-sama, an urgent alert has been issued.
Bah.
When peons send transmissions,
it gives me a headache.
This smells like...
Taragette's blood.
There are bloodstains and dirty shoes.
An intruder!
If he took his shoes off here
to avoid leaving footprints,
he must be somewhere deeper within.
He didn't hide his shoes because
he had a pressing mission and
couldn't afford to lose time...
That day last week, when it rained?
That was the day Taragette went missing.
I'm pretty sure that the intruder killed him.
But that means he disposed of Taragette's body
while leaving his shoes behind.
There's no blood trail nearby.
If he wrapped the body in something to move it,
he must have come prepared.
Was kidnapping a soldier his mission?
Why would they do that?!
Damn, I don't get this!
Should I ask Shaiapouf for advice?
No, I'll catch the intruder,
and get the answers from him.
He did head inside the palace!
This guy comes before Bizeff's woman...
Follow me!
What is your name?
It's K-K-Komugi.
Can you please tell me what your name is?
I didn't get to learn his name...
I can't wait to play him again!
Who am I?
A nameless king... in a borrowed castle.
My subjects are mindless puppets.
If this is the fate that the
heavens have granted me...
I have no doubt that I shall
be slowly bored to death!
Don't follow me.
Yes, but—
Do not make me repeat myself.
Now we've all been beaten by the King.
The King says your En is irritating him.
I figured he would be saying that soon.
But I can't remove our security...
Then you go and tell him that!
I don't want another beating.
How does this sound?
We can block all aura in a radius
surrounding Your Majesty.
This way, my presence will not bother you.
Are you telling me to stay in one place?
Given that keeping
the aura-free zone around me
while I move wouldn't be possible.
I refuse to have my movement
constantly monitored.
No, that would not be our proposal.
So if I do not wish to deal with your presence,
I will only be able to move
within that confined area.
I must order you to move that zone
should I wish to go elsewhere?
There is nothing more I can say.
Keep your En focused outside the palace.
I shall put up with that until tomorrow's selection.
Are you dissatisfied?
Should that not suffice to guard
against outside attacks?
Or are you saying that there
are already enemies inside?
That would be admitting that your En
is completely worthless, would it not?
You're absolutely correct.
If my En is focused only outside, it cannot detect
any attack from underground.
In addition,
my En is not capable of recognizing
an enemy that is already inside.
Do you mean Komugi?
No, eleven soldiers still remain within the palace,
and they are free to enter and leave at will.
A check is performed each time someone enters,
but if the soldier were being
controlled by the enemy,
it would be difficult to know for sure.
That means—
Enough.
You may use En on the first floor of the palace!
That will permit you to guard
against any underground attack!
Tell everyone that no one is allowed
on the second floor or above.
Should an intruder come, I shall
deal with them personally.
Likewise, you will not come unless summoned!
If you disturb me, it will
have violent consequences!
The other Ants
were never allowed on or above the second floor...
But where do I go now?
The central stairway connecting the
first and second floors, I suppose...
If an intruder comes from underground,
you will be in position to deal with them.
Still, the King's been in a bad mood lately.
Is he upset about losing
all those Gungi matches?
I have an idea as to the cause of his irritation.
My ability, Spiritual Message, would be
able to confirm my suspicions.
However, that would be an insult to the King!
No, I'm just making excuses...
The truth is that I'm afraid.
So afraid of what it is
that grows inside the King even as we speak,
I cannot bear it...
Tsk, the rain washed away the scent.
But now I have the answer.
The intruder hid here to
check the second floor,
but instead of going upstairs, he exited.
Something made him give up his mission?
Or did he accomplish his objective?
No, he may have used his power!
I should probably warn you...
If any of you go to the second
floor, the King will kill you.
Tell everyone else in the palace.
Yes, sir.
Wings!
What if the intruder has the power to fly?
The shoes and scent could have
been there to mislead us.
He could have flown up to the second floor!
Youpi-dono...
Huh?
Uh, er...
Pitou is monitoring the palace with En.
If they'd gone to the second floor,
they would have been caught...
Ah, sorry... It's not important.
Huh?
That doesn't make sense!
Then how did the intruder reach the stairway?!
Youpi-dono...
Huh? What is it?
Has Pitou-dono ever ceased to use En?
For example, that day last week when it rained?
What? You didn't hear what happened?
There was a huge uproar...
The King tore off his own arm!
Pitou had to heal the King,
so Pouf was using his En instead.
How wide is his En?
I wouldn't know about that...
Wouldn't it be just as large as Pitou's?
No, I'd guess that Pouf's En only
reached as far as the stairway.
The intruder saw that aura,
and gave up on ascending!
That all makes sense.
The question is what the
intruder's objective was,
and whether he's still hiding around here.
Do I tell Youpi?
No, I can't do that...
I should report this to Pitou or Pouf.
Pouf would be the best choice.
And if possible, I need to determine
what the intruder's objective was.
Otherwise, my report would be
that the intruder somehow
made it inside the palace,
but turned and ran when he felt Pouf's En.
I won't get any credit.
I can make up an objective,
but if the intruder is captured,
they'll find out I lied.
But if I tell the Royal Guard my suspicions
and the intruder is never found,
it would only waste their time
and damage my own standing.
Is that Bizeff's cell phone again?!
I have a great idea...
So the intruder captured one of my men.
According to Leol, that intruder
has the ability to teleport.
I believe that he and the
woman are working together.
They probably teleported out together.
Damn, but why would they do that?
Yes, that's the question.
However, I've discerned their objective.
What is it?
To blow up the palace.
That's a lie.
What?
We must tell the Royal Guard!
Wait.
Don't be in such a rush.
We can tell them after we've found the bomb.
There's no time!
Calm down, and consider this
from their perspective...
Eh?
If they want to blow up the palace,
they'll wait until they're sure the King is here.
When would that be?
When all the citizens have assembled...
Right before the ceremony begins!
There will be five million humans!
What a sight that will be to see...
Just imagine looking down on them!
The King would not allow a double
to steal that gratification from him!
So he will be there in person!
It's only logical to assume the enemy
reached the same conclusion.
True...
I've stood at the former Supreme Leader's
side for many of these celebrations...
The experience brings indescribable
pleasure beyond even sexual gratification.
We still have over half a day
before the ceremony.
If I use my nose to track the intruder,
we can find the bomb with time to spare.
If we have proof when we report to the
Royal Guard, we'll look much better.
If we save the King's life, they'll be quite grateful.
Right?
Yes... That's true.
As soon as I find the bomb, I'll contact you.
Okay, that sounds good.
The coward finally calmed down?
I'm getting closer to becoming
the King behind the scenes!
Seven minutes to go.
I'll give a call when it's down to one minute.
Assemble near the exit then.
Until then, stand by.
Meleoron, about your power...
I know.
I'll tap your shoulder ten seconds
before I need to breathe...
And then, I'll tap you again when
I start to hold my breath again!
You don't need to push your limits.
You should catch your breath
whenever you need to.
When God's Accomplice isn't active,
you can trust me to handle things.
Why don't you have a smoke?
If you underestimate their sense
of smell, you'll die quickly...
Tracking someone by the smell of
cigarette smoke is simple for them.
We could be knocked out the
second I take my first breath...
The boss will be putting up a smokescreen
when we go in. It'll be fine.
I know, but I'd rather avoid unnecessary risk.
I don't want to regret my decision.
The Royal Guard is on the move.
The three of them gathered above the
front gate to discuss something.
Pitou stayed there, and Youpi went back inside.
Pouf returned to the air to scatter his scales,
so I don't think anything has changed.
I'll let you know if anything else happens.
Yeah, until we leave, feed us as
much information as you can.
Essentially, that eliminates the
possibility of the Royal Guard
being out of the palace.
Essentially, but not completely...
Well, I guarantee that they'll be near the King.
You can't guarantee anything.
We have to be prepared for any possibility,
or we'll be slow to react when
something goes wrong!
You only say that because you don't
understand how loyal they are.
It's impossible that they'd leave the King!
The Royal Guard is always with the King!
And it's fine to believe that!
But we should prepare for any exceptions!
Give me an example of one
of these exceptions!
There are all kinds of exceptions!
Honestly, how can they be having
a dispute at the last second?
You're being too unrealistic!
One exception could be a woman...
Isn't one of the King's objectives to reproduce?
I wasn't sure what the King was doing in
the palace, but he was reproducing.
That must be it.
I see...
That would give the King a reason to keep
the Royal Guard from his bedroom...
Perhaps Bizeff was bringing
women in for the King.
Palm and the King?!
We're sticking to the plan...
No matter what's happening to Palm!
Gon has no idea what they're talking about.
I'm glad we realized this before we set out.
If we'd seen something like
that without warning,
we'd have frozen in our tracks.
Get it now?
You can never overthink something.
There are probably other unexpected
situations that we haven't considered yet.
Yes, something is still bothering me.
Gon...
Do you understand?
Let Palm take care of herself!
No matter what you see,
you must stay focused on Pitou.
Yeah!
It bothers me, but whether
a woman's involved or not,
I believe we should be prepared
for a third party in the palace.
I have a feeling that the third party
is causing my anxiety.
Why did the King injure himself?
Hold on...
That was just a theory of yours.
Yeah, but you agreed that there
was no other logical explanation.
You're contradicting yourself...
Didn't you say there could be other exceptions?
Following that logic,
Pitou could have stopped using En
for other, unexpected reasons.
I understand that...
But something doesn't feel right.
With three minutes left to go, is this
something worth thinking about?
Yeah.
Yeah, think about it...
When would you try to hurt yourself?
When I couldn't forgive myself...
When you couldn't forgive yourself?
That's the logical conclusion...
But that would mean the King
is a ruler with personal pride,
and not just a cold tyrant.
True.
For the sake of his pride, he's willing to endure pain.
Speaking from experience,
people like him will never
be willing to compromise.
If the leader refuses to compromise,
neither will the Royal Guard.
You should assume that combat
will be our only option!
Morel was able to sum everything up...
But he's wrong.
The King's self-injury...
The third party...
We still haven't correctly
deduced what happened.
I have a feeling...
that the truth has the potential
to completely ruin our plans!
It's time!
One minute to go.
Gather around.
Damn! We're out of time...
At ten seconds left, I'll begin the countdown.
Let's do this, boys.
Get ready to rumble!
Next time: Charge x And x Invade.
Yeah, hot pots are great in winter...
Which reminds me of mystery pots.
Charge into the pot!
I think you mean toss into the pot...