Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I have a bad feeling.
I feel like I'm missing something.
There's a gnawing anxiety that won't go away.
A x Fated x Awakening
Kite, Gon, and Killua have
taken care of Hagya's soldiers.
As they head deeper into NGL in
search of the Chimera Ants' nest,
within the Queen's castle,
one of the soon-to-be-born
King's three Royal Guards
is about to awaken.
What kind of magic did they use?
Wow, all of them were split cleanly in half.
Impressive.
This one almost looks like he was smashed
by a rock, or some other hard object.
And Baro's the one with an iron shell.
So this is the rare humans' power.
Are you worried now?
The king of the jungle's blood
runs through my veins.
A few humans can't scare me.
Of course...
Whew, that's a relief.
I thought I was gonna miss out on tonight's feast.
These must be extremely rare humans.
We'll tear them to shreds and gobble them down!
We're being followed.
Not from there.
There's quite a number of them.
Listen up...
Your job is to distract the enemy,
while attacking from a distance.
Do not get too close.
The 2nd Platoon will take the right,
as the 3rd Platoon pincers
them from the left.
My 1st Platoon will trap them,
preventing a rear retreat.
Go!
Gon and I didn't notice them.
They're coming from the left and the right.
Keep up your guard.
Damn...
The trees are getting in the way.
Yeah.
Shouldn't we get out of the forest?
This is a trap.
Okay, keep up the chase.
Hagya-sama, all goes according to plan.
Good work, Flutter.
Once we drive our prey into range,
one strike with my fangs will finish them.
This doesn't feel right...
Eh?
You ordered Flutter to chase the prey,
while you hid in the grass to ambush them.
That's pretty lame.
Huh?
Aren't you the king of the jungle?
A king should face his prey, rather than hiding.
Just jump out and go,
"Roar! Chomp! Ga ha ha ha!"
That's so much cooler.
But you know...
This is how the king of the jungle hunts.
Shut up and watch!
Yeah, yeah.
Well, I don't care, so long as I
get to eat the rare humans.
Rare human?
What's that?
I'll explain the details later.
Its number is 4-933.
It was captured and brought
in by Zazan's squadron.
Number 4-933...
Doesn't mean a thing to me.
It was probably given to the Queen.
Her appetite is even more insatiable these days.
She'll give birth to an incredible king.
Don't see 'em.
It must already be inside the Queen's belly.
Are you certain?
It isn't here...
Where else would it be?
Could it have escaped?
Any creature poisoned by our nerve toxin
will be paralyzed for at least a month.
After a mere three days, it couldn't move around.
You can't be sure when it
concerns the rare ones.
They aren't like normal humans.
You should know that very well.
I'm not the same creature I was before.
The next time I see them,
I'll crush them, rip them apart, and eat them.
The antidote I hid in my
back tooth came in handy.
But I could barely drag myself across the ground.
For the time being, I'll have to hide here...
But what's going on?
How can a Chimera Ant use Nen?
Could you check once more?
Come on, give me a break...
I'm busy enough as it is.
Didn't you hear me say the Queen
has a huge appetite now?
I am well aware of that.
I don't know anything about this "rare" stuff,
but why are you so obsessed with this human?
I'd like to ask it a few questions.
Can't you see the light surrounding his body?
Light?
No, I don't see a thing.
I see.
Then it's true that only some
can identify this power.
Meaning it's a talent.
Exactly.
This talent is my destiny, bestowed
upon me by the heavens.
The power of a chosen few...
If I master this power, I can become the king!
I will be king!
Retreat! Retreat!
Hmm? What's wrong, Flutter?
Wh-What's that?
He's gorgeous!
We're leaving.
Huh?
What about the feast?
He was able to understand
that he was outclassed,
and he calmly backed down at once.
Most likely, he was a Squadron Leader.
I always believed that the world
revolved around my claws and fangs.
That if I brandished them,
I could take the life of any other creature,
could always satisfy my own hunger...
And that I was truly blessed.
However, that wasn't the case.
Others were stronger,
so I never could have ruled.
Death taught me that lesson.
But I am stronger now.
At the moment, we may not be
strong enough to defeat them.
But now we are armed with the ability to learn.
We're following them.
Their nest must be nearby.
If we follow them,
we will find the Queen.
What is that?
Something is coming!
That was a fascinating conversation...
You mentioned something about talent.
Allow me to take part.
O-One of the Queen's Royal Guards!
If I master this power, I can become the king!
I will be the king!
A short and foolish dream...
I am totally outclassed.
I can never escape the position
I've been born into...
You can relax.
Let's talk over there.
Y-Yes!
This power is not for me...
But for this Royal Guard...
And for the King it serves!
This power is for serving them!
Impossible...
What is that
evil aura?
By the way...
Yes?
Why is a live human underneath those bones?
Hmm... Nyow I understand.
What are you researching?
I'm learning about those rare
humans you mentioned.
I've attempted to study them many times,
but it wasn't written in any books.
Asking one of them is faster
than flipping through books.
Wasn't that why you were looking for him?
Th-That's exactly right.
There we go.
Ah!
"New memories are stored
in the hippocampus,
while old memories are kept
in the cerebral cortex.
To invoke those memories..."
Nyow I understand.
Ah, you... Come over here.
Hatsu is a technique for
manipulating aura at will.
To summarize the categories of Nen users...
They are:
Enhancers,
Transmuters,
Conjurers,
Emitters,
Manipulators,
and Specialists,
for a total of six categories.
C-Categories...
Every Nen user belongs to one of these.
You want to increase the amount of your aura,
as well as the speed of its flow.
Most of your basic training will
be spent on these two tasks.
In a battle between Nen users,
those are the factors that...
That...
Th-that are pivotal
in determining the victor.
Nyow I understand...
In addition to the basic Nen
abilities Zetsu and Ren,
there are also unique techniques that reflect
the Nen user's individuality.
If you develop a technique that synchronizes
with your style and Nen category,
the manifestation of your ability has
a better chance of being stronger.
And how do you identify which
Nen category you belong to?
Water divination
is the simplest
and most commonly used method.
Water divination?
Give it a try, Rammot.
Right.
Since the water's overflowing,
that makes you an Enhancer.
An Enhancer?
Which confirms that Rammot is a Nen user?
Seems so.
Oh, yeah...
Didn't you say you fought a rare human?
Y-Yes.
The impact from its attack opened your pores...
And released your aura.
Pores?
Apparently, they're small holes all over your body.
If they're sealed, aura can't be released.
I see...
Colt also thought that Rammot's change
was triggered by his fight
with the rare humans.
It seems he was correct.
So if Rammot is a Nen user now,
can we use him to open everyone's pores?
Sure, sounds good.
I think I'll give this a try.
The leaf wilted...
Unbelievable.
One of us was born possessing Nen ability,
without having to fight a rare human!
Then, Commander, that makes you a Specialist,
not belonging to another category?
Neferpitou.
Huh?
That is the name the Queen gave me.
From now on, call me Neferpitou.
Right!
I don't need him anymore.
Feed him to the Queen now.
Right!
From birth, Neferpitou already
possessed incredible power.
This presence casts a dark shadow over the fates
of Gon and his friends.
Next time: Light x And x Darkness.
Wake up!
C'mon, it's morning.
It's 10:50.
I'll kill-you-a!