Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I saw him back at the staircase...
Did he do it?
Sorry, but what's about to happen is
just me blowing off some steam.
Strong x Or x Weak
He disappeared?
Godspeed.
The difference in initial action
speed was so overwhelming
that Youpi had no time to
make a sound or transform.
Killua's Godspeed placed an
electrical burden upon his own body,
making it possible for his body to
perform at a level far beyond
what should have been possible.
Killua had divided this power
into two different abilities:
Speed of Lightning, which allowed
him to control his body at will,
Speed of Lightning
and Whirlwind, which allowed his body
to react automatically to his opponent.
Whirlwind
In a previous fight, he'd used the
latter to stop his opponent's dart.
A preprogrammed attack is triggered in response
to vibrations in aura that
indicate the opponent's hostility.
The attack bypasses commands from his brain,
unleashing attacks that transcend his
own limits by relying on reflexes alone,
allowing him to easily surpass
his opponent's physical speed.
What's going on here?
All of these guys have less than
ten percent of my raw power.
This makes no sense...
I can't do a thing against him.
Whirlwind!
Profound...
This "aura" stuff is intense...
This is getting interesting.
Before my explosion, I never would
have enjoyed fighting an uphill battle.
Youpi's change in heart would lead him
to make an unbelievable choice,
but this would not happen until later.
Crap!
I used it all up!
Hold it!
You're not getting away!
You're seeing this through with me...
Until you die!
He disappeared?
Again.
He vanished, as though he were
never here to begin with.
That's it...
At least one of them must have the ability
to make people appear and disappear at will.
Huh?
Please enter your passcode.
Damn, I didn't get a code.
Your passcode and name do not match.
Please reenter your passcode.
A second input error will result in your restraint.
He came down here without a passcode?
Okay... Guess I'll have to step out.
The door has been locked.
Please enter your passcode.
This is my chance!
I have two options.
The elevator will fill with
sleeping gas eventually.
Once he's asleep, I have to decide.
One, I leave Brovada in the elevator,
Monitor Room
and head for the surface through the cargo entrance.
This way, when he wakes up,
he'll still be stuck in the elevator.
But there's a high risk that someone above
will notice that the elevator isn't coming up.
Two, I move Brovada somewhere
else while he's asleep.
There are plenty of trucks parked around.
And the warehouse doors require a
passcode to open from the inside.
When he wakes up, Brovada won't
be able to open them.
And if I use the cargo entrance
to return to the surface,
the risk that I'll encounter enemies will
be much lower than if I take the elevator.
No! That won't work!
I have to kill Brovada while he's asleep!
That's the safest option!
Then, I have to take control of Brovada's corpse,
and use it to take out other Squadron Leaders.
That's the least it'll take!
I'll stick the barrel of my gun through
the gap in his armor and open fire.
Ikalgo had the ability to control dead bodies,
but he had never killed anyone
with his own hands before.
Enter your passcode at once.
If a passcode is not entered
within thirty seconds,
the restraining process will begin.
The monitor room in the border guard area...
There should be a monitor
for the elevator camera,
and a button to open the doors!
Well, I'm outside now,
but I had to destroy the elevator...
Is there another exit?
I was naïve...
I didn't expect him to shoot the door.
What now?
Do I wait for him to lower his guard,
then sneak out the cargo entrance?
Or do I wait for him to leave?
Either way, if he goes back to the surface...
That's not good enough!
I'm being naïve!
If he returns to the surface,
and tells the others that Flutter's dead,
I'll be able to move around freely!
Am I an idiot?
If I allow an enemy to return to the surface,
I'm putting everyone else in more danger.
This one's tough.
I can't let him go back up...
If I can't stop him, I've failed my friends!
Yes, this way!
I'm gonna trap you.
A little farther...
Wait until he's a little farther from it...
Now!
So there was someone besides Flutter...
Looks like you were trying to lure me in there...
Too bad for you.
If only one path remains, it's too good
to be true. Anyone would be suspicious.
Well, now I know about you.
And I bet you're hiding in the
monitor room to watch me, chicken!
Damn...
I could have completely
trapped him in that hallway...
But there's no way out from where he is now.
He's still trapped.
Sleeping gas will eventually
fill the room, and he'll...
Crap! He isn't trapped!
There's a way out!
I should get out of here...
That's probably sleeping gas.
I have to do something before he realizes.
I know...
The armored vehicles in the garage.
With those, I could at least lock him in.
But then I'll have no way to get
back to the surface, either!
Think...
Is there anything I can use here?
Come up with the best possible plan, fast!
I guess I have to blow through this shutter...
How annoying!
I have to do this!
Damn! All that firing, and I
barely scorched the surface?
Guess I'll need to think of something else...
I know!
You can operate the shutters
from the monitor room,
Monitor Room
so I can go there to open the shutters.
Nice idea!
Wait,
I have to go through the shutters
to reach the monitor room.
Damn, so I have to get through these
shutters to return to the surface?
Wait...
There might be a way
to escape without busting down the shutters.
The shutter's opening?
An armored vehicle?
That's something a chicken would use.
But the shutter behind it is still shut.
The door to the monitor room is beyond that shutter.
Which means that...
First,
he closed the front shutter and
parked the vehicle there.
Then he returned to the monitor room,
and started raising the front shutter
and lowering the back one,
before racing back to the vehicle?
Doesn't that mean he's also trapped?
He closed off his only escape
route, just to finish me off?
Heh... Yeah, right.
So there's more than one...
The other's watching in the monitor room.
Pisses me off!
Watch this, you peeping tom...
I'm gonna drag your buddy
out of the armored vehicle
and rip him to shreds!
I'm the only one here.
I have to do something...
By myself!
That's tough armor!
I did it!
Crap! He blocked the elevator!
I could have blown a hole in the
ceiling, and climbed up the wire!
I've blocked his escape route.
First hurdle cleared!
You have guts to show yourself...
I'm gonna riddle you with bullets!
Smoke?
Did he kill himself?
Miss his chance to escape?
Either way, there's no way to move this thing!
There's only a few centimeters of space.
The elevator's completely blocked!
Hey! Your friend's gonna burn to death!
If you act now, I'm willing to spare you!
Open the damned shutter!
You hear me?
Being an octopus, I only need a few
centimeters to squeeze through.
Second hurdle cleared.
Hey!
Open the shutter!
Now, I just have to wait for the
sleeping gas to fill the room.
I can hold my breath,
but I don't want to waste time.
Wait for the right timing!
Third hurdle cleared.
Be patient.
Nice and slow.
This is the final hurdle.
I just have to pull the trigger, and I'm done.
Fire! This is the best option!
I'll be safest if I control his body
and return to the surface!
Which means I have to kill him...
I'm the only one here.
There's no one else to help me!
I h-have to...
kill him!
I can't do it!
I'm...
just a coward!
While Ikalgo was lamenting his weakness...
Within the shifted central tower,
as Morel faced off against Pouf's cocoon,
he was battling doubts of his own, as well.
Hold on.
What if...
Pitou! Pouf!
Are you there?
Hey!
What if it isn't that he chose
not to respond to Youpi,
but that he wasn't able to respond?
Within the cocoon should be
nothing but a goopy mess.
He shouldn't be a completely formed creature yet.
If he's utterly defenseless
while he changes forms,
this is the time to attack.
Would he really make such a literally
fatal mistake in this situation?
It's not possible!
This must be a trap. It's guaranteed to be a trap.
But the question is whether the
trap activates when I attack,
or if it's already been activated,
before I've even attacked.
Which is it?
You have doubts because you
are good at what you do.
However, that is all there is to it.
Attack? Don't attack?
What do I do?
Next time: Fake x And x Real.
Hey... If not now, when?
Not yet!
You're a fake. You aren't Killua.