Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fearsome monsters... Exotic creatures...
Vast riches... Hidden treasures...
Evil enclaves... Unexplored lands...
The word "unknown" holds magic.
And some incredible people are
drawn to that magic.
They are known...
...as Hunters!
Then x And x After
"Dear Mito-san and Grandma,
how are you doing?
I'm doing great, as always.
So, I actually passed the Hunter Exam.
While I managed to pass the exam,
I'm not too happy about it.
That's because of what happened
during the Final Phase."
You really don't get it...
If you die, you'll never get another chance.
If I kill you here,
I need only try again next year.
We are not on equal footing!
You value your pride more
than your own life?!
You're really willing to die for your pride?!
I'm going to find my dad.
My dad is a Hunter.
So I'm going to become a Hunter
and find him!
I believe that I'll find him one day...
But I have a feeling that if I give up now,
I'll never find him!
So I won't surrender.
If you don't yield, you'll die...
He defies reason.
I give up. You win.
That's not fair!
We both have to think of
a way to settle this fight!
You fool!
"He knocked me out.
So Satotz-san had to tell me
what had happened next."
Begin!
It's been too long, Kil.
Brother...
You're not cut out to be a Hunter.
You were born to be...
a killer.
What would you accomplish
by becoming a Hunter?
True,
I don't desire to become a Hunter.
But...
I do have something I want...
You don't.
I do!
There's something I really want!
Tell me what it is that you want.
I want to become friends with Gon...
I'm sick of killing people...
I want to become friends with Gon,
and to live a normal life...
That's impossible.
You'll never be able to make friends.
Because you have the soul of a killer.
If you move an inch, I'll assume
that the fight has begun.
And if our bodies make contact,
that will also mean the fight has begun.
If you don't fight me,
your dear Gon will die.
I surrender.
I lose...
"Killua gave in to his despair after that."
Apologize to Killua!
Apologize? For what?
You don't know what you did wrong?
Don't bother apologizing.
Just take me to see Killua.
What will you do then?
That should be obvious...
I'm gonna rescue Killua!
"After that, Kurapika, Leorio, and I
went to Kukuroo Mountain,
where Killua lives."
This gate's official name is the Testing Gate.
Anyone who cannot open this gate
is unqualified to enter the Zoldyck estate.
Listen to me, Gon-kun.
You three are allowed to work together
to open the door.
With a little training, it should be possible.
Let's do this, Kurapika!
Right, let's push!
Here we go!
One!
Two!
Three!
Ow...
It opened.
Yes!
We did it, Gon!
Uh-huh!
Leave.
You're trespassing on private property.
I cannot allow you to pass
without permission.
If you take one step beyond this line,
I'll remove you by force.
What's the problem?
I'm just here to see my friend.
I'm just here to see Killua!
Why do I have to do this?!
You're different from Mike.
You may try to hide your feelings,
but you have a heart.
When I mentioned Killua,
your eyes softened for a moment.
Please...
Help Killua-sama—
You must be Gon.
I heard about you from Illumi.
Killua knows that you're here.
Why can't Killua come see us?
Because he's in solitary confinement.
Solitary confinement?
Kil returned because he regretted his actions.
And he voluntarily entered
solitary confinement.
I will take you
to the butler's office.
There is a phone that connects to the mansion.
If Zeno-sama is the one who answers...
Well? Which hand?
I have known Killua-sama his entire life.
I dare say that I care for him
as though he were my own.
In all honesty,
I must despise you for trying
to take him away.
If one of you answers incorrectly,
that person is out of the games.
Should you all be disqualified,
I shall tell Killua-sama that you left.
And that he will never see you again.
Here I go.
One second!
What is it?
If you're trying to buy time,
I'll kill one of your friends.
That's it...
He's bleeding himself, to reduce the swelling.
Okay!
Now I can see.
Give me your best!
Who now holds the coin?
The person right behind me.
Brilliant.
Gotoh, is Gon here yet?
Killua!
Oh! You're here, Gon!
Along with...
Kurapika?
I'm just an afterthought?
Liorio!
Leorio!
It's been a while.
I can't believe you came.
What happened?
Your face is a wreck!
Yours isn't any better!
"And just like that,
we managed to rescue Killua.
However, there is one more piece
of business I must take care of, Mito-san."
Hunter Vocabulary
Alphabet
"The business I still need to take care of
is left over from the exam's Fourth Phase."
I will need you to draw lots.
Lots?
For what?
To determine who will hunt
and who will be hunted.
Listen carefully!
Your target's ID tag is worth three points.
Your own ID is also worth three points.
All other ID tags are worth one point.
You need six points to advance
to the Final Phase.
So while on Zevil Island,
you must gather enough ID tags
to total six points.
That is the condition for clearing
the Hunter Exam's Fourth Phase.
What number did you draw?
Show each other our numbers
at the same time?
Okay!
Ready, and...
#44 is...
Seriously?
In a straight-up fight,
I wouldn't stand a chance.
But if I only need to steal his ID tag,
then I have a real shot.
Yeah.
I might actually have a chance.
That scares me a little...
But I think it's worth it.
Now!
I did it!
I figured it out!
I have to aim for my target as
he hunts his own prey!
There!
At this rate, Hisoka will spot him
in the next minute.
I have to figure out where
their paths will cross...
Over there!
I've gotta hurry.
Hisoka will attack,
as soon as he notices that guy.
This is my chance to steal his tag...
My last chance!
I have to conceal my presence, too.
Completely conceal my...
presence.
Here he comes!
Hisoka!
Damn... Bring it!
I did it...
I took Hisoka's tag!
Approximately, seven thousand.
Do you know what that
number represents?
The number of chances
I had to kill you.
It's also the number of times you swung
your fishing rod when you were training.
Next time, remember to
watch your own back.
So long.
Damn it...
You surprise me.
You hid your presence,
while waiting for your chance?
Waiting for me to attack another?
Did you teach yourself how
to conceal your presence?
Marvelous...
Like a wild animal.
And your timing was impeccable.
You concealed all traces of your attack
by timing it with my own attack.
A splendid job.
Wait...
Didn't you come to take back your tag?
No, I just came to commend you.
You owe me one now.
Feel free to pay me back when you want.
Goodbye.
I don't want to owe anyone...
You can have it back now.
I refuse.
Right now, I'm letting you live.
And I'll continue to keep you alive,
until you've grown enough
to be worth killing...
I'll only take it back
when you're able to punch me
in the face, just like that.
Until then, I shall leave the tag with you.
"It's the first time I've ever
felt that frustrated.
So I need to find a way to return the favor.
I can't return to Whale Island
until that's done.
That's why I'll be going to
Heavens Arena with Killua,
to train as a Hunter.
Please take care until I get back.
Gon Freecss."
I didn't expect him home anytime soon.
He really is your son...
Are you watching over him,
Ging?
Next time: Arrival x At The x Arena!
Off we go!
Gon Gon!
Again?