Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fearsome monsters... Exotic creatures...
Vast riches... Hidden treasures...
Evil enclaves... Unexplored lands...
The word "unknown" holds magic.
And some incredible people are
drawn to that magic.
They are known...
...as Hunters!
I'll tear your body apart.
Last x Test Of x Resolve
During the exam's Third Phase,
which requires applicants to
reach Trick Tower's base
within seventy-two hours,
Gon and his friends have incurred
a penalty of fifty hours.
Meanwhile...
Gerreta, applicant #384,
is the fourth to pass.
Total time, twelve hours
and twenty-seven minutes.
Eh...
Not bad, I guess.
If you hesitate on the first step,
you'll hurt yourself.
Got it.
Hey, Kurapika.
Once we've spent fifty hours here,
we'll have fewer than ten hours, right?
Yes, that's correct.
That's way more than enough time!
You're a fool.
What's that?
Phase Three lasts seventy-two hours.
And each phase is designed to weed out
half of the remaining candidates.
So, on average, it's meant to
take seventy-two hours.
Just more proof that you're an idiot.
Well, our chances of reaching
the goal within ten hours
will depend on the remaining trials.
Yeah, that's true.
But when we've got a guy
who's so down on his luck,
he can't even win a simple game
of rock-paper-scissors...
What was that?!
You deliberately lost a bet,
just to satiate your libido.
Then you chose rock-paper-scissors,
a contest you couldn't win.
Shut up!
You surrendered without even a fight!
I...
I give!
Sure, I surrendered.
But I only wasted a second of our time.
You lost,
squandering fifty of our remaining hours.
Take some responsibility, huh?
Besides, what kind of Hunter
is so bad at gambling?
Shut up!
You don't even want to become a Hunter...
You only care about ruining our chances.
And now, you'll have
the guilt eating at you
for the rest of this exam phase.
Hey! What are you doing?
Sorry about that.
Don't skateboard inside this tiny room!
Aww...
Can't sleep?
That's not it.
I can go two or three days
without sleep.
Ten hours have passed, huh...
There aren't any windows,
so it's hard to tell.
But it's probably morning.
Most likely.
Hey, pipe down.
Let me sleep some more...
That stinks!
What's wrong with you guys?
That wasn't funny.
Bastard, you'd better not
be pretending to sleep.
Damn, now I'm totally awake...
And we still have forty hours left?
Oh, I thought you just had
to stick bait on a hook,
and you could fish.
Yeah.
You have to think like a fish.
Think like a fish?
Yep!
How would a fish feel if it saw
bait dangling in front of it?
Give me that.
Wow!
Let me try.
Like this?
You missed.
Just watch.
H-Hey...
What are you doing?
Hey...
Just as planned!
Nice.
Hey, you'll tear my pants.
Stop it...
See? I caught him.
Yep.
What's that supposed to mean?
I'm a fish now?!
You don't have to get so mad.
It's not like I'm gonna grill and eat you.
Don't mess with me, fool!
Man, I can't even take a nap.
What are you smiling about?
Nothing, really.
You must be up to something again.
Of course not.
I just want to spend
the rest of my time here peacefully.
Liar!
I don't trust you, got it?
The feeling's mutual.
Yes, the goal!
Pokkle, applicant #53.
Goz, applicant #371.
Both arrived simultaneously.
Total time, thirty hours
and four minutes.
Damn.
Old timer...
In a tie, the applicant with
the lower number wins.
These guys must be very skilled.
I would love to fight them eventually.
You lost,
squandering fifty of our remaining hours.
Take some responsibility, huh?
Ow!
One more hour...
Sommy, applicant #118,
is the thirteenth to pass.
Total time, sixty-one hours
and fifty-four minutes.
Man, still ten hours left?
I finished too early.
Okay...
Ready to go!
One more minute.
This is one long minute.
Ah...
Wait up, Gon!
Hunter Vocabulary
Bored
Thirty minutes of running,
just to end up where we started.
We should have taken those stairs down.
Shut up!
We all agreed on this route!
Man, I'm covered in dust.
H-Hurry up.
We only have an hour left...
We're supposed to vote on
whether to open the door?
We need to move on. So obviously,
we want to open the door.
I've had enough of your crap.
Wait, I pressed O.
Don't lie...
You specialize in ruining
other people's chances!
Sorry, Leorio.
Eh?
I accidentally pressed the wrong button.
What?
Oh, I see.
Wait.
Huh?
You owe me an apology.
I can't let that slide.
It's your own fault,
for doing things to make me distrust you.
I don't owe you anything.
You make it sound like I'm to blame
for everything that's gone wrong.
What?
Have you forgotten
who cost us those fifty hours?
You're the one who made
a critical mistake.
Hey, Leorio...
Shut up, Kurapika!
Stop this, guys.
It's my fault for pressing
the wrong button.
Stupid.
I'm moving on.
Wait, Killua!
Hey, Gon...
We're getting close to the goal.
What? Really?
Let's see...
"This will be the last decision
made by majority rule.
Are you ready?
Choose O or X."
That's it.
Am I ready?
You bet.
Bastard...
Stop!
We don't have time to argue about this!
Please select a path.
There are two choices.
One path allows five to pass,
but is long and difficult.
The other path allows only three,
but is short and easy.
Incidentally, the long and difficult path
requires a minimum of forty-five hours.
The short and easy path leads
to the goal in approximately three minutes.
Press O for the long and difficult path,
and X for the short and easy path.
If X is selected,
two people must be secured to
the wall with handcuffs,
before the door will open.
The two chained members
will be unable to move until
the time limit expires.
The examiners were very prepared.
I think they have
every weapon under the sun here.
Two out of five...
So we're supposed to fight,
to decide the three who pass?
Let me make this clear.
I'm going to press X.
But I have no intention of staying behind.
I'll do whatever it takes to
be one of the three...
You're shameless.
Had you not wasted fifty hours,
we could have taken the long path.
Shouldn't you take responsibility
and stay behind?
What?!
I'm sure everyone else agrees!
Have I said anything inaccurate?
Hold on.
I'm going to press O.
We made it all the way here together.
I want us all to pass together.
Gon...
Even if it's a big risk,
I want to give it a shot!
Come on...
You can't really call this a risk.
We have less than an hour.
Gon, there's only one choice
if you want to pass this exam.
There you have it.
Now we have to decide how to
choose which three pass.
Well, I'm planning on
two of them being you and me.
Heh, I've made it this far.
I won't fail now.
Whoever makes the first move wins.
Must we really fight amongst ourselves?
Tonpa, that was dirty!
In a fight,
there's no such thing as dirty!
Bastard!
Stop this, you two!
Come on... Let's do it together.
Before we start fighting,
we have to choose O or X!
It's too late for that!
Time to put you in your place!
Right back at you.
Seems our only choice is to fight.
What should I do?
Three minutes remain.
It's finally over...
Yeah, that took forever.
Made it in time...
He's dead.
The fool.
Better to live and try again,
than to pass and die.
One minute remains.
Looks like it'll just be
the nineteen here.
Kurapika, applicant #404,
is the twentieth to pass.
Killua, applicant #99,
is the twenty-first to pass.
Gon, applicant #405,
is the twenty-second to pass.
Total time, seventy-one hours
and fifty-nine minutes.
My butt hurts...
I didn't expect a slide
for the short and easy path.
Three of them...
Thirty seconds remain.
That was really close.
My hands are covered with blisters.
Same here.
Leorio, applicant #403,
is the twenty-third to pass.
Tonpa, applicant #16,
is the twenty-fourth to pass.
Total time, seventy-one hours
and fifty-nine minutes.
My hands are blistered,
but all five of us cleared
the tower together.
All thanks to Gon!
We entered the long and difficult path.
Then cut a hole in the wall,
to sneak into the short and easy path.
Man, I can't believe
you actually came up with
that idea on the spot.
I realized that we could break
the walls, using the weapons.
But it took over fifty minutes.
In an extreme situation,
you were able to calmly evaluate
our two options and circumvent them.
That's what makes you special.
The Third Phase of the exam is over.
Twenty-five applicants have passed.
One has died.
Though the team members
had their differences,
Gon was able to bring them together,
to overcome the trial.
However, a friend today may
become a foe tomorrow.
Gon doesn't know that before long,
they'll be pitted
against each other,
in brutal, individual battles.
Next time: Letter x From x Gon!
Now I'm worried.
Because of me?