Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fearsome monsters... Exotic creatures...
Vast riches... Hidden treasures...
Evil enclaves... Unexplored lands...
The word "unknown" holds magic.
And some incredible people are
drawn to that magic.
They are known...
...as Hunters!
Right now, I'm letting you live.
Until you've grown enough
to be worth killing...
I'll only take it back
when you're able to punch me
in the face, just like that.
Until then, I shall leave the tag with you.
Trap x In The x Hole
Gon was humiliated,
after Hisoka recovered the tags
taken by Gerreta.
As for Killua...
You're wasting your time.
I'll never give you an opening to attack.
Tremble with fear.
Wear yourself out.
I am a very cautious man.
I go to any lengths necessary,
even when facing a child.
Once he exhausts himself,
and has no choice but to sleep,
I'll attack!
I am a very cautious man.
Man...
If you're not gonna show yourself,
I'll come to you.
Huh?
What a pain...
You're only worth one point to me.
He wants to fight?
I can't possibly lose, right?
He's just a kid.
But...
Why is he so calm?
Is he really that strong?
Right... I am a very cautious man.
I should esca—
I mean, I should back off.
But...
My brothers will yell at me!
Actually, if I go back without
taking his tag,
they'll definitely yell at me!
Bro!
We ran into some trouble.
You're done, right?
You idiot!
You can't even beat a little kid?
Y-You got it wrong, Amo!
What do I have wrong?
I-I didn't want to hurt a little kid.
So I figured I'd take it while he slept.
You're lying through your teeth!
F-Fine!
If you insist, that leaves me no choice.
Time for a beat down.
If I start to lose,
my brothers will come to my aid.
Hey, kid.
Just give me your tag.
Do as I say, and I won't hurt you.
Stupid.
Aw, don't say I didn't warn you.
Right in the gut.
Must hurt like a bitch.
Huh?
What?
Did you go easy on him?
You're too nice, Imori.
Y-Yeah...
#198, huh?
What? No way...
Since it's only a number off
from the one I'm after,
maybe #199 is one of your two buddies?
Umori...
Yeah.
Get in formation.
Time to get serious.
This is no ordinary kid.
It doesn't matter how strong he is.
He stands no chance
against our teamwork.
We three have
defeated many tough opponents
with this formation.
Just you wait...
We're gonna rip you to shreds.
A-Above?
Don't move.
My fingers are sharper than knives.
Huh?
You're #197?
I'm so bad at guessing these things...
Hey.
Are you #199?
Yeah...
Hand it over.
Thanks.
Now, for the tags I don't need...
And the other one goes this way.
You still have three days.
Good luck finding them.
See ya.
Damn it!
#197 was always accompanied by #199...
I didn't expect that little kid to
deal with them for me.
Good thing I was watching
from the shadows.
Made it easy to grab the tag I wanted...
The kid noticed I was there...
I've failed...
Man, that was boring.
Wonder what Gon's doing.
Hunter Vocabulary
Too Bad
Six days have passed.
Only one day left...
It's been four days since
we ran into Hisoka.
And we haven't seen anyone else.
Wanna head back to the starting point?
It's possible that people have
already finished.
No, we won't find anyone there.
This phase is unique because
you have a chance to recover
your tag if you lose it.
On the other hand,
you might have six points
in tags right now.
But that doesn't guarantee you'll have
them when the phase ends.
You can't finish it early.
I see.
But it's worth a shot.
Only one day remains.
People who already have six points
will be inclined to wait near the goal.
I would do the same.
Okay, let's go.
Well? Anyone there?
No...
No one that can be easily spotted.
Damn...
Perhaps we should split up to search,
after we decide on a time and
place to reconvene.
It'll go faster with three people.
Gon!
I guess we all had the same idea.
I've been watching from up above,
and a number of people are nearby.
Really?
I see... We should search from above.
That won't work.
It's only possible if you have eyes
as sharp as Gon's.
Gon.
Huh?
Do you have the tags you need?
Yeah, I guess...
Damn, so I'm the only one
without enough points.
Who's your target?
#246, a woman named Ponzu.
I heard that she uses chemical weapons.
Gon, did you see any women
when you were up there?
Nope.
I see.
We can assume that there
are four possibilities.
She's in good shape,
and she still has her tag.
but she's lost her tag.
She's out of action,
but she still has her tag.
and she doesn't have her tag.
Is it really likely
that she'd still have her tag
if she's out of action?
If she were caught in a sudden accident,
or if she were defeated after
hiding the tag.
If she died after concealing her tag,
we won't be able to find it.
Sounding grimmer by the second.
Hey, do you know anything
else about Ponzu?
Does she wear a special perfume,
like Leorio with his cologne?
Oh, that's right.
Gon can follow her scent!
But she might not wear perfume.
He can smell the chemicals she uses.
She's known for using drugs, right?
Some of them must have strong scents.
Well, Gon?
Okay, I'll give it a shot.
That's why I'm here.
Is she in there, Gon?
Yep, definitely.
What do you want to do?
I'm going inside.
You guys, wait here.
There don't appear to be any traps.
I'll head inside.
Don't enter until I give the okay.
Thirty minutes.
Huh?
If we don't hear anything from you
after thirty minutes,
we're coming in.
Yeah.
Unacceptable.
If that happens, you guys
should return to the start.
I can't do that.
Since we've teamed up,
I won't abandon you now.
Then I quit the team.
It's selfish, considering all the
help you've given me,
but I'll do this alone.
No.
What did you say?!
We're staying here, no matter
what you say.
Still got a problem?
Do whatever you want.
Hold onto that for me.
I have to go for it...
Isn't that...
Bourbon?
I'm guessing that
I'm your target?
Ponzu!
There's no point.
We gain nothing by fighting here.
I have everything to gain.
It's just as you said...
You're my target!
Let's pretend that a miracle occurs,
and you defeat me.
You still won't be able
to leave this cave.
What?
What do you mean?
He's taking too long.
Is Leorio okay?
Yeah.
It's been nearly thirty minutes.
Kurapika! Gon!
Don't come in!
Leorio!
You fools...
Why did you enter the cave?
He has bites all over his body!
If those snakes were venomous...
They're vipers.
Their poison isn't that strong.
But he's been bitten
too many times!
S-Stop it!
If you have any cavities or
open wounds in your mouth...
No problem!
Leorio, do you have any
serums in here?
If I did,
I could have saved you guys...
Leorio!
Anyway, we have to stop the bleeding.
Uh-huh!
That should do it.
We need to take him to a doctor!
I would stop if I were you.
You cannot leave.
What do you mean?
When someone tries to exit this cave,
snakes attack them.
Bourbon, the snake charmer,
set this trap.
If you're bitten,
you'll end up paralyzed like he is.
And then you'll die.
Bourbon!
You're looking for tags, right?
We'll give you every tag
in our possession.
So let us out of here!
It's no use.
He's already dead.
D-Dead?
Gon and his friends have
been caught in Bourbon
the snake charmer's trap,
and can't leave the cave.
Will they pass the Hunter Exam?
Will Leorio survive the
venomous snake bites?
Next time: Big x Time x Interview!
Thank you, Kurapika.
Thank you, Gon.