Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hello? Pitou-sama?
This is Komugi.
I'm fine, so don't worry.
Got it...
Now, Pitou is also under my spell...
The spell of the lie that will
free Pitou from that curse.
Gon...
You listened to my request.
So I will be honest with you.
He is
already
dead.
His soul is no longer here.
There is no way to heal him.
I am sorry.
Huh?
Why is it healing Pitou's arm?
Turn Kite back to normal.
Please...
After you finish what you're doing...
Anger x And x Light
The tables have been turned.
Pitou believes we have recovered Komugi.
The way things are looking,
that Gon boy will be killed.
I am the only one who can stop Pitou.
If you hand the woman over
to me, I will stop Pitou...
Get lost, scumbag!
Leave her to me.
I swear upon these eyes that
I will not let them have her.
Yeah, I'm counting on you.
Speed of Lightning!
Gon...
Wait for me to get there!
I'm sorry to say this,
but I must kill you.
For the King.
You must
kill me?
You aren't going to heal him?
Then you really aren't
going to heal Kite...
Liar.
What?
What is this?
I don't care
if this is the end...
So...
I'll use everything.
I was right.
His power is now equal
to that of the King!
I'll kill you,
Pitou!
Terpsichora!
Exceed your limits,
and dance!
I must stop him here!
It can't be!
Is he heading for the King?
Come.
I don't want to destroy this place.
This way.
Follow me.
I don't know how he did it,
but he's forced his body to mature to a point
at which he's able to defeat me.
First comes
rock...
Rock.
Paper.
Sinking deeply into unconsciousness,
Pitou felt a sense of relief.
Thank goodness...
This power could only be achieved through
the sacrifice of his own life energy.
He's prepared to never use Nen again.
That was the resolve required
to perform this feat.
An enemy blessed with immense talent
has been forced to exchange all
of that talent for this power.
I'm so glad
I am the one
that he will kill...
Having used Speed of Lightning to race
to Gon, Killua arrived to hear...
Which one of them is doing that?
Gon!
And what he found was...
A silhouette that looked nothing
like the person he'd known,
swinging a fist, bloodied from countless punches,
downward toward the skull
of an already-broken Pitou...
Rock.
Paper.
...for the final, shattering blow.
Kite...
I finished the job, the way you taught me to.
So...
Gon,
is that you?
Killua...
Having seen Gon's appearance,
Killua immediately thought of Bisky.
But he realized the difference at once.
Bisky's appearance changed,
but there wasn't a massive increase
in the aura contained within her.
And in Bisky's case,
she was merely reverting to her original form.
But Gon's done the opposite!
How many years?
More than ten?
Decades?
This would have been the result
of years of endless training.
What price did he have to pay
to obtain so much aura?
Pitou's devotion to the King was so great
that even after death, Terpsichora clad
itself in even more powerful Nen,
transforming Pitou into a corpse puppet
ready to leap forward in pursuit of its prey,
its sole purpose to kill Gon.
In that fraction of a second,
shorter than the blink of an eye,
Killua heard Gon speak.
It's okay.
It doesn't hurt.
I'm not trying to be tough.
I'm kind of happy...
I finally
get to be the same
as Kite was then.
Gon...
I feel like
I've been redeemed some.
You can have my right arm.
First comes rock...
Gon!
It's time for you
to sleep, too.
Stop...
You can't!
If you keep using this power,
what will happen to you?
Rock.
Paper.
Gon!
Next time: Flash x And x Start.
I never got a chance to say this, but thank you...
For everything.