Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I have a duty to fulfill...
I must give birth to the King!
I am the Queen!
Unease x And x Sighting
After using Accompany,
Gon and Killua were transported
to Ging's student, Kite.
After Gon remembered having
met Kite years before,
he felt that Ging intended
for this meeting to occur,
and his interest in Kite grew.
Hey, what kind of work do you do, Kite?
Biological surveying.
I focus on discovering and
researching new species.
Oh, have you heard of the Camp Tiger?
Camp Tiger?
They can use fire.
They use branches that have been
ignited by lightning as live kindle.
Other than certain Magical
Beasts that walk on two legs,
they're the first of their kind:
animals that eat their meat cooked, not raw.
Wow, they're really cooking it.
They really are using fire!
Hey, what else is there?
Oh, yeah...
You said the thing that attacked
me was a Chimera Ant?
Yes, a Chimera Ant.
Under a class-1 quarantine.
Normally, no one would be allowed
near such a dangerous insect.
Did you discover them?
No, I specialize in larger creatures.
But currently, I'm investigating these insects.
Something has been bothering me...
But it appears that now, I'll have
to move to a different location.
I must make a call, but I'm not
getting any reception here.
A call?
I'm working with others.
Seven of us are working as a team.
I guess I must wait for their arrival.
Once they're here, I'll introduce you.
They're amateurs, but they're still skilled Hunters.
Oh?
Ah, speak of the devil.
Kite, who are these kids?
My friends.
They dropped by for a visit on their travels.
Oh, it's a pleasure to meet
you all the way out here.
I'm Spinner Clow.
Call me Spin!
Nice to meet you.
I'm Gon Freecss.
Nice to meet you, Spin.
Freecss...
Wait, is this...
Yes, Ging-san's son.
Really?!
And you? Not you, too?
No, not me.
My name is Killua Zoldyck.
Zoldyck...
Um, forgive me if I'm wrong, but are you
part of the famous family of assassins?
Yeah, but I quit.
Additionally, they are both pro Hunters.
So you should show some respect.
Wow!
Man, that was a shock!
We've been conducting biological
surveys with Kite for three years,
but this is the most incredible
organism we've ever seen!
Yeah, no kidding...
I don't think we finished our introductions.
I'm Monta Yuras.
But call me Mon.
Nice to meet you, Mon.
I'm Stick Dinner.
I handle the cooking.
Know why?
Because my name is Dinner.
Nice meeting you.
My name is Banana Kavaro.
Good to meet you.
We have two others on our team.
Where are Podungo and Lin?
They're both headed toward
the area of the sighting.
They always move so fast.
Oh, and you were right, Kite...
This looks just like the claw
of a Chimera Ant queen.
We ran some computer analyses,
and the result was a 99% match.
Can I see it?
Sure.
This is a Chimera Ant claw?
It's as big as a human finger.
Does that mean there are huge ants?
We don't know.
Maybe one mutated and grew really big?
That's possible, though it may also belong
to a completely different species.
Regardless, we just don't know right now.
That's why we're investigating.
It all started with the wonkiest little thing...
His name was Won!
He was a Kakin official.
What's Kakin?
Right here.
It's this wild land, in the middle
of the Azian continent.
We had just completed a biological
survey they had requested when...
Magnificent.
You've completed two hundred years'
worth of work for this agency...
To be honest, I regret that I am
unable to pay you a bonus.
Don't say that, Won-san.
We enjoyed ourselves.
In lieu of that,
I'll be sure to recommend you
to other friendly nations.
We appreciate it.
Oh, that's right!
I'm going to ramble a bit.
I believe part of a very strange species was
brought to the Southern Piece auction...
There's suspicion that it's from
an unidentified organism,
so the seller couldn't list it in the catalog,
but since they'd have to donate it
to a government agency otherwise,
they hoped a licensed Hunter would
buy it from them for a high price.
Here you are.
Well, Lin?
Th-This clearly belongs to an
unidentified organism, yes.
F-From what I can see,
it resembles an insect's leg...
B-But no known insects have l-legs this large.
And the claw exhibits traits
not found among insects...
A leg typically has two claws, but this has six.
It almost looks as though the tarsi
evolved into something like fingers?
Yes, and this part is spiny,
so it could be the tibia.
If we take a sample and study
it further, we'll learn more.
Could you give us a small part?
Since Won-san referred you
to us, we cannot refuse.
Let's look into this, then.
We'll send you any results, once we have them.
Appreciated.
Chimera Ant...
Where did Lin and Podungo go?
Somewhere south of Yorknew City.
The person who found the insect leg
apparently lives in a city by the ocean.
Sorry you won't be able to catch your breath,
but we should hurry after them.
Hey, can we come with you?
Hmm?
Sure.
Yes!
Glad to have you.
Having two pro Hunters with us is reassuring.
And this is Ging-san's son and
one of the Zoldyck family!
Oh, sorry...
It's no big deal.
Anyway, you kids are already pros at your age?
We weren't born with the talent...
Talent, talent... Guess I have a
talent for saying "talent," huh?
In this brief period of time,
they've become friends.
Good Hunters are well-liked by animals.
And also blessed with good friends.
Gon might be the real deal...
He'll find you soon, Ging-san.
Not enough... Not enough...
I need more, bigger food.
It's been days...
No, it's been months since it last rained here.
The weather is unusual this year.
It's possible that this is affecting
the wildlife in some way.
So the insect with the large leg
could have been a mutation
influenced by those conditions.
But why would it have grown larger?
In order to survive, right?
If it's bigger, it'd have a better
chance of securing food.
But that would mean it'd need more, as well.
Being larger doesn't always aid survival.
I believe that this is
related to the Chimera Ant's unique
nature, not to the environment.
I agree.
Because they reproduce in a way
not found in any other organism.
What do you mean?
They reproduce through a special
process known as phagogenesis.
Phagogenesis?
What's that?
Phagogenesis
When a Chimera Ant queen eats other organisms,
she is able to pass traits on
from those organisms to the next generation.
And she can also eat multiple species
to pass on a mix of genes to her offspring.
With each feeding, she lays one to five eggs.
The first generation of births has
no reproductive capability,
so they become worker or soldier ants.
They work in service to the queen
and her eventual successors.
Those successors are the king and
queen of the next generation.
The queen is thus always looking to
consume the genes of strong organisms,
so she can pass them to her offspring.
And she may consume any species she
particularly likes to extinction.
To extinction?!
Yes, her voracious appetite can drive her
to consume her own weight many
times over, in a single day.
That's why Chimera Ants are
under a class-1 quarantine.
So if she sets her eyes on you, you're finished?
Judging from the size of that claw,
her length is at least two meters.
That thing could devour a human in no time.
Yes, you are correct.
Stay back! Go away!
B-Big Brother...
Reina, stay close to me.
Take that!
It's okay now.
Thank you!
You can count on your big brother.
I'll always keep you safe!
Yeah!
Okay, let's go home.
Hey, my brother was amazing!
There was a big snake, but he was like,
"Stay back! Go away!"
Whack!
Come now, don't wave your spoon around.
It's bad manners.
But that's what he did.
Yes, yes. I know.
That was very brave.
If a big snake showed up,
your mother might be too scared to move.
You're truly a young man, Kurt.
Yeah, I guess.
You're already nine...
And a reliable big brother.
You must continue to look after Reina.
I'm counting on you, Kurt.
I'm counting on you, Brother.
Yeah, you can count on me!
I'll keep you both safe forever!
This area is about to hatch.
Soldiers, hear me!
My duty is to give birth to the King.
In order to give birth to a strong king,
I require large quantities of highly nutritious food.
Search out the best food you can find!
This area will also hatch soon.
I require a large nest in
which to birth a strong king.
I also need time to rest, free from concerns
of outside disturbances, during the pregnancy.
In order to give birth to a strong
king, I need strong soldiers.
Are you okay?
Uh-huh, thank you...
Hey, Brother...
When I grow up, I'm gonna marry you.
Sure.
Let's wake up early tomorrow
and go fishing at the river.
Yeah.
We can cook some fish to surprise Mom.
Uh-huh, I can't wait.
This is enough fish for a feast.
Yep.
B-Big Brother...
Big Brother!
Reina, it's okay.
I'll...
Your big brother will protect you!
I promised Mom!
I'll keep you safe!
Go away...
Go away!
This is delicious,
and very nutritious...
The ultimate food.
I need more of this species.
They're the ones I mentioned on
the phone, Gon and Killua.
Oh, I'm Lin Koshi.
N-Nice to meet you.
My name's Podungo Lapoy.
Glad to have you on board.
Glad to be here, Lin-san, Podungo-san.
Hey.
Let's get down to business.
Where was the leg discovered?
On the beach over there.
A-According to the locals,
it washed up on sh-shore.
There's a forest right behind us...
It'll be difficult to find the
Chimera Ant if it ran in there.
We can't be certain that it's still alive.
We don't even know if it ended up
on the same island its leg drifted to.
Let's find out, then.
Here, remember this scent.
I'll help, too!
Huh?
His nose is as sharp as a dog's.
He can't find anything...
The scent may have disappeared.
It was raining.
I couldn't find anything, either.
That means the Chimera Ant isn't here.
It may have washed ashore elsewhere.
In which direction do the currents flow here?
It's complicated...
The direction is reversed
between day and night.
And it also changes with the seasons.
I've even heard it's different on certain days.
So it'll be tough to pinpoint a location...
It's too early to give up.
Let's split up and search.
You're right.
No luck...
Continuing to search blindly is pointless.
Let's return to Yorknew City.
We may be able to find a new lead.
Her length is at least two meters.
That thing could devour a human in no time.
A voracious appetite...
Phagogenesis.
Your Majesty...
Oh, you can speak?
So that I may fully receive,
understand, and execute your orders.
That pleases me.
I assign you to be a squadron leader.
I am most grateful.
I already have your mission.
Lead all the soldiers here on a mission
to capture my food...
Capture more of those highly
nutritious organisms for me.
At once!
A Chimera Ant has been born with human genes.
Kite's worst fears have been realized.
Next time: Very x Rapid x Reproduction.
My name is Gon Freecss.
My name is Killua Zoldyck.
What's your name?