Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Heavens Arena.
The 251-story, 991-meter
building is a mecca for fighters.
When combatants win a fight,
they may advance by one class,
and receive a corresponding reward.
After reaching the 100th floor,
you are assigned a private room.
After reaching the 200th floor,
you receive the right to challenge
the strongest fighters,
the Floor Masters, in an intense
battle of survival.
This is the best stage
a warrior could ask for.
Then, your brother is able to use Nen?
I need to know what Nen
and Ren even mean!
I'll agree to the full learning process
rather than a quick explanation!
I understand.
Nen x And x Nen
After Killua fought Zushi,
the young Shingen-ryu practitioner,
Zushi mentioned the four major principles.
Gon and Killua are about to learn the secret
of those principles from Zushi's master, Wing.
Do I have your attention?
Nen means to burn your own soul.
In other words,
it tests your strength of will.
Burn
Nen
And the four major principles are part
of a training curriculum for
strengthening your will.
Strengthening your will?
Training?
That's correct.
Ten
Focus
Ten means to focus your soul to a single point,
to increase awareness of your ego and goals.
Express
Zetsu
Zetsu means to express yourself in words.
Temper
Ren
Ren means to temper that will.
Act
Hatsu
And Hatsu means to act upon that will.
Focus
Express
Temper
Act
Four Major Principles
Ten.
Zetsu.
Ren.
Hatsu.
Those are the four major principles.
Killua-kun, Zushi tempered his "refusal
to lose," during his fight with you.
So, allow me to demonstrate.
Killua-kun...
I think I'm going to kill you now.
Are you ready?
Yeah, sure.
It's not happening.
Then I'll take this step-by-step.
First comes Ten.
I focus my soul into a single point.
Zetsu.
You can express yourself mentally or verbally.
I will kill you.
That was Ren.
If I temper my will enough,
then I can act. Hatsu.
If your will is strong enough,
you can make your opponent back down,
without moving a muscle.
The concept of bluffing derives from this.
Ren hardens that which is soft,
and you lose the ability to
correct an incorrect idea.
Therefore, you should avoid using Ren
until your soul has fully matured.
Right now, you boys and Zushi
should be training your souls.
Let's go, Gon.
If you wish to learn about Nen,
you should focus on mastering Ten.
If you master Ten,
you will no longer feel the pressure
of an opponent's will.
Thank you very much!
Wait up, Killua!
Zushi.
Yes, sir.
Let's begin training.
O-Osu!
First...
He was lying?
Yeah. The explanation made perfect sense,
and Wing is clearly very strong.
But his story had holes.
Huh?
Zushi's toughness.
He kept getting up after
I knocked him down.
I was getting irritated,
so I used all of my strength
during my last attack.
Brat!
Crap!
He flew out of the ring!
Even an amateur can see that
he's headed for the hospital!
Oh! He stood back up.
Zushi must be invincible.
Impossible.
However, the referee has awarded
a critical hit and knockdown.
Killua wins by TKO, with eleven total points.
Willpower didn't keep him standing.
He's hiding some other secret.
What's wrong, Zushi?
Your Ten is unstable.
Master...
Hmm?
Why did you lie to them?
Lie?
You mean my explanation?
Yes!
The four major principles are
Ten, Zetsu, Ren, and Hatsu.
But they don't mean what you said.
Did you lie because they aren't your students?
I didn't lie.
Nen is an important method
for training your soul.
Force
However, it's true that I can't teach Nen
to someone who is not a student.
So I used the other Nen as a hint,
to help them along.
If Nen is used the wrong way,
it can become a terrible weapon.
For example...
You could turn a piece of paper
into a blade to harm others,
while hardening your body,
as a defensive measure.
With enough work, anyone can use Nen.
That is why
you must be careful when
deciding to teach it.
Master...
I didn't
have a chance to read that book yet...
And that can of juice was mine...
S-Sorry...
It's time for the day's biggest match!
The rookies Killua and Gon have advanced
to the 190th floor without dropping a fight.
Will they be able to keep moving on?
Okay, everyone...
Get ready to press your gamble switches!
Unfortunately, your shove won't work on me.
That's because
I am as slippery as a snake,
with sharp fangs,
to bite at your vital points.
You may sport a vicious chop,
but you can't overcome these muscles!
That's because...
I'm totally ripped!
Begin!
Critical hit and knockdown...
Three points.
Knockout!
The winner is Gon!
Critical hit and knockdown...
Three points.
Knockout!
The winner is Killua!
Once again, Gon and Killua have knocked
out their opponents with one attack.
And both of them have
successfully cleared the 190s!
Both have advanced to the 200s!
They've already reached the 200s?!
Zushi.
Master!
Killua-kun and Gon-kun have
already reached the 200s?
Yes, they're amazing!
I need to train more...
Huh?
Master?
I have no choice.
Enjoy.
What's the 200th floor like?
Beats me.
I've never been up here before.
Wow!
The 200th floor is so fancy!
Where's the receptionist?
This way?
We finally made it.
Yeah.
What is this?
All of a sudden, it feels like
we're in a monster-filled jungle.
But this is an ordinary hallway.
Let's go.
We can do this!
This isn't working...
I can't move forward!
I don't want to move forward...
This is murderous intent,
aimed at us.
Hey! Who's there?
Show yourself!
Killua-sama and Gon-sama, correct?
The receptionist's desk is over here,
so please register for a 200s match today.
You won't be able to register
after midnight, so please be careful.
Was she the source of all that?
I can't tell.
By the way, there are currently
one hundred, seventy-three
contestants in the 200s class.
And starting from the 200s,
all weapons are allowed in matches.
So please use whatever you have.
Also, you will no longer receive
prize money in the 200s class.
You will fight only for glory,
so please understand that
if you're going to participate.
Huh?!
H-Hisoka...
Why are you here?
It's hardly that strange.
I love to fight,
and this is a temple to fighting.
And why are you here?
Just kidding...
This was no coincidence.
I've been waiting for you.
Remember how you ordered airship
tickets over the cybernet?
With a little effort,
it's possible to determine where
and when someone will arrive.
Well,
I knew you would come here eventually.
And so,
as a veteran, I have a warning for you.
It's still too early for you boys
to step on this floor.
How early depends on your efforts.
Leave for now.
It's too early right now.
That's stupid!
We just got up here...
I won't let you pass.
Not that you could, anyway.
Wh-What is...
...this?
Don't be reckless!
Wing-san!
You have no defense
against his Nen.
Nen?
Right now, you are like someone standing
naked in a blizzard, wondering why it is cold.
If you continue to strain
your body, you may die.
This is Nen?!
He can stop us from moving
forward through willpower?
Don't lie!
Yes, I was lying.
Though technically, I wasn't lying completely.
I will teach you the truth about Nen.
So retreat for now.
Hey, receptionist lady.
Oh, yes?
What happens if we don't register
for a fight today?
Gon-sama, you would have to
start again, from the first floor.
However, Killua-sama
refused to register once before.
So if he fails to register again,
his commitment will be questioned,
and he will be banned from participating.
Hey, Wing-san.
If we back down now,
will we be able to return here
by midnight?
That depends on you.
Simply put,
this is Nen.
Nen refers to the ability
to manipulate your aura,
Force
Nen
also known as life energy.
Every person possesses a
small amount of life energy.
But in most cases, it's simply discharged.
The ability to build up
a shroud of life energy is known as Ten.
Shroud
You can make your body harder,
Ten
Shroud
and considerably slow the effects of aging.
Then comes Zetsu.
Null
Zetsu
As you may guess, this nullifies your aura.
It is effective for
concealing your presence,
and recovering from extreme fatigue.
Which brings us to Ren.
Enhance
Ren
A technique to create an especially strong aura.
Can you feel that?
Yeah, I can feel the pressure.
But it doesn't feel dangerous.
That's because I have no hostile intent.
However, I must admit I am
impressed by their senses.
Perhaps it's because of
how they've grown up.
But their natural potential is
also a major factor.
Aura is an energy that comes
from within humans.
Which makes it very effective
against other humans.
For better or worse.
If you attack a helpless person, with ill intent,
you can use aura to kill.
Only one thing can protect you
from someone who uses Nen.
You must also learn to use Nen.
You must use Ten for defense.
Block the other person's aura with your own.
Otherwise...
Your body will be crushed.
Hisoka blocks the path leading
beyond the 200th floor.
Will Gon and Killua be able
to learn enough about
true Nen to pass Hisoka,
and reach the receptionist,
before the clock strikes midnight?
It's too early.
Coming up, we have Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
It's Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Today, we introduce Wing-san!
Master of Shingen-ryu.
Zushi's teacher.
He's Zushi's teacher!
And a master of Shingen-ryu!
Very serious about teaching Nen,
Seems he's pretty good with Nen.
but sloppy about everything else.
Oh, Wing-san's shirt isn't tucked in.
And his hair's a mess!
Next time: Awakening x And x Potential!
Did you feel anything?
Nope, nothing.