Edited at https://subtitletools.com
To become kings, the Chimera Ants
have spread across the world,
committing acts of utmost
tyranny wherever they go.
Fearing the damage will spread,
the government asks the Hunter
Association to exterminate them.
Finally, the Hunter Association makes its move.
Ah, is that all?
Infiltration x And x Selection
Sneaking in was easy.
But the question is how to get
close enough to the enemy.
And we can't let just anyone see us, either.
Informants
This country has a powerful
information regulation system that
operates in secret using groups of informants.
Informants?
Yeah, if you discover an enemy spy,
you receive a reward.
If you find evidence of insurgency,
If you stop someone from fleeing the
country, you receive a reward.
So the people will do anything for that reward.
And they aren't just after money.
After racking up enough informant points,
the entire group is promoted.
But if someone provides false information
or a member commits a crime,
the entire group is punished.
Carrot and stick, huh?
It's pretty nasty business.
Family members are put in different groups.
So if an entire group tries to escape,
the other family members can be
executed or imprisoned for life.
If a family is caught trying to escape together,
they'll be executed, no questions asked.
For this country's elite to live the good life,
the rest of its citizens must scrape by.
But the media also spreads lies.
Such as that, in other countries,
half the population starves by age ten.
Foreign aid never reaches the needy.
Instead, it's spent on cars, jewels, and missiles.
It's even said that East Gorteau spends
grant money developing nuclear weapons
that become bargaining chips in negotiations
for unprecedented foreign aid increases.
Hey, don't overheat!
I th-think I'm okay...
That was just so complicated...
But you sure know a lot about it.
My brother told me everything.
And he probably heard it from Grandpa.
Your grandpa?
Yeah. Long ago, he infiltrated
the country for a job.
And I've seen similar information
on Hunter websites.
The system is likely still in use.
There's a village.
Yeah... It's not very big.
What do we do?
Sneak in.
Is that a good idea?
We need current information.
Knowing what kinds of clothes they wear or
how to identify someone's rank will help.
They may have certain practices to root out spies.
The more data we have, the better.
Wait here.
It's completely deserted...
Maybe everyone already left for Peijing?
No, something happened here.
And someone's trying to hide it.
Huh?
They did a sloppy job.
They didn't dig deep enough,
so wild dogs got to the bodies.
I'd imagine the entire village is buried here.
What's going on?
This is the true purpose of
the national celebration.
It's a pretense for entire populations of towns
and cities to vanish without raising suspicion.
The selection has already begun.
In hindsight,
it would be tough to summon all citizens to
the capital and make the selection so quickly.
This nation has a population
of around five million.
Clearing out one town or city
at a time is more effective.
In that case, their only concern would
be coworkers or family members
raising a fuss over the missing.
But with the pretext of the national celebration,
no one will find it strange that
they can't contact someone.
In this nation, cell phones aren't allowed,
so if they believe the other party is traveling,
it makes sense that they can't contact them.
The selection will go very smoothly.
The capital city, Peijing, is in the southeast corner.
They only need to attack the farthest
towns first and work their way east.
If each town is told that the government
will assign its people a time to depart,
there won't be any problems regarding
communication between towns.
So, by preventing people from meeting
between towns to travel together,
they eliminate any cause for commotion.
But...
Hmm?
That means
they have to run around the nation
to attack all five million citizens.
Yeah.
If one percent survives, that gives
them fifty thousand soldiers.
No, I mean before that.
There are ten... No, nine days left.
If you wanted to check five
million people in that time,
you'd need a lot of help.
Assuming that one Nen user
can check ten thousand citizens in ten days...
Five hundred Nen users.
Exactly!
You're getting at the fact that there can't
be that many Ants who can use Nen?
Yeah.
I agree, but it probably isn't that hard.
They don't need Nen users to check everyone.
Huh? Why not?
They can use manipulation.
The power that Chimera Ant used...
I'm guessing it can be used
to automate victims or,
like Genthru's power, can probably be
used to control multiple people at once.
Ordinary humans have aura as well,
so the manipulator could force a
victim's aura to concentrate in his fist.
One punch alone could create
an army of fifty thousand.
While leaving four million, nine hundred
and fifty thousand dead in the process.
Well, it isn't all bad news.
If my theory is correct,
causing a commotion to stop their
selection will be simple.
We merely have to pop up,
take out whoever is being controlled,
and cause a panic.
Then we just encourage
the people who escape to
check on other towns nearby.
If the Chimera Ants have sent controlled
puppets, rather than actual Nen users,
taking them down will be a cinch.
We'll just run around, taking them down
one after another, and wreak havoc.
Yeah.
The problem is that they'll detect us quickly.
Once we make our move,
they'll know we're here.
If we want to go with the old man's
plan, we should stay hidden.
What do you think?
Let's do it.
If the selection has already begun,
we can't just stand around watching.
Okay, let's do it.
Uh-huh!
But I'll do this alone.
Huh?
You stay in hiding.
Why?
It'll go better if we both—
Don't forget our main mission!
Defeating that Chimera Ant.
That should be your focus.
Let me handle everything else.
I'll stir things up.
And no offense, but I work more easily alone.
Jeez... Fine, I got it.
Really?
Huh?
Do you really understand?
Killua?
Promise me you won't make a move!
Not even if people are killed
right before your eyes!
Promise!
I'll contact you by text.
Our cell phones should still work in this area.
Killua?
Sorry... It's nothing!
I'm just a little tense.
What's this?
They aren't citizens of this country.
I would expect a couple of kids to be spies.
But they're definitely strong...
Are they assassins?
Are they here to hunt down the King?
Then I can't ignore them...
But I don't want to fight them both at once.
I definitely don't want to fight the
silver-haired one on the left.
Just watching him walk, I can tell he's strong.
As much potential as a Squadron Leader?
That kid is something special.
I completely concealed my presence,
but he still sensed something?
How convenient!
Are you sure about this?
You'll really transport my family
and me to another country?
Do not worry.
We have received official approval,
and prepared the necessary documents.
All that's left is for you to sign the papers.
However, the condition that you share
your complete knowledge of military affairs
in exchange for your freedom is essential.
As mentioned in the agreement,
if you do not keep up your end after signing,
we shall both find ourselves in difficult positions.
That won't be a problem.
I'll tell you everything...
All I know about the atrocities
that Diego has committed.
We appreciate it.
Our lives are on the line, as well.
"That Diego has committed"?
You talk like it doesn't concern you.
The wine you're drinking and
the room you stand in
were earned by following that bastard.
You mean "that we've committed,"
you son of a bitch.
But I get it... We're here on business.
So, Marcos-san...
Continue going about your business as normal.
In two weeks, you and your family
will be relaxing on the beach.
I can't accept it!
We're supposed to stand around,
watching as people are killed?
Are you sleepy?
Want me to put you to sleep, eh?
Calm yourself.
If they're gonna check five
million citizens in ten days,
simple arithmetic says that's
five hundred thousand per day!
Of which one percent will survive!
And your point is?
That means four hundred, ninety-five
thousand have already been killed!
How can you be so calm?
Because if we lose our cool, billions could die!
If the plan fails, everyone dies.
If we can't draw the three Royal
Guards away from the King,
not even the Chairman will
be able to defeat the King.
Thus, we cannot let them discover
our existence before the time is right.
If that happens, security around the
King will be even further tightened.
You must endure this.
You're telling me to sacrifice five
million to save the human race?
That's right.
If blaming me consoles you, go ahead.
But if you don't have a better idea,
don't be too self-righteous.
Damn it...
We must do only what we can.
But we must put our lives on the line to do so.
Yeah...
Is Killua okay?
He was acting a little weird.
Maybe I should have stuck with him?
But if I'd followed him, he'd be mad.
You did well to avoid that.
How about this?
I use my strong tail as a spring,
to propel me among the trees!
In the darkness, following my
movement is impossible!
Caught you!
Now I'm going to crush you!
You're not crushing me!
Huh?
I'm the one who caught you!
He seems to have a snake's genes,
so he should be able to go ten
days without starving to death.
As I thought... He's strong...
But I should continue to observe.
I already let them find me...
I need to hide better.
But it's strange...
Why are there soldiers around if the
selection is already finished here?
Maybe there are extra guards
because we're near the border.
An owl and a bat?
This time, he's facing two...
What will he do?
The Chimera Ants are using
darkness to attack Gon.
And why is Meleoron following him?
Next time: Combination x And x Evolution.
Come on down, everyone...
I have a perfectly ordinary box,
which has not been touched.
One, two, three!
That would be an illusion.