Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Train and earn money?
The Heavens Arena.
Heavens Arena...
Yeah, I'll explain later.
We should get moving.
Okay!
Whoa.
Look, it's huge!
Yep.
That's Heavens Arena.
Two hundred and fifty-one stories.
Nine hundred, ninety-one meters tall.
The world's fourth tallest building.
So this is where we'll be training...
I used up all my money on the trip fare.
We'll have to make more here.
After we disembark, we'll start from zero.
Okay, got it.
Good... Let's go.
Yeah!
Arrival x At The x Arena
Gon and Killua
head to Heavens Arena,
seeking to get stronger.
Gon.
There's a really long line.
Everyone's going to Heavens Arena?
There aren't any conditions here,
like there were for the Hunter Exam.
You just have to defeat your opponent.
Oh...
The higher you go, the more
prize money you earn.
This is as good as it gets for those looking
to make a living with their fists.
Welcome to Heavens Arena.
Please fill out this form.
Killua Zoldyck-sama, you are #2054.
Gon Freecss-sama, you are #2055.
They'll call your number
on the first floor of the arena,
so make sure you remember it.
Then please go ahead.
Go!
Take him out!
It's been a while,
but the place hasn't changed.
Huh? You've been here before?
Yeah, when I was six.
My dad left me here without a penny.
He said I should reach floor 200
before coming home.
It took two years.
Two years...
Sure, he was only six, but it
really took Killua that long?
If you want to fight people of Hisoka's level,
you'll need to go higher.
Let's hurry.
Okay.
#1973.
#2055.
Please enter ring E.
#2055! That's me!
I'm getting nervous now.
Gon, you got through the
Testing Gate, right?
Huh?
In that case...
Look at that! It's a little boy!
Hey, kid!
This is your last chance to run!
This ain't a game!
One punch, and he'll fly out of the ring!
On the first floor, we appraise
each participant's level.
You are allowed three minutes
to demonstrate your prowess.
Then... Begin!
Sorry...
I'll end your suffering with one punch.
You got through the Testing Gate, right?
In that case, all you have
to do is push hard.
Just push
hard!
No way!
Yes!
That kid's incredible!
He's got some crazy power!
When did I become so strong?
#2055, proceed to floor 50.
All right!
Hey, here's another kid who's a beast!
Oh?
You've already been to the 200th floor?
And this was a strong performance.
Very well. You may go to the 180th floor...
Oh, I'll start from the 50th floor.
Huh?
I want to take it easy.
That's enough!
Yet another strong kid there!
You are permitted to
advance to the 50th floor.
Osu!
The first 200 floors of Heavens Arena
are divided into classes,
each comprised of ten floors.
So after someone defeats an
opponent in the 50s,
they advance to the 60s.
If they lose, then they'd
drop back to the 40s.
Oh, so that's how it works.
Plus...
I've heard that
after you pass the 100th floor,
you get your own room!
Oh, I forgot to introduce myself.
Osu! My name is Zushi!
What about you guys?
I'm Killua.
I'm Gon.
Nice to meet you.
We've arrived at the 50th floor.
I saw your fight earlier.
That was really amazing, yo!
What are you talking about?
You made it up here with one match, too.
That's right.
No...
I still have a long way to go.
By the way, which martial arts
discipline do you practice?
I study the Shingen-ryu fighting technique.
School? We don't have one, right?
No...
What?
You're that strong with no training?
I'm kind of shocked...
I still have so far to go!
Zushi.
You did well.
Master!
You adhered to my teachings.
Osu! I am honored!
Master, your shirt is untucked again.
Oh, sorry about that...
Who are they?
Oh, these are Killua-san and Gon-san.
Nice to meet you. I'm Wing.
Yo!
I didn't expect to meet other children.
Why are you here?
Uh...
Well, we want to become stronger.
But we're also broke,
so we're making money simultaneously.
Killua's a veteran here.
Oh?
If you're up here, you must be fairly skilled,
but you should pay strict attention
to your opponent's body,
as well as your own.
Osu
Killua-sama, Gon-sama, and Zushi-sama?
Please hand me your tickets.
Here is your prize money.
One hundred, fifty-two jenny...
On the 1st floor, win or lose,
your reward covers a canned drink.
But beyond that,
a loss gets you nothing.
A win over an opponent in the 50s
nets you fifty thousand.
Fifty thousand...
That's a lot.
In the 100s, I think wins are worth a million.
What?
Once you're past the 150th floor,
you get ten million a pop.
Ten million?
Didn't you make it to floor 200
when you were here before?
Th-The 200th floor?
How much do you get for
winning on the 200th floor?
Well... I don't really know,
because I quit once I reached 200.
But when I was winning in the 190s,
I had around two hundred million, total.
T-Two hundred million...
Where's that money now?
That was four years ago.
Of course it's gone now.
Spent it all on snacks!
Two hundred million on snacks, in four years?
What kind of snacks are these?
Hey, let's head to the waiting room.
We didn't take any damage in the last fight,
so they'll probably assign us
another match today.
Well, these opponents should be a cinch.
Just take it easy.
Really?
Killua-san!
You're too loud...
#2054, Killua-sama.
I'm already up.
And #1963, Zushi-sama.
What?
Please head to arena A, on the 57th floor.
Oh.
Osu! I shall give it my best.
Sure. Well, you can't win them all.
Better luck next time.
I'll head out.
Yeah. Good luck, guys.
I'll wait for you above.
Uh-huh...
He really didn't have to be so blunt...
Okay, everyone!
The event you've all been waiting for!
We have a unique match-up for you!
Two young boys, fighting it out!
However, you don't want to
underestimate them!
Both had strong showings
in their first rounds!
They both advanced directly to the 50s!
We will now replay
their matches on the big screen!
Killua defeated his opponent in a flash!
One chop was all it took to knock him out!
Meanwhile, Zushi used martial arts
to punish his opponent,
scoring a flawless knockout
of a 200+ kilogram giant!
Okay, everyone!
Are you ready to press
your gamble switches?
In that case, switch on!
All bets are in, and the odds favor Zushi!
Perhaps his martial arts
knowledge gives him an edge?
This is bad...
Killua-san is mad...
This match will consist of three,
three-minutes each,
decided by the points and knockout system!
Begin!
I see.
His stance leaves few openings.
He's trained long and hard
to master that stance.
But he has no chance against me.
Wow... Killua is
boldly walking toward his opponent!
Sorry.
But I'm sticking to one chop per
match until I reach the 150s.
Clean hit!
Amazing!
Killua has knocked out another
opponent with only a single chop!
A clean hit and being knocked
down get him 2 point.
As you already know, under the
points and knockout system,
There are clean hits, critical hits,
and knockdowns.
Superb attacks count as "clean hits,"
worth one point apiece.
Unusually superb attacks
are classified as "critical hits,"
worth two points.
Knocking down your opponent
earns you one point.
After amassing ten points, you are
awarded a technical knockout.
Of course, if your opponent cannot
continue to fight after one hit,
you win due to a knockout!
That chop ended the fight, stupid.
Can you fight?
Yes, I'm okay!
He got up!
Zushi will continue!
Fight!
Did I hold back too much?
He's taken another hit!
Zushi has been knocked down!
But he's already standing up!
If you stand before the referee reaches you,
your opponent isn't awarded the point.
Tsk. Not bad.
So the same attack won't
work twice against you.
But something's wrong.
That attack was strong enough that a graze
should have rendered him unconscious.
Unbelievable...
He has dominating power and speed!
At this rate, I won't stand a chance!
I have to...
try it!
Oh! What's happening?
Killua has backed away!
Zushi!
So, an incredibly loud shout from a spectator
interrupted the fight,
but let's get started again!
Oh, Killua!
Over here!
See? I got sixty thousand.
How about you?
It took you a while to get here.
Yeah, I ran into a little trouble.
Then Zushi was pretty strong.
No, not at all.
He has potential.
One day, he'll be strong.
But right now,
he's just target practice for me.
His punches were weak...
I was completely able to knock him around.
But I couldn't defeat him.
Huh?
I received the TKO from points,
but I couldn't knock him out.
Further...
When he changed his stance,
his aura reminded me of my brother's.
I don't know what it was,
but it felt dangerous.
It must be some kind of technique.
His master
called it "Ren."
Forgive me, Master!
I thought I made myself clear, Zushi.
You were not supposed to use Ren yet.
Forgive me!
My opponent was so strong,
I couldn't help myself...
Sure. Wanting to win is good.
But your true goal lies beyond this.
At this tower's top floor.
Focus too much on simply winning a fight,
and you reduce your own potential.
Yo!
You must be prepared to lose a
thousand times while you're here.
Yo!
So he isn't supposed
to use Ren until he reaches the top floor?
The strongest fighters are at the top, right?
Gon, change in plans.
Huh?
I'm aiming to reach the top floor!
Uh-huh!
Actually, that was my goal all along.
Killua defeats another opponent
with one chop!
A knockout!
Oh! In the other arena,
Gon has knocked out another opponent
with a single push!
Each of them has won six
consecutive matches
over the past three days,
to reach the 100s without a scratch!
Killua's chop.
And Gon's push.
How far will they be able to go?
And who is going to be able to stop them?
Yay! A private room!
We won't have to worry about
money and lodging anymore.
I wouldn't be too sure about that.
If you drop
below the 100s, you have to
check out of this room.
A world of difference separates making it
to the 100s and staying in the 100s.
The 100th floor is like a ceiling.
A ceiling?
Once you pass it, you get special treatment.
So everyone focuses on holding their spot.
Some people will do anything it takes
to stay in the 100s.
You can waste a lot of time on them.
Be careful, Gon.
Yeah.
Gon wins another match
with a single push!
Guess I didn't need to worry about him.
Your prize money has been deposited
into the specified account.
You were right...
I've never seen so many zeros before...
And just a week ago, I was totally broke.
I'm a little annoyed.
Huh?
My first time here,
it took me two months to reach floor 150.
Meanwhile, you're breezing through.
But you were only six back then.
Well, that's true...
Oh, that's right.
I saw Zushi on TV earlier.
So did I.
He's still in the 50s.
I wonder what that Ren you sensed
could have been.
Maybe if we fight opponents higher up...
Or wouldn't it be faster to just ask Zushi?
Ren is one of the four major principles.
The four major principles for
disciplining your mind and body.
Fundamental to every martial art!
You must know "Ten," learn "Zetsu,"
achieve "Ren," and reach "Hatsu"!
This is all part of "Nen" training!
That covers everything!
I've no idea what you just said!
Zushi...
Are you sufficiently educated
that you can teach others?
Gon-kun, Killua-kun.
There's an old saying
that if you learn something piecemeal,
you'll end up knowing less
than when you started.
So a little knowledge is a dangerous thing?
But I want to know right now.
Because it's related to the secret
behind my brother's power.
Then, your brother is able to use Nen?
I need to know what Nen
and Ren even mean!
I'll agree to the full learning process
rather than a quick explanation!
And if you're willing to teach me,
I won't try to figure it out myself.
I understand.
Come with me to my residence.
What is Nen? What is Ren?
Killua believes they are related
to his brother's abilities.
Gon wishes to learn what these mean, as well.
Brush your teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Coming up, it's Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
It's Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
Today, we introduce Zushi!
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Learning Shingen-ryu kung fu
from Wing.
He practices Shingen-ryu kung fu.
He's considered a one in a hundred thousand talent!
Very polite and earnest.
But we're considered one in a hundred million talents!
Likes to say "Osu."
Osu!
Next time: Nen x And x Ren!
That was a rough episode...
Good work!
Osu!