Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Staff of Judgment
If player names a target,
while raising staff toward the sky,
disaster will befall either player or target,
depending on which has done more evil.
Elder's Growth Pills
Each pill taken helps player grow 1 centimeter.
Each bottle contains 100 pills.
Not recommended for those under 20.
Fledgling CEO
If you warm this fledgling egg
in your hands 3 hours a day,
it will hatch in 1 to 10 years.
The feelings you put into warming
it will speed the process.
Yes! Halfway there!
That makes fifty types!
15 x 15
Genthru and his men have a plan in mind,
as they prepare to trade
with Team Tsezgerra.
Let's get this over with, then.
Okay, trade complete.
No, hold on.
I cannot accept this.
This is an unfair trade.
What? Don't complain once it's done!
We gave you three cards!
What more do you want?
Wait a second...
That isn't what I meant.
I'm saying that it's unfair to you.
It's too skewed in our favor.
I dislike the idea of
benefiting from charity.
And it will continue to bother me,
even if we clear the game first.
So I have a proposition.
Right or left.
I'll give you one of these cards.
One is worthless,
but the other is Breath of Archangel.
Good Luck
Okay!
Levy on!
Crap!
Return on.
To Masadora!
Let's go after them!
Wait!
First, check your cards!
I lost one of the #80 cards
we were monopolizing.
As well as a #65.
Hey, what did you lose?
I lost #42 and #53.
I lost #29 and #24.
They got me good!
I lost two of the #85
cards we were hoarding.
All the ones they took were
restricted slot cards...
And they took both card types
that we were monopolizing.
Damn!
They must have used Risky Dice.
We're not with them!
They used items to change our faces!
Anyway, we have to pursue them!
No!
Hey, is Genthru the Bomber?
U-Uh, we don't know.
But he went like this with his hand and
blew the head off the guy I was with.
A power clearly meant for murder.
So he's a fighter.
It would be unwise to
fight them head-on.
But they took at least five
different card types from us!
They could have completed
their collection!
List on!
#2!
Currently, 0 players own #2, Patch of Shore.
Currently, 0 cards in play.
We're still okay.
They haven't found #2,
Patch of Shore, yet.
Our immediate priority
is to find #2 before they do!
We still have our voucher
for Breath of Archangel,
so we can still beat them.
Right, let's find it first, then.
Accompany
Warp all players within 20 meters
of caster to city (must have been visited)
or player of your choice (must have
been met inside the game).
[SR][NORM]
Accompany on!
To Soufrabi!
We did it... A big success.
The Risky Dice and Levy
combination paid off.
That puts us at ninety-three types.
No, we used one up to
change those faces,
so it's ninety-two.
The important thing is that we took
the cards they were monopolizing.
And for two of the others, we're just
waiting for someone to use Gain on them.
The biggest obstacle is #2.
But we know that it's in Soufrabi.
All right, we'll go after #72,
#21, and #9 in that order.
Then we'll make for
Soufrabi, to find #2.
For #75, we simply need to find
someone with it, then take it.
I think it's time we began thinking...
About the three restricted
slot cards we want to keep,
and how we want to spend the 50 billion.
Hey, Killua...
Something's been bugging me.
Huh?
Aren't there hundreds of players?
Isn't it weird that we've been able
to turn all our items into cards?
What do you mean?
Even B-rank restricted slot types
have a thirty-card limit.
The players here before us should
have already collected them.
That's true.
But you can also see it this way.
Fewer than thirty teams in this game
are capable of making real progress.
Oh, I see.
Most players aren't worried
about getting restricted slot cards.
They're just struggling to find
a way out of the game.
It would suck if you got to Masadora,
and there weren't any Leave cards.
Yeah, that's why...
I get it...
Huh?
If you guys got to Masadora,
but there weren't any Leave cards,
what would you do?
Well...
I'd save money until a Leave showed up.
Yeah.
Okay, then what if
you acquired a super rare
spell card while waiting?
Sell it and buy more spell
cards until a Leave came in.
Really?!
I would save it...
Wouldn't it suck if all the cards you
bought ended up being worthless?
If you saved it, you might be
able to trade for a Leave—
See?
Need a Leave?
Want to go back to the real world?
We've gotten four restricted
slot cards for three Leaves.
Okay, that makes a total
of fifty-four types.
Score!
So the cards that wouldn't fit in
our binders reverted to items.
We're running out of free pockets.
Then we should organize them now.
We three have a total
of 135 free pockets.
We should each leave
around 5 pockets free.
You keep the spell cards, Killua.
Bisky should also have
a few defensive ones.
Wait! I have to use spell cards?
No way! I don't know how they work.
The hell? Then learn how they work!
Okay...
Book.
We've been deliberately
avoiding other players,
but we'll have to take risks
to obtain the rarer cards.
Yeah.
Well, let's get what we can ourselves,
then negotiate aggressively
with any players we come across.
Sound good?
Yeah.
Yep!
See ya.
Hold on.
This is worthless.
It's a transformed Fake.
Sorry about that.
I gave you the wrong one.
Here's the real one.
Man, you can't lower your guard
around any of these guys.
No kidding...
Still, that necklace is quite useful.
Hey, this necklace can
remove curses, right?
Only from spell cards.
Oh, so it won't work.
Did you have an idea?
I was wondering if a curse
was behind the disease
that all those villagers
were suffering from.
Villagers?
Oh, those people...
The ones who took all your money.
But it won't work since
they aren't cards.
No.
It's worth a shot.
Will you trust us with your lives?
You freely gave us everything you had.
We will trust you!
Sick Villagers
Villagers struck by a
contagion passing
around the island.
Healthy Villagers
Healthy villagers who
recovered from the contagion
going around the island.
It worked!
Thank you very much!
This treasure has been
passed down for generations.
Please accept this
token of our gratitude.
Awesome!
Lucky Alexandrite
Owner will enjoy
once-in-a-lifetime experiences,
for better or for worse.
Lucky Alexandrite! Score!
Another player has used
Contact to reach you.
Yo, this is Kazsule.
I'd like to talk to you.
Could we meet in person?
About what?
Some people are close
to clearing the game.
Huh?
It's a team of three,
led by someone named Genthru.
Genthru!
Thanks for coming, everyone.
Much appreciated.
Team Kazsule
As I mentioned via Contact,
Team Asta
Team Genthru is close
to completing the game.
Team Hanse
I just checked the ranking,
Goreinu
and they're currently
at ninety-six types.
Team Yabibi
We must figure out a way to stop them.
Can I ask something?
What is it?
How do you check the ranking?
Well...
You don't know how to do that?
If we answer all their questions,
we'll be here till dawn!
Just cut to the chase.
Now, don't be so mean...
We're all here to exchange information.
They could have information
you don't, Asta.
That's impossible.
Those kids are amateurs who don't even
know how to use the Trade Shop.
In the Trade Shop,
there's a ranking that lists
players and their total
restricted slot cards.
If you pay a fee, you can even learn
the numbers of their cards.
But getting a player's name from
the ranking still won't let you
use Contact or Fluoroscopy on them.
Not until you actually meet them.
Don't you feel smarter now, boys?
In other words, if we know
the members of a team,
we can determine how
many cards they have.
And Team Genthru is only missing #0,
#2, #9, and #75.
#75...
There's a solid theory that #0 appears
in an event after the other
ninety-nine are collected,
so they only need three.
We propose to find one of those
three types before they do
and monopolize it, to prevent
them from clearing the game.
There's gotta be something else.
We could deluge them with spell cards.
They already have a Paladin's Necklace.
So Levy is the only
spell that will work.
Levy
Take 1 card at random from every
player within 20 meters of caster.
[SR][SP]
And they can block Levy if
certain conditions are met.
It's safe to assume
that Genthru is willing to reveal
that they have ninety-six types
Prison
All slotted cards on target page are
immune to theft or destruction via spell card
until removed.
(Only targets
pages 1 - 11.
Free slot pages
cannot be targeted.)
[DEF][CONT]
because their pages are
protected by Prison.
That's possible...
Genthru was collecting
a bunch of spell cards
with the others who tried to recruit us.
It's a reasonable assumption.
We could always take
their cards by force.
Would you be willing to lead the attack?
We don't know what kind
of abilities they have.
Finding a card type to monopolize
is the most practical option.
I assume no one has objections.
Then let's get to business.
We'll need everyone here to cooperate.
I'm fine with the proposed plan.
But I have a problem with these members.
Hold on, Asta.
I followed your condition...
Have over fifty types of cards.
These six teams met that condition.
I also said that they had to be
people who could contribute.
I don't see how these kids
can contribute anything.
You're the one being uncooperative.
You've got a smart mouth.
Then show me some proof
that you can be useful.
We know Team Genthru's abilities.
We have one of the three
cards they're missing.
Still dissatisfied?
No, that's good enough.
So tell us what their abilities are.
What about you?
Show us some proof you
can be useful to us.
We have seventy-one types
of restricted slot cards...
Significantly more than you.
I'll give you an A-rank card in
return for the information.
You shouldn't have a problem with that.
I have a problem.
We can obtain A-rank cards ourselves.
So give us two S-rank cards or
equally valuable information.
Otherwise, we won't tell you a thing.
Don't get too cocky, brat!
Did you hear that, everyone?
These kids won't be any help.
They want two S-rank
cards from each team.
That's ten cards they'd take.
Don't be a fool.
I'm only taking cards from your team.
Huh?
I'm fine with giving information
to the other four.
I'll let them decide
what to offer in return.
But I won't tell you anything
until you meet my condition.
You are a stupid brat...
Throwing a tantrum because
I didn't baby you, huh?
Stop this, both of you...
We don't have time to
fight amongst ourselves!
I haven't agreed to
team up with them yet!
It's fine, Asta...
Give them two cards.
We need to move on.
What?!
I have no problem with
giving them cards!
But that kid's trying to pick a fight!
You're the one picking a fight!
Hey, let's leave.
I don't want to team
up with these people!
Come, now...
Though I admit I'm a bit peeved.
But given the circumstances...
Genthru has these two abilities,
Countdown and Little Flower.
So it's best to keep
your distance from him.
Seriously? He got me...
Same here.
He touched me when we
were making a deal.
Me, too...
Sounds like a bunch of
them might be victims.
A chance!
Isn't there any way to
disable his technique?
Yep, there is...
You have to touch Genthru and say,
"I caught the Bomber."
Stupid! Why did you tell them?
We could've gotten more
cards out of them!
That would have started another fight.
The bombs can't be armed until Genthru
explains how his ability works,
so if you keep away from him,
you should be safe.
Did you know there are
two ways to cast spells?
Yep, I did.
A spell card is used up the
moment you say its name aloud.
But it's possible to
keep reusing a spell.
Huh?
For example, you know how a list
of players you've met appears if
you put Steal in your binder?
If you remove the card without
pressing the select button,
the spell card isn't used up,
so you can keep reusing it.
I never tried that.
Yeah.
You can buy all B-rank
restricted slot cards at stores.
You simply need to buy from the
same Trade Shop over fifty times.
If you become a frequent customer,
they'll start making you offers.
Do you have two Skeleton Glasses cards?
Or Emerald for Beauty and Mystery Pond?
Is that enough information
to satisfy you?
I'll give you another
card if you're not happy.
Nope, that's enough, thanks!
I'm up next, then.
I'm Goreinu.
Nice to meet you.
Thanks, everyone!
That was very educational.
The question now is which card
we should try to monopolize.
It's probably impossible to
monopolize the #75 we have.
Each team can only obtain one,
and the limit is twenty,
which is too high.
You obtained #75?
That's impressive.
List on!
#75.
Currently, 6 players own #75, Lucky Alexandrite.
Currently, 6 cards are in play.
So five other teams each have one.
Monopolizing this one
will be impossible.
What about the other two?
List on!
#9!
List on.
#2.
No good.
There are three teams with #9.
No one has #2, Patch of Shore...
We can make it work!
Guide Post On.
#2.
I know where to find it...
Soufrabi.
I've been there before!
I have an Accompany card here.
Okay, let's go.
Accompany on!
To Soufrabi!
This is Soufrabi?
It's a pretty big city...
Soufrabi
Let's head in and snoop around.
Search every room, one by one.
Some characters may not
give you information
until you visit multiple
times, so pay attention.
Okay!
Hey!
I found someone with information.
Fast!
The pirates rule this city...
There's a legend about
an underwater cavern
called the Sea God's Grotto
located somewhere in this area.
Patch of Shore is the entrance to it.
A few years ago, having heard of the
legendary cavern and its treasure,
fifteen pirates arrived in this city.
Razor and the fourteen devils...
The city fishermen were
all tortured and killed.
The pirates murdered anyone who
knew about Patch of Shore.
If you get rid of the pirates,
I'll tell you what I know.
When we visited a few months earlier,
we couldn't find a single clue.
This must be information only
available at certain times.
Maybe an event that only
occurs at this time frame?
Razor and the fourteen devils...
It's possible that the event
was triggered by the
number of players here.
Huh?
There are fifteen pirates.
And it just so happens that
there are fifteen of us.
So the event won't start until you
have a party of fifteen or more?
But how would a game
character know that?
Oh, Accompany!
Yes, a group of fifteen or more must
reach Soufrabi with Accompany.
That's probably the
trigger for this event.
Brutal...
Huh?
Oh, nothing.
Let's go to the pirate's base!
Gon and his friends stand before
some unpleasant looking pirates.
Will the fifteen allies be able
to obtain Patch of Shore?
G.I. Tutorial
Coming up, it's the
Greed Island Tutorial!
Today, we introduce the card
Tax Collector's Gauntlet.
Tax Collector's Gauntlet
When equipped, player has
the ability to cast Levy. But
each cast will destroy a random
card from player's restricted
slots. (Cannot use Levy if
restricted slots are empty.)
If you turn this card into
an item and equip it,
you can steal random cards from others.
And you can keep reusing it!
Clunk.
Continue!
Next time: Pirates x And x Guesses.
Go!
I can't say that!