Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Ah, this is the foundation I wanted!
I also want this lipstick and manicure spray.
Oh, what a cute wig...
Boss, we should get going soon.
Just a little longer.
I should buy this camisole too.
Her shopping's gonna be the death of me.
I concur.
A x Brutal x Battlefield
Was there anything else we needed?
Did you want anything, Eliza?
No, nothing at all.
I have to go to the restroom.
It's okay...
Watch my stuff for me.
Will Kurapika be okay?
I used my flute to help him recover a little.
How do you feel about the
whole assassins business?
The Ten Dons are hiring professionals
to handle the Troupe.
Professionals?
So, Kurapika...
I want you to join those hit men.
Judging by his heartbeat,
he wasn't entirely pleased
about joining the hit men.
Of course not.
However, Kurapika is extremely determined.
To achieve his goal, he's certainly
willing to sacrifice everything.
That's a hard road...
I couldn't do it.
What's the point of a life in which
you're basically killing yourself?
She's taking a long time.
Once we finish this job,
I'm using the money to see
the world on my bike.
That sounds really nice.
Not enjoying yourself is a crime.
There are many ways to spend a life.
Everyone has different ideas
about what's important.
Huh?
What's wrong?
She's gone!
Huh?
What?!
Daddy's such a liar!
He wasn't going to take me to the auction!
Fine, I'll just go by myself!
Come in.
Forever Active
One, two, three, four, five, six...
Looks like everyone's here.
No, not yet.
I thought the team only had eight members.
Nostrade is sending an additional person.
Tsk, the guy who uses that
voodoo fortunetelling?
Then, has everyone arrived?
The job is to annihilate the Phantom Troupe.
When the auction kicks off again,
they may show up.
If they do, dispose of them.
You're free to use any means you want.
This team will be after the same target.
We should decide how we address
each other when communicating.
Just use colors.
Call me Blue.
I'll be Red.
It's like playing a game.
Eh? What about you guys?
Silva.
I'm Zeno.
Zeno? What color is that?
We will both use our real names.
What?
You're welcome to call me by name,
but I won't take orders.
We'll do this our own way.
Silva and Zeno...
Of the Zoldyck family?
Let me know if you want someone killed.
I'm willing to give you a thirty percent
discount for being in the same line of work.
They're from Killua's family.
Does it really matter
what we call one another?
Agreed.
There's no requirement we work together.
But we're talking about the Troupe.
Attacking alone will be dangerous.
And you?
Shaky teamwork will only cause confusion.
I will move alone.
So it's 5 to 4.
We have our answer.
The auction begins at nine.
We will transport you to the auction hall.
Please wait here until it's time.
Yo, Nostrade...
How are you feeling?
Not too bad.
Not too bad?
You've gotten pretty full of yourself.
Not too long ago, you were just
leading a little country gang,
and now you're acting like my equal.
I hear you've been rubbing your hands
together so much, your skin rubbed off.
You okay?
It's sad when a man shows jealousy.
Bastard!
What's this about?
Go ahead and stick that knife in me!
Kurapika, that's enough!
Let's be clear...
No one's impressed by you!
Many people envy my success,
while they ignore their own failings.
However, I intend to continue to rise.
By using Neon's fortunetelling.
I expect great things from you.
You will be appropriately rewarded
when the time comes.
Yes.
The police are cooperating?
Sixty percent of the votes
in the Yorknew City mayoral
election were bought.
And the police chief is the mayor's protégé.
Redirecting traffic is quite easy for us.
Hello?
Kurapika, it's terrible.
The boss ran away!
She changed clothes in the restroom,
so she must have planned ahead.
Then I can guess where she's going.
Return to the hotel and stand by.
What's wrong?
Your daughter's run away.
What?!
We probably have the same destination.
The auction?
Damn, she's turned off her phone.
But Neon doesn't have a pass...
She'll be turned away at the gate.
This is Light Nostrade!
I need you to convey an order
to all the guards at the gate!
If a girl about seventeen or
eighteen arrives with no pass,
they should take her into custody!
Her description...
Okay, please go ahead.
Whew,
I was stuck without a way
to get past that gate.
Thank you so much.
You're very welcome.
Really?! When was that?
About five minutes ago...
Her hair and attire were slightly
different, but it was probably her.
She didn't have a pass?
She didn't appear to realize that
the auction required a pass.
She mentioned something about
her daddy, but then she left.
Yes, she got in a taxi alone.
Yes, goodbye.
Nice work.
Neon, where have you gone?
I'll search for her.
Do you have a map of the city?
I've heard that you're a good fortuneteller.
Huh?
Someone once mentioned it to me.
I can't remember who...
I'm good.
Important people request
my services all the time.
What's your accuracy?
They say I'm always right.
They say?
Aren't you the one telling the fortunes?
My hand moves on its own.
Oh, how impressive.
Would you tell me mine?
Sure.
Write your full name, date of birth,
and blood type on a sheet of paper.
Will this work?
Let me see.
Chrollo Lucilfer...
That's a strange name.
My friends call me "boss."
What?
That's even stranger!
Then, I'll tell your fortune.
Your daughter is already in the
Cemetery Building on the auction site.
What? But how?!
Regardless, we should hurry.
Okay, all done.
May I have a look?
Sure.
My fortunes are a little strange.
They usually have four or five verses.
Each one corresponds to
a week of the month,
so the first may have already happened.
Oh...
The calendar loses a precious component.
The remaining months gather to mourn.
The mourners play a melody,
while the eleventh moon quietly rises.
Amazing.
It's correct.
About this first verse...
Huh?
Oh, stop...
I never look at the fortunes I write.
Why not?
I have a feeling they're more accurate
if I stay away from them.
Then may I ask you a question?
Uh-huh.
This verse refers to a requiem for the dead.
Do you believe in the afterlife?
Hmm...
Not really.
My fortunes are for people who are alive.
Like you, Chrollo-san.
I'm guessing that the requiem
is meant to help you, not the dead.
You're probably right.
Let's go.
They'll let us start browsing
at the auction soon.
Actually, I heard that from someone else.
Eh?
When I was little, I saw a
fortuneteller on TV say that.
That fortunes were meant to
make the living happy.
Really?
So the fortuneteller tried to
avoid giving negative fortunes.
Negative fortunes?
The idea was
to encourage people to wish for and
work toward better things.
At the time, I was really moved...
From then on, I wanted to be a fortuneteller.
The calendar loses a precious component.
The remaining months gather to mourn.
The mourners play a melody,
while the eleventh moon quietly rises.
The chrysanthemum withers and falls,
to lie on the ground beside bloody Scarlet Eyes.
But you will remain supreme.
Even after losing half your limbs.
Enjoy the interlude.
Search out new allies.
East is the direction to go.
You will find one who awaits you.
A few years later, that fortuneteller
was arrested for being a con artist.
Are you talking about the Galactic Grandma?
Yep!
I remember that she didn't
believe in the afterlife.
Right, so that's why I don't, either.
Personally, I believe in ghosts.
Huh?
And that's why I'll do as he
would have wanted.
What do you mean?
Go wild.
Are you okay?
Call a doctor!
We're on the first floor,
by the north elevator.
Someone's ill. Call an ambulance.
We can't.
They won't let an ambulance
inside without a pass.
What did you say?
What if the unthinkable happens?!
This is the daughter of the
Nostrade Family boss!
Will you take responsibility for her life?!
Tsk, got it.
She has fans among the Ten Dons.
Fine, we'll make it happen.
Hey, call for an ambulance!
Got it.
Are you able to rewind this monitor?
Huh? Yeah.
That chop was incredibly fast...
Only I could have caught it.
It's been a while since I was this excited.
There is my prey.
Nostrade-sama, your daughter is
resting in room 501, on the fifth floor.
She shouldn't have been able to secure a pass...
How did she get in?
Your daughter's picture is on the Hunter website.
What?
Most likely, someone found
this picture on the site,
approached her, and then brought her here.
I'll find that person and kill him!
Please remain calm.
I don't believe capturing your
daughter was their objective.
She may have been a hostage in case they
had trouble infiltrating the building.
It's dangerous here.
I called Melody and Basho.
They should arrive soon.
Can I trust them?
You should go with them.
But the auction...
There won't be one.
This place will become a battlefield.
The auction will be postponed again.
A trail of blood.
He wants to be found...
By leaving a scent that only another killer
would catch.
You are just like me.
We are the same.
Addicted to murder.
Relax.
I won't use any cheap tricks.
Let's play one-on-one.
Yeah.
I have a message from the boss.
He wants to go wild in the Cemetery
Building, so we should come.
We aren't too far away.
What about everyone else?
The rest had the same idea.
They've been cleaning up the trash,
while approaching the building.
Okay, then let's go.
Also, the boss actually added a rule this time.
A rule? What?
Go absolutely crazy.
The calendar loses a precious component.
The remaining months gather to mourn.
The mourners play a melody,
while the eleventh moon quietly rises.
The chrysanthemum withers and falls,
to lie on the ground beside bloody Scarlet Eyes.
But you will remain supreme.
Even after losing half your limbs.
Enjoy the interlude.
Search out new allies.
East is the direction to go.
You will find one who awaits you.
Why?
Why am I still alive?
This is known as an Indoor Fish.
Made from Nen, it can only
exist in enclosed spaces.
It's a carnivore that enjoys human flesh.
Its victims don't bleed or feel pain.
And they won't die until the
Indoor Fish disappears.
Won't die...
The calendar loses a precious component.
The remaining months gather to mourn.
The mourners play a melody,
while the eleventh moon quietly rises.
Uvo-san,
can you hear us?
We are playing a requiem for you.
It was the start of a stormy night,
fierce and drenched with blood,
yet somehow overwhelmingly sad.
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Coming up, we have Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
It's Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Today, we introduce Phinks.
A Phantom Troupe member.
A member of the Phantom Troupe.
He's an Enhancer.
An Enhancer.
He's strong enough to punch through a body.
The greater the windup,
the stronger his punch.
Sometimes, he dresses like an Egyptian mummy.
It's his name.
Next time: Assault x And x Impact.
Oh, Gon...
Wherefore art thou Gon?!
Killua, that's because
I'm Gon!
That's it?