Edited at https://subtitletools.com
As Gon was dedicating all of his
power to finishing off Neferpitou,
Meruem, Pouf, and Youpi were
inside the west tower, where Komugi had been.
Once we're through here...
The west tower's second floor.
Once we've passed this area,
the King will never remember her!
As long as I don't give him
an opportunity to see her...
Flash x And x Start
Something is missing...
But what is it?
I don't know.
I know...
I won't say anything.
I agree that we shouldn't let the King see her.
Ideally, he should stay as he is now.
I have
a feeling that something is
missing from this place.
Though it may just be a side
effect of my memory loss.
Exactly...
Your memory can be verified
through what you see.
Which means you can recover all
of the memories you need.
I believe the selection was to begin at 12:00.
Yes.
However, that can be moved up.
By 9:00,
the remaining humans will be gathered
in the plain before the palace.
What is it?
I have not used my scales
on the humans still on their way in.
We don't want them to cause a commotion,
so I will summon my clones to hypnotize them.
What will you do, Youpi?
Right...
I'll look for Pitou.
Right now, I don't have the
strength to protect you.
Pitou...
Did you just remember something?
Oh, yeah... We haven't told
the King about Pitou yet.
Meruem-sama, do you remember who Pitou is?
Yes,
one of my three Royal Guards.
I can recall Pitou's appearance so clearly,
it seems a mystery that I
didn't remember it until now.
So words can also trigger his memory,
not just images...
We cannot let him hear her name.
We must be very careful...
The key will be convincing Pitou.
I know...
Tell Pitou to keep quiet, right?
There it is again...
I'm counting on you.
Yes...
I...
asked Pitou
to do something for me.
Youpi.
Yes...
Bring Pitou to me at once.
Yes.
What will you do, Meruem-sama?
Enemies are still around.
Indeed...
As I search for Pitou myself,
I shall hunt down the remaining intruders.
This is bad!
Your Majesty, that would be...
It is merely for entertainment.
And I am sure these enemies
have useful information.
However, we won't be at your side,
and we don't know what enemies remain—
I want an honest answer,
Pouf.
Do you believe there is a chance
that these intruders could get the better of me?!
No...
Absolutely not.
Th-This exceeds my expectations...
The King...
Meruem-sama...
is the ultimate being.
That much is certain!
The overwhelming aura
left Knuckle and the rest, still concealed,
in total despair.
Th-This isn't something we can deal with...
To handle this, you'd need an entire
nation's military might.
Meleoron, we're making a run for it!
Seriously?
You bet!
We'll head back to Peijing under
the cover of this crowd!
What about Killua, Ikalgo, and the others?
There's nothing we can do!
If they can see that, they'll understand.
They'll run away, too.
That's the only option.
That isn't...
something we can handle.
But if you and I team up...
We could land one attack, sure.
And we could probably attach APR.
But...
APR only adds interest if I'm within fifty meters!
If we're within fifty meters of him...
Do you think we'd last long
enough for him to go bust?
You'd have to have lungs as strong as the boss's!
The situation's changed...
The enemy knows about our powers!
They can prepare for us.
I was an idiot.
We needed to notify the Association
right away of the chairman's defeat,
so they could immediately initiate
the next plan of action.
Hurry!
Revenge and duty...
The difference in motivations
between Meleoron and Knuckle
placed growing distance between
them as they walked.
At that moment...
Meruem's En lit up the palace and the
surrounding area in a literal flash.
Sensing there were two enemies nearby,
he began with Knuckle.
Next was Meleoron, who had barely thought
that he should activate his power
when he was knocked out.
Where's the King?
It disappeared!
I shall be interrogating them.
Once I am done, do as you like.
There were two other Nen users whose aura
reacted to my En.
One of them must be carrying
the unconscious Komugi.
What do I do? What do I do?
I must stop the King...
Your Majesty!
If your purpose is entertainment,
shouldn't you take your time?
It appears
that you have a proposal.
Yes... Would you be willing
to engage in a contest with us?
A contest?
Again...
A contest...
What contest?
Youpi and I will search for Pitou,
while you search for the
two remaining Nen users.
A contest to see who locates their target first?
Yes.
But don't you need to go and spread scales?
Correct.
So while I hypnotize the remaining humans,
I would request that Meruem-sama wait here.
It is very clear
that the difference in power between you
and the intruders is insurmountable.
Finding and capturing them should
only take you a few seconds.
That cannot be called entertainment.
Meanwhile, we must find Pitou,
who has engaged an enemy that
seems capable of teleportation.
And Pitou's current location is unknown.
To make up for the difference,
we request additional time,
as well as one further handicap.
One further handicap?
What is it?
You are only allowed to use En once more.
How does that sound?
Amusing.
I accept this contest.
Thank you very much.
Perfect...
I can use the extra time to kill that woman!
As long as we are playing,
I have a proposal, as well.
If you win, I shall grant each of you a wish.
Yes, sir.
We are very honored.
And what if you win, Meruem-sama?
If I win,
you will tell me what you are hiding from me.
Your Majesty...
Silence.
I already told you...
You and I are united as one.
Did you think that I could not sense
the guilt that you now feel?
However, I sense that your feelings
of loyalty are stronger.
Otherwise, I would have sent
your heads flying long ago.
I am certain you have your reasons.
I shall not ask them...
Assuming that you beat me.
You will obtain what you desire,
and protect your secret.
You could not wish for better terms...
Assuming that you beat me.
Meruem-sama...
I shall immediately begin to spread
scales, and not waste a moment.
If we lose, we will tell you everything.
I swear it on my life.
You do not appear to be treating
this as mere entertainment.
Once Pouf finishes spreading his
scales and returns, I shall begin.
Is that acceptable?
Yes.
Victory goes to whomever returns to
this room with their target first.
If Pitou should return,
you are to explain the objective of this contest
and order Pitou to hide.
As you wish.
I shall tell you that
the two Nen users my En registered
were an octopus and a human
carrying some sort of burden.
I must win.
No, victory is already assured!
The question is what to do
about Pitou and the woman.
Then...
Start!
Where do you think Pitou went?
It'll be fine! Pitou should return soon!
Turn around and wait by the west
tower for Pitou's return.
Do not allow Pitou near the King!
You can't use clones while you
spread your scales, right?
Then you aren't buying us any time.
Trust me!
I'm begging you!
Unbelievable... Such tremendous aura...
Those two are dead.
No,
they're still alive.
They were only knocked unconscious...
Where's Gon?
Killua's carrying him...
His hair is long?
Is it someone else?
No, those are the only two
figures in my crystal ball.
That is Gon!
Something must have happened
when I wasn't watching.
Where's Pitou?
In any case, don't come back here... Please!
Pouf is spreading scales on the citizens...
Are they poisonous?
It would help me more if he'd stay near the King.
In any case, he's on the palace's opposite side.
I must get as far from my
previous location as I can...
After that En wave, I immediately used Wink Blue,
and the King appeared next to Pouf,
carrying Knuckle and Meleoron.
Only a few seconds had passed!
Next, he will pursue Ikalgo or me.
The King could be standing behind
me at any moment...
I must hurry and get farther away...
Before the King uses En again!
I must go in there!
If I'm crossing the plain when he uses En, I won't be able to escape!
If I'm deep underground,
perhaps his En won't reach.
But I'm also trapping myself.
Should I escape outside the palace,
and hope that the King doesn't
make a move for a while?
There's no reason to expect him not to!
What should I do?
What is the right decision?
Ikalgo!
I thought you might come here...
Let's go in! Hurry!
Yes, but...
Hurry!
Isn't that why you came here?
If he uses En again, we're finished!
Where's Killua?
He went after Gon.
They're together now.
I don't know what happened to Pitou.
I see...
So Meleoron and Knuckle were captured.
The King is on a whole other level.
Why do you think their lives were spared?
Um, well...
It's possible that I just want
to think that they're alive...
They're alive.
Probably so they can be exchanged.
You mean the way Killua discussed
exchanging hostages?
I'll set a trap...
I'm not going out without a fight.
First, we'll hide the girl in Bizeff's room!
A contest...
Next time: Deadline x To x Live.
Killua...
Don't you dare speak his name!
You would never understand!
Killua!