Edited at https://subtitletools.com
No way...
Where did he go, in that condition?!
Shoot...
Fake X And X Real
You intend to fight?
You will abandon your original plan, and
commit yourself to a baseless assumption?
You really believe...
Smoky Jail, undo!
I see you've made your decision.
Once I stopped to think about it,
it was pretty simple.
You used your cocoon after I played my card.
Since you went into hiding
only after learning my agenda,
I knew that was your ability,
and that it was a trap.
Your lack of reaction when I lifted
my pipe to strike confirmed it.
It made no sense that you showed
no sign of reacting at all.
Fifteen minutes.
That was how long I expected you to take
before deciding to remove the smoke barrier.
During that time, I intended to slip
through the smoke and move freely.
You trapped me within that barrier
to separate me from the King, yes?
Meaning, as long as your
prison of smoke was there,
your allies would see it and
conclude that I was still inside.
I decided to take advantage
of that misconception, and
quietly dispose of your friends.
I knew you would hesitate long enough
to give me plenty of time to act.
You thought I'd spend fifteen minutes
waiting in front of an empty cocoon?
You really underestimated me.
No, on the contrary, it appears...
I overestimated you!
He instantly broke himself up into tiny particles?
If that's how he broke through Smoky Jail,
I wouldn't have seen a thing!
You should have waited longer...
Because my strategy was a last resort.
To be honest, I was upset by the
fact that I'd been trapped.
Not a very good diversion strategy.
You just contradicted yourself.
You made it through the smoke just fine!
At that point, that was all there was to it.
I was under the impression that
you were a more capable soldier...
One who would carry out his original
plan and be faithful to his mission.
However, you made some wild guesses
and removed the barrier.
I must thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you. Thank you.
Deep Purple!
Run!
I can't destroy them?
They just break up and reform?
He's invincible?
Thank you! Bye-bye!
Don't be fooled...
He's playing mind games!
My decision to attack the
cocoon was the best option.
No, the moment I second-guess myself,
I've played into his hands.
My next job
is to predict his objective, and stop him...
To join up with the rest of the Royal Guard,
to find and eliminate my companions,
and to reunite with the King!
That must be it...
His interests are consistent with mine.
There's no problem!
I'll take this!
He's fast!
I'll find somewhere safe to throw this away!
He got me...
I can't use any other abilities.
If Deep Purple is undone,
I'll be completely helpless!
I'll have to find a way to get by,
using Deep Purple alone.
Yo, are you
the esper?
What'd you do with Shoot, huh?
What?
Eighty-nine Deep Purple puppets...
The maximum number I could
produce in my current state.
I'll use them to support Knuckle as best I can.
I see what you're doing...
I'll let you hit me once.
But in return...
I'll take your life!
Okay, no one's here.
This is our chance to escape.
Let's go.
Man, they said we'd be safe here.
I can't get in touch with Leol-sama.
Since my stomach shrunk, that probably
means Cheetu-sama's dead...
And I haven't heard anything from
Flutter, so I guess that's it.
I'll leave to become a Queen!
I'll make you my second-in-command.
How's that?
Help...
Please...
get me out of here...
Help!
Oh, Secretary Bizeff...
You're in trouble.
I can't move my legs...
Whatever, let's go.
This looks dangerous.
What? Wait... Please!
I'm going to die!
No can do... I can't move all that.
Then, could you call for help?
Like, seriously...
I'm in a hurry to get out of this place!
The boss is missing, our link
with the King is gone,
and the palace is a mess.
I have no reason to stay here!
I'll give you whatever reward you want!
There are mountains of treasure underground!
If you help me, I'll give you anything you want.
So please pull me out!
Where underground?
There's an area for the Supreme
Leader beyond the shelter.
I've been managing the treasure inside.
I'm the only one with access...
You'll give me anything I want?
You'd better keep your promise.
Or I'll kill you!
Treasure! Treasure!
Treasure, treasure, treasure!
It's over...
This nation is finished.
That was clearly proven
when the air assault began before
I was able to make any arrangements.
They're probably calling the Ants biological
weapons, to use them as an excuse...
If I'm captured by the Federation,
they'll force me to confess for a cover
story and throw me in prison for life,
or they'll execute me, so I can't talk.
I won't let them capture me...
I'm going to escape!
The smoke-user is now out of action.
Now, I'll go back to the palace,
evaluate the current situation,
and return to the King.
Though I'm sure that even if I stay with him,
the King will only find me a nuisance.
Beelzebub!
Lord of the Flies
Beelzebub
Go forth, my clones...
Identify the location and status of
every person inside the palace!
Pouf's Beelzebub was an ability that allowed him
to disassemble into copies of himself
as small as one billionth his size.
He was able to control the size
and number of copies produced,
and the smaller the copies,
the more he could produce.
However, his main body,
which served as a control center,
could only be reduced to a bee's size.
Smoke-man, if you hadn't removed the barrier,
my main body could not have escaped.
My combat capacity would
have been reduced by half.
I'm sure a puppet master such as yourself
must know the incomparable difference in
strength between a clone and your own body.
Now that my main body is free,
I have no weaknesses.
You have lost.
You should have been more careful.
If you had, then when you realized
the cocoon was empty,
you should have wondered
whether what had been inside it
had actually escaped the barrier.
And if I had spoken to you
from outside the barrier,
you should have wondered whether
that was my real self.
The plan I executed was an act of desperation.
I could attempt to confuse your allies,
but my clones are mere husks.
Assuming that your allies were as strong as you,
even if it took a few casualties,
they would have noticed
that my clones were fakes!
Had you comprehended the truth,
and realized that my main body
remained within the barrier,
you would have understood my
ability, and searched for me.
If you had done so,
I would have had no way to
fight you in my reduced state...
In other words, if you had maintained
the barrier as per your original goal,
your allies may have suffered a bit,
but you would have been able to defeat me.
And I was ten-percent resolved
to accept that fate.
Your emotions were perfectly
aligned to accomplish that.
I suppose the explosion
must have thrown you off.
A pity...
However, I am now free.
Next, I will evaluate the situation in the palace!
From the start of the mission,
Morel's condition was less than optimal.
His exhaustion and impatience, combined
with the extreme tension of the situation,
clearly led him to the hasty decision
to engage Pouf in a battle of nerves.
However, he arrived at the
perfect time to support Knuckle,
keeping him from engaging Youpi alone.
As a result, it could be said that
he made the correct decision
to remove Smoky Jail at that time.
And it was more than simply
a product of coincidence.
It would be valid to say Morel's wealth of
experience played a role in saving him.
Upon entering the palace,
Morel had weighed the strength of the enemies
against that of his allies.
Subconsciously, he knew that they
had underestimated the enemy.
When he realized the length of time his allies
could hold out was shorter than anticipated,
he was led to attack the cocoon in order
to avoid struggling with the pros and cons
of removing Smoky Jail to go help them.
Morel's cunning, derived from his knowledge
of the battlefield, saved his comrades.
The real one's hidden among the fakes,
trying to attack me, right?
This time, I'll land a counter on you!
Five were taken out...
I have eighty-four left!
The smoke ones are fake.
They feel completely different.
When the real one lands a hit, I'll know.
That's when you'll be finished!
Seventy-five left!
Seventy-two...
Seventy...
Pitou and the woman are on the
west tower's second floor.
Pitou appears to be healing the woman.
A boy, who appears to be an
enemy, is sitting nearby.
Three near the entrance to
the underground shelter...
Hina, a Soldier Ant, and Bizeff!
They may be heading underground.
Welfin is behind them.
He appears to be following them.
The woman was injured by the dragon spears.
But why doesn't the enemy attack Pitou?
Could he be acquainted with the woman?
One in the soldiers' lounge, in the east tower...
The human captured a few days ago.
It will be born soon.
Oh, this area's crazy...
There are lots of enemies.
One, two, three...
But Youpi is taking them out quickly.
Youpi and approximately fifty enemies
are in the north area of the palace!
It's the smoke-guy and a bunch of thugs.
Also, a weird fatso with a spike on its head!
Unable to determine if it is friend or foe.
Is the spike-head Youpi's true power?
Only one of the thugs is real,
while the rest are made of smoke.
The number of puppets is not increasing
because he needs the pipe to make more.
It'll take Youpi less than a minute
to find the real one.
The King is gone! Where is he?
Everyone, return!
What's wrong?
You're running out of clones.
My attacks are too fast for you to get close.
Should I leave an opening for
him to come in and attack?
Carefully...
Act natural.
Here you go...
Come on!
He's a fake?
Wait...
You finally figured it out, idiot?
There never was a real one.
I'll kill you!
There is a real one, right here!
No kidding!
An aura explosion?
From Youpi?
Did he really need to use such an ability?
I'm worried...
But locating the King is my first priority!
You saved me, boss!
If you hadn't set that restriction,
I would have snapped and rushed him!
Listen to me...
I will create only angry clones of you
when you've lost control of your temper.
If that happens, you are to join the clones,
and give careful thought to what must be done.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got it.
After cooling down and thinking about it,
I realized that he wouldn't have taken Shoot.
But if Shoot couldn't move on his own,
who would have moved him?
Damn... Stop thinking about it!
I need to focus on the opponent before me!
Where...
am I?
That's...
Uh-oh!
Hurry up!
Go in before the entrance is blocked!
Damn, Bizeff is my prey!
If I knew what powers they had,
I could make a move.
Don't come any closer...
Pouf!
Next time: Defeat x and x Dignity.
I'm Gon.
And that's all there is to it.
I'm Killua!