Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Once someone comes out,
follow their directions.
It's been fun.
Good luck.
Yeah, thank you.
Is this Mikhail's residence?
Go do some shopping at
Dick Sakura, by the station.
At check out, give the cashier this card.
Please come this way, sir.
Strategy x And x Scheme
There are more people this time.
I wonder if there's anyone I know.
Yo.
Last year, you had your way with us.
But that won't happen again.
We've undergone some hellish training.
Our teamwork is perfect now.
Thank you for coming!
This year, 1,489 applicants
have made it this far,
but the Phase Two examiner has asked me
to trim that number to about 300.
As for the exam...
There are two hours before lunch.
Defeat five people before then.
Grab their tags when you defeat them,
and see me when you have all five.
I'll wait on the other side of the door.
Got it?
As soon as I shut the door,
you may start.
Every stage of the exam should be like this...
You've gotta be strong to be a Hunter.
Oh, you're here!
Killu—
Sucks for you.
I'm the only one passing this year.
He's totally out of our league...
So that's what it takes to
become a top Hunter...
This will be the last time I
attempt the Hunter Exam...
We finally have our first applicant.
That took an hour and a half.
What happened to everyone else?
They're all asleep.
It took me a while to collect all their tags.
Is there going to be a second stage?
That won't be necessary.
He's demonstrated his skill.
Killua, denizen of the darkness...
He's returned much stronger.
Applicant 1219, Killua-kun.
Yeah.
You've passed
the Hunter Exam!
Welcome back, Killua.
How was the exam?
I passed it in no time, naturally.
Yay!
Sorry to interrupt your celebration,
but look at these spell cards.
Wow...
There's even an S-rank card!
How much can we sell it for?
Oh, let's go ask around!
No, we should use it wisely.
So what should we do?
Well, I guess it's safe to hold on to it.
With all these defensive spells,
we don't need to worry
about it getting stolen.
Have you tried any of these?
Just Blackout Curtain.
What?
If you have all these cards,
you should use them...
Start by using this one.
You can choose a player you've
met before, and talk to them.
Contact
Communicate with one target
player (encountered within the
game) via your Book.
(Connection maintained for
a maximum of 3 minutes.
May only be broken by
player who used this card.)
[LR][NORM]
Who should we talk to?
We won't know until we see who's available.
Contact on!
Oh, I see a lot of names.
Hey, Gon...
When did you run into him?
Huh?
Chrollo Lucilfer
Chrollo?
Who's Chrollo?
I haven't seen Chrollo inside the game.
Does that mean you guys passed
each other without noticing?
Huh? What are you talking about?
That doesn't make sense.
Kurapika sealed his Nen.
Yeah, and you have to use
Nen to enter the game.
Who's Kurapika?!
That only leaves...
Let me in on this!
I get it. So that's what's going on.
Hey, Shal...
Stop laughing, and explain
what this is about.
Sorry about that.
Chrollo Lucilfer
This probably isn't the boss.
He hasn't purged the Nen from his body.
Purging Nen?
It's very doable.
Seriously?
Of course!
If you can place Nen on others,
it's not unreasonable to think
Nen can be removed, as well.
Does that mean Chrollo has removed
Kurapika's Nen, and entered the game?
Why would he be here?
I'm not sure,
but we should probably let Kurapika know.
I'll leave the game real quick.
You can use a spell card to leave.
Save it.
I can be out and back in four hours.
I should have realized this sooner...
Yorknew City                                        Greed Island
This island is directly east of Yorknew City.
East is the direction to go.
You will find one who awaits you.
I see.
So the boss came here to find
someone to purge that Nen.
The boss arrived the same way we did,
but then Razor kicked him out.
That was when he realized
this was Greed Island.
But since the boss can't use Nen,
he can't enter the island
via the usual channels.
So he must have hired someone
to come to this island for him.
He had them use his name
as a hidden message to us.
The one who can purge this
Nen is on Greed Island.
Change in plans again...
Let's bring everyone else here.
Yes, we'll all start looking
for this Nen exorcist.
I have a small correction.
You're...
Hisoka!
It was my idea to use Chrollo's name.
Because I didn't know you could
enter any name you like
until I was already inside...
You should praise my initiative.
Since I helped you understand Chrollo's message.
Ah, so that's what this is about.
I'm dying to kill you right here and now,
but I'll let the boss do that.
Well, if anything comes up,
use Contact to get in touch.
If I learn anything new, I'll let you know.
Bye.
So the boss hired Hisoka...
He probably didn't have much
choice, but it's still weird.
And his reward is probably a duel,
once the boss is cleansed.
But now, it's only a matter of time
until the boss comes back!
I doubt it.
I would know at once
if Nen I placed on a spider
had been removed.
So when you chose your power, you
knew something like this might happen?
Of course...
If you're able to place Nen on others,
it only makes sense to assume
that one can also remove Nen.
Well, now you know.
What you do from here is up to you.
Thanks for taking the trouble.
You have my gratitude.
Did you need anything?
What am I...
What am I supposed to do this month?
Tell me...
What should I do?
It'll be fine. Let me handle...
What could you possibly know?
You have no idea what's going
to happen to us now!
Neon... I need Neon!
Restore Neon at once!
Damn! Why did this happen?
I wonder what's wrong...
Why did it stop working?
See ya.
Looks like it's not the real Chrollo.
Oh...
Kurapika was pretty calm about it.
Like he wasn't concerned or just didn't care.
Well, it sounds like you
got worried for nothing.
Now it's time to focus on yourselves.
Osu!
Start with the basics...
We're not going to train.
It's time to start
beating this game!
It's said the legendary King Great White Beetle
lives only on this tree!
There's only one way to capture it!
Hit the tree hard enough to shake it out.
First comes rock!
Rock, paper...
Rock!
Wow!
It's raining bugs!
Found it.
Difficulty rank A!
King Great White Beetle
A legendary insect that
releases pheromones
which attract other insects
to start a massive colony.
Can only leave the colony
for brief evening walks.
That's three King Great White Beetle cards!
You could've gotten more if
you'd thrown a real punch.
Well, I didn't want to damage the tree.
There is no such girl in this mansion.
Even if there were, it would be impossible
for you to bypass all the traps and find her.
Found her.
She was in a hidden room,
four floors underground.
What?
Curse you!
Got an A-rank Gold Dust Girl!
Gold Dust Girl
A girl who releases golden dust.
One bath a day will net approx. 500 G.
Very shy and quiet.
The guard was a rank F.
Next, let's head to the
City of Gambling, Dorias!
Wait, wasn't today supposed to be
the monthly contest in Antokiba?
We'll be passing through, so let's give it a go.
Our winner is the Killua and Gon team.
Paladin's Necklace
When a player wears this,
all spells targeting player
will be reflected.
Can also dispel curses
placed on any card
touched by player.
A Paladin's Necklace! Score!
I don't understand this description.
We can ask one of the shopkeepers.
When you wear this necklace,
you can reflect all attack spells.
And if you touch cards under the
Transform
Change one card in your possession into any
other card in your possession. (Card will now
count against the limit of new card type. If limit has already been reached, nothing will happen,
and the Transform card will be destroyed.)
[SR][NORM]
Fake
Change Fake into any card type from 001 to 099.
The new card can be placed in a restricted pocket.
But it will not count toward Book completion,
and cannot be transformed into an item.
It also will not count toward card limit.
[SR][NORM]
effects of Transform or Fake,
you can restore them to their original state.
Wow...
If we wear this, we won't have to
worry about losing any cards.
Memory Helmet...
Memory Helmet
A player will always remember
everything seen or heard
while wearing this item.
Unfortunately, helmet is
very large and heavy.
Witch's Love Potion.
Witch's Love Potion
If player kisses a pill before
feeding it to a target, target will
become beholden to player.
Each pill will remain effective
for one week. Each bottle
contains 500 pills.
Risky Dice.
Risky Dice
A 20-sided die. One side says
Bad Luck, while the other nineteen
say Good Luck. If player rolls
Good Luck, something good will
happen. But if player rolls Bad Luck,
something bad will happen to cancel
out everything that was good.
King Great White Beetle.
King Great White Beetle
A legendary insect that
releases pheromones
which attract other insects
to start a massive colony.
Can only leave the colony
for brief evening walks.
Gold Dust Girl.
Gold Dust Girl
A girl who releases golden dust.
One bath a day will net approx. 500 G.
Very shy and quiet.
Paladin's Necklace
When a player wears this,
all spells targeting player
will be reflected.
Can also dispel curses
placed on any card
touched by player.
Paladin's Necklace.
A total of six different restricted slot cards!
Piece of cake!
Piece of cake?
Not in the least.
This was only possible because you
underwent that grueling training.
Another player has used Contact to reach you.
Yo. It's been a while, Gon.
Who are you?
You don't remember me?
Do you remember the player
who took the Sword of Truth
from you in Antokiba?
What do you want?
Up for a trade?
I have #66, Witch's Diet Pill,
and #17, VIP Multi-Pass.
You can talk it over with your friends.
What do you think?
Another player has used Contact to reach you.
It's Tsezgerra.
You again?
Interested in trading your
Breath of Archangel for our Patch of Forest?
It's an SS-rank card.
No way.
I've already said I won't
deal with you people.
What if I throw in a Clone?
I'm telling you that there's no deal here.
You already have ninety-two different cards.
All that's left
are the cards monopolized
by other players, yes?
Actually, we have ninety-five...
And you probably have many items
that you haven't used Gain on yet.
It's possible that Breath of Archangel
is the final card you need.
If we give that to you, we'll lose.
Stop playing dumb.
I know that you're monopolizing
both Breath of Archangel and Night Jade.
This game isn't over yet.
I see.
Good luck, then.
But we'll never let you have these cards.
What if I offer three cards?
We'll give you Patch of Forest,
Patch of Forest
The entrance to an enormous
forest known as the Mountain
God's Garden. Many species
exist only in this forest.
All are friendly to humans.
Hidden Hollow
Upon entering and exiting hollow,
player will be transported to a
desolate location. However, player can
return to original location
without spending any money.
Hidden Hollow,
Palmtop Dragon
As the name implies, this dragon
fits on your palm. Willingly obeys
its master. If raised lovingly,
it can learn to speak.
and Palmtop Dragon.
And you only have to give us Night Jade,
not Breath of Archangel.
We'd be giving you one SS-rank
card and two S-rank cards,
while you'd only give up one A-rank card.
I believe this deal is too good to pass up.
Give us some time to discuss this.
Just to be clear, this is our final offer.
We won't accept any further negotiation.
Book.
It's gotta be a trap.
That offer's too good.
Tsezgerra is a careful man.
He wouldn't try to pick a fight.
But at the same time, he would
never make a losing deal.
Breath of Archangel
An angel who can cure any mortal
injury or terminal disease with one breath.
However, angel will appear only once.
Meaning that he thinks
he can obtain a Breath of Archangel.
Does that mean they've assembled
all forty spell card types?
It's possible.
So they're waiting for Gain to be
used on a Breath of Archangel.
Night Jade
A jewel blessed by the devil.
When the holder is in danger,
peril will be shifted to another.
On the other hand, Night Jade is a card
that we monopolized through hard work.
If one of the cards were to be destroyed,
one of our jade jewels would
automatically turn into a card.
Which means the A-rank
Night Jade is much harder
for them to get than the
SS-rank Breath of Archangel.
This is a gamble.
Witch's Love Potion
If player kisses a pill before
feeding it to a target, target will
become beholden to player.
Each pill will remain effective
for one week. Each bottle
contains 500 pills.
VIP Multi-Pass
Present this pass to gain
entry into any location.
Contains 1000 passes.
Book.
See ya.
That was uneventful.
Kind of disappointing.
I was so nervous...
But now we've gathered
seven types, in three days!
We're making decent progress.
Okay, let's keep this up.
Are there any other events in the city
for getting restricted slot cards?
Hmm... I think there are...
Prizes from the slot machines?
Should've expected as much from
Dorias, the City of Gambling.
You have a 0.01% chance of winning.
That's one in ten thousand tries.
So it all comes down to luck.
Pretty risky.
I know, Gon!
Use that dice!
This is it...
If we get Good Luck, we can win!
But if you get Bad Luck,
something bad will happen that cancels out
everything good that's happened.
There's only a one in twenty
chance of getting Bad Luck.
There!
Next, we try the slot machine!
Awesome! One try!
Rainbow Diamond
A diamond that glitters like
a rainbow. If this diamond
is presented when proposing,
you will never be turned down.
A Rainbow Diamond! Score!
That's what I thought...
This die is the key to winning in this city.
But if you roll Bad Luck, it could be scary.
Don't worry.
It can't kill me...
Oh, no! A slot machine exploded!
I knew something was wrong.
That guy hit the jackpot five times in a row.
And he was acting weird...
He kept rolling a funny-looking die.
Yikes, his face is mush...
Anyway, let's make the trade.
Yeah, we want to get cards of rank S
and above as quickly as possible.
Yeah.
As for cards rank A and below...
Roll.
S-Spare me...
This is only your third time.
You'll be fine.
I-I know someone who got
Bad Luck on the first roll and died!
If I roll Bad Luck,
I'll be hit for every Good Luck
that the other players rolled!
Not my problem.
Roll.
Or would you rather die right now?
Come on...
See?
It's pretty rare to get Bad Luck.
Now we use the Lottery card.
We want #75, Lucky Alexandrite.
If you obtain one, we'll set you free.
C-Come on...
Lottery on!
Well?
#76!
So close!
Your luck sucks.
Okay, one more time!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Time for Motarike-kun to
show us what he's got!
No good, huh?
Hey, Gen.
Should we make the first move?
I already told you that combat
should be our last resort.
It's too early for that.
No, we're trying to stay
one step ahead of them.
Though, once we commit,
further negotiation will be impossible.
What do you have in mind?
Tax Collector's Gauntlet
When equipped, player has
the ability to cast Levy. But
each cast will destroy a random
card from player's restricted
slots. (Cannot use Levy if
restricted slots are empty.)
We use Tax Collector's Gauntlet,
combined with Risky Dice.
I understand.
We use this to steal eight cards
from them immediately...
But it's definitely dangerous.
If someone rolls Bad Luck, they'll probably die.
But this job is too important to leave to them.
We can do this!
We've come this far.
Let's clear the game.
Hey, Gen...
What are you up to?
I've told you this many times.
When taking a risk, we three share the danger.
It's Tsezgerra.
Have you reached a decision?
Okay, you have a deal.
I can do this...
One more time!
I said I can do this,
so I'm gonna do it!
Okay, let's move on to the next city!
Gon's team has begun
working to beat the game.
The story is nearing its climax.
G.I. Tutorial
Coming up, it's the
Greed Island Tutorial!
Today, we introduce the card Lottery.
Lottery
Change this card
into a random item card.
[SR][NORM]
When you use this card,
it changes into a random card.
That's why it's effective to use with Risky Dice.
Continue!
Next time: 15 X 15.
Hey, Killua, is this fifteen?
What did you think it was?
One five.
Cute, huh...