Edited at https://subtitletools.com
The Hunters have entered the palace in
order to defeat the Chimera Ant King.
My attacks don't work?
What is this thing?
Don't you run!
Answer me!
What is this thing?!
I ain't gonna tell you, fool!
If you wanna know, catch me first!
To save the injured Shoot,
Knuckle taunted Youpi to draw his attention.
Knuckle's planning to fight Youpi alone...
I can't weave through those
blades of death to get to him!
In that case...
I must not lose consciousness...
If I pass out,
Hotel Rafflesia will stop...
Every little bit of damage counts...
I can still fight...
I can still...
Right now, my job...
isn't to help Shoot!
It's to use my power to help the others,
so they can complete their
missions as fast as possible!
Though it broke his heart,
Meleoron had to leave the two Hunters
and follow Gon and Killua instead,
in order to fulfill his mission.
Meanwhile, Ikalgo proceeded further into
the depths of the palace to rescue Palm.
Satellite Dragonflies!
I'm gonna rescue her.
Palm is a friend of a friend.
That makes her a friend...
My friend!
As Morel, the first Hunter
to reach the throne room,
waited to continue his battle with Pouf,
who remained in his cocoon,
Netero and the King were leaving the palace,
and Gon and Killua had finally located Neferpitou,
their target for avenging Kite.
Revenge x And x Recovery
Do you
remember me?
I'm Gon Freecss!
I came here
to get Kite back from you!
Pitou didn't hear a single word Gon said.
The only thing on Pitou's mind was
surviving the current threat
while carrying out the King's order.
Every cell in Pitou's body was focused on that task.
I must protect Komugi...
At any cost!
Something's not right.
Watching from a short distance, Killua
noticed that something was strange.
Why isn't the enemy preparing for
battle when we're right here?
I can't sense any aura at all...
Pitou might as well be completely
naked... Utterly defenseless.
Does Pitou think it can win without aura?
No, that isn't possible.
The aura coming from Gon now
doesn't even compare to his usual.
Even Pitou can't fight that without using Nen.
Is it because of where we are?
Does Pitou believe that, at this distance,
there'll be time to activate Nen if we do attack?
That's possible.
However, for some reason...
That doesn't seem to be it.
It almost looks like...
That's it.
It looks like...
a mother
using its own body to guard something weaker.
That's ridiculous.
Pitou isn't someone who's capable of that!
But then, why did Grandpa...
I'll let you draw your own conclusions
about what's happening inside.
...say something that cryptic?
While Killua was fighting his natural instincts,
the girl lying before them brought back
images of a broken Kite to Gon's mind.
Get away from her.
I'm telling you to take that
monster and get away from her.
And then, fight me!
Fight me, so I can get Kite back!
The act of placing both palms face-up
to display one's lack of malice
was a gesture Killua recognized...
Please
wait.
What the hell?!
What am I supposed to wait for?
Get up! We're going outside!
Pitou's unexpected lack of resistance
left Gon without a target for his rage.
Meanwhile, Killua was close to fully
understanding the current situation.
It was...
I know nothing beyond the mission I received.
He was saying something
unexpected happened!
Grandpa knew nothing when
he brought the dragon down.
Grandpa's mission was probably
to use Dragon Dive and Dragon Head to
separate the King and Royal Guard.
But he didn't know that she was here, too.
Wait, this woman must be
the third party that none of us knew about!
And she's most likely
the reason the King hurt himself.
Why would the King do something
so out of character?
Because she is someone
who's special to the King.
Pitou isn't taking her apart.
Pitou is healing her at the King's command!
Pitou isn't only prevented from using
En when healing someone.
All aura must be focused on
healing ability when using it.
However, Killua knew that this
information would only have
a negative effect on Gon.
What do I do?
What do I tell him?
Go—
I'll do anything!
I'll do anything you say!
So please wait.
I...
must save this person!
Save...
Save what?
"Anything"?
When you say "anything"...
Killua...
I'm asking the questions.
What is it that you must save?
Amidst the extreme tension,
the answer Pitou chose to give was...
This person is someone...
Someone who's important
to someone important to me.
...the truth.
She is the reason the King is who he is.
If she dies, the King will cease to be who he is.
She's that important.
So...
All I care about is saving her!
Once she's healed, I'll do anything you want.
So please wait!
You want to save her?
You must save her?
Save her?
How dare you say that...
How dare you?!
Damn it!
The hell if...
The hell if I'll listen to you!
Gon, hold on!
It's likely that we were
the ones that injured her.
It was probably Grandpa's Dragon Dive.
And?
Pitou is probably telling the
truth about healing her.
So?
Let's wait until it's done.
"Likely"?
"Probably"?
You want me to wait because
of "likely" and "probably"?
And after we wait, it's likely that this thing
will do what I want?
Likely? Probably?
Seriously?!
That's crap!
That's just crap!
Is something wrong with you?!
You want... You want me to trust this thing?!
I can't do that!
If you want, you may also have my right arm...
If that isn't enough,
you can take both legs...
If you're worried I'll change my mind
after the healing finishes,
you can break any part of my body
that isn't required to heal her.
Please let me save her!
That isn't fair...
That isn't fair, damn it!
Why are you helping her,
after everything you did to Kite?!
Gon!
Why?!
To hell with that.
First comes—
Gon, if you kill Pitou,
we'll never get Kite back.
You have it easy, Killua.
You're perfectly calm.
Since it means nothing to you...
I'm only saying this because
you're out of control.
Did you forget the first thing
you said when we came here?
We're here to get Kite back!
Pull it together!
Yeah.
I'm okay now.
How long?
How long do I have to wait?
To completely heal her
will take three to four hours.
No, I can't wait that long.
If I have an hour,
I can heal her most critical injuries.
Please give me that.
In one hour, you're coming with
me to Peijing, to heal Kite.
Can you promise me that?
I swear to keep that promise!
I'll wait right here for one hour.
Next time: Insult x And x Payback.
I can't think of anything right now...
Killua, insult me back!
I... feel better now.