Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Fortunes x Aren't x Right?
Ready, go!
Kurapika!
This is great.
Huh?
The spiders are dead,
so you can finally focus on your main goal.
You have to find the eyes of your people.
Gon...
Yep.
If there's anything we can do to help—
Hey!
You did it first.
I was getting revenge!
But I didn't do it on purpose.
You did it deliberately!
Why are you so upset?
We sold that piece for 355 million Jenny!
It could have sold for more...
We got a decent price!
No, we could have gotten over 400
million if we'd sold at a different time.
We had bad luck...
You sure take this seriously.
It isn't like you would've gotten anything
if we'd gotten a better price.
That's not the issue here.
If we run with the money,
we'd each get a 170 million cut!
Are you really friends with Gon and Killua?
I was joking.
Hello?
Oh, Kurapika!
It's been a while since we
were all together last!
Yeah.
Where's Zepile-san?
He wanted to validate our check
and find more hidden gems to sell.
Anyway...
What?
You've got this intensity about you...
You seem a little more intimidating now.
Really?
You don't seem to have changed much.
And you're more annoying, too!
Oh, I heard that you defeated
a member of the Troupe.
Having only just learned Nen,
how did you manage that?
If you're looking for advice
on catching the spiders,
then stop.
That's not the only reason.
We want to master Nen.
Because we'll definitely
need Nen in the future.
Then you don't want my advice.
It won't do you any good.
Why not?
My power can only be
used against the Troupe.
Huh?
Restraint and vow?
Yeah.
Nen is strongly affected by your mental state.
The stronger your resolve,
the more power you receive.
However, you also incur a
big risk at the same time.
In return for Nen power,
I vowed to use it against the spiders alone.
I established a rule for myself.
What's the rule?
If I use my chains on one who isn't a spider,
I will forfeit my life.
Huh? What do you mean?
There is a Nen blade pointed at my heart.
If I break the rule,
that blade will pierce my heart, killing me.
This is the rule that shows my resolve.
Restraint and vow.
My power is the product of pure hatred.
It only works on the spiders.
I'm telling you because I trust you.
Don't tell anyone else.
Why...
Why would you tell us something so important?!
I'm not sure.
With their leader's death,
I must have relaxed.
It'll be fine if we keep our mouths shut.
It's too dangerous.
One of the surviving members can read minds.
If they find out, Kurapika won't
be able to beat them!
But she didn't learn anything last time.
That's because we didn't know
Kurapika was the chain user.
Then we just have to stay away from them.
They've already checked you,
so they think you're clean.
But there's also a guy called Nobunaga.
He's especially dangerous.
He's looking for Kurapika,
and he's still trying to chase us down.
Is he aware that you guys know Kurapika?
No...
Then it's okay!
As long as no one around the mind reader
knows Kurapika, then you're safe.
Well, I've also been in
contact with Hisoka.
What?!
Hisoka?
He knows that I am the chain user.
We made a pact,
but his target, the leader of
the spiders, is now dead.
So I don't know what he'll do.
What do you mean?
We're leaving?
I mean exactly what I say.
We're departing tonight.
We'll take the rest of the treasure tonight.
That will be the end.
It isn't.
What else is there?
We have to find the chain user.
You seem obsessed.
Yes, I am.
We're going to scatter
without avenging Uvo?
Uvo will be bored in the next
world if we don't send
the chain user to join him.
Cut it out, Nobunaga.
The boss has issued an order.
Yeah, and an order from
the boss is absolute.
But is that really an order from our boss,
Chrollo?
Nobunaga, watch yourself...
Shut up!
I'm talking to Chrollo!
Before I can answer your question...
Nobunaga,
I need you to answer my question.
What's your date of birth?
Huh?
What day were you born?
September 8th, 70.
Blood type?
B.
Name?
Nobunaga Hazama...
You already know that!
The hell is this about?!
What do you want next?
No, that's enough.
Write all of that on this sheet of paper.
Why didn't you tell me to
do that in the first place?
Huh? What's this?
A one hundred percent accurate
fortune written in verse.
The ability to see the future.
I stole this power from Nostrade's daughter.
One hundred percent accurate?
Each of the four verses predicts
what will happen in that week.
The calendar loses a precious component.
The remaining months gather to mourn.
The first moon, having missed his opportunity,
continues to pursue the eleventh moon alone.
The chrysanthemum withers and falls,
to lie on the ground beside bloody Scarlet Eyes.
But the spider does not stop.
Even after losing half its limbs.
This is the fortune his
daughter gave me yesterday.
Is the precious component of the calendar...
Uvo.
That girl didn't know anything about Uvo.
In other words, she predicted our attack
on the Mafia auction.
And there were fans of her
fortunetelling among the Ten Dons.
I get it.
That explains why the merchandise
had already been moved the
first time we attacked.
What does Nobunaga's fortune say?
The pen writes by itself.
I don't know what was written.
Ask Nobunaga.
Well, Nobunaga?
Next week, five of us will probably die.
Which five?
No idea...
I can't interpret this.
I kind of understand the second verse.
The spider loses half its limbs.
The spider would be us?
Yeah.
And the limbs would be the members,
so half would be six.
That means five more after losing Uvo.
The same line was in my fortune.
Let me see.
Boss, can you tell my fortune?
The calendar loses a precious component.
The remaining months gather to mourn.
You join your ally as an offering,
to keep him from being lonely.
You will find eternal rest
in a room filled with black merchandise.
Beware solitude above all.
You have the most to fear when
you are alone with another.
I thought so.
I'm going to die next week.
Seriously?
Yep.
Because I only got two verses.
And Pakunoda and Shalnark will die, as well.
How do you know that?
It seems the numbered months
here refer to Troupe members.
November is the eleventh month.
Uvo was member #11.
Exactly.
The chrysanthemum is the
flower of September.
It blooms in August, the eighth month,
and it withers in June.
This refers to members #6, #8, and #9.
And since the word "falling"
is used, it implies death.
I'm not certain to whom "Scarlet Eyes" refers.
It isn't one of us.
I'm guessing it's the chain user.
Scarlet Eyes...
I remember now.
The clan whose eyes turned red.
Then there was a survivor?
So it seems...
Will he also die?
Hard to say.
It could just mean that he's covered in blood.
Nobunaga, this means we'll
suffer serious casualties
if we fight the chain user!
We'll lose half our members.
You and I have abilities that
can be easily replaced,
but Shizuku and Pakunoda have rare powers.
The Troupe can't afford to lose them.
Today is Saturday of the first week.
If we return home today,
we won't run into the chain user next week.
The advantage of being able
to predict the future
is that we can avoid undesirable prophecies.
If we leave this place without
fighting the chain user,
this fortune is one hundred percent
certain to not come true.
Nobunaga, you and Uvo were
the Troupe's attackers.
To die is just part of your job.
I believe that you both chose
that role voluntarily.
Yeah, that's right...
Shizuku, Paku, and Shal collect intelligence.
They provide our support.
You could say they're our lifeline.
Isn't it your job to serve as their shield?
Yeah, it is!
Wait...
You should tell some of the
other members' fortunes.
Perhaps we could gather additional
clues for avoiding the prophecy.
What do we do?
Now that we know Kurapika's secret,
it's dangerous to wait around.
If Nobunaga captures either Gon or me again,
we probably won't be able to escape.
But we have Kurapika with us now.
We should take them out
before they have a chance
to recover and escape.
We know where their current base is.
If we take too long, they might get away.
We need to move fast.
They could be making an
escape as we speak.
We don't have time for too much thought.
The woman you mentioned
is certainly a threat...
But since their leader is dead,
I'll do as Gon says, and focus on
recovering my brethren's eyes.
Seriously?!
Yeah.
You're sure about this?
Kurapika's made up his mind.
We can't force him to change it.
Sorry, Killua.
Thank you for the valuable information.
It's from Hisoka...
The dead bodies were fakes.
Kurapika?
The dead bodies were fakes...
Huh?
You mean the dead bodies
of the Troupe members?
Yeah, the dead spiders were fakes!
It would be possible for a
Conjurer to accomplish that.
Damn!
Why didn't I realize this sooner?
The situation's changed.
What now?
We're here to help.
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Hello?
Kurapika, it's me.
Melody?
What is it?
The community has called off the hunt
for the remaining Troupe members.
What?
We've learned that they
came from Meteor City.
The Troupe comes from Meteor City?
The Ten Dons gave the order directly.
The reward has been rescinded.
The reward has been rescinded?
Seriously?
The Troupe comes from Meteor City.
Makes sense...
That explains why their
identities are still unknown,
and why the cops haven't
been able to catch them.
What's Meteor City?
A city populated by people who,
as far as society is concerned, don't exist.
There's a city like that?
Yeah.
Officially, it's unpopulated,
but it's said that ten million people live there.
It began as a dump over 1,500 years ago.
People began to live off the garbage
that was dumped there.
You're allowed to dump anything there.
From garbage to weapons, and even people.
And the residents
will accept anything left there.
I've heard that Meteor City
residents share a bond
thinner than that between strangers,
stronger than that between family.
Actually, there are those
who provide Meteor City
with weapons and precious metals
under the pretext of garbage.
That would be the Mafia community.
What do you mean?
But the Mafia is hunting the Troupe!
In return, the Mafia recruited
people from Meteor City.
People who didn't exist, as far
as society was concerned.
Perfect for committing crimes.
The Troupe destroyed the
normally intimate relationship
between the Mafia community and Meteor City.
But the Mafia has decided to
prioritize that relationship.
A red-eyed customer will visit your shop,
half angel, half death-bringer.
You would do well to sell
the calendar's secrets.
He will be especially pleased to
learn the eleventh moon's secret.
The customer will return on a hot day,
leaving you alone with a man
bearing St. Peter's cross.
The false fourth moon will be
torn away from the calendar.
Only six pages remain.
What does your fortune say?
Let me see.
I don't recommend it.
It'll give you a shock.
Just let me see it.
Very well.
Look at this, everyone!
"A red-eyed customer will visit..."
"The calendar's secrets..."
That would be our secrets, right?
Hisoka, what is this?
Lemme see!
A red-eyed customer will visit your shop,
seeking to make a trade.
The customer will use the
sword of law upon you,
taking the calendar's secrets with him.
The eleven-legged spider grows homesick,
losing five more legs.
Do not leave your temporary shelter,
for you are one of the remaining legs.
Hisoka...
Did you sell him out?
Sell out Uvo?!
Hisoka's fortune changed when
it was passed to Pakunoda.
What could that mean?
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Coming up, we have Gon
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
and Killua's
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Hunterpedia!
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Brush Your Teeth.
Unripe Fruit
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
It's Gon
and Killua's
Hunterpedia!
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
Today, we introduce Bonolenov.
A Phantom Troupe member.
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
A member of the Phantom Troupe.
A Phantom Troupe member.
Responsible for
guarding their base.
His face, body, and powers
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
are covered by bandages.
Responsible for
guarding their base.
When he removes the
bandages, strange
holes appear.
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
are covered by bandages.
Spin, spin, spin!
Gon and Killua's Hunterpedia
When he removes the
bandages, strange
holes appear.
Spin, spin, spin!
Next time: Allies x And x Lies.
My Highness.
Your Highness?
His Highness Killua!
Yeah, yeah.