Edited at https://subtitletools.com
So, then...
Where are we on the island?
Let's steal an Accompany card and go.
Uninvited guests?
I'm getting nervous...
Just so we're clear,
you didn't wash up on shore, right?
After all, if you'd let the waves carry you,
it would be impossible to reach this island.
This guy's strong.
Who are you?
Are you supposed to be our tour guide?
I'm one of the designers of this game.
The name's Razor.
I mainly handle the Emitter spells,
including all movement via spells
and dealing with external threats.
Eliminate
Send all trespassers
on Greed Island to a
random location on
the Azian continent
[LR][SP]
This is a special spell only usable by Game Masters.
Sorry, but you'll have to leave.
You're more than welcome to
visit via official channels.
From there, if you defeat me,
you can receive an item.
Should you decide to play,
we'll probably get to fight eventually.
Sounds good...
We'll come back.
Through the front door.
Eliminate on.
Hmm, those were some strong Nen users...
Evil Fist x And x Rock-Paper-Scissors
As Gon continues to train,
he discovers a hint to developing
a new technique, and that is...
First comes rock!
Rock... Paper...
Rock!
I see.
Here comes the next one!
First comes rock!
Rock... Paper...
Paper!
Bisky, how do I make my Nen fly?
Train more!
So paper is an Emitter technique?
Uh-huh.
And Scissors is a Transmuter technique.
I wanna be able to cut through rock.
I understand.
That's a reasonable fighting technique.
But such a childish idea.
You know how it takes time
to focus Nen in my fist?
I was trying to think of a good
way to spend that time.
And when you were talking about
rock-paper-scissors, it hit me.
Because I like rock-paper-scissors.
Trusting your instincts is important.
Your gut plays a big role in
techniques that require
multiple Nen categories.
The key is that it should feel right to you.
Ah... Ahem.
Well, this is all I can manage right now,
but if I charge it up, it's pretty strong.
That's awesome, Killua!
You're like an electric eel!
That's a horrible comparison!
He can already change Nen into
electricity at such a young age?
Frightening...
And very tragic...
His childhood must have been a living hell.
It's a miracle that he can smile now.
Indeed...
They make a great team.
Well, let's take a break, then.
It's a little early, but we can have a party.
A party?
What do you boys do back home to celebrate?
Celebrate?
In the outside world, it's almost New Year's.
Time flows at the same speed
inside the game as outside.
Oops!
The deadline to apply for the
Hunter Exam is coming up!
And our training was just starting to get fun...
I believe you're required to apply
before the end of the year.
We need to hurry.
How do we get outside?
I'm guessing there are spell
cards to leave the game?
In that case, let's head to Masadora.
Agreed!
Well, let's find a place to have a drink.
We can't... There's no time.
We can ask around the stores.
How to leave the island?
That'll be 3,000 Jenny.
If you go about fifty kilometers west,
you'll reach the island's only port.
You must defeat or bribe
the chief of that port
to receive a ticket that will
transport you outside.
How big of a bribe are we talking?
Depends on how the chief's feeling.
Ah...
Your other option is to
use a Leave spell card,
but that's a rare one.
What do we do?
Let's head for the port.
If it's a rare card, we could buy
a bunch without finding one.
True.
Passage Ticket
Voilà.
Well, I'll go pass the test real
quick, and then hurry back.
There are monsters called Kiriko
that live beneath a cedar tree
on the mountain behind Dolle Harbor.
If you tell them you're my friend,
they'll take you to the exam area.
Okay.
See ya.
Then let's get back to training.
Osu!
Welcome.
Is this where I started?
No, it's not...
The girl looks similar, though.
Well, that's not so unusual in games.
You are leaving the island, right?
Please select a destination.
Do you know Dolle Harbor?
Yes, I do.
Then send me there.
Understood.
When you leave this island,
the cards in your free slots will disappear.
Is that okay?
Yeah, it's fine.
Then we shall await your return.
I'm back in the real world now?
Doesn't feel that way.
Book.
Oh, it doesn't work out here.
Once I submit my application,
I'll head for that cedar tree.
First, I should shower and
change into fresh clothes.
Okay, train while you run!
When you can form the numbers from 0 to 9
in one minute, you'll clear this stage.
That hurt!
What are you doing?
Aren't you...
Your other friend isn't here?
What's that machine on your shoulder?
Did something happen?
We were fooled by the Bomber.
Will you listen to my story?
So he was the Bomber...
The others are waiting at our base for
the Bomber to disarm the bombs.
They believe the terms he gave them,
even though it was probably a bluff.
Can't anything be done?
If they're prepared to accept casualties...
It's impossible.
The first people to attack
will be the ones who die.
Who would volunteer for that role?
True...
Jispa was our group's strongest fighter,
and he was defeated in an instant.
At that point, our loss was assured.
And allowing him to leave the game
was a fatal mistake.
We indulged in a moment's victory cheer
before we could verify each
member's cards and assign roles.
That's when he caught us off guard.
It's embarrassing to admit,
but I was so distracted,
I didn't notice him using Leave
until it was already too late.
You were probably focused on
understanding his explanation.
Yeah.
We were thrust into that
situation with no warning.
Given our mental state, there was
no action we could have taken.
But why are you telling us this?
Because, of everyone I've met on this island,
you are the ones I believe I can most rely on.
If you run into any other players,
please tell them about the Bomber.
Once everyone knows how his ability works,
they should be able to protect themselves.
And if possible, I would
like you to avenge us!
If not,
could you at least promise that
you won't let him clear the game?
Yeah.
Understood.
Sorry...
I'll use what time I have remaining
to tell as many as I can about the Bomber.
Book.
Return on.
Bunzen!
Just kidding...
The truth is that they were
the only players I could find
using Magnetic Force.
Even a pig can climb a tree if
you give it enough praise.
Every thousandth of a percent counts
when it comes to deactivating someone's Nen.
Well, Nickes probably left to
meet with the bombers.
If the mass disarmament
turns out to be a mass explosion...
I should get started.
You're finally here.
Now give me your ring.
Jispa's dead.
That's nice. Your ring.
Disarm everyone's bombs first!
Hell, no.
I have to enter the game with your ring,
and confirm that the cards
really are all inside.
I'll disarm the bombs after that.
I'll give you one more chance.
Hand over the ring.
Sub, put it on.
If you put on a second ring outside the game,
you'll overwrite the data.
Now, let's head back inside together.
Wait, what was your name?
Migamura, Samingadura,
Interaminga, Zenberarubura.
Spirits of the forest,
remove the tainted Nen that resides within me.
Now, then...
What horrors will come of this?
I borrow power from the forest spirits,
to use my Conjurer ability
to create a Nen beast, capable of
consuming other people's Nen!
It's huge!
The Bomber's Countdown must be
a particularly strong technique.
How'd it go?
Has he disarmed the bombs yet?
Book.
81 restricted slot card types.
They're all here, all right.
We did as you requested...
Disarm the bombs!
But of course.
I'm a man of my word.
But first, hand over three Leave cards.
Okay, we have a deal.
Sub... Bara...
Let's do this.
Release.
I released you
from your terror.
Th-That wasn't the deal...
Why should I keep a promise
I made to a bunch of scum?
Release was the signal to explode, not disarm.
Leave on!
At least now, I don't have
to worry about exploding.
But until Genthru reverses his ability or dies,
this thing won't disappear.
I have a troublesome partner now...
Hey, stop moving!
The Bomber thinks he killed us all.
I'll let him believe that...
Until I make my move!
Bisky...
I think we should drop by
their base real fast.
They already ran out of time.
Besides, he didn't even
tell us exactly where it is.
And even if we did know,
we don't have a spell card
that could take us there.
I know.
But some of them might have
survived the explosion...
Doubt it.
If the Bomber's strong enough to place bombs
on all his targets without anyone noticing,
he wouldn't have made that kind of mistake.
However...
If we continue to play this game,
we'll probably run into the Bomber.
Given that, we may need
to visit their base soon.
Uh-huh.
We need spell cards.
Let's go to Masadora and
sell our monster cards
to buy spell cards.
Yeah!
Hey, Bisky...
How long do you think it'll take me
to master my special technique?
You're just starting to develop your Nen.
It's hard to predict when your
power and speed will peak.
Oh...
But it shouldn't take too long
before you get the form down.
Really? How long?
Let's see...
Hopefully, you'll have it ready
by the time Killua returns.
All right!
I'll finish my technique and surprise him!
You two are lucky!
We just received a huge
shipment of spell cards.
These are the spell cards they'd gathered.
We bought sixty between us,
so there are lots of different types.
Look.
Prison
All slotted cards on target
page are immune to theft
or destruction via spell
card until removed.
(Only targets pages 1 - 11.
Free slot pages
cannot be targeted.)
[DEF][CONT]
An S-rank card...
There are only ten in the whole game!
What do you think?
Should we save it?
Or use it now?
I don't know what to do!
Shh!
You're too loud...
People will get suspicious!
If only Killua were here...
I can smell Gon on you.
I'd like to see him again...
We'll take you to the exam site.
I need to zip on over and
breeze through the exam,
so I can hurry back to Gon.
But the exam won't begin for a few days.
Oh, right.
In the meantime, you can tell
us about yourself and Gon.
Okay.
I'll start with the story about
when he came to visit my home.
You're making steady progress.
You're on track to have your
special technique ready.
This is a safe place to practice.
Since we'll be able to spot anyone
before they're in attack spell range.
I can sense people watching from Masadora,
just like I sensed people
watching us at the start point.
But we have plenty of defense spells now.
Well, just to be safe,
I used a Blackout Curtain card.
Blackout Curtain
Block one instance of enemy Steal or Fluoroscopy.
(Does not stack when used on target already under
effect of Blackout Curtain.)
[DEF][CONT]
But no point in worrying about spell cards.
Just focus on training hard.
Osu!
Okay, one minute's up.
Next.
It didn't work.
I can't reach it...
That was just fine.
You're in far better shape than
a Transmuter would be!
Be patient, and start by focusing
on maintaining your aura
in a sphere for extended periods of time.
Osu!
The longer you can maintain the
sphere, the stronger your Ten.
Once you've trained long enough,
you'll be able to maintain an aura
sphere for two to three days!
You should be able to reach that
stone before the day's out.
You're right! I reached it!
That was fast!
This proves he's been hard at work
on his Ten and Ren every day.
Then, we'll go back to practicing the basics.
Osu!
Gon continues to train with Bisky,
to master his special technique.
Killua has temporarily left the game
to retake the Hunter Exam.
The two boys are working
hard toward their goals.
G.I. Tutorial
Coming up, it's the
Greed Island Tutorial!
Today, we introduce the card Blackout Curtain.
Blackout Curtain
Block one instance of enemy Steal
or Fluoroscopy. (Does not stack
when used on target already
under effect of Blackout Curtain.)
[DEF][CONT]
With this card,
other players can't see inside your binder.
You can see inside my binder
whenever you want, Killua.
What?!
Continue!
Next time: Strategy x And x Scheme.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Gon-kun!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, Killua-kun!
Hey, hey, hey, hey, show me what you've got!