Edited at https://subtitletools.com
This is a tomb.
Your tomb.
I am very thankful.
Thankful for everything
that has made our meeting possible!
Zero x And x Rose
As his time was compressed to its utmost limits,
the King, his consciousness alone barely following
the afterimages of Netero's movements,
found that a single emotion reigned within him...
Complete and utter admiration for his enemy.
That's it.
He brings his hands together to start the attack.
That's the only motion he has
that far surpasses my speed.
Such wasted movement could
cost one's life in battle,
but now, it works as a weapon
that may allow him to defeat me.
Trying to guess what drove
him to do this is pointless.
It would have required choosing
a path that defies reason.
I would presume that, at one point,
he was on the verge of madness...
Five years... Perhaps ten years...
And the entire time, he focused on this alone.
I recognize that
you have dedicated an incredible amount of time
to achieve the power you have displayed.
After all that, he's barely been scratched.
Not that I expected any different.
An individual
can reach his limit after much training.
You are a rare example of one
who has transcended that limit.
Bravo.
You have earned my praise.
An insect
should not talk down to humans!
The King's strategy was quite simple.
Keep attacking.
If the only attack capable of besting him,
100-Type Guanyin Bodhisattva,
could do next to no damage,
the King had no cause for fear.
These are no more than dummy hands.
They can only move in set patterns.
If I attack from an angle that he can't
block with a move he's already used,
he'll have no choice but to reveal a new move.
Once I have verified all of the combinations,
I can find the angle of attack that will
force him to reveal another new move.
However, while he may have a limited
number of attack patterns,
the number of combinations they can
be used in may as well be infinite.
But every individual has a rhythm.
There will be an unconscious bias for,
and against, certain patterns,
and that bias naturally shapes one's identity.
If I can identify his personal rhythm,
I have a fair chance of guessing
which patterns he will select.
To find the single correct needle
among countless millions,
and thread it accurately...
is what it will take to pierce my target.
It may prove difficult...
But I will succeed.
I can accomplish it!
Old soldier, I beg of you...
Don't lose your life before I succeed!
He's laughing?
Well, I'm also enjoying myself, so I can't blame him.
No matter my attack trajectory,
he recovers immediately and moves to counter.
If I make a wrong move, his speed won't
allow me time to unleash the next Hand.
If I lose focus, he'll tear me
apart before I realize it.
This is a contest of endurance, in which
I must keep choosing correctly...
When I fail, you win.
That's probably what you're thinking, Ant King!
No matter.
I shall checkmate you shortly.
Checkmate me if you can.
I'll show you my Zero Hand!
After hundreds and thousands of hits,
the King was beginning to feel the slightest
hints of dull pain within his body.
However...
Stop the bleeding.
Then tell me my name.
You have done well for a human.
What's wrong?
If you don't act, you'll die of blood loss.
Don't make me laugh.
I'll die?
You shouldn't get cocky after
landing a lucky punch...
The battle's just begun!
You have truly earned my admiration.
I am amazed that your spirit has not flagged.
However, losing your leg was basically inevitable.
It is the consequence of using a defense that,
while not bad, was not the best choice.
After playing against Komugi, I learned
the art of anticipating enemy actions.
Your unconscious bias against certain patterns
gives me insight into the otherwise
limitless options you have.
Next, I'll take your left arm.
The ensuing fight
did not even last a minute.
This is
my life's final act!
As he released his 100-Type, Netero's resolve
heightened his physical and mental senses,
resulting in an exchange of more
than a thousand punches,
and sparking countless fireworks
between the combatants.
And then, the moment arrived.
His attacks began to show a slight inclination,
one not quite significant enough
to be called a habit or bias.
After using his body to bear the
brunt of Netero's attacks,
the King was able to find
the faint light beyond, and...
he reached it.
Are you satisfied now?
Then tell me my name.
Ant King...
You believe I cannot pray with a single arm?
A prayer comes from the heart.
If the heart achieves the correct
form, it becomes emotion...
And emotions may be manifested.
100-Type Guanyin Bodhisattva Zero Hand
was a Buddha that appeared behind an enemy,
gently enveloping the target
with an indiscriminate love.
Previously, Killua had sensed its murderous
intent from a great distance away.
Not this way!
It had left such a strong impact,
Killua had changed his direction.
The entirety of Netero's aura
was transformed into a light as
blinding as a star, and fired
with a merciless roar.
The pinnacle of individual strength.
That was a magnificent attack.
Zero wasn't enough?
I was born to be King of the Ants,
to rule over all organisms.
I represent the instinctive hope
long nurtured by my species,
and that species continues to evolve for my sake.
I stand here now, the resulting boon
of the total support of my species.
You are an individual human, not a king...
I am the King that bears his kind's fate.
That was the difference in this battle.
The Chimera Ants' long evolution
has culminated in me.
This is a feat the human race, with its
individuality, can never match.
However, humans will no longer
be used to propagate our species.
We have learned that
the strong human ego disrupts
the bonds between Ants.
Out of respect for your efforts,
I shall allow humans to permanently
survive within a special zone.
We shall reevaluate the number and
quality of humans to be used as food.
Your lonely battle was not in vain...
I shall not repeat myself again.
Tell me my name.
I am not alone.
Don't underestimate the human race, Meruem.
Meruem... That is your name.
As Netero spoke the King's name,
the King had no time to consider it,
as he watched the old man who was
supposed to be surrendering.
What is this?
Meruem, King of Ants,
you understand nothing...
of humanity's infinite potential for evolution!
It was the first time the King had felt fear.
One look at the face of this beaten old man,
who should have been waiting for death,
made it clear that his seemingly
vain words were no mere boast.
Should your heart stop beating, this will activate.
If there is a hell, I'll see you there.
I see now...
Yes... I see...
You had me in checkmate
from the start...
The bomb was both low-budget and compact,
while also proving surprisingly lethal.
With the right technology,
it was possible to quickly mass
produce these bombs.
Due to the shape of the smoke cloud,
it was called the Miniature Rose,
or the poor man's rose,
and was popular with small dictatorships.
Next time: Hostility x And x Determination.
No matter what happens,
I won't betray my friends.
I'll believe in my friends.
Thank you, Chairman Netero.