The body found at the crime scene belonged to Enforcer Yamatoya from Division 2.
The enforcement was carried out with a Dominator,
and the shooter was Division 2's own Inspector Shisui.
After carrying out the enforcement, she absconded with Yamatoya's Dominator and hasn't been seen since.
So an Inspector went missing...
Frankly, I don't know what to make of this.
We don't have much else to go on for now.
WC?
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
the creeping unknown
Akira Yamatoya
I've written up a report detailing our approach to capturing the bomber the other day,
including my observations as to what I believe we mishandled.
Please submit it to the Chief.
The emphasis of this report is not appropriate.
Your focus on an Inspector who
deviated from her duty is misplaced.
I had some choice words for you as well, Ginoza.
To think that you, an Enforcer, would point a
Dominator at a fellow Enforcer from Division 2.
Going by the book doesn't always yield the best results.
You should keep that in mind.
I don't need to take any advice from an Enforcer.
You may want to ease up a little, Inspector Shimotsuki.
Ginoza was an Inspector too.
His opinions are based on experience and can certainly come in handy.
Yayoi...
The fact that he's no longer an Inspector
only makes taking his advice less judicious.
Yeah, I think it's a good report.
Are you sure about this?
I gave you permission to utilize it,
so you won't be sanctioned, Ginoza.
I'll go question Kitazawa.
Who's conducting the Holo analysis of the crime scene?
I am.
All right. I want Hinakawa to take over.
You want Hinakawa to do it?
You can handle it, right, Hinakawa?
Yes...
Inspector Shimotsuki, I want you and the others to decode the message left at the crime scene.
I'll leave matters here to you, okay?
Inspector Tsunemori.
Kitazawa Akira.
Your Crime Coefficient suffered an acute spike
immediately following the fourth of a series of bombings.
Normally, that wouldn't be possible.
How did you keep your Psycho-Pass clear up to that point?
Answer the question.
What's so funny?
My Hue is clear.
It can't get clouded.
I've always been clear.
It's all thanks to him. He always helps me out.
He's the best.
“He”?
Why did you go so far as to use a Holo to fabricate a hostage situation just to lure out the Bureau?
Huh?
Holo? What're you talking about?
I'm talking about the hologram you used to make us think you took a hostage.
No!
That was him!
He made me clear!
I'll take on the world with him!
We're getting nowhere.
We questioned him too, but it was just more of the same.
He kept raving on and on about that imaginary accomplice of his.
He must be mentally ill.
Raving...
Since the cymatic scan didn't detect anything,
no one else could've been there.
Any news on Inspector Shisui?
It's strange.
Although it comes and goes, we've been able to track her whereabouts via GPS.
Her Dominator is still online and remains properly authenticated.
In other words, Inspector Shisui's actions are approved by Sibyl.
Chief Kasei thinks so too.
Shisui is conducting an investigation that Sibyl acknowledges. She isn't breaking any laws.
If we are to trust the Dominator's response,
that's the only possibility.
You're saying that Yamatoya's
enforcement was also appropriate?
He might've tried to run.
That's more than enough reason for enforcement.
Then why did Inspector Shisui disappear?
Circumstances might have forced her to operate in secret.
That could explain why she left a message.
WC...
Right.
Do you really think that's the case, Inspector Aoyanagi?
Well, do you have any other ideas?
What if...
What if there was someone else there? Someone outside the Bureau?
What if this third party shot Yamatoya and wrote that message?
Don't tell me you actually believe what Kitazawa said?
I'm saying it's possible.
There's no such thing as a person who can't be seen by the Sibyl System.
Searching for ghosts...
isn't in my job description.
The first thing that comes to mind is “water closet”, isn't it?
Huh? Most people would think “World Cup”.
It could be “wild-caught”, too.
Captive-bred wild animals, huh?
But that wouldn't make sense.
Says the guy whose first instinct was “restroom”.
What's the point of writing “restroom” on a wall?
If you gotta go, no one's stopping you!
Hey, I didn't write it.
You need to do more than watch if you want to ease your stress...
Inspector.
Thank you for giving me permission to
tag along when you questioned Kitazawa.
Keeping me out would've been playing by the book.
Are you referring to the Tougane Foundation?
Yes. As I'm sure you're aware,
one of Kitazawa's targets, OW Pharmaceuticals,
is run by the Touganes—
my relatives.
You don't seem the type that allows emotions to cloud your decisions,
so I decided that the benefits of taking you with me outweighed the risks.
You were a therapist, weren't you, Tougane?
So you came to that conclusion by considering my background.
Your ability to read people is impressive.
This is... amazing!
You left the Holo verification to Hinakawa
in order to capitalize on his background as a Holo designer.
That's only natural.
A boss should know her subordinates.
What is it?
The ghost exists.
I think you're right.
There's no proof.
I also know that it's not that easy to deceive cymatic scans and Drones.
Even so, Kitazawa doesn't appear to be delusional.
It's hard to think that someone like him would commit a crime on his own in the first place.
I agree. There must be someone behind him, pulling the strings.
Otherwise, it doesn't make much sense.
I-Inspector...
What's the matter, Hinakawa?
That Holo is amazing!
Yeah, the design is incredibly elaborate.
It uses a massive amount of data to define its appearance.
If you're just trying to deceive the eye,
there's no reason to use this many layers.
Is it actually possible to create such a sophisticated Holo?
If you have a model, yes.
Karanomori.
On it.
I can't find her in the Ministry of Welfare's database.
Right. It's hard to use an existing person.
They could bump into each other.
But if it's someone who's not with us anymore...
So she's a victim?
Okay. Let me try searching a different database.
There's one person with matching characteristics.
It's a girl who died in a plane crash fifteen years ago.
Not too shabby, Shou.
Hold on.
The deceased was eight years old at the time.
Yeah, that Holo doesn't really
look like an eight-year-old, huh?
Basically, this Holo was designed by
extrapolating the physical features of the deceased
into an approximated model of her
present-day appearance, now fifteen years later.
It just doesn't add up. This is way too elaborate,
no matter how you look at it.
Maybe they're the type that wants to go the extra mile?
It happens more often than you might think.
Inspector Tsunemori, where are you right now?
I'm in the Analysis Lab. Did something happen?
Kitazawa's Crime Coefficient...
has dropped so low that he's
no longer a target for enforcement.
How could this...
Yeah. To see a Crime Coefficient
that had risen to a level for enforcement
actually go down this low...
It must be unprecedented.
It's thanks to him.
He came to see me. He made me clear.
Let's check the visitors' record.
Way ahead of you. What he's saying is a lie.
According to the security footage,
his only visitor was a therapist
from the Bureau's medical agency.
There was no one else.
I'd like to speak to that therapist.
It's been a while.
Under normal circumstances,
I couldn't bring myself to face you.
Don't blame yourself. It wasn't your fault.
Was there anything unusual about
your therapy session with Kitazawa?
I simply provided my usual services.
The security cameras will confirm that, I'm sure.
They do, yes.
You look very tired. Maybe you're overworked.
You lack both sleep and relaxation.
You need some time to refresh yourself.
Maybe, but that's easier said than done.
Also, this advice is outside my field,
but smoking is harmful to your health.
Keep it in moderation.
This is unprecedented.
I never thought I'd see someone who committed such serious crimes relocated to a general medical facility.
We have no choice now that his Psycho-Pass has cleared up.
Those are the rules.
Inspector, why did you outsource his transfer to
Division 2 when we were the ones who brought him in?
Sorry. I wanted to go home early today.
Huh?!
A therapist told me that my Psycho-Pass
might get clouded, so I got a little spooked.
I'll finish the report by tomorrow.
I'll see you then.
Wait!
Once Kitazawa is in that facility,
he'll be out of our jurisdiction.
This transfer is the last opportunity to question him.
Right, and that's exactly why...
Tsunemori is probably considering Aoyanagi's feelings.
Try to understand.
I wonder if this is enough to get the smell to stick to me.
Secondhand smoke is harmful to your health!
Give it a rest. I know that.
Why don't we clean the room for a change? It'll cheer you up!
Sure, whatever.
Oh? There's a scratch on the wall.
Would you like me to contact a repairman?
A scratch?
There's no way...
Inspector! Kitazawa escaped!
It happened in the Tama ward's KT Building.
When Division 2 asked him where he made the bombs,
he showed them to a rental office in the building.
He then wounded Inspector Aoyanagi
with a knife he'd hidden in the room beforehand
and escaped with the bombs he had prepared.
He is currently at large.
Inspector Aoyanagi...
How could someone with a clear Psycho-Pass be capable of this?
We've imposed a traffic restriction in the area
and advised residents to evacuate.
Considering how little time has passed since the incident, Kitazawa is likely still close by.
There's a narrow alley behind the building that leads to an entrance to the sewers.
True, but it's locked.
He can't utilize it.
What if it was unlocked beforehand?
That's not possible.
There's a scanner at the entrance.
Anyone who might've gotten close to it would've been detected.
I see Kitazawa at the sewer entrance. Looks like it was unlocked.
Impossible! How?!
At any rate, we should follow him.
We're too far from his location.
We'll take care of it.
Is that you, Tsunemori?
You predicted Kitazawa's escape route?
It seemed unlikely to me that he could formulate an escape plan during his transfer all on his own.
Moreover, being in custody,
he couldn't have prepared a weapon himself.
There's no doubt that someone out there
acted as an accessory to Kitazawa's escape.
Someone who has the means to evade cymatic scans.
And whoever they are, they're challenging the Public Safety Bureau.
I... I...
Don't move.
Stay away from me! I planted another bomb.
If you come any closer, I'll set it off!
Just give up.
You think I'm lying, don't you?
Damn you... Always mocking me...
Don't do it!
Did he...
I've still got one more bomb.
He went to a lot of trouble to help me escape.
So I have to go.
Even you said I wasn't wrong, didn't you?!
That may have been the case...
before you pressed that button.
Crime Coefficient is 357.
Lethal Eliminator.
Inspector, please grant me permission to fire.
Forgive me, Kamui. After all the trouble you went through to make me clear...
Kamui?
Who is Kamui?
Please, tell me.
What color am I now?
What color?
All I see in you is the color of raw sewage.
That's it. I get it now.
The meaning behind that message...
How foolish the Public Safety Bureau is.
He could've been made clear again.
He still could've been saved.
Tsunemori Akane...
I had hoped that you would understand.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".