There are times when sensory overload works to purify one's Hue
even better than trying to maintain calm.
Wh-Who's there?
No!
Sorry.
I really needed an eye from an Inspector.
Crime Coefficient is 129.
A target for enforcement action.
No! No!
Your fear will end soon, Shisui Mizue.
I'll make you clear to atone for taking your eye.
I understand very well how you are suffering.
Your worries about your Hue
worsening every time a crime occurs.
Your fears toward Enforcers,
who may turn on you at any time...
The only one holding you back is yourself.
You have the strength to accept any circumstances.
But, that's precisely why you've been suffering.
Now, I'm going to release you from yourself—
from Sibyl.
Remember...
Remember the true you from long ago.
The one you've come to forget.
Target's Thread Judgment has been updated.
Crime Coefficient is 85.
Not a target for enforcement action.
Who are you?
My name is Kamui Kirito.
I want to make you and this world clear.
So clear that they're completely invisible.
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
the devil's proof
In any case, this place is quite a mess.
Excuse me for not being more organized.
Inspector, it may not be too late.
Therapy could still help you.
You mean to say that I wrote
this myself, Inspector Shimotsuki?
The scans for this area didn't detect anyone suspicious,
which means no one else entered your apartment.
You'd believe the same thing, Ginoza?
That I lost my mind and wrote this?
Then point your Dominator at me and check my Hue.
That's...
What are you doing?
Didn't you just hear him say
that no one else has been here?
There's no way that someone could've broken in.
But there's also no reason to think that the Inspector lost her mind.
So as things stand, we're faced with two impossible scenarios.
But one of them must have happened.
If the chances of each having occurred are equally probable,
Enforcers should trust the Inspector.
Tougane...
According to protocol, your family should be moved to a
safe location and put under the protection of Guard Drones.
Though I have my doubts about how necessary a measure that is.
I guess my parents will be moved to a nearby Bureau facility,
although it might be difficult for my grandma.
Difficult?
She can't move.
I see.
Take a right at the next exit.
But the Bureau is straight ahead.
There's a stop I want to make first.
You could've just dropped me off and headed back.
What business does an Inspector have at an isolation facility?
I have a duty to find out.
This is a surprise. You're not
exactly who I was expecting.
Saiga Jouji?!
You know him?
Yeah... I've seen his file.
Please excuse me, Inspector.
I don't feel well, so I'm going to head back.
That girl seems quite scared of me.
I'm sorry.
The clearer one's Psycho-Pass is,
the more they're afraid of having it clouded by others.
She must've thought that talking to me would raise her Crime Coefficient.
That's only natural for someone who's read my file.
You think so?
The outlier here is you.
You should realize that.
But my Psycho-Pass has never been clouded by talking to you, Professor Saiga.
Fair enough.
Well, then. What brings you here?
Please tell me...
Do I appear sane to you?
A message no one could've written, huh?
Right, save for one person.
True. Writing a message in your own room
without it being logged would be a simple matter.
I see.
You want to use me as a mirror, then?
What you're after is probably better
left in the hands of someone healthier.
I'm not suited for the job.
I don't know anyone better suited than you.
Good grief...
Well, then. First, tell me the answer.
You figured out what the message means, correct?
Yes. I'm convinced now that I've heard what he said.
Hey, tell me. What color am I now?
“WC” stands for “What color”.
“What color”?
That's a strange question in this day and age.
Right. If “color” suggests Hue, I don't see the point in asking humans such a thing.
A checker is all you'd need to verify that.
Let's start from the beginning.
Who is the message for?
Someone at the scene as the crime took place, or the Bureau's people who would see it later,
or...
...a question asked inwardly.
One commonality between the two messages
is that neither could've been written by anyone but the Inspector at the scene.
Inspector Aoyanagi said it'd have to be a ghost.
A ghost who lost sight of its color
and is searching for an answer about it?
Sounds like a fairy tale.
Could you tell me what you think?
A missing Inspector and messages that logically can't exist.
I'm going to investigate this case,
but I'm sure to have my work cut out for me.
So you thought you'd pay this old geezer
a visit for some help, huh?
I'm flattered.
You're the only one who can help me.
Then let's start with the irrefutable facts of the case—
the events that are rooted in reality.
The messages written on the walls,
and the decrease in Kitazawa's Crime Coefficient.
Very well. Next, let's identify the elements that are only conjecture at this point.
The existence of a person who
bypassed scans and wrote the messages,
and the existence of Kamui, who supposedly lowered Kitazawa's Crime Coefficient.
That's right.
But even if this Kamui doesn't exist,
the person who wrote the messages and the means of lowering Kitazawa's Crime Coefficient do.
It's called the Devil's Proof.
The Devil's Proof?
At this point, there's no way to prove that this ghost exists,
but at the same time, we aren't able to disprove its existence, either.
In other words, I don't know what to do.
Then if we can prove its existence, we can move forward, right?
Are you trying to negotiate with me?
Inspector Shisui from Division 2 is still missing and believed to be acting on her own.
Don't you have some thoughts on that?
After all, you felt compelled to turn yourself in
out of guilt after helping Kougami.
Do you think I'm the type to be swayed by appeals to the heart?
You know the value of trying to do all one can despite overwhelming odds.
That's the kind of person you are.
You are an excellent student.
It's all thanks to your guidance.
Care for a drink? My father left this bottle behind.
Are you joking? I'm an Inspector.
You're also human.
Are you okay?
That sounds sarcastic. How can I be okay?
I'm sorry.
It's all right.
After ten years of service as an Inspector,
there's a position waiting for you
at the Ministry of Welfare.
My life from that point on would've been so secure.
But life isn't that simple.
Are you being sarcastic?
What?
That's kind of a sore subject for me now.
I guess it must be.
I wonder where I screwed up.
When I assisted Division 1 in Kougami's escape?
Or when I shot that man?
You mean that Enforcer?
You shouldn't blame yourself.
It's an Inspector's duty to shoot a deserting Enforcer.
There are times when one's duty and one's feelings don't quite align, wouldn't you say?
Sometimes, I wonder...
if I put a lid on my feelings the moment I killed him.
A lid?
When both my joy and my sadness reach a certain point,
the lid makes sure they don't boil over.
Even when I try to feel with everything I've got,
it's as though I can only see from outside that lid...
with cold eyes.
However...
I can feel the lid start to come off while I'm holding a Dominator.
When it does, my rationality slams it shut.
Maintaining that composure is what
allows me to function as an Inspector.
Back when I shot Kitazawa, I almost enjoyed it.
I guess that's a bit of a red flag.
All I have now is this job.
I have to hold on to it.
Thanks for the drink. I enjoyed it.
We should've shared one sooner.
If I were my old self, I wouldn't be drinking in the first place.
Who's this?
Inspector Aoyanagi.
It's me, Shisui.
The investigations of the missing Inspector Shisui from Division 2
and the messages you believe were left by a third party.
I see. You want me to let Division 1 take the lead on both.
Yes. Of course, we won't neglect our usual operations as a result.
Very well. I'll allow it.
Thank you very much, Chief.
Inspector Shimotsuki, you can go.
You only want me to leave?
I'd like to speak with Inspector Tsunemori alone.
Understood. Please excuse me.
Well, then. What do you think of this case?
I have a question.
Is there someone out there who Sibyl doesn't recognize?
No such person can exist.
But with that question, you've made your thoughts clear to me.
Do you doubt my sanity?
That would be the usual judgment.
But at the same time, it's intriguing.
Can one lose their sanity when their Psycho-Pass is so clear?
If you just want to sit back and watch, be my guest.
One more thing. I have a question about Division 1's personnel.
Is the new muscle doing well?
You mean Enforcer Tougane and Enforcer Hinakawa?
Right. Tougane Sakuya.
I want you to report his status to me as often as possible.
Why?
Although it's been erased from the official documents,
he exhibited the highest Crime Coefficient we've ever had on record.
He's useful as a model case.
Be careful how you treat him.
I know this is asking a lot of each of you.
But an Enforcer died, an Inspector has disappeared,
and we can't even manage to locate one Dominator.
I hardly believe that we can just leave this case alone.
Tell us what you're really thinking, Tsunemori.
Your true concern is the ghost, right?
Don't let this get personal.
I'm going to ask Inspector Karanomori to assist us.
Please back me up on this.
This is an elevated Area Stress Level warning!
A Psycho-Pass above the regulation value has been detected inside the Daiba Tower Hotel in Minato.
I'll go. Kunizuka and Hinakawa, come with me.
Roger.
R-Roger.
Inspector on duty, please bring your Enforcers and make your way to the scene immediately.
There's no way Kamui exists.
You can go ahead and chase after an imaginary culprit...
Inspector.
Let's begin our investigation too.
I've kept a close eye out, but nothing
suspicious has turned up at the crime scene.
Suppose Kamui does exist.
He posed as a hostage to lure out the Bureau
and then killed an Enforcer and abducted an Inspector.
But why? What's his goal?
What's the meaning behind the message?
Why did he set his eyes on me?
Be careful.
You're getting too obsessed with this.
Inspector Tsunemori is fine.
It'd take more than this to cloud her Hue.
Now is the time for us to put the lessons we've
learned to good use and carry out a new policy!
This is all to improve citizens' lives!
In order to do so, we must first...
It was a wonderful speech.
Representative Masuda Koutoku.
We're from the Public Safety Bureau.
We've detected a lapse in your Hue.
Per this diagnosis, you require emergency therapy.
Please come with us.
Th-There must be some mistake!
Restrain him, Hinakawa.
This is how it should be done.
What could the Chief see in someone like her?
So Inspector Shisui is here?
Yeah. She told me so herself.
You two stay here.
You don't want to make things worse.
Understood.
No! That won't work!
Medication can't save anyone.
It changes nothing!
But...
Everyone needs to open their eyes.
They can't just rely on medicine
if they really want to be saved.
I have to save you all.
Stop it!
Crime Coefficient is 23.
Not a target for enforcement action.
The trigger will be locked.
This isn't possible...
What the hell?
Look.
Find something?
One of the Drones sent to defuse the bombs where the first message was left
was found some distance from the crime scene.
It had already been sent in for maintenance before.
The documentation says it was missing a part.
Looks like its impact absorber had been removed.
It's hard to think that it just came off by itself.
Could it be...
Inspector...
Inspector Shimotsuki? What's the matter?
Kamui! Call Kamui in here!
He can make me clear!
I want to be a savior.
I want to save everyone...
Just like Kamui does.
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".