You don't deserve to exist!
Don't!
Begone, you pitch-black soul.
Crime Coefficient is 31. Not a target for enforcement action.
The trigger will be locked.
He's the reason your grandmother is dead!
Why are you protecting him?!
I don't think Kamui had anything to do with her murder.
Are you insane? He's the one
who had her kidnapped!
I know he had the means to
obtain information on my family,
but the same can be said about
the people at the Bureau, too.
You'd put your own colleagues under the microscope before this criminal?
You're just afraid of clouding your Psycho-Pass,
so you're trying to ignore your hatred for him.
Your desire to kill won't just go away.
I haven't always been able to protect the people I care about in the line of duty.
But still...
That doesn't mean I should
give up on protecting the law.
Let's go.
Get back here, Tsunemori Akane!
Don't you dare mock me!
I won't let you disgrace my mother!
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
Stand your ground!
Stop right there, Shisui!
I can still go on, Kamui!
A neuroactive drug? She'd go that far for him?
Soon, Kamui will change the world...
for us!
Why did you decide to show me the way?
So I can judge you the right way.
You could've gone outside the law for that.
That was never an option.
I can tell that that assertion
is what's keeping you clear.
What do you expect Sibyl to do?
To bring an end to itself?
What is the right judgment in this “ideal” society where people are stripped of their humanity?
I want to see that thing judged!
There's another possibility.
You already...
Rather, all of you already know, right?
You may not get the answer you're looking for.
Will you still move forward?
I'm standing here now...
because I tried to find out why we died.
I wanted to find meaning in our undeath.
The hopes of many rest on us.
We are all suffering from the
abuse they call “treatment.”
We must find peace.
Sibyl needs to be brought to justice.
That is our only path to salvation.
People's anger makes society clear.
This is a game...
between Sibyl and us!
You could've chosen a way that didn't mean becoming
the champion of all those who hold a grudge against society.
That was never an option.
Even if I had been able to talk to you sooner.
Imagine my surprise when I discovered that
my lab rat had caused such a commotion.
Tougane Misako.
They haven't come to a conclusion yet.
Am I wrong?
Tsunemori Akane, your rights as an Inspector have just been rescinded.
Now leave, and die like the dog you are.
First, I'll go beyond those doors
and ask Sibyl if that's their answer.
Kamui?
Putting our lives on the line, we ask you:
Sibyl...
Can you see our color?
As long as I had Mother,
I didn't need anything else.
And yet...
I have to say goodbye to you, Sakuya.
I'm to join the entity that rules this society.
This is quite a wonderful thing.
You will eventually be led
to the same place yourself.
Goodbye.
Sakuya?
You belong only to me!
...I got painted black.
Whether they're latent criminals, Enforcers,
or even the Inspectors you work with, you purposely
cloud others' Hues and administer justice on them.
Why do you do that?
Because that's why I exist.
My role is to darken souls—even pure ones—
until they're pitch black.
That way, you can keep shining
bright and beautiful, Mother.
I do it all out of love for you.
Mother...
Not a target for enforcement action.
The trigger will be locked.
It's no use.
Sibyl System.
If you fancy yourselves the god of judgment, there is only one choice before you.
The one you need to overcome in order to
maintain the status quo is right in front of you!
Can you judge us?
What color are we?
What color are you?!
Crime Coefficient is over 300.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
So this is your color, is it, Tougane Misako?
I won't accept a change like this!
The time for judgment has come.
Crime Coefficient is over 300.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
So this is your color, Sibyl.
Welcome, Kamui Kirito.
Upon deliberation, we have decided to acknowledge all of you.
Additionally, as Tsunemori Akane suggested,
we will introduce a collective Psycho-Pass.
Then, we will discard any elements that increase our Crime Coefficient.
We have obtained a new awareness and perfection now.
This is what evolving means for us.
Target's Threat Judgment has been updated.
Crime Coefficient is 0.
Not a target for enforcement action.
The trigger will be locked.
There's your answer.
Kamui Kirito...
You are under arrest.
Go!
Surrender! It's all over!
Stop this!
Shisui!
No... It's not over yet.
I'll be the path for Kamui.
Thanks to the bombs that Division 3 took such care in planting,
you'll the ones meeting your end here!
Don't!
Thank you...
Kamui.
Sorry I was late.
No kidding.
But you made it this time.
Yes.
It's okay. She's still alive.
We got your lieutenant back, Aoyanagi.
We're in the middle of an operation.
Shut up and do as I say!
You're an Inspector. You should know my location!
Get over here!
Mother...
Things can't stay like this.
This is all his fault.
It's him...
The Chief's ordered me to handle a different task.
You Enforcers, follow Inspector Doumoto's orders!
“A different task”?
Crime Coefficient is 400.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
What color am I now?
Inspector Tsunemori.
It is recommended that you administer justice immediately.
Do not resist, and hand over that Dominator.
I can feel it.
Even as a part of that thing, some of them are happy to have their own color back.
Happy?
Why aren't you pointing that Dominator at Sibyl?
As a collective entity,
it encapsulates the one who wields the Dominator.
If someone else points it at them,
it may show a different color.
You...
Sibyl can't turn back now.
No matter how many brains it removes,
Sibyl's Crime Coefficient may remain high when a true judge appears someday.
This was your plan from the start?
Administer justice, Inspector Tsunemori.
Maybe that judge is actually...
the one who stands before me right now.
Stop it.
I'm not like you.
I don't live to satisfy anyone else's expectations.
If you had only found a way to do this without getting anyone hurt!
That was never an option.
Get out of there!
Desecrators!
Stop it!
I like the look in your eyes.
You know, don't you?
I was the one who killed Tsunemori Aoi.
She put up a pretty good fight for a shriveled old hag.
She kept calling your name. “Akane, Akane”...
There's another option.
You know it too, don't you?
You believe the spirit of
the law should be respected.
If the spirit—not the letter—of the law were given the opportunity to weigh the scales of justice,
it may allow that monster to become a real god someday.
This isn't possible!
There's no way you can be purer than my mother!
Why isn't your soul turning black?!
Tougane Sakuya.
You're under arrest for committing acts of rebellion
and for the murder of Tsunemori Aoi.
Inspector Tsunemori Akane.
It is gratifying that, following your suggestion,
we have solved the problems we had been discussing among ourselves throughout this ordeal.
However, with our current processing ability,
we cannot judge the collective
Psycho-Pass of this society quite yet.
In order for that day to come, we recommend that you continue to contribute to society and live a healthy life.
So you came.
Crime Coefficient is 899.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
You're no child of Sibyl.
You're pitch black.
Mother...
In the end, you and I were merely slaves to Sibyl.
I can't forgive myself for obeying you.
I can't keep myself clear unless I do this.
So she's your new slave, huh?
Do everything you can, and live only to keep Sibyl beautiful.
Someone like you who would cloud my Psycho-Pass should disappear.
I won't go any further than this.
I'll keep the secret.
No, I'll forget everything!
I don't know anything!
I trust Sibyl!
I love this society!
Tsunemori Akane!
I've been informed that your rights as an Inspector have been rescinded for disobeying orders!
Do not resist, and put your hands behind your...
Don't!
Stop it!
H-Her rights have been reinstated.
What color am I now?
As clear as crystal.
I located the escaped Enforcer Tougane Sakuya.
He died before I administered justice. That concludes my report.
Well, thanks for seeing me off.
Your Psycho-Pass is on its way to recovery.
You don't have to...
I know why it's recovering.
Being dependent doesn't quite suit me, though.
I'll come see you again!
Looking forward to it.
A man who clouds the Psycho-Pass of anyone he touches, huh?
Now that he's gone, I feel like I've missed my chance.
According to Kuwashima,
Tougane Sakuya was the one who leaked the
information on Inspector Tsunemori's grandmother.
But now we'll never find out where he got that info in the first place.
That's unfortunate.
I'll never forgive the one responsible.
Neither will I.
Now that this whole affair is over,
we have many vacancies in the system.
To tell you the truth, some of us suggested that we bring you in.
If change is what you strive for,
why don't you try instituting it from the inside?
I know you're not that interested in me.
Are you trying to provoke me?
Are you turning it down?
For now, yes.
When you decide for yourselves that it's time to oust the system,
I'll go to hell with you.
A collective Psycho-Pass...
In the not-so-distant future, there will be a society in which groups become the standard unit for judgment.
When confronted with the idea that a group isn't clear despite the clarity of each individual,
the resulting doubts and fears could lead to chaos.
People all over society may become targets in an unprecedented witch hunt.
As a result,
judgments may turn into massacres.
And you're the one who opened the door.
I'm not that pessimistic.
What comes of this may be righteous law and order, and peace and freedom.
You're as idealistic as ever.
Maybe it's idealistic, but we can't know unless we try.
It is not society that determines people's futures.
It is people who determine society's future.
That's what I believe.
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".