Enforcement mode is Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be completely eliminated.
Please exercise caution.
Are you sure, Karanomori?
Yeah. The Drones are being remotely operated by...
Crap, where'd he go?
Find him!
There he is!
To the right!
They're civilians?
I'll send you to the scrap heap, you son of a bitch!
No! Don't go after it!
Hasuike!
Oh, crap!
Run away!
The fact that the Ministry of National Defense's Drones were hijacked is shocking enough on its own,
but for them to be controlled by a horde of random people?
That's unheard of.
They probably aren't aware of what they're doing.
It's using a masking program made for border security drone operators.
That was close!
Masking program?
It converts video into a virtual Holo representation
to ensure that the operator's
Psycho-Pass doesn't get affected.
It's making the video feed from the Drones look like a video game.
If you kill without intent,
what color are you?
Is that what you're trying to say...
Kamui?
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
The game has been posted to multiple sites.
those who cast stones
When we delete it, it gets re-uploaded within a few minutes.
It's like I'm chasing my tail.
Hungry Chicken!
It's only a matter of time before all the Drones at the port get hijacked.
Can't you gain control over them and shut them down?
It's a cloud-based app, so I'd need access to the cloud server.
They've gone to a lot of trouble to mask the server's location,
so I'll need some time.
Please work as fast as you can so we can warn the players.
We need to stop this from spreading.
Dominators can only fire three Decomposer shots.
We're in a tight spot.
Yeah. In any case, we all need to get out of here.
You lured the Bureau into a game of cat and mouse.
No... There's more to it than that.
Kamui has been investigating how Dominators work.
He must know that we can disable Drones with Decomposer shots, and yet...
Does he have some other objective?
This is a warning to all Enforcers!
I forbid you to act alone!
You must coordinate with an Inspector!
The Drones are just decoys!
There's someone with a Dominator behind this!
Crime Coefficient is 322.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
Y-You...
Inspector... Shisui?
Hunting dogs have no place
in the world Kamui is creating.
How do you feel?
Very clear.
Even without a scan, I can tell that my Psycho-Pass isn't clouded at all.
That's precisely your natural state of mind.
You've been set free. Congratulations.
It's all thanks to you, Kamui.
I don't deserve such kind words.
I did a terrible thing to you.
It's okay.
I...
I never liked my eyes anyway.
User authentication: Inspector Shisui Mizue.
Dominator usage approval confirmed.
That eye is essential to me.
It's perfect.
Now this Dominator will continue to recognize me as you.
I'm glad that my eye became yours.
If it can be of use to you,
I want you to use my body as you please.
Thank you.
For now, let's proceed with our plan.
His goal isn't to kill Enforcers?
Considering each incident so far,
there's only one thing it could be.
Now I see.
So what you're actually after is...
Collecting Dominators.
He's been recording the progression of Inspector Tsunemori's Psycho-Pass?
He's been at it since he started here.
Every single day?!
How creepy!
Mika.
Where did you wander off to while your senior Inspector is in trouble?
Huh?
What in the...
Inspector Shisui activated two Dominators,
and they're heading in different directions?
It means someone else is using one of those Dominators in her place.
That doesn't make sense.
But there's no other way to explain it.
When Inspector Shimotsuki is ready, we'll go back them up.
Don't.
As long as our enemy has Dominators,
Enforcers need to stay away.
Aikawa!
Tsunemori!
Ginoza!
You all right?
We can't get through to the Inspectors from Division 3.
What should we do?
Karanomori.
Please send us the location of both the Dominators registered to Inspector Shisui.
Are you going after them?
All of you should prioritize your own safety and get out of here.
Don't tell me you're going alone!
Dominators can't kill Inspectors.
I'll have to capture Kamui on my own.
She's delusional!
I can't believe she's calling off Enforcers and moving herself to the front lines.
She thinks she's so great just because her Psycho-Pass is kinda clear.
I hope it gets clouded.
What am I saying?
That's reckless!
Those Dominators are surrounded by Drones!
Isn't it possible that the cloud server hosting that game is right in front of our eyes?
You're right.
Why didn't I think of that?!
If they're being controlled directly from the Drone
management server at the Ministry of National Defense...
Bingo!
Now, crack the game program and terminate the Holo generated by the Psycho-Pass shielding program.
And show the players what's really going on?
That's the fastest route.
I'd expect no less from a Ministry of National Defense program.
Even terminating the Holo display
seems to be quite the task.
I-I'll do it.
You can do it, Hinakawa?
Yeah... I have to help Akane.
I'll back him up.
Defeat the Evil Witch!
Akane, take a right at the hangar at the end of that path.
There are a few less Drones down there.
Eight playable Holos,
each constructed with fifteen different layers.
Analyze them quickly!
I-I'm on it.
Sugou!
Get up!
What the... Why can't I shoot?
Enforcement mode is Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be completely eliminated.
Please exercise caution.
What the hell?!
Inspector!
Tougane?
Inspectors are supposed to do the babysitting.
Ginoza!
Don't make us do your job.
More importantly, what just happened?
That's a safety mechanism that
keeps them from shooting each other.
The guns are designed to lock when multiple Drones of the same type
are within a certain shooting range.
You know this place like the back of your hand.
Yes. I've got a plan.
I might be able to incapacitate most of the Drones.
“Might"? And if you fail?
I'll die, that's all. It won't set you back.
Give me the details, Enforcer Sugou. I'll do it.
Tsunemori!
This is Shinjou from Division 3!
Everyone's dead. Please help me!
Calm down. We're headed your way now.
Crime Coefficient is 311.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Fuck!
Enforcer Shinjou!
Come in!
Shinjou!
Sugou, fill me in already!
That's an order!
An order?
Tsunemori, there's no need for you to...
Now! Before there are any more victims!
We need to get to the operations testing site up ahead.
Let's go.
Don't get ahead of yourself, Tsunemori!
Even under these circumstances,
she's as clear as the sky.
And that's precisely why I want to color her black.
The Drones are all focusing on Inspector Tsunemori.
We'll use that to lure them in here.
What's this?
Drone firearms.
That's it, Akane. Keep it up.
What's going on?
Enforcement mode is Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be completely eliminated.
Now!
Oh, crap! Game over!
There are five Dominators in Inspector Shisui's vicinity.
Kamui should be there too.
I think most of the Drones around here
have been taken care of.
Given their current course,
they may be planning to escape by sea.
What are you going to do with that thing?
It's very likely that Dominators don't work on Kamui.
Are you trying to cloud your Psycho-Pass?
Call it a good luck charm.
What's going on?
"Continue"? All right!
They actually tampered with
Public Safety's systems, too...
This just keeps getting worse.
I-It's...
It's done!
We're sending it your way, Shion!
You rock, Shou!
All right. Use it on the game program right away, and terminate the Holo being displayed.
Wait! Won't that show the players what's been happening in real life?
Do you have any idea how many people's Psycho-Passes will get clouded?!
Dealing with that is your job.
What do you think will happen if we just sit back and let them take control of every Drone?
This isn't how the Bureau operates!
You can't solve every problem by following the manual.
My Dominator's out of juice!
I'm sorry, Enforcer Ginoza.
Just shut up and run.
Okay!
Let's give it a whirl!
What the hell is this?!
The Drones have stopped moving!
All right!
An Area Stress warning has been issued.
I told you this would happen!
There's no way we can deal with all this!
Don't whine. You're an Inspector, aren't you?
Let's move out, Inspector Shimotsuki.
But...
Group Psycho-Pass pollution, huh?
It's as if Sibyl's weaknesses are being exposed one by one.
Kamui!
To think that the Dominator doesn't even recognize him...
A ghost...
Crime Coefficient is 28.
Not a target for enforcement action.
The trigger will be locked.
So this is your color. Remarkably clear, as I thought.
Who are you?
What are you after?
Inspector Tsunemori.
When judgment comes, I want you to see it with your own eyes.
Judgment?
Wait!
I know you can't shoot.
Stop!
Tougane!
Leave the dirty work to us.
No!
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".