Inspector Aoyanagi, come in.
Inspector Aoyanagi!
The medicine they give you here modulates your Hue,
but in doing so, it slowly drains you of what makes you feel alive.
I will free you from this false cure...
just like Kamui does.
If you help me, I'll make it worth your while!
I'll put in a good word for you
at the Ministry of Welfare!
Just call Kamui in already!
Inspector Shimotsuki, please bring Representative Masuda to me.
I'll handle the interrogation.
Because you're unwilling to defer to someone who doubts Kamui's existence?
It's because we should question him
based on the evidence left at the scene.
Understood.
It's hard to think that this is a coincidence, but we need some hard evidence.
Otherwise, we'll make the same mistake we made with Kitazawa.
Take a look at this.
This space was left open when the
Drone's impact absorber was removed.
Don't you think a person could easily fit in there?
The Drone was discovered about two kilometers away from the crime scene.
Although it's quite rare, Drones can malfunction.
But if this was a result of human tampering, there should've been a record of it.
In that case, Kamui must have a
means of doctoring a Drone's logs.
So you're sticking with the assumption that he exists?
Will you not explore this under that premise?
No, I'll play along until you're satisfied.
This was a calculated maneuver.
We're left trying to dig up some definitive proof while Kamui is out there making his next move.
There's no more doubt in my mind.
Kamui does exist.
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
in view of the end of days
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
Who are you?
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
the salvation of job
No luck accessing either the security cameras or the scanners.
The entire building is dead.
Has anything like this
ever happened before?
The only cases I can think of are
big disasters like fires breaking out.
This doesn't exactly fit the bill, though.
Hey.
The Area Stress Level has
climbed into the warning range.
What on earth is the Inspector doing?
These are your natural selves, as you were born.
Do you feel the joy of being alive?
That's right. Good.
I understand your pain all too well.
Rather than having your minds healed,
you're on the verge of being killed by false medication.
Let the stress in. It's the proof
that we are alive in this world.
Feel!
Feel the pain!
Feel your heart beating!
Feel your life!
It's so great to be alive.
Let's request assistance.
In any case, we're sidelined
without an Inspector present.
Oh, I'm well aware.
I'll handle the assistance request from Division 2.
Thanks. Given the timing,
please make sure you use discretion.
This isn't a big deal.
I'm sure the people who got
trapped inside have just panicked.
It's certainly easy for confusion and fear
to spread within mental care facilities, but...
Do you think that even something like this is too overwhelming for a tenderfoot Inspector?
Huh?
I'm sure you're quite pleased now that
someone else has mentioned Kamui, aren't you?
It's rather the opposite.
Thanks for bringing him in.
Leave the rest to me.
And be careful.
You sure are confident.
Why would Aoyanagi go to a
mental care facility, of all places?
I don't know, but let's focus
on the interrogation for now.
Thank you for your cooperation, Representative Masuda Koutoku.
Who is Kamui?
That doesn't ring any bells.
I hear you wanted us to call Kamui in.
I don't recall.
You relied on someone named Kamui
in order to keep your Psycho-Pass clear.
How did you communicate with him?
Where did you make contact?
So suddenly he's got nothing to say?
This is strange.
Don't move.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry. He... He ordered me to do it.
You are all alive!
Everyone... Everyone is alive!
Life is wonderful.
This is terrible.
No.
Don't do it.
But...
Don't worry. Just trust me.
I'm going to save them all.
Because it's my job.
What's the situation?
We still don't know what's
going on inside the facility.
There haven't been any incidents reported nearby, but the Area Stress Level keeps going up.
It's almost certain that
this place is the source.
We should force it open
from the outside.
No. We need to pinpoint the cause
of the stress before taking any action.
If we carelessly release them,
the situation might get worse.
So our only option is to find a way
to make contact with someone inside.
I narrowed the Area Stress check
down to the building's immediate vicinity.
See for yourselves.
It's way over the emergency threshold.
I wouldn't be surprised if everyone
in there were a target for enforcement.
Someone else mentioned Kamui's name.
In addition, one of the Drones sent to defuse the bombs had been moved and was missing a part.
This could be a breakthrough for the Devil's Proof.
Is that what you're implying?
The man we brought in is hiding something.
Can you help me, Professor?
I want to be a savior!
I want to save people, just like Kamui does!
That's enough!
So this representative, Masuda,
experienced a clouding in his Hue
before giving his speech.
And you're certain of that?
Yes.
After the speech, Inspector Shimotsuki took him into custody.
It's often the case that this sort of person's Hue
will consistently worsen under like circumstances.
Look into the days he gave speeches over the past several months.
His phone records, too.
A savior? Don't make me laugh.
You're just a crazy latent criminal. Either surrender now and be sent to a facility, or be judged where you stand.
Crime Coefficient is 76.
Not a target for enforcement action.
The trigger will be locked.
Why?!
Good. Keep it up.
You of all these people should
understand very well what I'm saying.
Fuck... Why is this...
Crime Coefficient is 112.
A target for enforcement action.
No! Not him!
I'm detecting the use of a Dominator.
Is Inspector Aoyanagi the user?
There's a target for enforcement inside.
What should we do?
Nothing.
We'll await contact from Inspector Aoyanagi.
If we act on our own and something goes wrong, it'll be on my shoulders.
We've received a response from the Analysis Lab.
They've identified the device Representative Masuda
was contacting one day before each of his speeches.
Who's the user?
That's still unknown,
but the device is currently at
the mental care facility in Shibuya.
The place where Division 2 requested assistance?
That means...
Kamui is there!
Inspector Aoyanagi. We're currently standing by in front of the facility.
Please report back with the status inside.
To those who use force to suppress those trying to live healthy lives:
Heed my words!
What?!
I know full well what becomes of those who have
all their stress taken away by erroneous medication.
Eustress deficiency.
I no longer responded to stimuli, and I felt numb inside.
I was ready to give up on my own life.
The reality of destructive mental care that sucks
the joy of living out of people must be overthrown!
And I will save them, just as Kamui has saved me!
Kamui?!
Not again... What is this, some kind of shared psychosis?!
He's even bringing up a stupid
urban legend like eustress deficiency.
An urban legend?
Did you hear back from Inspector Aoyanagi?
Not yet, even though
she was online at one point.
Couldn't the man we just heard have restrained everyone?
If so, we should subdue him and rescue them right away.
But no one's called for anything like that yet.
Kamui again...
What the hell is going on?
Hinakawa, come in.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Look around for anyone with an active Holo in the area.
What kind of Holo?
I don't know if it's the same woman from the Kitazawa case or not,
but you're the only one who can figure it out.
Please.
U-Understood.
I see. Considering that the Holo
we saw was abnormally elaborate,
Kamui could very well have
a strong obsession with them.
Like the clothing a ghost would wear?
If this is all part of Kamui's plan,
then what could he be after?
Why is he going this far?
No, not here.
No, not here...
No. No...
Excuse me. What are you doing?
I... I got an order from Inspector Tsunemori...
Don't act on your own. I'm the commanding officer here.
But...
Division 3 will take over from here.
Just follow our instructions.
What?! By what authority do you...
These orders come straight from Chief Kasei.
We'll carry out enforcement immediately.
Chief Kasei took me off? Why?
Yes, that's right.
Scatter the crowd and don't let any media organizations into the area.
It'll be problematic if a groundless delusion
such as eustress deficiency is allowed to spread.
Though no one in this society
would believe in such a thing.
There's one common thread
between this case and the first one.
They separated and isolated
an Inspector from her team.
Kamui's targeting Inspectors?
Or maybe not Inspectors themselves, but rather...
Dominators instead.
It wouldn't be possible under normal circumstances, but it may not have been Inspector Shisui who shot Enforcer Yamatoya.
It was Kamui?
Someone was somehow able to use a Dominator without authorization.
That case itself was an experiment for that.
That's enough, Tsunemori.
Your Psycho-Pass will get clouded!
A ghost...
Even if we can't see it,
we can still follow its trail.
Okay, commence operation!
The Public Safety Bureau. How foolish.
I am... an Inspector.
Elevated Area Stress Level
m 0 0 l 100 0 100 100 0 100
Special Warning Issued
An elevated Area Stress Level hazard warning!
There's no way that anyone inside
can sustain a stable Psycho-Pass now.
An experiment...
Kamui is trying to learn
how to use a Dominator.
But he's already shot one Enforcer.
If being surrounded by Bureau officers was also part of his design,
his goal this time isn't to pull the trigger himself.
Are you saying that he wants someone else to shoot, then?
With such a roundabout way of doing things,
who the hell is he trying to...
In order to protect citizens and the law, I will...
They shot through the wall?
That's the Bureau's new armament, the Assault Dominator.
When walls hinder access to the crime scene,
we've got this to fall back on.
Looks like it went extremely well.
"Extremely well"?
You think something that can elevate the stress of those inside
so severely as to trigger Eliminator mode is a good thing?
Kunizuka...
I'm just following orders.
You're certain the one you shot was the culprit?
I don't know. I just shot the one
with the higher Crime Coefficient.
Help!
We're the victims!
Crime Coefficient is 322.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
What the hell is this number?!
Everyone is a target for enforcement!
Don't let them escape!
How terrible...
Inspector Shimotsuki!
What can I do? This case no longer belongs to Division 1.
We have nothing to do with it.
Stop!
What are you...
What are you doing?!
I now know the answer.
Inspectors can be judged by the Dominators too.
Thank you.
With your help, we were able
to move one step forward.
Let's go.
I've prepared our escape route.
I wonder what color I am now.
When I met you,
I was a walking corpse whose life had
lost its color due to eustress deficiency.
But I'm different now.
I was finally able to get my presence back.
Please let me stay here.
I've done all I can.
You can change the world.
I'm glad that I met you, Kamui.
Thank you.
Can you see it?
The color of the blood we shed?
Why don't you tell me: What color are we?
It can't be... Aoyanagi...
Inspector Tsunemori.
This question may be directed toward all of society.
All of society?
Asking each of us to question our color. As well as...
Sibyl... What color are you?
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".