Psycho-Pass treatment has evolved to the next level!
If your Hue takes a turn for the worse due to stress or mental disorders,
you could find yourself at risk of becoming a latent criminal and end up relocated to a rehabilitation facility.
However, with the new psychotropic medicine Lacouse, you have nothing to fear!
however
Lacouse
This is Lacouse!
Lacouse is available in six varieties, each designed to treat a specific type of stress that may be clouding your Hue.
Please give it a try!
Its unique ingredient, Admin, powerfully blocks undesirable mental substances.
This is Lacouse! Please give it a try!
Lacouse is all new. Please give it a try!
With Lacouse, you can keep your Psycho-Pass clear!
This is Lacouse!
This is Lacouse! Please give it a try!
At precisely 6 PM this evening,
someone posted a video claiming responsibility for this attack on a major web-streaming site,
which matches the MO
of the last three incidents.
We're being deceived by the Sibyl System.
Right after the explosion, a cymatic scan of the crime scene detected an individual whose Hue had suddenly clouded.
“A system that makes everyone happy”?
Don't make me laugh.
Getting pigeonholed and allowing our futures to be determined by a machine
is no way for humans to live.
The government is treating its citizens like cogs in a machine!
Suddenly clouded?
And OW Pharmaceuticals, the distributor of Lacouse,
Karanomori, run a match between
that individual and the man in the video.
is simply milking this demented system.
If we extrapolate his vocal cords via his bone structure
and overlay the result on the voice in the video...
Bingo.
The man's name is Kitazawa Akira.
He's an on-site supervisor for a demolition company.
A demolition worker...
So he's an expert on explosives.
Please superimpose Kitazawa's
movements over the detailed area map.
Roger.
We'll let the Drones handle the on-site inspection.
Inspector Shimotsuki, please change our route.
Understood.
This is where Kitazawa's employer stores its equipment.
A camera caught him entering
the building 20 minutes ago.
He also hinted in the video
that he's got more bombs.
Things couldn't be worse.
Yeah. With the citizens already on edge,
the Area Stress Level could rise in an instant.
We'll be coordinating with Division 2.
Ginoza.
Please assist Inspector Shimotsuki.
Roger.
Enforcer Tougane, Enforcer Hinakawa.
Sorry you have to start off with such a demanding case.
Try to be careful out there.
Understood.
Dominator Portable Psychological Diagnosis and Suppression System has been activated.
User authentication: Inspector Tsunemori Akane.
Affiliation: Public Safety Bureau,
Criminal Investigation Department.
Dominator usage approval confirmed.
You are a valid user.
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
in view of the end of days
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
the scales of justice
Inspector.
Why are we just standing by instead of moving in?
Why do you think that Kitazawa's Psycho-Pass
didn't get clouded by any of the previous bombings?
Kitazawa is a supervisor at demolition sites.
Making bombs wouldn't exactly
be stressful for someone like him.
Well, it's not quite the same
when done in service of his job.
No one asked you, Enforcer.
Normally, one's Psycho-Pass would be
exacerbated by planning a terrorist attack.
There's no way to keep one's Hue clear while preparing an array of bombs.
But in this case, Kitazawa's Psycho-Pass
only dropped after the bombs were set off.
In other words, he previously had
some means of keeping his Hue clear.
Is that important right now?
Will that information help us resolve this case?
Inspector Tsunemori.
I'm in favor of moving in as well.
This is the Public Safety Bureau.
We are issuing an Area Stress Level warning.
The Area Stress Levels have gotten
precariously high since these bombings started.
To all residents:
Please stay indoors and focus on managing your stress.
We need to take care of this bomber
before new latent criminals are created.
I repeat: This is...
But...
We shouldn't waste time.
Division 2, move in!
Please wait!
We should move with them, Inspector.
No.
Why?!
Please listen, Inspector Aoyanagi.
These serial bombings have yielded no casualties.
I can only conclude that the culprit has taken care to avoid harming citizens.
That being the case, what could he be after?
If you consider the potential fallout of an explosion,
one thing you can count on is an elevated Area Stress Level.
It's awfully cold.
It's also a sure bet that the
Public Safety Bureau will pursue the culprit.
Does that mean...
It's very likely that the culprit is provoking us
and is waiting in ambush inside.
Looks like you were right, Inspector Tsunemori.
Let's go, Yamatoya!
Roger!
Keep your guard up, Inspector Shimotsuki.
You don't have to tell me that!
Don't let him get away!
It's on autodrive?
Watch out!
Just a decoy.
Are you okay, Inspector?
Thank you.
Inspector!
I-I'm enforcing justice!
Wait! He's got a hostage!
Inspector Tsunemori!
Take a look at this guy's back.
Tougane and Hinakawa, I want you to go after the culprit.
I'll handle this.
What?
Shouldn't it be the other way around?
She should be using the Enforcers as a shield!
Target's Threat Judgment has been updated.
Enforcement mode is Destroy Decomposer.
Target will be completely eliminated.
Please exercise caution.
Are you okay, Inspector?
We're going after the culprit. Move out!
Excuse me for worrying about you...
Enforcers' hands are tied without an accompanying Inspector.
I'm sure you're aware of that!
The culprit is currently on Route 20 heading toward Shinjuku.
We'll limit his escape routes and
drive him into the Yoyogi Park area.
Inspector Shimotsuki, please work with the Enforcers to help residents evacuate the neighborhood.
What, are you afraid that my
Psycho-Pass will get clouded?
Don't underestimate me.
I have a year and a half of experience as an Inspector under my belt.
I'm plenty capable of keeping my Psycho-Pass clear.
She sure is confident.
This is Shisui from Division 2.
The situation has changed.
It appears the culprit has released
the woman he was holding hostage.
The timing doesn't seem right.
I agree with you.
Karanomori.
Right here. I was wondering when you'd call.
Oh? Now this is a surprise.
The hostage that's walking away from the culprit...
No such person exists.
She's a hologram?
This is probably...
A trap?
Yes.
Despite the fact that Kitazawa was an excellent student,
his path to elite status hit a dead end when his occupational aptitude assessment revealed that his Hue was easily clouded.
Considering his past, that video,
and his actions at the warehouse,
I'd say he's trying to retaliate against society...
by attacking the Public Safety Bureau.
The most effective way to eliminate us, his pursuers,
is to draw us in by releasing his hostage.
All that awaits us once we catch up to her...
is a bomb.
So he set this trap in order lure us out into the open where he could kill us?
Inspector Shisui, please locate and extract the bomb, and leave the culprit to us.
Understood. Consider it done.
Crime Coefficient is 302.
A target for enforcement action.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
Aim carefully and eliminate the target.
Stay back!
Please, no!
Mommy!
Oh, no!
Inspector?
Hinakawa, get back!
A-Are you okay?
Wait!
It's not too late for him.
299.
I see. 299, huh?
Tsunemori sure is something.
That's...
Let's go.
We'll back up the Inspector.
What's the matter?! Why don't you just shoot already if that's what's right?!
I won't.
If I shoot you now, this gun will kill you.
Attention, please.
This is the Criminal Investigation Department,
part of the Public Safety Bureau.
Please evacuate immediately!
We are currently providing evacuation assistance in response to an emergency situation.
This way!
Please don't panic!
Please follow instructions and evacuate.
Why do I have to do this?
What are you doing, Ginoza?
Our goal is to eliminate the culprit.
Tsunemori is...
willing to take a chance.
Could you overlook her foolishness for the time being?
You've changed.
It's only natural after having
worked with her for so long.
Ginoza, an Enforcer from Division 2 is heading to the adjacent building.
Wait!
What the heck is going on?
So that's what she meant by “299”?
She's unbelievable! Is this really
appropriate behavior for an Inspector?
If you just avert your eyes and
forsake those you don't understand,
you'll come to regret it someday.
Recognize what's happening before your eyes as fact.
That's a shortcut to becoming an adult, missy.
S-Stay back!
We're controlled by the society that Sibyl created!
Doesn't that bother you?!
Our potential and our future are decided for us!
Only a select few reap any benefit from the system!
Does that mean the rest of us aren't needed?!
No, it doesn't.
You are needed.
And so are the bombs that you made.
What are you saying, Inspector?!
Society doesn't always do what's right.
That's precisely why it's up to us
as individuals to live virtuous lives.
I...
Your expertise and desire to right a wrong are both needed in this society.
Society is comprised of individuals.
The virtue of the individual is ultimately what makes the society itself virtuous.
Your sense of justice is noble.
You're not just a cog in the machine.
Even if society oppresses you,
as long as you have the spirit to resist,
you are a human being.
Tougane...
What the hell's taking them so long?
Crime Coefficient is over 140.
An Enforcer registered at the CID.
This target has Enforce At Will status.
Put the gun down!
Ginoza.
What on earth is going on?
Crime Coefficient is 299.
Target's Threat Judgment has been updated.
Enforcement mode is Non-Lethal Paralyzer.
Aim calmly and disable the target.
I'm enforcing justice.
It was thanks to all of you.
Thank you very much.
An enforcement target's Crime Coefficient rarely goes down.
To think that you'd build your strategy around it all the same...
Sibyl had decided he wasn't worthy of living!
And yet...
But in the end, Sibyl reversed that decision.
We need to find out how he was able to
keep his Hue clear while making those bombs.
I made a judgment call with
the future in mind. That's all.
Inspector.
You're...
wrong.
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
Don't tell me... It's a Holo?!
The fact that something is false
does not invalidate its existence.
You all failed to recognize that.
That's why...
I am here.
Crime Coefficient is 48.
An Inspector registered at the CID.
Warning: Any rebellious conduct by Enforcers
will be recorded and reported to headquarters.
Stop...
That's right. It was a new start.
The start of my own internal struggle to determine who I am.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.