A train is arriving. Please stand clear.
Train A1971 suddenly started accelerating.
It's out of control.
A runaway train?
At this rate, we've only got a few minutes before it crashes into the train ahead of it.
Evacuate all trains in service immediately.
I want all those passengers out of there now!
All trains have been brought to the emergency station.
Okay. Switch the tracks back.
It's rejecting the signal!
A1971 is headed to the emergency station!
Let's get started.
We will be stopping momentarily for a quick car inspection.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
Please stand by and remain on the train.
Decomposer.
Target will be completely eliminated.
The wastewater facility in the subway's emergency station has been destroyed.
They used one runaway train to gather the rest of them together
and isolated them using wastewater
from the neighboring area.
Fortunately, the shelter is keeping them from being submerged, but...
...because they can't drain the water, the passengers are trapped.
Kamui and his group have
trapped themselves as well.
Why would they do that?
We've taken too much backbone out of the MLIT.
To think that they still haven't been able to drain the wastewater...
I see.
So we kept proof of the scandal in case they try to take our place again, did we?
As a result, it looks like more than 500
passengers have become Kamui's hostages.
His goal? This?
Surely not. If he merely wanted to reproduce the Season of Hell, we would've been able to take care of him by now.
Division 3 can't handle them all on their own.
Where do you think you're going?
This is an emergency.
We need to analyze the situation
and come up with a plan right away.
From the moment a member
of your family became a hostage,
you were rendered unfit to participate in this investigation.
That's my decision to make.
I'm the Inspector here.
But this is Chief Kasei's decision.
Step aside, please.
It's not my fault. It's not my fault.
It's not my fault. It's not...
That's right.
Feel the pain of knowing you're responsible for the death of someone precious to you.
Paint yourself black, Tsunemori Akane.
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
Crime Coefficient is 148.
A target for enforcement action.
gauging the soul
Start with those who are likely to go over 300.
Knock them out with Paralyzers.
They're randomly shooting passengers?!
How terrible!
I'm counting on you since the Chief has ordered Akane on standby.
Right. I'm the only one they've got.
I'm in charge of Division 1 now.
It's okay. I simply acted according to Sibyl's will.
There's no way my Psycho-Pass will get clouded.
D-Dominators don't work on Kamui.
H-How are we going to...
Still, we can't just sit back and let this happen, can we?
If only we knew more about his goal.
Kamui is seeking revenge against the Tougane Foundation.
This incident must relate to that somehow as well.
It's true that both Kitazawa's crime and the barricade incident are connected to the Tougane Foundation.
But what grounds are you saying it's revenge?
Take a look.
It was the Tougane Foundation
that pushed for Kamui's surgery.
They used him in a clinical trial
for the benefit of the Foundation.
Surgery... A multi-body brain transplant...
With that in mind, I suspected that Kamui harbored a grudge against the Tougane Foundation.
It's going all over the place.
With this much data flying around...
I suspected that might be what they were up to.
A ruling will always be handed down for each crime using information captured by the Dominators.
If enough are being used at the same time,
the amount of data becomes massive,
which should overload the normal processing routes.
When that happens, a bypass route
appears on the network for them to use.
Security isn't as tight on our backup data channels.
So they wanted to trigger the bypass.
We've located the bypass.
This may actually work!
Stay on top of it.
You gathered Dominators in order to locate the Sibyl System.
Isn't that right, Kirito?
I thought I ordered you to stand by.
I don't think we can afford to
sit on our hands in this situation.
Fair enough. I'll assign you a different task, then.
Assassinating Kamui Kirito.
Correct.
I knew it.
What?
Given the nature of his crimes and
his connection to the Season of Hell,
it's obvious that the Tougane Foundation isn't his target.
He wants to know...
what color Sibyl is.
You want eliminate Kamui right away
because he's about to come in contact with Sibyl.
You've always enjoyed sticking your nose where it doesn't belong, haven't you?
As it stands, he'll probably find his way
to us within an hour, as you've guessed.
Of course, I don't intend to let that happen.
I ordered the first responders from Division 3 to place
bombs above the area where the culprits are holed up.
What are you thinking?!
There are more than 500 hostages down there!
Humans are very unlikely to keep their Psycho-Passes clear while being hunted in such an ill-fated environment.
Most of them are probably latent criminals by now.
That doesn't mean we can just let them die!
This is a farce!
This isn't up for discussion.
And it happens to be your duty.
Take command of the detonation.
Finish it with your own hands.
Your motives are obvious.
You just want Kamui dead.
I'm doing this to protect society and Sibyl.
Unless we put an end to Kamui's attempts to
destroy order, many more people are going to die.
Also...
I received an unfortunate report just a moment ago.
Your grandmother Tsunemori Aoi's body was found in the warehouse district.
It appears that she was restrained and beaten to death.
A cruel crime, indeed.
I'll entrust the last trigger to you.
Protect the society that we call home.
I have faith in you, Inspector Tsunemori.
Kill Kamui, Tsunemori Akane.
Realize how powerless you are.
Give in to the desire to kill,
and become your own person again.
Let it paint you black.
Are you going to kill him?
Blow it all up?!
And there's no need to watch facilities
connected to the Tougane Foundation?
I was not made aware of those orders!
This is our top priority.
Have your Division stand by until further instructed.
Why the...
Time is of the essence here.
What's going on?
I don't know. Maybe I should do it.
This isn't like you.
You said it yourself, remember?
“The law doesn't protect people. People protect the law."
You believed in that enough to try to stop me, didn't you?
Yes, I did. But that was then.
Well, I guess I don't personally
have a leg to stand on.
Sibyl can't judge Kamui,
but we have to stop him.
This is the only way.
You're wrong.
There's always another way.
The alternatives just haven't materialized yet.
All the pieces should already be in place.
You're just hesitating.
I can't afford to fail.
But...
Isn't it worth taking a chance?
Don't let them win.
Thank you.
What're you...
Kuwashima Kouichi.
I have a favor to ask.
Is this Kamui Kirito?
This is Tsunemori Akane from the
Public Safety Bureau, CID, Division 1.
How's Kouichi doing?
He agreed to cooperate after I talked to him.
Sibyl is trying to bury you down there with the other passengers.
We'll find a way out before that happens.
In that case, all the Inspectors and Enforcers will stand in your way.
Is that supposed to scare me?
Kamui Kirito.
If you release your hostages, I'll grant your wish.
I've sent you a map of the underground.
Come to the location I've marked.
There, I'll...
What are you thinking?
The omnipotence paradox.
Kamui's goal is to judge the Sibyl System.
You should let it happen.
As a result, you'll be
able to judge him as well.
You've been perfecting your judgments by
taking in criminally asymptomatic people—
the ones you cannot judge.
However, a new exception has appeared.
Kamui exists as a collective entity, not as an individual.
Sibyl has no choice but to accept the concept that makes him valid in order to judge him.
You don't know what you're talking about.
That would require us to measure his Psycho-Pass as a collective entity.
But if that happens...
...Sibyl, as a collective entity itself,
will also become judicable.
That was his goal.
By turning himself into a threat to society,
he creates a situation where you have no choice but to acknowledge a collective Psycho-Pass,
which then creates a paradox.
After all that, he judges you.
That's all the more reason why we can't allow him to get closer to Sibyl.
So you'll kill him without judging him?
By denying your own perfection?
You're too focused on the immediate objective to recognize the bigger picture.
How will society be affected once a
collective Psycho-Pass is acknowledged?
Judging people as groups despite individual clarity will have its risks.
That much I understand.
But if you confront the problem you've been avoiding,
you will be able to evolve as well.
Contrary to what you seem to believe,
if you feign ignorance and choose the easy way out by killing Kamui,
then there's no future for the System.
I'm tired of listening to your pretentiousness.
If you're going to act on your own,
I'll rescind your authority as an Inspector.
We'll have to think about removing you from society as well.
I'm saying your individual opinion doesn't matter, Tougane Misako!
Sibyl System...
You are allowed to exist in this society due to your ability to cast an equal and perfect judgment.
Now that there is an error in that perfection, one could say that the value of your existence has been called into question.
You don't know what you're talking about.
What will allow you to continue
to serve a purpose in society?
Think over that carefully as a group.
Are you really sure about this?
Yes. Do it.
Roger!
This is for Aikawa, you bastards!
Die!
What's going on?
They aren't detonating.
Since the Bureau doesn't have its own explosives,
employing them requires you to use
what's been seized from criminals.
There's only been one case that involved bombs in the past few months.
Kitazawa's bombs were fashioned such
that we could override and control them.
Isn't that wonderful?
Kamui can see through everything.
That's exactly why he can make everyone clear.
All we need to do now is keep the Bureau here.
Kamui will make the world clear before long.
DRAINING WATER
The water level has fallen!
They must've used a different wastewater facility.
The hostages have been released?
Roger that.
We'll make our way there to apprehend the culprits.
Inspector Shimotsuki!
No, this can't be...
Victim   : Tsunemori Aoi
Death from hemorrhagic shock resulting
from external injuries caused by physical
trauma
It's not my fault... It's not...
Inspector, what are you doing?!
Huh?
What's the matter?
Wh-Where's Enforcer Tougane?
Inspector.
Chief Kasei told me you'd be here.
Please let me come with you.
Why?
You must already know the connection between Kamui and Tougane Misako.
My mother created that monster.
The responsibility for correcting that falls to me, her son,
even if it means I have to bloody my own hands.
Are you going to kill Kamui?
Enforcer Kougami would have done it.
Let's go, Inspector.
Why don't you drop the act, Tougane?
The multi-body brain transplant your mother had performed on Kamui—
I know a certain system that
makes use of the same concept.
Of course, she must've known about it too.
But no one in this society
should be privy to that information...
TOUGANE MISAKO
except for the criminally asymptomatic.
If Tougane Misako was criminally asymptomatic, she must've been taken in by the system.
And, it's highly likely that she's been forced to oversee this whole matter.
In other words, the one who's acting as
Chief Kasei right now is Tougane Misako.
I have no idea what you're talking about, Inspector.
I read up on your background.
Your real file's been hidden this whole time.
(TOUGANE SAKUYA)
Affiliation
CID Division 1
Public Safety Bureau
Occupation
Enforcer
DoB
Age
Blood Type
It all started with Inspector Shimotsuki's report.
Affiliation
Occupation
DoB
Age
Blood Type
CID Division 1
Public Safety Bureau
Enforcer
A lot of it was inconsistent with what we had on you,
so I looked into it again.
I see.
You drove all of your previous
Inspectors to latent criminality.
To tell you the truth,
I didn't want to believe it.
Or rather, I at least wanted to believe
that you weren't doing it intentionally.
Like Professor Saiga?
But you were different.
Looking back on what you've said
and how you've behaved,
your true intentions gradually become clearer.
You wanted to paint me black.
Isn't that right?
You aren't capable of clouding her.
Kamui Kirito.
This is perfect.
Your existence demeans my mother.
Crime Coefficient is 769.
Lethal Eliminator.
You don't deserve to exist!
All is calm, all is bright
Don't!
Begone, you pitch-black soul.
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".