That is the reality of the Sibyl System, which maintains order in this society.
Incredible!
That's incredible!
This is the true fruit of man's intellect!
I can't believe the criminally
asymptomatic provide judgment.
It's amazing that such a wonderful system protects our society!
She unconditionally accepts
what society considers right.
She's a model citizen if there ever was one, wouldn't you agree?
Yes, her Hue is quite clear.
Unlike your own.
He is the only criminally asymptomatic person
successfully created through artificial means.
Mom!
You really are a good boy.
Wonderful!
I'm so moved!
This is an ideal form of law!
Mother, if she keeps you pure,
we no longer have to color her.
We can find another use for her.
Oh? Like what?
To color Tsunemori Akane...
black.
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
Professor,
omnipotence paradox
suppose there's a perfect being
that passes judgment on others.
omnipotence paradox
Is it possible to judge that being?
“A perfect being”...
Are you talking about God or something?
They call that the omnipotence paradox.
Can an omnipotent being create a stone so heavy that even he cannot lift it?
A paradox?
Right. If he can create a rock that cannot be lifted,
then he's surrendering his omnipotence the moment it is created.
And if he cannot create the rock,
then he was never omnipotent to begin with.
Either way, it leads to a contradiction.
As does the question you asked earlier.
If the being casting judgment is perfect,
then it has to be constantly judging itself as well.
Is there any way to resolve the paradox?
There's a mistake somewhere in the
assumption, process, or conclusion.
That, or you need to prove that
one of them is actually correct.
A mistake or a correct answer...
I have to wonder what brought this on.
I thought we were talking about Sibyl.
“What color”?
You want to know what Sibyl's color is.
And your own.
If the two happen to be the same...
The god of this world, huh?
I should be telling her to avoid
discussing such dangerous topics,
and yet I'm looking forward to her answer.
Guess I'm not exactly a model citizen.
Dependent, am I?
This must be how Kamui's sympathizers felt.
Who are you?
It's been a while, Dr. Masuzaki.
I don't believe we've met since Kirito's surgery.
So you really are still alive,
Director Tougane!
How does one resolve the omnipotence paradox?
One possibility is that the omnipotent being doesn't have to be omnipotent every single moment.
After creating a rock that even he cannot lift, he makes it lighter.
This way, he maintains his omnipotence.
The Sibyl System takes this approach too.
By taking in criminally asymptomatic people—the ones it cannot judge—
it maintains its perfection.
But by clearing people's Hues, Kamui himself created stones that cannot be lifted,
effectively making all those people criminally asymptomatic.
As a result, he's invalidated that as a possible resolution to the paradox.
Going beyond that, he further asks,
“Can Sibyl judge Sibyl”?
If it cannot judge itself, then Sibyl
becomes an exception to its own rules.
The solution in that case would be for Sibyl to be integrated into itself.
Of course, such a thing isn't possible, and thus the perfection is lost.
What if they can judge themselves, then?
In terms of judging everyone without exception, the perfection is maintained.
But in this scenario, those who comprise Sibyl cannot be criminally asymptomatic.
Therefore, the system didn't judge
people who should've been judged.
There's only one way to resolve this paradox.
Someone shot him with a Dominator.
It seems I've lost another conversation partner.
If a Dominator was used,
we should assume that Kamui was behind this.
The Bureau's surveillance logs from 10 PM onward
have been overwritten with feed from a different date.
So they accessed the Bureau's systems?
Yeah. They left some sort of trace, but...
it's pretty bizarre.
Masuzaki knew too much.
We need to eliminate those
who know my mother's secret.
So it really was you.
What's the matter? Are you scared of me?
You shouldn't feel that way.
After all, I am my mother's child—
a child of Sibyl.
My will is society's will.
My eyes are society's eyes.
Since you vowed to respect the law, you cannot deny me...
no matter how much you despise latent criminals.
What do you want?
There's something I want you to look into.
Find Tsunemori Akane's grandmother.
What?
We'll have the Inspector play the role of Kamui's killer.
There's one thing I'm concerned about.
An official from the Ministry of Land, Infrastructure, Transport and Tourism has been holding a lot of meetings lately.
His name is Kuwashima Koichi.
23 years old.
People call him the young hope of the Ministry.
I looked into him and found out that he went to the same elementary school as the students from that plane crash,
but he transferred to a different school one week before the field trip.
So he escaped the accident right before it happened.
That's his connection to Kamui.
Yeah.
Kuwashima is also a stockholder of the company that manages the port where we found Kamui's hideout.
And he's an official at the MLIT as well.
If we can assume he's working with Kamui,
it would explain how Kamui's been able to get in touch with influential figures from every sector of society.
Let's ask this official about it directly.
Find out his current location.
We'll take Kuwashima Koichi into custody right away.
To the dawn of a new society!
Cheers!
Sorry for the trouble.
That's okay.
I'm well suited to be the Master of Ceremonies for such a charade.
We can finally eliminate the Sibyl System.
That's right!
At long last, it will be our time!
Thanks to you, they feel free to openly denounce Sibyl.
That's revolutionary in itself.
Let's get on with it.
I can't bear to see this.
Yeah.
Thank you for all your help.
You have now fulfilled your roles.
Gentlemen.
To conclude this meeting,
we offer you tonight's main dish.
We hope you enjoy it.
Crime Coefficient is over 250.
A target for enforcement action.
Poor thing.
Wh-Why?
Why are you...
I'd like to ask you the same thing.
Each of you turned a blind eye during the Season of Hell
and rose to power by taking advantage of its many victims.
As if that wasn't enough, you played with
people's lives in order to keep Hue clear.
Crime Coefficient is 313.
Enforcement mode is Lethal Eliminator.
Help me, Kamui!
This is your true color.
S-Stop it!
Inspector Shisui's Dominator has been used.
The location is Central Hall in Chiyoda Ward.
Isn't that where we're headed right now?
Have the Drones form a perimeter
and seal off the area. Hurry!
Thank you. I can finally pay my respects.
You shouldn't feel responsible for what happened.
I almost became a latent criminal as a child
through the guilt I felt for escaping the crash.
The Sibyl System maintains order in this society.
The reality principle got 184 of my friends killed and almost removed me from society.
I won't let you get clouded.
Let's go see judgment carried out together.
I cannot guide people like you do.
In the end, I'm just like these men.
I'm one of the saved.
I see.
Do the rest as we planned.
I had my doubts about the intel,
but we had no issue getting our trump card.
I thought I told you that wasn't necessary.
Tsunemori Akane is the biggest potential threat to our plans.
We're better off containing her movements.
That wouldn't be enough to stop her.
She keeps her color no matter
what kind of situation she's in.
That's exactly why I want her
to bear witness to the judgment.
Then consider this a test.
Koichi...
Go, Kirito.
I'll stay here and do my part.
Kamui! The Bureau is coming.
You were already our precious friend long before you and I were reunited.
You guys can change the world.
All of you...
Go and judge Sibyl!
That was rather quick.
I'd expect no less from the Bureau.
Where is Kamui?
He left.
But coming here wasn't a waste of time.
You get to see these people off in lieu of him.
This is terrible... How could you...
How could human beings have done this?
A veritable vision of Hell, isn't it?
Really makes your blood curdle.
Did Kamui do this?
Don't be silly.
It's those dead officials in there who were unable to keep their Psycho-Passes clear
without playing these sorts of games.
And you're saying this is retaliation for what they did?
The ones burning are all illegal aliens.
They abandoned their own countries for some reason or another.
Officials used sweet talk to gather them together...
and then toyed with them.
They committed terrible acts like this, but when their
Crime Coefficients rose, they sought help from Kamui.
That brought Kamui's wrath on them.
These people who were turned into livestock asked to be burned themselves!
They couldn't go back to their former selves.
Just as Kamui can't.
Could you come with us?
Of course.
But before that, please take a look at this.
What did you do?!
Tsunemori!
Tsunemori! Stop it!
What did you do?!
Kunizuka!
Tsunemori Aoi...
What?!
I'm Saiga Jouji.
I'll be in charge of your interrogation.
There's an odd rumor about me spreading around.
They say that one's Psycho-Pass gets clouded by talking to me.
This is the first time I've
wanted to see if they're right.
What is it that you want?
Tsunemori Akane has closed in on Kamui.
She's a bother to us. A sacrilege, you could say.
I want her to behave herself for a while.
Do your associates share that opinion?
After all, Kamui wants Tsunemori to come, right?
Where's Kamui?
He's in the guts of this city.
The subway?!
Security cameras captured Kamui 15 minutes ago.
Who are the people with him?
They're of various ages and occupations.
Check to see if any of them lost someone close to them in traffic or plane accidents 15 years ago.
Got it.
Hasebe Ryousuke lost his parents in an
accident caused by a defective runway light.
Ogi Shinichi's older brother died in a rear-ender caused by a malfunctioning crossing gate.
Oura Yukiho lost her father in a plane crash, too.
Just as I thought.
The Season of Hell is the link between them all.
Kamui has been operating as an invisible man up until now,
but he has now made a move out in the open.
Which means...
He wants to settle this once and for all.
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
Are you one of Akane's colleagues?
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".