Patent Office
Ministry of Economy
This is Shimotsuki Mika from CID Division 1
at the Public Safety Bureau.
Requesting permission to enter the
Ministry of Economy Patent Office's archive room.
Archive Room
Patents owned by the Tougane Foundation...
Kamui Kirito
Kamui Kirito's medical records
One record found
There we go.
How to create a composite body for multi-body transplant and live organ transplant
Transplant rejection immune evasion medicine
Decellularization method and artificial tissue for implantation into human body
Transplant materials and how to create them
These are all the patent applications related to Kamui Kirito's surgery.
“Multi-body transplant"?
How to create a composite body for multi-body transplant and live organ transplant
A surgical procedure to combine parts of 184 bodies, creating a composite body.
A surgical procedure to combine parts of 184 bodies?
How to create a composite body for multi-body transplant and live organ transplant
A surgical procedure to combine parts of 184 bodies, creating a composite body.
The plane crash victims' bodies were cut into pieces
and grafted onto a single boy.
And that boy was Kamui?
He has said himself that he has the
flesh and personalities of 184 people,
including seven people's brains.
I'm amazed a multi-body brain transplant was even possible.
To be honest, the chance of success was all but zero.
If I were asked to do it again, I would probably fail.
However...
That boy has lived on
as someone whose Psycho-Pass cannot be measured at all.
After all,
in the scanners' eyes, he's nothing but a jumble of corpses.
So that's who Kamui Kirito is.
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
At the conclusion of the surgery,
he was still a normal human that scanners were able to recognize.
conception of
the oracle
He told me that he realized his uniqueness
after he was able to return to a normal daily life.
The more his body accepted the grafted parts,
the less often he was recognized by scanners.
As time passed,
I soon became a ghost who was cut off from society.
To begin with, I did try to be recognized.
At times, I would purposefully commit crimes in broad daylight, hoping to be judged.
I also consulted people I thought I could trust,
including doctors and counselors.
But when they saw my uniqueness with their own eyes,
they walked away.
I can imagine.
Acknowledging someone who isn't recognized by Sibyl
is tantamount to doubting the very foundation of this society.
I'm not only invisible to Sibyl.
No one dependent on this system will acknowledge my existence.
Why did I have to fade away like a ghost, forsaken by society?
While searching for the answer to that question, I discovered...
the Season of Hell.
I knew you'd be no stranger to that incident.
I've only heard of it. That's all.
At one time, the Ministry of Economy proposed a support system for citizens to replace Sibyl, leading to controversy.
It would control the traffic and banks, supervising all of them.
It was called “Panopticon."
The original Panopticon was a system that allowed one to monitor everything from one place.
It was an architectural form designed as a detention facility by Jeremy Bentham.
By monitoring and recording people's actions and economic activities,
it would prevent crimes before they happened,
guiding citizens toward the best way of living.
It was quite a simple proposal,
but you could also call it the ideal solution.
Ideal, huh?
If you need to monitor everything your citizens do,
they might as well be in prison.
And how is that any different from our current society?
Let's get back on track.
They began test deployments of Panopticon for traffic monitoring.
But did you know it soon suffered a series of crippling malfunctions?
Yeah. And that's when they shelved the wider adoption of the system.
Indeed.
And so, Sybil's rule has continued until today.
But what if someone had intended for that to happen?
What if everything had been set up in order to ensure that result?
I recall hearing conspiracy theories like those at the time, too.
Conspiracy theories? Don't make me laugh.
Interference with the Ministry of Economy,
manipulation and draining of valuable human resources,
the scramble for a budget,
backroom dealings amongst politicians...
Those things really did happen.
In fact, as a result...
The number of plane crashes and traffic accidents around that time
were dozens of times higher than average.
A large number of people were victimized during that time.
It came to be known as the Season of Hell.
So you found your answer there.
I learned all I needed and discovered what I had to do.
Then I became a present-day medicine man.
It was about five years ago that I was reunited with him.
My excessive stress at the time had left me dependent on medication.
The cause was simple.
My mind couldn't endure the
heavy responsibility of a doctor.
A trite story that I'm sure you've heard many times before.
Kamui healed me.
He had obtained the medical data that we were forbidden to see
and gained the ability to clear
people's Psycho-Passes
by teaching them how to meditate
and providing them with appropriate medication.
So he can clear the Psycho-Pass of any criminal, eh?
That alone would allow him to exact revenge for his past.
He won't stop at simple revenge.
Kamui will overturn everything for us.
Thanks to him, we can dream of something bigger.
He'll overturn everything?
Is that Kamui's goal?
I understand now.
It's not just me you want to judge,
but the entire Sibyl System, is it, Kirito?
A human put together from the flesh of countless corpses?
That's disgusting.
This file was last accessed only two months ago.
Access Date
and Time
User
Shimotsuki Mika
Uchikoga Shunji
Who's this?
There he is.
One of Kamui's Holos.
So Kamui came here?
Where's Inspector Shimotsuki?
She said she'd continue checking medical institutions for clues.
Okay.
In that case, why don't we all give our status reports?
I'll go first, then.
I searched for people with the same names as the accident victims
and found fifty-four matches
within the inner-city area alone.
Those fifty-four people...
No, it's probably safe to say that all 184 victims excluding Kamui
are the Holos that he wears.
Yes.
The therapist who offered his services at the Bureau,
the pharmacist at the mental care facility,
and the hostage from the first incident...
were all Kamui.
B-But this might also mean that h-he only uses the Holos of those victims.
Yes, I agree.
Kamui is obsessed with the accident and the 184 people from which he received transplants as a result.
In that sense, we can say that we
finally know the perpetrator's face.
How was your investigation, Ginoza?
Based on the organs left at Kamui's hideout,
we've determined the people who may have been replaced.
They were influential figures from every sector of society.
Dr. Masuzaki was the one who replaced these people with impostors.
He confessed to it himself.
He murdered them under the guise of treating them.
And yet he kept his Psycho-Pass clear even while performing such atrocities.
That is what makes Kamui unique.
With prepared medication and psychological counseling,
he can even clear even the Psycho-Passes of high-level latent criminals
to the extent that it could be called brainwashing.
Medical care is his most powerful weapon, huh?
How troublesome.
At the same time, he's limited his attacks to medical institutions.
Remember the claim of responsibility made by Kitazawa, the bomber?
H-He said he targeted a pharmaceutical company.
And the barricade incident happened at a mental care facility.
The strange thing is that he used the port as his hideout.
There must have been some advantage to doing so.
But what would that advantage be?
Kunizuka, have there been any unsolved
missing persons cases over the past few months?
I don't think there's anything on the record.
Isn't that strange? From what we know, people must have gone missing.
I agree.
If the people killed for their organs were replaced by impostors,
the original identities of those impostors would also have had to disappear.
That is true.
So we're dealing with people whose
disappearances aren't recognized by society.
Wait.
I recall seeing foreign newspapers
and currencies left behind at the site.
I see. Illegal aliens.
So the impersonators are illegal aliens?
It's definitely a possibility.
What could he hope to achieve
with such elaborate measures?
What do you want?
Can you afford to be loitering around here?
I didn't come to see you because I had too much free time on my hands.
Rather, I've been interested in you for some time.
Saiga Jouji, a lecturer who colored his students black.
I'm not exactly pleased about that.
Influencing the Psycho-Passes of others is no mean feat.
There has to be more to it than a simple trick.
Indeed. If anyone could learn to do it,
this society wouldn't hold.
If it's not a trick, it must be a talent.
You have a talent for clouding a person's Psycho-Pass,
which is the exact opposite of Kamui's talent for clearing it.
Am I supposed to be proud of that or something?
And as a result,
you're dependent on Inspector Tsunemori, whose Psycho-Pass doesn't change no matter how much you get involved.
Oh?
Excuse me.
Understood.
Dependent, huh?
So what does that make you?
You're sharp.
Too sharp.
The data Kamui accessed is heavily focused on drug-related categories.
Such as the manufacturing technologies for the new drug LACOUSE,
Lacouse
which was related to the Kitazawa bombing incident.
There's also an access record for several drugs used at the mental care facility
where the barricade incident took place.
And the common link is...
Patent Owner: The Tougane Foundation
Could Kamui be trying to take revenge against the Tougane Foundation?
Their patented technologies were used in the surgery carried out after the plane crash.
Brain extraction from living subjects?
The grafting of multiple extracted brains into a single recipient?
Why did they own technologies like these?
What's in the related categories?
Fully automated brain extraction by Drones,
and a proposal for other unmanned surgical procedures...
What on earth are these?
The applicant for this latest patent...
Tougane Misako
Chairperson,
The Tougane Foundation
Applicant
Information
was one Tougane Misako.
Tougane Sakuya's mother.
Chairperson,
The Tougane Foundation
Applicant
Information
Birth Date:       February 19, 2034 (died in 2099)
Address:          268 Ichiban-cho, Chiyoda Ward, Tokyo
She died five years ago.
What about his father?
This information is classified
Classified?
Could this mean he was born through patented technologies?
Proof of the congenital nature of the 'AA' idiosyncrasy related to Psycho-Pass
One record found
“Proof of the congenital nature of the ‘AA' idiosyncrasy..."
This information is classified
No...
My Psycho-Pass is gonna get clouded.
What should I do?
Oh, yeah.
That's right!
It fell through.
Yeah.
I was going to check the impostors one by one, but...
We were always one step behind.
An alarm?
What's going on?
Something triggered the weight sensor I had installed in my apartment floor.
So you were using yourself as a decoy.
You're unbelievable.
Sorry. I'll listen to your complaints later.
I-I came to check the fire prevention and water supply systems.
You were occupied with work,
and you had signed a permit to let us
access the property in your absence...
I'm surprised you left that thing up.
Well, there didn't seem to be any harm in doing so.
You thought the best way to get into Kamui's
frame of mind was to preserve the view he saw.
Right on the money, was I?
I'd expect no less from you.
I'm impressed.
You're a born detective.
Thank you very much.
By that, I mean you lack charm.
A notification from the Bureau?
Grandma?
The alarm at your home has been triggered.
Therefore, the security level for
Tsunemori Aoi in protective custody
has been raised to B.
Oh, this is... Uh...
Your grandmother, huh?
It all started with a plane crash fifteen years ago.
It was a tragic accident that claimed the lives of
201 passengers and crew, including 184 children.
One party profited greatly from this accident:
the Tougane Foundation.
And the sole survivor of the accident...
the sole survivor of the accident was Kamui Kirito.
was Kamui Kirito.
Tougane Misako, the one who was running the foundation at the time,
was obsessed with research into an idiosyncrasy called “AA."
As part of that research,
she conducted an experiment to demonstrate a patented technology owned by the Foundation
in which multiple extracted brains
were grafted together.
She used Kamui, along with the cadavers of the accident victims, to push her research forward,
and as a result, the Foundation's
patented technology advanced further.
Kamui Kirito perpetrated his crimes to exact
revenge against the Tougane Foundation.
Kamui Kirito perpetrated his crimes to exact revenge against the Tougane Foundation.
Thus, keeping an eye on the Foundation should lead us closer to arresting Kamui.
However, Division 1 is currently burdened with a significant liability.
Namely,
Tsunemori Akane and Tougane Sakuya.
Tougane Sakuya was the result of an experiment conducted by Tougane Misaki to artificially create a human with “AA."
It can be speculated that this is what led to him
exhibiting the highest Crime Coefficient ever recorded.
Therefore,
Kamui, the ringleader of this crime, and Tougane
Sakuya are connected by the key word 'AA.'
we can surmise that Kamui, the ringleader of this crime,
and Tougane Sakuya are connected by the key word “AA."
Kamui Kirito and Tougane Sakuya are equally dangerous.
Tougane Sakuya is a deviant who takes pleasure in raising the Crime Coefficients of others.
One need look no further than the five Inspectors he worked with in the past, who all became latent criminals.
It is anticipated that Tougane Sakuya's influence
will also cause Inspector Tsunemori's
Crime Coefficient to rise in the near future.
However, Inspector Tsunemori
does not appear concerned by this
and shows no intention of
accepting the advice of others.
Inspector Tsunemori does not appear concerned by
The situation is critical.
Many Inspectors and Enforcers
have already lost their lives as a direct result of Inspector Tsunemori's poor decision-making.
As it stands,
not only will we be unable to arrest Kamui
or suppress Tougane Sakuya,
unable to arrest Kamui or suppress Tougane Sakuya,
the Bureau itself could be at risk.
but the Bureau itself could be at risk.
Hence, I strongly advise the dismissal of Inspector Tsunemori or the suspension of her rights as an Inspector.
November 27th, 2114.
November 27th, 2114
Shimotsuki Mika,
Criminal Investigation Department
Division 1, Public Safety Bureau
Shimotsuki Mika, Criminal Investigation Department Division 1, Public Safety Bureau.
I'm sure Chief Kasei will understand.
No progress, huh?
We checked all the impostors' houses and secondary places of residence,
but we found no trace of them at all.
Considering the timing, it's hard to believe they all just flew the coop.
I agree.
They've begun moving toward their goal.
We need to do whatever it takes to stop them.
You sound as if you know their objective already.
If we are to trust Masuzaki, Kamui's goal is revolution.
In order to overturn society, he will pass judgment on the existence that embodies it.
There is only one such existence.
The Sibyl System.
This is an interesting report.
You must have amazing investigative abilities to have reached this conclusion in so short a time.
Thank you very much.
Now, concerning this “AA" you mentioned.
That is what we call “open-door data."
Open-door data?
A honeypot designed to catch those unfit for society who intend to expose top-secret information.
And you fell for it, hook, line, and sinker.
“AA" stands for “a priori acquit."
It refers to those who have a criminally asymptomatic constitution by nature—
Sibyl's most closely guarded secret.
Hm? Huh?
Now, how should I deal with the girl who deviated from the
investigation only to poke her nose where it shouldn't have been?
And yet your Psycho-Pass has barely changed.
Why?!
We can still make use of her.
Could you leave this one to me,
Mother?
“Mother"?
Tougane Misako
Chairperson,
The Tougane Foundation
Applicant
Information
It can't be.
I mean...
You may do as you please.
I can deal with her whenever I want.
After all, the real problem is...
If you're thinking of Tsunemori and Kamui,
there is no need to worry.
I'll bring them both down.
It's my role to make you and Sibyl
beautiful and pure, Mother.
What?
What are you talking about?
Stop it!
I don't wanna hear anything!
I don't wanna see anything!
I... I don't know anything!
I won't tell anyone!
I'll forget about everything!
A wise decision.
You really are an ideal citizen—
so ideal that you're boring.
Based on her reaction,
she might be a good model case for when we eventually reveal the system to the public.
In that case, why don't we give it a try?
Well, then...
Inspector Shimotsuki, we'll reveal to you
the secret behind this world.
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
No...
No!
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified. While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".