So it went well?
Yeah.
Did you kill her?
An Enforcer did.
Does it hurt to know she's dead?
I don't know.
Although I do feel a little sad.
Looks like you've been following my dosage instructions.
How about I check your Hue?
It's clear.
I can't believe how little medicine it took to make me feel this much better
despite it supposedly being ineffective.
Prescriptions should be unique to the individual.
Ignoring that fact and prescribing heavy doses
is no better than using violence.
Why are you helping me become clear?
Because I want you to keep your own free will.
My own will?
Yeah.
Stay by my side.
I'll do anything you ask.
Thank you.
Sibyl...
It won't be long
before I bring you to justice.
I'll go check the back door.
Okay.
Crime Coefficient is 26.
An Inspector registered at the CID.
Warning.
Any rebellious conduct by Enforcers
will be recorded and reported to headquarters.
How very clear.
What's with him?
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
unforbidden games
Impressive as usual.
Already finished reading the case files?
unforbidden games
I should be the one telling you that.
Huh?
It's only been a day since that truly awful incident,
and yet you're so calm.
Are you really human?
Some people might take that the wrong way.
I'd be lying if I said it didn't shock me.
More than that, it makes me feel like I have to work even harder.
I see.
Sorry, but I'll get straight to the point.
I'd like to ask you to interrogate Representative Masuda.
The representative, huh?
He's calm at this point, right?
Unnaturally so.
He could be part of a trap...
Is that what you're thinking?
By analyzing the logs,
we think we've succeeded in pinpointing Kamui's hideout.
We've already sent in Drones, but...
You'll probably end up going there yourself anyway.
There's no doubt that it was
Inspector Shisui's voice on the phone.
She's the one who called Inspector Aoyanagi to the scene.
If Kamui is capable of winning over an Inspector,
there's no way he'd leave a trace
for us to get a lead on him this easily.
So you think he's really that good.
Enough to think that we should be on guard.
Just yesterday, we couldn't detect his Psycho-Pass
despite the fact that he had to have been at the crime scene.
Is that not reminiscent of someone?
Makishima Shougo.
I suppose he does give off a similarly eerie vibe.
But there's something different this time.
If we can figure out what that something is,
we'll probably get closer to Kamui's true identity, right?
That's one of the reasons I came to you.
Sorry, but I'm not a magician.
I can't pull on a string and turn it into flowers.
You're just being modest.
Are you leaving?
Be very careful.
Division 3 will be joining us for this investigation.
That should give us enough firepower.
I'm surprised the Chief is going along with this.
Well...
She probably isn't keen on the strategy itself,
but she must've decided the
best option was to hedge her bets.
Like I said, impressive as usual.
I do understand that there's no
basis whatsoever for her actions.
However, she's easier to handle as a part of the chain of command rather than as an autonomous entity.
In any event, our losses thus far aren't
so substantial as to warrant taking action.
Though it will take some time to replace the Inspectors that have fallen.
As for the surplus Enforcers,
assigning them to other Inspectors
will allow us to keep them operational.
The name's Hasuike Kaede. I've been transferred to Division 1 as of today.
What a warm welcome.
I hear you've been transferred to Division 1.
Yes.
You were a friend of Inspector Aoyanagi's.
You both started working here in the same year.
She was also your boss.
I...
You carried out enforcement
on a latent criminal. That's all.
You did nothing wrong.
But...
Just...
I don't want you showing your
face around me for a long time.
I'm scared.
I saw such a terrible thing happen right before my eyes.
I want to tell myself that this won't change me, but...
Kunizuka...
It's okay.
Even Inspectors have the right to cry.
Right.
Yayoi.
Yes?
What do you think of Tougane Sakuya?
I think he's an excellent Enforcer
with outstanding judgment and ability.
I guess you're right.
I see.
So I'm in charge of this case, am I?
But no matter how much you blame me,
I can't take responsibility for it all...
because we can't change the past.
Let's just do our best to make use of that which was brought to life...
in order that we may evolve.
Besides, aren't you curious?
It will be interesting to see how this affects her.
We'll be arriving soon.
Our destination is a military Drone testing site.
Our purpose is strictly investigation.
However, equipment with Hazard Level B
has been permitted as a precautionary measure.
Also, this operation is being carried out in tandem by Division 1 and Division 3.
Enforcers are expected to consider the situation and follow any appropriate instructions,
regardless of who your lead Inspector is.
I didn't think I'd ever come back here.
Inspector, is there a point in taking so many people with you?
The Chief assigned all personnel herself.
The interrogation of Representative Masuda,
the analysis of the barricade incident site,
and the Holo analysis you requested...
We've got so much to do that
we're about to explode over here.
I only gave everyone tasks that I determined they could handle.
I'm saying that it might actually be too much to handle.
Besides, Drones have already
investigated that site, haven't they?
There are things that can only be discovered by seeing a scene in person.
That way of thinking is out of date.
Just because an approach is new
doesn't necessarily mean it's right.
We've arrived at the site. I'm going to hang up.
Inspector Shimotsuki.
The Ministry of Welfare has instructed us to release Representative Masuda given the improvement in his Hue.
What?
No matter how you look at it,
someone's putting pressure on us.
Japanese society has always been
held up by the vitality of its citizens.
We can't just dismiss the Ministry of Welfare's orders.
I have been stressing that, in order to maintain that vitality,
we need to provide security and well-being above all else.
Even feigning ignorance would probably buy us no more than a day or two.
This place used to be a trading port.
After the port was closed, it was used as an unmanned warehouse.
Then, the Ministry of National Defense's Military Drones Research and Development department set their sights on it.
There's enough space to store parts and equipment,
not to mention the Drones themselves.
In addition,
it's unmanned, so accidents are unlikely.
There's no better place for conducting active military Drone experiments.
I see.
Whoa!
Next up is the test on data synchronization between two Drones.
Is that you, Sugou?
It's been a while!
I don't think I've seen you
since you went to the facility.
When did you come back?
I didn't exactly come back.
What?
I'm an Enforcer with the Public Safety Bureau.
Oh... I see.
I have to get back to my post.
I'll see you later.
I see. So he used to work here.
Nothing out of the ordinary, huh?
Can't we just stand by for orders?
Why don't we leave the rest to Division 1,
since they're so gung-ho about this?
Chief Kasei's favorite, huh?
Having to work with her is such a pain in the ass.
No one can enter this area without authorization,
and there's no chance that anyone's been living here.
That's what the operations manager said, right?
Yeah. There's no record of anyone
other than the staff having been present.
Cymatic scans are inconsequential to a ghost.
What he really needs to look out for are human eyes.
Somewhere that has scanners installed
and is also deserted.
Dead end.
Tougane?
The building on the left
has emergency exits facing the street.
That being the case, it's unnatural that the building next to it would have nothing but a wall.
A structurally unnecessary wall, at that.
It's within the range of cymatic scans' monitoring,
and it's the deepest end of a deserted path.
It's a Holo.
I think this is what they call a detective's intuition.
I've submitted my reports to you plenty of times, Chief.
There's a problem with the way
Inspector Tsunemori conducts herself.
What do you think about that?
Oh, it doesn't concern me much.
Don't you think that kind of behavior can be dangerous?
Oh?
She's excessively hands-on,
her judgment is easily compromised due to her groundless obsessions,
and the way she treats Enforcers...
Inspector Tsunemori has major issues in all these areas.
And your point is?
I believe that helping a colleague
come to her senses is part of my job.
Is that all you wanted to discuss?
No. There's one more thing.
I am concerned about a troubling action taken by Enforcer Tougane Sakuya.
Are you referring to his pointing
a Dominator at an Inspector?
Yes.
He might have been concerned about
Inspector Tsunemori's mental state, just as you are.
Though it's true that it wasn't
the best way to go about it.
Inspector Tsunemori pays no mind to the risk posed by Enforcers, who are latent criminals.
I have no doubt that this will escalate eventually.
When that happens, could you...
consider giving her treatment?
I'll think about it.
Please do not forget what you just said.
Excuse me.
That girl will be eaten alive.
This is...
A face transplant mask?
This is strange.
What did he need these for?
In order to maintain Japan's vitality,
we must ensure the security and well-being of its people.
I have consistently held this position
What a complete farce.
Huh?
ever since I was first elected.
Japan has always been supported by the vitality of its citizens...
I've watched videos of all your speeches over the past three years.
You certainly have a way with words.
Charisma is a necessary skill
for a politician, wouldn't you say?
One of the distinguishing characteristics
you've had ever since becoming a representative
would have to be that masterful enunciation of yours.
You purposely dial it down for the vital points, and as a result, the audience is captivated.
The balance is superb.
No...
It was, I should say.
In the videos of your past speeches, at least.
Your recent speeches have paled in comparison, though I'll give your imitation points for effort.
Just...
Who are you?
Oh?
Is something wrong?
The new Hungry Chicken is already out!
Seriously? Did they even announce it?
Hungry Chicken!
A video game?
I keep telling you to put that stuff away while on duty, don't I?
Come on, just let me play a little.
Hungry Chicken!
Whoa...
What the hell?!
Die, small fries.
I won't let you get away!
Inspector!
Looks like he was expecting us.
You are a messenger.
You got arrested on purpose and lured in the Bureau with the information you provided.
But what's your goal?
What are you trying to achieve
by roping in the CID?
SENDING SHUTDOWN SIGNAL
It's not stopping!
Why?!
What the hell's going on?!
Hungry Chicken!
What're you doing?!
Stop them already!
It's not working!
The shutdown signal keeps getting rejected!
Three Drones have just been activated in Block F!
All Drones in Block G and Block H are active!
This can't be...
I'm in luck!
Game on, Bureau.
This is...
Door unlocked by Inspector's request.
What the hell is this?
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".