This case isn't even over yet,
and we're already relying on Drones.
This is awesome!
Realistic games are way better.
Freeze! CID!
Hinakawa!
Crime Coefficient is 133.
A target for enforcement action.
I'm enforcing justice!
The next Area Stress warning has been issued in a commercial area eight kilometers away.
Give me a break! It never ends!
In a society under constant surveillance by scanners, you can't pass yourself off as another person.
But that's not necessarily the case if one can take measures to keep his Psycho-Pass clear.
Through organ transplantation, for example.
Transplanting a lot of one's organs is like transplanting one's Psycho-Pass.
If the Hue is clear, any discrepancy is likely to fall within the margin of error.
I've heard that quite a few organs were stored in Kamui's hideout.
Representative Masuda, I'm here to pick you up.
There are other impostors out there just like you.
Are they Kamui's accomplices?
Inspector.
Once again, I couldn't shoot.
If it hadn't been for you, we'd all be dead.
What matters is that we were able to see the ghost with our own eyes.
If anyone's going to arrest Kamui, it'll be you after all.
I will go insane
if the world keeps ruining my life
I've stopped breathing
from the nervousness every day
Enigmatic feeling
I have to be the aggressor
The world has stopped making sense
It's dissolving
God has come to us
with sword in hand
The world has split in two
Half is mad,
and so am I
Where's the difference?
Only God can walk the borderline
I'm going crazy, I'm going crazy
Will I find you killed by my own hand?
Crazy, crazy, floating on the water
I have no focus in my soul
Shake me, shake me, floating on the water
I can't even look into the mirror
untraceable children
He tested an unauthorized user's ability to wield a Dominator.
That was the first case.
He then experimented with a Dominator's capacity to judge Inspectors.
That was the second one.
This time, he attacked the Bureau and obtained multiple Dominators, presumably to distribute to his accomplices.
In other words, his goal isn't something he can achieve on his own.
Who on earth are you trying to point those Dominators at?
And Dominators can't even recognize you,
much less judge you.
But why?
When the impossible happens,
there are only two possibilities.
Either your assumptions are wrong,
or you have gone insane.
It'd make more sense if I were imagining all this,
but that's not the case.
Kamui exists. That's an indisputable fact.
And yet Dominators don't even recognize him.
He's not just another Makishima.
He's unique, not criminally asymptomatic.
There's something else that makes him invisible in this society.
He knows how to fool the system—
to exploit a weakness in this society of total control over the individual.
The...
The answer may be...
...closer than we think.
Something wrong?
Oh, sorry. I spaced out a bit.
What were you saying?
I was talking about Kamui.
I think that determining his bodily constitution, which isn't perceived by cymatic scans,
is the best way to solve this whole thing.
I agree. If we figure out why he isn't recognized,
we may be able to decipher his color.
How can Kamui persist as a ghost?
Let's examine the scene for clues.
What color... are you?
Transplant organs weren't all that Kamui was storing in his hideout.
It seems they've found bio-contact lenses with a traced retinal pattern there, too.
The retinal pattern must belong to Shisui Mizue.
Very perceptive. I'm impressed.
The only way an unauthorized user can wield a Dominator is to have it falsely recognize them as authorized.
Kamui probably considers Shisui
a pawn that can facilitate that, so...
So that's why we detected
more than one Inspector Shisui.
Eight Dominators have been taken so far.
Therefore, we can assume that up to eight Shisui Mizues may be detected.
You don't sound very fazed.
Am I to assume you've already
come up with a way to stop them?
Nope, I've got nothing.
Those Dominators will be put to use as long as Sibyl continues to recognize her actions as valid.
Oh, my. Is that a knock on Sibyl?
It's suspicion.
That's even worse.
Doppelgängers are roaming free without a care, and an Inspector aiding a criminal is at large.
I'm just stating the facts.
Well, then. Both of you should head back.
I'm going to stay behind for a bit and go through Kamui's hideout.
You should get some rest, Tsunemori.
I agree.
It's kind of hard to get any rest at my apartment,
since I've been leaving the crime scene untouched.
Wait a second!
You haven't moved?! What are you thinking?!
Are you trying to use yourself as bait?
I'm not that reckless.
I just haven't had the time.
You're unbelievable.
Grandma's...
There was a malfunction with the nursing Drones at the nursing home fostering Tsunemori Aoi's protective custody.
Grandma!
What's the matter? You look pale.
Grandma...
It's been a while, Akane.
Tsunemori Aoi
I'm so glad you're okay.
You're overreacting.
You didn't have to neglect your work and rush here over such a trifling matter.
Well, I wouldn't say I'm neglecting it.
You haven't changed a bit.
You relentlessly focus on the needs of others without even considering your own.
I'm sorry for always causing you trouble.
Don't be silly. I never think you cause me trouble.
You appreciate the value of human life.
You must always hold on to that, okay?
Grandma...
Thank you.
I've already been briefed on the case.
I came here today to hear Sibyl's thoughts.
Why haven't you deactivated the Dominators that Inspector Shisui is using?
I'm sure you've been keeping tabs on all of her actions.
Of course we have.
But Inspector Shisui's Psycho-Pass is still clear.
There's no reason for us to prevent an Inspector with a clear Psycho-Pass from taking action.
You mean you can't, because doing so
would be admitting the system is flawed.
Watch your mouth, Inspector Tsunemori.
We can't bring this culprit to justice
while being bound by the current rules.
You're talking about Kamui?
I've read your report.
You said the Dominators didn't even recognize him.
Yes.
That's not possible.
It'd one thing if he were criminally asymptomatic, but no irregularity can allow a person to bypass scans entirely.
But the reality is that this impossible irregularity has appeared.
How are we supposed to deal with someone like that?
It's simple. You tried to do it yourself, didn't you?
Are you suggesting that murder is appropriate?
Was stopping Enforcer Tougane really the right decision?
It's strange.
The Sibyl System has maintained itself by taking in irregular, criminally asymptomatic people.
But when it comes to Kamui, you'd rather remove the irregularity from society without even bothering to study it.
In other words, you've already come to your conclusion.
Kamui is the kind of outlier whom you cannot take in.
You're as interesting as ever.
Let's say your theory is correct. What's your next step?
I'll solve the mystery behind Kamui, arrest him,
and make sure he faces rightful justice.
Any problem with that?
No. Continue to fulfill your duty to the best of your ability.
Excuse me.
You tried to cover your tracks,
but things are out of order and out of alignment.
You're not very thorough, are you?
Looks like whoever it was copied some data.
My background, huh?
I see.
You must really have it in for me, Inspector Shimotsuki.
An old personnel file?
He was previously assigned as an Enforcer eighteen years ago at age 23.
All the Inspectors he worked with became latent criminals and were executed with Eliminators.
This data wasn't made available to us.
What's with this guy?
All right. Is everyone here?
Yeah. I was told that Enforcer Sugou won't be making it back for a while.
Then let's begin.
The question right now is how to pursue Kamui after losing him at the port.
We searched for Representative Masuda Koutoku,
thinking that he might report to Kamui,
but it looks like he died soon after his release.
He chose to die without a second thought.
That's how much he admired Kamui.
We knew he wasn't the real Masuda, and yet our hands were still tied.
We won't let Kamui have his way anymore.
First, let's talk about the evidence left at the scene.
What really stood out were the large number of organs
and the stockpile of stress-care medicine.
Th-This is amazing.
What is it, Hinakawa?
Th-These drugs are a product of clandestine chemistry.
I've never seen cocktails like them.
Plus, they should be impossible
to adjust at this level of detail.
I don't understand.
Even I can do some basic, straightforward compounding,
if that's what you're looking for.
But if these were his target results,
his knowledge must be far beyond average.
So he has an extraordinary knowledge of drugs?
Y-Yes.
Maybe using a Holo to disguise himself as a pharmacist wasn't just a feint.
Kamui disguised himself as a pharmacist?
U-Uh, yes.
I discovered it during the barricade incident.
I only noticed it after looking very closely.
I-It was well made, but it was definitely a Holo.
Why didn't you report it?
I... I sent the data to Inspector Shimotsuki.
I have a log of the transmission.
Why didn't you report it verbally?!
You didn't notify me properly!
Operational improvement can wait.
Hinakawa, send the data to the Analysis Lab.
You know, I wonder if this one is the same as...
Look. I knew it.
This Holo is an approximated model of a younger person.
I just cross-referenced it with the victims in that plane crash.
There's a perfect match.
The plane accident fifteen years ago.
Just like the female Holo Kamui used in the first incident.
Our assumptions were wrong.
It's not the first woman whom we should be focusing on.
It's all the children who died in this accident.
Can you pull up some more details on it, Karanomori?
Sure.
NIKKU AIRLINES FLIGHT 321 CRASHES!
Status of the 205 passengers
and crew is currently unknown
NIKKU AIRLINES FLIGHT 321 CRASHES!
Status of the 205 passengers
and crew is currently unknown
The crash happened fifteen years ago in May.
A plane carrying elementary-school students on a class trip crashed into Mt. Kumataka.
NIKKU AIRLINES FLIGHT 321 CRASHES!
NIKKU AIRLINES FLIGHT CRASHES WITH 205 ON BOARD
School Trip Tragedy: Nikku Plane Crashes
It says the cause was a problem with the airframe.
There was a total of 202 people on board.
Victims included 185 children along with chaperones, crew members, and pilots.
Wait!
There was one survivor.
This name...
Kamui Kirito.
He was the sole survivor.
It's no use.
Even the Bureau's clearance doesn't seem to be high enough to access records on Kamui Kirito.
It's citing medical confidentiality as the reason.
Let's check into the people involved with his surgery.
The one who would appear to be the most informed is...
Oh, his operating surgeon is still practicing.
I'll go see him immediately.
Inspector Shimotsuki, please come with me.
Roger.
Thank you, Hinakawa.
We couldn't have found him without you.
S-Sure...
I want you to work on approximating models of the 185 children
who were victims in the accident.
A-All of them?!
You expect one person to do all that?
We might be able to identify a third or even a fourth Holo.
Can you do it, Hinakawa?
I... I can, Akane.
Kunizuka, please look for anyone who has the same name as one of the victims.
Okay.
Ginoza and Tougane, I want you to use the organs we seized to identify any potential impostors out there.
Got it.
Understood.
I finished all the necessary preparations.
Once you receive them, all of you will be able to use the Dominators.
Thank you.
All I have to do now is find the one who makes this society what it is.
The Bureau people are here.
They say they want to talk to you, Dr. Masuzaki.
Show them in.
Right away.
Looks like they're here.
I really appreciate your help.
I should be the one thanking you.
I wish you all the best in your plan, Kirito.
You're Dr. Masuzaki Youhei, right?
Could I ask you to come with us voluntarily?
I'm rather a poor talker.
I'm worried that I won't be able to properly convey Kamui's gospel.
Inspector Shimotsuki, I want you to look into Kamui's medical records as soon as we get back.
Is that necessary?
We have a witness. All we need in order to get answers now is an interrogation.
If Kamui helps him maintain a clear Psycho-Pass as well,
we can't assume he'll be honest.
We need to corroborate his story.
Kunizuka, there's something I want you to...
help me with...
I guess you'll do. Give me a hand.
He suffered serious depression and became dependent on medication.
Poor thing.
He improved his skills to use as a defense mechanism, which helped him become a Holo designer.
How cute. That's just like him.
If that were the whole story, he wouldn't have been disposed to become an Enforcer.
The authorization level for the surgery records is quite high.
Why?
How should I know? I'll leave the rest to you.
One possibility is that it involved patents for drugs or technology.
Drug patents...
If I'm not mistaken, one of the leading organizations in drug patents in Japan is...
The Tougane Foundation.
On second thought, I'll handle this.
Keep working on the Holos as per Inspector Tsunemori's orders.
G-Got it.
Can I ask you to interrogate him, Professor?
I don't think there'll be much need for interrogation this time around.
He's planning to tell us everything. Right?
I won't talk to just anyone.
But fortunately, it seems that you're wise and trustworthy.
Thanks.
I'll tell you about Kamui.
Shou just informed me via email that he finished with the 185 aged-up Holos.
He's...
That guy is...
the programmer at the Military Drone facility.
I remember seeing some others, too.
I think this guy was in charge of vehicle maintenance.
You probably think that one man, Kamui, has been making fools of you.
But that's wrong. He was never alone at all.
Forget the third or the fourth Holo.
Kamui...
has been right beside us this whole time.
All is calm, all is bright
A whispering angel falls to Earth
Now it eats your body whole
It's my fault
You open your eyes
and in their grey-blue depth
I see your coldness
Call my name and give me a kiss
Embrace me
with your empty body
There is still life of sorts
left within you
in blood red
I can see a brilliant eternity
You sing to me of it
What was I born for?
Love me
Don't let me go
This story is a work of fiction. The names of all individuals and organizations that appear
in this show are fictitious and any similarity to those in existence in the real world is purely coincidental.
This is a world where the mental state and personal tendencies of humans can be quantified.
While all sorts of inclinations are recorded and policed, these measured numbers used to judge people's souls are commonly called "Psycho-Pass".