Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Umm, excuse me.
Yes?
Where is the kitty litter?
Oh! Kitty litter, is it?!
Here! Right this way!
This way!
Over here we have paper litter, cypress litter, soy pulp litter, gravel litter.
Litter you can put in the burnable garbage.
Litter you can flush down the toilet.
Clumping litter.
Non-clumping litter.
Odorless litter.
Anti-bacterial litter.
What were you looking for today?
S-So many varieties!
U-Umm...
Yes?
Umm.
What should I buy?
This is your first time, isn't it?
That's right. It's bewildering, isn't it?
I was like that too.
First, tell me about how you're keeping it.
Okay.
Litter you can flush down the toilet?
It's easier because it's flushable.
After all, dogs and cats are prohibited in this apartment complex.
Ah, I see.
And we can't put kitty litter in the garbage!
Yeah.
Huh?
Kitty, we bought something great, okay?
What?
Huh?
My play bed got all lumpy!
Huh?!
Yay!
Play! Play!
Gotta pee!
Ah!
It peed again in a place like this!
Pee! Pee!
You're supposed to pee in the toilet, right?
That's right.
Where are you going?
To kitty's toilet.
P-Pee in a place like this...
Even though it was my play bed!