Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hey!
Ah, Chi.
Want to play?
Come here.
Dad will take me to a horrible place, so I hate him!
Is she still angry about the animal hospital?
Man, she scratched it this much!
Oh dear.
Did Chi do this?
Yes, she did.
She was scratching away with a grinding sound.
Oh well, it's all right.
It's not all right!
Note: Just under $500.
This sofa cost fifty thousand yen!
I'm itching to do something.
Scratching this is no good.
This is no good either.
It doesn't stand out that much.
It does!
Huh?
Shouldn't I wash those jeans?
They're all torn!
The torn look is in!
Don't you know anything about vintage jeans fashion?
Ah, Chi!
These are cool, Dad.
Is Chi the only one that gets it?
This feels good!
Please stop!
Hey!
Hey, Chi!
Stop it! Stop it!
Swing! Swing!
No! No!
These are vintage!
Chi!
Chi, are you okay?
Let's tear them one more time!
You shouldn't do that.
I said you shouldn't do that.
Dad!
Chi, no!
Chi likes Dad's jeans.
Isn't that good, Dad?
You've made up with Chi.
These are cool, Dad.
Although these are more expensive than the sofa...