Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I'm going home, Mama.
Huh?
Where is this?
Kitty is moving!
You're the one that fell at the grassy place!
Why are you here too?
Oh, you've woken up?
Are you feeling better?
It's a dead end!
Oh dear.
I wonder if we scared it?
What's that?
I thought it might be hungry.
I wonder if it will drink.
I smell something yummy!
Oh! Milk!
Are we keeping kitty?
Well you see, dogs and cats aren't allowed in our apartment.
It won't work here, so we'll have to find someone to take it.
I'm full!
I'm going home!
Kitty, do you want to go outside?
Home! Home! Home!
Home! Home! A-Ah...
Youhei!
It will be caught by the landlord, right?
What's wrong?
I'll hide here just a little bit longer.