Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Dad, what's that?
This?
It's a board for Chi to sharpen her claws on.
What do you think, Chi?
What's that?!
If you use this, you can sharpen your claws as much as you want.
Do you like it, Chi?
What?
This is cool!
Why doesn't Chi use the stuff we buy, no matter what it is?
I think all we can do is to teach her patiently.
This really is cool!
Chi.
Not that.
This.
Look.
What's this?
That's right.
That's where you sharpen your claws.
This is a nice bed!
Chi's playing.
Chi.
Look.
Watch me.
Put up your nails like this.
And this way you can sharpen your own claws.
There.
You try it too, Chi.
Chi's not sharpening them.
Clean! Clean!
Not that.
Look.
Like this...
And then...
you do this.
What are you doing?
Okay, you understand now, right?
Chi's paw...
Dad squeezed...
Ouch!
Oh my.
She got you.
She got mad at me.
Chi's still mad.
What should I do?
Somehow or other, we need to trim Chi's claws.
Dad, would you please do that?
Eh?
Well...
I'll give it my best and see how it goes.
I wonder if Chi will let me trim her claws quietly...