Edited at https://subtitletools.com
What's this?
H-Hey, Chi.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
I'll figure something out.
So take Youhei.
Well then, we're off.
We'll be back.
Have a safe trip.
Now then, Chi-chan.
And then you know...
Good morning.
Ah, good morning.
Have a safe trip.
And you know, it really looked like one.
What did?
Chi, let go.
Listen, Chi.
Pets are forbidden in this apartment complex.
It'll be a world of trouble if you're found.
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
Huh?
Where did it go?
Good morning, Yamada-san.
Good morning.
Say, have you heard?
About what?
It seems someone is keeping a cat in this apartment complex.
Eek.
What should I do?
We've been exposed!
I heard that it came along the veranda.
A cat this big.
Eh?
A big one?
That's right.
A cat this big.
That big?
Surprising, isn't it?
Safe.
I didn't know.
Since cats are forbidden in this apartment complex, right?
Right.
Oh my, what's wrong?
Umm, just a little something...
You look pale.
Ah, that's right!
I left a pan on the stove.
See you later.
Mom, this is amazing!
You can see outside!
Safe.
You can't do that, Chi.
If you're found, it'll be a world of trouble.
Outside!
Outside! Outside!