Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Dad, these are cool!
After the animal hospital, Chi wouldn't ever come near me, but...
now Chi is so tame.
B-But, these jeans are expensive.
They're vintage!
I'd finally bought them!
Ah, what should I do?
It's all right, isn't it?
One pair of tattered jeans.
It's not all right!
Sorry, Chi.
What's up with Dad?
Who knows?
Oh my...
How about these, Chi?
If you use these jeans, then...
you can scratch them as much as you like.
Not these.
Huh?
Apparently she only likes the jeans from before.
But...
Ah!
No!
Chi, the sofa is a no-no!
Goodness me.
I wanna scratch.
Ah!
Not that.
Dad, let go!
Let go!
Mum and Dad are getting in Chi's way!
Chi seems to be sulking.
But it'll cause problems if she leaves scratches here and there.
That's it!
So you're looking for a kitty scratching post.
We have some made of cardboard that are long and slender or round.
And some that are covered with cloth or carpet.
Also some thin mats, shaped like a house or a doll.
What were you looking for today?
The most common one please.
Okay!
Thank you for your continued patronage.
Chi!
Hold out just a little bit longer.
I'll be home soon.
Huh?
Chi!
Dad's vintage jeans!
Just as I thought, these are cool.