Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Chi, there you go!
Wait!
Yes, it looks good.
It's been a long time since the last class reunion.
I have to make an effort.
Now, makeup, makeup.
I can't reach it.
I can't reach.
Mom.
Could you get Chi's toy?
Toy?
Wait a second.
There you go.
Thanks.
Now I have to prepare.
There, Chi.
Yay!
Now I'm done.
All I have to do is put on my ring...
Huh?
I know I took it off here a while ago.
Eh? Why isn't it here?
Is it there?
Not here. Not here.
Not here!
No!
I wonder where I put it.
Is it in the bathroom?
Huh?
I really wonder where I put it.
Mom, could you get the toy?
Eh? Wait a second.
Hey, did you see Mom's ring?
Eh?
I didn't see it.
That's strange.
It must be here somewhere.
I'm going to get it!
Huh?
There it is!
I'm so glad!
Chi, thanks.
No, no, I want to play!
So you found my ring for me.
Thank you.
Mom, let me go!