Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Thanks for inviting me.
No, not at all.
Let's hide here, okay?
Oh! What I wanted to talk to you about...
is a cat.
A cat?!
Yes...
Huh?
Propping your screen door?
Th-That's because...
Is it because of that cat?
So, just as I thought.
That bear cat enters your house too, doesn't it?
Bear cat?
Suzuki-san is also propping his door.
He says that the bear cat enters by opening the screen door.
O-Oh, is that so?
We're safe.
This is fun!
No, stop it, Chi.
Huh?
I wonder what that is.
U-Umm, Youhei is cleaning the bathroom.
Huh?
Right, right, his favorite thing now is cleaning.
K-Kids are mysterious.
Really, they are mysterious.
This is nice.
Chi!
He's quite enthusiastic.
Umm, could you tell me the rest?
Oh, yes!
Rumor says that someone in this apartment complex is keeping that bear cat.
Do you know anything about it?
No.
Nothing.
No!
Hush.
Thanks for the tea.
If you hear anything, tell me.
Youhei-kun, are you all right?
There is...
She found it.
This is bad.
So you're cleaning the walls too, Youhei-kun.
You really are an impressive boy.
Well, see you.
We're safe.
Chi, there you go.
Yay!
This is fun.