Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hmm?
I wonder what that is?
Oh my!
Youhei!
What?
You left these in your trouser pockets.
Put them away properly.
Okay!
Youhei, let's play!
Chi?
Huh?
Ugh, it got away.
Aw, it went in.
Ball!
Gimme!
Hey, gimme!
Ouch!
Amazing!
Wait!
Wait! Wait!
What's that sound?
This is quite a ruckus.
Hurry and clean up the super balls!
Okay!
Making the place this untidy...
Chi is dangerous with a super ball.
Ball! Ball!
That's true.
This is fun! This is fun!
Chi?
I heard that your manga's about to come out!
Chi's book?
The latest comic, volume 5 and "Neko-moto nya."
On sale Wednesday this week!
I'm happy!
I'll be waiting at bookstores all over Japan!
Koudansha!