Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's a souvenir.
Open it and see.
Oh, wow!
I'm scared to hold it.
What, what!
Chi.
Huh?
It's weird!
A crab.
Huh?
A-Amazing!
Juri-chan's amazing.
This is nothing.
I feel like I'm going to lose...
Huh?
Here!
I won't lose!
Juri-chan...
Don't surprise Chi so much, okay?
Okay.
There.
Chi!
Come here!
She's on a rampage.
I need to be careful.
What are you doing?!
Juri-chan, what are you doing?
Animals like it when you pet around their necks.
Is that so?
See?
Our horse and dog say it feels good too!
Eh?
Thank goodness.
It was just petting.
Chi!
I have a way to make you even happier!
What are you doing?!
There, there, there, there.
There!
What are you doing?!
Chi, you're cute!
There, there, there.
Juri-chan, stop.
Our dog really likes this!
There!
See? She's happy!
Huh?
Juri, you can't be rough with Chi-chan.
She's just a kitten.
Chi?
That was fun!