Edited at https://subtitletools.com
What do you think?
Hey, Chi.
It's lots of fun!
What's this?
Hey, Dad.
A kitty toy.
It seems kitties like to play with these.
Eh?
Chi is going to have lots of fun!
Now then Chi, it's okay to play as much as you want.
Ah!
Huh?
Chi's not playing.
I see.
It doesn't know how to use it yet, since it's just a kitten.
If you do this, see.
Yes!
Huh?
It's not playing.
That's strange.
Listen Chi, you do this.
Make it move!
Chi, it's your play thing.
Then, next is...
Umm... Umm...
I'm home.
Oh my.
Now then, how about this?
It's calling me!
You bought so many kitty toys?
There's even this.
You said, "Bring it on!"
Eh?
Chi seems to prefer that.
This is fun!
This thing is fun!
So...
What's this?
This is fun!
Chi is happy...
Oh well, I guess it's okay.