Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I'm home.
Welcome back.
Chi, here's a present for you.
What's that?
It's a kanikama, a cat snack.
Snack?
There, Chi.
It's nice.
There.
It tastes good!
So you think it tastes good.
I want to give her one too!
Here.
Dad, more!
Okay, okay.
There.
This tastes good!
If she has too many snacks, she won't eat her dinner.
Youhei and Chi are similar that way.
Yeah, you're right.
Chi, you can have more tomorrow.
Dad, more!
This is the last one for today.
Dad.
Y-Yes, I know.
Dad, gimme more! Gimme more!
There, Chi. Here's your dinner.
Huh?
I don't want this.
Chi.
It's because you gave her too many snacks.
Sorry.
No, no.
Chi.
If you're not going to eat your dinner, I'm going to put it away.
Gimme the yummy stuff!
Have it your own way!
Good night.
I'm hungry.
Chi.
You're hungry, aren't you?
There.
Mom.
Don't eat just snacks.
If you also eat nutritious food, you'll get big and strong.
This tastes good,
Mom!