Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Chi...
Oh, that's nice.
I think I'll be able to take a cute photo.
You don't need to come here.
What's this?
Not that...
Okay, Chi.
Just like that, just like that.
Huh?
This pose is good too.
Just the tail.
Dad, it's prey!
I'll capture this facial expression.
I'm home!
Did you take a photo?
A photo?
Remember how Juri-chan in Hokkaido said she wanted us to send her a photo of Chi?
Show me!
Huh?
What's this?
The little black thing on the bottom is Chi's shadow.
You should capture Chi.
When I try to take her picture, she runs away.
Huh?
They ran away.
That's it!
Youhei, it's up to you.
Huh?
Daddy, like this?
Is this okay?
Cute!
This is great!
Oh, my...
Chi...
Youhei, what are you doing?
Chi, over there, over there.
Huh?
Not there, over there, Chi!
Here!
Huh?
Leave this kind of thing to me.
Hey! Hey! Hey! Hey!
Chi, you're cute.
Here's my chance!
This is the only one I could get of her face.
That surprised me.