Edited at https://subtitletools.com
What?
Humans are not comrades.
Yeah, they're not comrades.
Yeah.
I knew it.
See ya.
Huh?
Where are you going?
I'm going back home where my humans live.
It's time for my meal.
What?
Even if they're not comrades?
And everyone is waiting for me.
What?
Well, it's something called a give-and-take relationship.
I'm hungry.
I'm back here just to have a meal.
Yay! It's temaki sushi.
Oh, Chi!
You were a good girl, putting up with the injection.
Huh?
This is a reward.
Do you want some?
Come here, Chi.
There.
Chi, it's tuna.
Huh?
I have fried egg.
I have salmon roe.
I prefer tuna first.
This is mine.
It tastes good.
Chi.
Wasn't that nice?
Chi, it's nice, isn't it?
Chi, did you like it too?
It was nice, everyone.
So it tasted good to you as well?
Good for you, Chi.
If you'd like it, I'll be your comrade!