Edited at https://subtitletools.com
You don't happen to know someone who could keep it, do you?
Hmm...
Mama! Mama!
Mama!
Mom!
Chi's sound asleep.
Sure is.
Babies sleep well, don't they?
We can't keep Chi, but we can't seem to find someone to take it.
Now then, it's beddy-bye for you too, Youhei.
Night night!
Yup, good night.
Mom! Let's sleep together!
Okay, okay.
You still can't be by yourself?
Huh?
Where's Mama?
I'm scared, Mama!
I wonder if Chi can survive alone.
We can't find anyone to take it.
Dogs and cats are prohibited in these apartments,
but it's still that kind of baby kitty, right?
That's true.
We even gave it a name,
and abandoning it would be unbearable.
I slept well!
Huh?
Are you worried about something?
I suppose we'll have to keep it.