Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Huh?
Is this Chi's fur?
Chi, what's up?
Are you itchy?
Oh my, Dad.
What happened to your back?
Huh?
Huh?!
Well, there's a lot of fur.
I guess it's her season to shed.
Do we have to brush her?
Maybe.
Huh?
I got some sweets as gifts, so I thought you might like some.
Thank you very much.
Then can I come in?
Eh?
In?
U-Umm...
It's quite messy.
I don't mind.
U-U-Umm...
It'll be bad if she sees we have a cat.
Where should I hide Chi?
Dad, what are you doing?
Excuse me.
Oh?
W-Welcome.
Nice to see you.
Your house is in good order.
Take a seat on the sofa.
You two take a seat, too.
This is really nice.
I'm on a diet.
Why, surely you can have one?
Yes, of course.
Oh! What a beautiful bird.
Eh?
Look there.
Eh? Where?
Can't you see it?
I don't see any bird.
Good morning.
Youhei, take care of her.
Eh?
This is really nice.
Thanks.
Oh! I forgot to make some tea.
Hush.
Thank you for the sweets.
Well, say hello to Youhei-chan.
U-Umm...
Eh?
Chi's fur...
Th-There's some dust...
I don't care.
These are my everyday clothes.
It won't take long.
I wonder if she noticed Chi.
I assume it's okay.
But we have to do something about this fur.