Edited at https://subtitletools.com
We're finally here, the animal hospital.
Let me out!
It's open!
Huh?
Chi!
What is this place?!
Chi.
Chi, come on out.
It's Dad!
Dad, I was so scared!
There, there.
As a precaution, please don't let it out of the cage.
S-Sorry.
Yamada-san!
Yamada Chi-san!
Ah, yes.
Dad, I don't like it here!
Let's go home!
Dad, let's go home!
Huh?
You took it in, you said?
Let's see.
Two or three months old I'd say.
It's a girl.
Oh, a girl?
What on earth is this place?
Her ears are clean.
There's no sign of conjunctivitis.
Her teeth and gums are both clean too.
Right, I'll take her temperature.
Hold her down please.
Okay.
No! No! No!
What are you going to do with me?
I never want to come here again.
It says "Ms. Yamada Chi"!
Isn't that amazing, Chi has a surname.
"Ms" as well.
It was really tough.
Right, Chi?
I hate Dad!
Chi hates me.