Edited at https://subtitletools.com
This is cool! This is cool!
That's right, it's a kitten.
Is that so...
No, thanks anyway.
No good, huh?
I can't think of any other places to call.
Yeah, we shouldn't abandon Chi at this point, but...
I'll catch it again!
But cats and dogs are prohibited in this apartment.
Ah! I hadn't called this person yet!
This is Yamada. We went to the community seminar together.
Yes, the truth is...
Eh?! Really?!
What is it?
What's the matter?
Okay, talk to you later.
Is it really true?
They said they wanted a kitten. They'd been looking for one.
What?
What? What?
But, it makes me sad.
They said they'll come to see Chi soon...
I see.
S-So cute!
What, what?!
It's a good kitty, it can even go to the toilet properly.
It knows its own name too.
Chi.
Who is this?!
It seems to be a little nervous, eh.
A stranger came around, so maybe it's surprised?
Th-That surprised me!
Usually it's affectionate with people.
Yeah. Chi-chan is really cute!
By all means I'd like it to be mine.
Eh?
Thank goodness.
That's a relief.
Ah, but this comes after talking with my husband,
and it was actually my husband who said, "I want to have a cat."
Well then, I'll call this evening.
Okay.
See you, Chi-chan.
I'll see you soon too, Youhei-kun.
Well then, I'll be on my way.
Hey.
Is Chi going to that lady's house?
Eh?
What's wrong, everybody?