Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hey, is Chi going to the vet?
Yeah.
It's time for her vaccinations.
She has to be injected so she won't get ill.
Youhei, let's play!
S-Scary.
No!
Ah! Chi!
Safety check before going out.
Yay!
The landlady is...
If now's the time, then...
Do your best.
All right.
Oh my, Yamada-san.
On your way out in such a hurry?
Ah, no.
It's not that, umm...
Oh my.
Huh?
I was just wandering around here,
and I thought, "The trees and grass are pretty."
I agree that the foliage is nice.
This is cool!
Well, then...
What is it?
L-Lovely weather today, isn't it?
That's true.
Well, then...
Is there something else?
Umm, well, err, umm...
It's nothing.
Well, then...
I-It's over!
Ah!
Ah! That cat!
Hey! Wait!
Wait right there!
We're saved.
We were saved by that black bear of a cat, of all things.
Amazing!
The black one caught something good.
Huh?
What was Chi doing?
I wonder what it was?
Gotcha.
Huh?
I wonder what it was?