Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Outside!
Just a little bit more!
I got up!
I can see!
I can see outside!
No!
You'll be found!
We're probably safe.
I didn't think she'd be able to get up on the bay window.
It's only a matter of time until she's found.
What should we do?
If it's come to this, I'll have to prevent you from going into Dad's room.
Okay?
No more going into Dad's room.
Open it!
No way!
Cats are forbidden!
I could see outside!
I said no!
I could see. Open it!
Open it!
No way!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
Where's Mom?
Shopping.
Where's Chi?
So she could sit on the bay window?
It's because she's not allowed in Dad's room.
Oh well, it can't be helped.
What's that?
Ah, this?
It was an impulse buy.
It's really cute.
What's that?!
Hey, Chi.
Boring!
Oh, no! She's really stubborn.