Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Chi.
For your sake, we're going for a health checkup.
That's right.
Be a good kitten, Chi.
What's going on?
Well then, we're counting on you.
Yeah.
I'll be going to the animal hospital as fast as possible.
Hello.
L-Landlady!
What are you doing together like this?
Are you on your way out?
W-Well, you could say so.
No. It's just Dad who's leaving for work.
Oh, is that so?
Lovely weather we're having.
You could say it's an ideal day for working...
Yes.
But it's going to get cloudy this afternoon.
Is that so?
Then perhaps I should bring in the laundry.
That's right.
It would be a bother if the dry laundry got wet again.
I should bring those in too.
W-Well then, I should be on my way.
Have a safe trip.
And then-
I just heard a cat crying...
I wonder where it is?
It sounded like it was very close.
Somebody might be keeping one here!
It's all over...
We'll be driven out of our home.
What should I do?
Oh! It was Youhei?
I thought it was a real cat!
D-Dear, your customers are waiting.
Eh?
Ah! That's right, my business.
Well then, excuse me.
Sorry for interrupting you.
We're safe.
Let me out!
Will we be all right from here on?