Edited at https://subtitletools.com
It's Blackie!
Where are you going?
Are you going to wander aimlessly again?
Wander aimlessly?
Chi will go too!
Don't follow me.
Where are you going?
Huh?
Mom, where's Chi?
She's not here?
What?!
Oh, no!
I forgot to push it completely closed!
She couldn't have gone outside?
She's not here.
What should I do?!
If someone sees her, it'll be bad!
I need to look for her!
Oh?
Coming!
There we go.
Hey, hey, what are you going to do?
If you're going to follow me, keep quiet.
Okay.
Good things!
Don't get side-tracked.
That's the story.
I'm asking every household whether cats have caused any damage.
Is that so?
Don't do anything unnecessary!
It smells good!
Let's hurry and go back.
Chi too!
Hot!
Take this, and this, and this!
What are you doing?
Hurry up!
Would you like some tea?
Oh, if you don't mind...
Hurry! Run!
Take this, and this, and this!
I was actually just thinking about having lunch...
Hello!