Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Chi was looking outside?
That's right.
She was sitting where she could be seen clearly from outside.
That was close.
I was so glad they didn't find out.
Don't sit on the bay window anymore, Chi.
I can see outside!
Didn't I tell you not to sit there?!
It's good no one saw you.
Listen.
If you're found, it'll be a world of trouble.
That's why you can't sit on the bay window.
Okay?
You understood?
She doesn't understand at all...
It should be all right if there are no stepping stones.
No more sitting up there.
Now we should be okay.
Yes, she can't reach.
Quickly! Quickly!
Chi seems really interested in the bay window.
Won't she sit up there again?
It's fine now.
I put away the stepping stones.
Oh my.
These pajamas seem to have gotten smaller.
Rather than the pajamas getting smaller, Youhei has gotten bigger.
Yeah!
Kids keep on growing.
Just a little bit more.
Just a little bit more!