Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Huh? Huh?
Huh?
This is fun!
Hey, Chi.
Don't disturb me when I'm cleaning.
What's this? What's this?
Chi.
I'll play too!
Let it go.
That scared me.
Are you all right, Chi?
Mom, I hate that bang.
Chi.
Now you know how painful it is
when Chi is mad at you.
Eh?
It was really hard after I took her to the vet.
No, I'm fine.
Eh?
She was just a little bit surprised.
She'll forget and return to her old self.
Dad, let's go.
Yeah.
We're going to the book store now.
Have a safe trip.
Huh?
Chi, I'm really sorry about before.
Let's make up.
No! No!
I hate Mom!
Was that so scary?
That's it.
There, there.
It's fun.
Oh!
Heh!
No!
You'll do that bang again.
Come on.
What about this?
There. There. There.
There.
Chi.
I'll give you a snack.
Come here.
Oh!
It's the yummy one!
There, there.
There you go.
This tastes good!
There.
I'll give you some more.
This tastes good.
I'm so glad!
Good for you, Mom.
Eh?
Why?
Dad forgot his wallet.
Now I know it's really painful when Chi is mad at you.
Mom, more!