Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I wonder if Blackie will come by!
I wonder if we'll go play soon?
Did you see, Yamada-san?
Eh?
The notice in the mailboxes.
Notice?
It seems to be starting in earnest.
Pet control.
According to this apartment's lease, pets are prohibited.
Get rid of your pet immediately, or leave.
Ah, there's no way we can let Chi out now.
Yeah.
I wonder if Blackie will come?
Ah! Oh, yeah!
Chi will go play with him!
Outside! Outside!
Huh?
It won't open.
Dad!
Dad! Open this.
Chi, you want to go out?
Open it, open it!
Sorry, Chi.
This is hard for Dad too.
Huh?
Outside! Outside!
Mom!
Chi!
Chi wants to go out!
Sorry.
You can't go out.
Mom! What are you doing!?
Outside!
No!
I we get caught, Chi, we won't be able to live here anymore.
Mom!
Outside!
Chi...
Chi?
Let's play inside.
No!
Chi wants to go outside!
Outside! Outside!
Outside!
Chi...