Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hide and seek with Chi?
Yes...
I wonder where Chi is hiding.
We'll soon find her if we all look together.
Huh?
Where am I?
I wonder what I was doing.
Umm...
Yes! It's hide and seek!
Youhei still hasn't found me.
Huh?
It's different from a while ago.
What's going on?
What?!
I can't get through!
I won this game!
Chi isn't anywhere.
It's going to be all right.
Let's think about this calmly.
Yeah.
Places that Chi likes...
Enclosed places like boxes or bags...
Behind doors or under laundry...
She likes narrow gaps like this.
Anyway, let's search some more.
Chi?
Chi.
Chi!
I'm hungry.
We really couldn't find Chi.
What should we do?
Let's think about it some more.
Places like boxes.
Gaps this narrow...
Oh!
Could...
that...
be...
Eh?
I don't like it!
I want to lose!
Huh?
There you are!
I've been found!
Chi's great at hide and seek.
Yeah.
Sorry for forgetting you, Chi.
You win at hide and seek, Youhei!
I lost.