Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Okay then, Chi.
Aren't you a good girl?
Now stay calm.
Dad, what are you doing?
Let's see...
It says if you hold the root, the claw will emerge.
I've never clipped a cat's claws before.
My heart is racing.
It's shining.
What's this?!
No! No!
Ah, Chi. Don't move.
No!
Let go!
What are you doing?!
Please stay still.
What if you hold her tighter?
A-All right!
Give it your best, Dad!
I cut the transparent part on the end of this, right?
It says if you cut the colored part, it will bleed.
Eh?
It will bleed?
I can't do it!
I'm so scared that I can't clip them.
Let me go!
Huh?
Chi, be quiet, okay?
What are you doing?!
Hooray!
You cut it well.
Yeah.
I finally cut one.
Ouch...
Only nine more to go...
That hurt...
It was rough, but we trimmed Chi's claws properly.
Isn't that great?
I wonder if she hates me again.
Chi!
Chi.
Let's make up.
I hate Dad!