Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Chi, where are you?
Chi.
Chi?
I wonder where she went.
Did she...
go out?
I couldn't get a souvenir.
There'll be other chances.
What's this?
It's my territory...
Get out of my territory!
Geez.
My car!
Run!
Wait!
Hey!
Where did she go?
Is she all right?
Did she get lost?
There are cars and other dangers outside.
There are scary dogs...
Chi!
Dad, I'm home!
Where on earth have you been?
You made me worry.
That black bear of a cat!
Was it here again?
Yeah.
It ran away in that direction.
It's a black cat.
And there was another.
A small cat was with it.
I wonder if it's still around here.
Those two ran in that direction.
Let's definitely find them.
Right.
Let's find them.
What did it do?
It peed on my car.
Oh my.
Come to think of it, that happened to someone else a while ago.
We're saved.
See ya.
Let's get a souvenir next time.
Yeah!
See you again!