Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Huh?
There, it's milk.
Milk?
Is it all right to give a cat milk?
It's all right if it's not that much.
Yummy!
I want some more!
Thanks for the meal.
Huh?
Milk!
What should I do?
Youhei.
Which one do you want for your snack?
This one.
Wait a second.
Mom, could you get milk for me?!
Please give it to me!
Mom, hurry.
Yes, yes.
Huh?
Where's my milk?
Yay!
Oh!
Oh, my.
Chi, you are clever.
I brought my plate.
Could you pour some milk?
Yes, yes.
Milk.
Huh?
You like crunchies a lot, right?
Good for you.
This isn't it.
I'm home.
Oh!
I-I-I-It's milk!
Mom, I definitely want milk.
I'll give you that.
Milk!
Huh?
You like plastic bags a lot, don't you?
No!
This isn't it!
I want milk!
Anyone else want to drink milk?
Yes!
Me too.
This is nice!
Hey Chi. Don't you want to drink?
What's this? What's this?
She's so absorbed in playing, she can't hear you.