Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Dad sure is late.
Even though I have to go shopping for dinner soon.
Youhei.
What is it?
I think Dad will be home soon, so be a good boy with Chi until then.
Okay!
Well then...
I'm off.
Ch-Chi...
A walk?
Going out?
Chi go!
Chi is house-sitting with me.
Do you understand?
Okay?
Let's go out!
Ch-Chi.
I can't go shopping like this.
Chi, dinner time.
Let's eat!
It's a chance to...
You shouldn't do that, Chi.
This tactic doesn't work.
I'm home!
Great timing!
What's wrong?
Well then, if you can go and get these.
Yeah. The side dishes for dinner, right?
Take care of that for me.
Have a safe trip!
Going out!
Now, now, Chi.
Thanks for your continued patronage.
Soba noodle shop here.
In the end we couldn't go shopping.
We have to teach Chi soon.
Teach her what?
House-sitting.
House-sitting?
I wonder if Chi will be okay alone...
Well, Chi seems to be getting used to this house.
I'm sure she'll be fine soon enough.
That's right!
Let's do that!
All right.
Now that we've decided.
Next Sunday will be Chi's first house-sitting!
Yeah!
What?