Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Here, here, Yamada-san!
Eh?
Hey, did you see, did you?
See? The second floor...
That's what they get for keeping a cat!
Apparently, there was no way they could give it up.
They decided to move.
Moving?!
That's right!
They were just loading their boxes.
Surprising...
It's so sudden, after all.
What's everyone doing?
The black bear cat's family chose their cat over their house, didn't they?
Yeah...
That's right.
Outside!
I'm so sorry.
As the landlady, I had no choice.
No, same here.
We're sorry.
Well then, take care.
Oh!
You were keeping two cats, right?
Where's the kitten?
We only have this black cat.
Eh?!
Ah, then, that kitten?
Then, excuse us.
Thanks.
It's Blackie!
Hey! Hey!
Where will that black bear cat go?
A faraway place?
I wonder.
Chi won't be able to see the black bear cat anymore?
They were getting along so well.
Oh!
What an amazing way to go out!
See you later!