Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Chi.
Wanna play?
I'm busy at the moment!
Huh?
Chi, let's play!
I'm home.
Welcome home.
A postcard from Grandma has come.
A postcard?
Hey, read it!
It says, "I've gone to Kyoto with Grandpa."
Kyoto?
There are lots of old temples and shrines. It's a lovely place.
Look.
Is Youhei-kun well?
Yeah! I'm well!
That's nice. Kyoto, huh?
We went there a long time ago.
Eh? I don't remember this place.
What are those three doing by themselves?
It was before you were born, Youhei.
There's a temple called Kiyomizudera and...
Kiyomizudera?
It's really high.
It's scary looking down.
Huh?
But the scenery is great.
I'm the only one being left out.
That's it!
I want to go and see it too!
Chi is here!
It's been a while since we went traveling.
I want to go somewhere!
That's true.
Once in a while, it's nice to go on holiday together.
Umm...
Is there somewhere you want to go, Youhei?
Hmm...
How about that?!
I want to go and check out that place.
Where is that?
Is it some place I know?
I suppose Youhei could enjoy that too.
That's true.
I don't want to be left out!
Chi!
We can't see the postcard.
Chi doesn't want too much attention,
but she doesn't want to be neglected.
After all, she's the type that wants to be right in the middle.