Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[The Shinsengumi has 45 articles strictly enforced
by the laws of the "Kyukuchu Hatto."]
[Hijikata, the man who created those laws, couldn't
possibly...?! And "the man" who returned is...?!]
[Shinsengumi Headquarters]
Did you hear? It seems that guy is returning
to Edo after finishing his job.
It's Sensei, right? His baggage
arrived already.
The new weapons he got are inside.
I heard he also picked up some
good quality swords,
so the top members are scrambling.
They're really lucky.
I want a new sword, too.
Ah-hem.
Ah, Yamazaki-san.
Ah! Could that sword be...
...an Osafune Mark II?!
[Note: Parody of Bizen Osafune, a famous sword.]
That's great! It's got the brand
name on it. So cool!
Well, it's not like I came
here to show it off.
I just happened to pass by. By chance...
I'm jealous.
Just a little... Please let
me try a practice swing!
Ah, of course you can.
Wow! I can really feel that
brand-name difference!
Additionally, it's waterproof. I don't
want to brag, you know...
Hey, what are you guys making
such a fuss about?
Ah, Captain Okita.
Look at Yamazaki-san's sword...
Huh?
That sword is a...
[Note: It's rumored the historical Soji Okita
used a sword named Kikuichimonji.]
Kikuichimonji RX-78!
It has a built-in digital music player with
a maximum playing time of 124 hours!
It's the Kikuichimonji RX-78!
It costs twice as much as the Osafune!
The swords at the captain's
level are really something!
Hmm... Is this sword that great?
I just picked it up without thinking,
so I didn't realize that.
Huh?
What's that stick? Yamazaki... What
is that? Did you buy that?
It almost looks rusted.
Captain, please let me try a
few practice swings for a bit!
Wow! This first-class stuff
is really amazing!
It sounds completely different!
The deep bass is amazing!
Hey, what's going on? Why
is it so noisy this morning?
Chief! I'm sorry. Well...
That sword is...
The Kotetsu Z-Second.
[Note: Kotetsu Nagasone was a famous swordsmith. The historical Isami Kondo was said to own a fake Kotetsu sword.]
Not only does it have digital
music equipment,
but it also has a special metal attachment on
the end that can be used as a floor cleaner!
It costs three times as much
as the Kikuichimonji! Cool!
You guys are using such cheap swords?
A sword is a samurai's soul.
If you use such shabby swords, it'll
reveal the true nature of your soul.
Kondo-san, you're great! We
won't ever be equal to you.
We should work harder and hope to some
day own stuff on your kind of level.
Kondo-san, can I try some practice
swings for a moment?
Ah, go right ahead.
There!
Kotetsu!
Ah, I'm sorry. I thought a sword like this
could cut through rock, but it failed.
You! You definitely did that on purpose!
You were jealous of my Kotetsu-chan...
You were jealous!
["Rules Are Made to be Broken"]
I'm not going to say a sword
is a samurai's soul.
Besides, I don't think the level of the
sword one carries raises his status.
For me, a sword is just a sword.
And that's the most important
thing to me.
Most important of all is a sword that can
break through the enemy's blade.
It seems you're overdoing
it as rashly as ever.
A sword can be used again
after it's been mended,
but humans don't work that way.
As long as a human doesn't
break, he can recover, right?
If you keep fighting in such a way that
damages your sword so much,
you'll end up being broken in two
pretty soon. That's what I meant.
This looks like a good sword.
Old man, until mine is repaired,
let me borrow this.
You can't use that one.
That sword comes with a story behind it.
What? You mean I can listen to music with
it or it can be used as a floor cleaner?
There's no question that sword
is terribly sharp. However...
It's cursed.
Cursed? You've got to be kidding me.
An ordinary sword user will be consumed
by the soul of that sword.
You won't able to handle it.
...Will you listen to my old
story for a moment?
It's a tragic tale of a reincarnated
demonic sword...
But I didn't listen to it.
In general, old men's stories tend to
be long. I don't have time for that.
Whether its price is high or low, whether
it can be used to listen to music,
or whether the sword is cursed,
it doesn't matter to me.
You must be Shinsengumi Vice-Chief
Toshiro Hijikata-dono.
Although you're a samurai, you've
sided with the Amanto for perks!
You're a traitor! We, the advanced
party of the Anti-Foreigner Faction,
are here to bring punishment
from heaven!
This is a chance to test it out.
Let me see how this cursed
demonic sword works.
Here we go!
I'm sorry!
Huh? What's this...?
Wh-What am I doing? My body
is moving on its own...
My mouth is moving on its own...
I'm sorry! My life! Please spare me!
I'll lick anything, even the
soles of your sandals!
Who's this pathetic guy?!
That's Toshiro Hijikata!
The man who is feared as the Demon
Vice-Chief! How miserable!
Wh-Wh-What's wrong with me?!
My body doesn't respond at all!
An ordinary sword user will be consumed
by the soul of that sword.
Don't tell me... This...?!
Why is the demonic sword's curse making
me act this way?! That's ridiculous...!
I don't know what's going on,
but we'll be paying you back for
everything you did to us before!
You just said you would lick the soles
of our sandals, didn't you?!
Then lick it!
Y-You bastard!
It may be a cursed sword or whatever,
but... I... Ugh... won't...!
Um... Please forgive
me by accepting this.
I have 3,000 yen.
But please don't take my Suica, because
I won't be able to go home without it.
[Note: Suica is a rechargeable IC card used
as a fare card on train lines in Japan.]
Don't screw with us!
What's with this guy?!
He's flip-flopping his personality!
Anyway, why does an adult like
you have only 3,000 yen?!
This is bad... There's something
totally wrong with me...
I'm a goner...
As things are...
I'll be finished...
Hey!
A familiar uniform.
A familiar stance.
But his face is...
I just saw a member of the Shinsengumi
being attacked, so I rushed over here...
What are you doing in a place like this,
Hijikata-kun?
You're...
A toast to Kamotaro Ito-kun's
return. Cheers!
Cheers!
Well, Ito Sensei, you did
a good job this time.
But that many weapons...
I wonder how you got those stingy people in
the government to loosen their purse strings!
Kondo-san, being stingy means being shrewd
enough to profit from a different viewpoint.
All you have to do is just explain that the government
will profit by making expenditures on us...
Though, just as you say, Kondo-san,
they're pertinacious people who don't care
about our hardships and groveling.
It wasn't easy for me to explain it to them,
in a way they could easily understand.
That's right! That's absolutely right!
They're pertinacious! They really are!
Kondo-san, what does
pertinacious mean?
You shut up! Kids should be quiet!
Kondo-san, if people like them stay at
the top, this country will be ruined.
We can't stay in a smoldering
place like this.
We have to move forward! We must
work toward a higher goal!
And we'll eventually become like the swords,
the keystones of this country.
I believe that saving this confused country is
the mission for those of us born as samurai.
For that, I wouldn't mind
giving my life to you!
Kondo-san, let's work hard together!
Right. Everyone, let's work
hard pertinacious!
No, you're using "pertinacious"
the wrong way.
Ito-san has started expressing
his valuable opinions again.
Even the Chief calls him "Sensei."
He's just a newcomer who
joined us only a year ago.
I wonder if he's getting so full of himself
because he was just assigned the title of advisor.
I'm not blaming him.
He's intelligent, really good at his job and
is fully proficient in Hokuto Itto Ryu.
[Note: The Hokuto Itto Ryu is a northern sword style.]
Vice-Chief is also intelligent, but he's
really only a battle strategist.
So Ito-san's the only person who
can manage political matters.
No wonder he is a great help to the chief.
Ito-san has hardly ever been in the headquarters...
but it might be about time...
For what?
I've never seen Ito-san and Hijikata-san talk
about each other, only about their jobs.
Hijikata-kun, I have something
to ask you.
What a coincidence... me, too.
You hate me,
don't you?
Because I'm Kondo-san's favorite,
and although I'm a newcomer,
I'm rising to fame so fast
that it threatens you.
I bet I'm an eyesore to you, right?
That's what you think? You want to advance
in your career, but I'm higher than you.
I bet I'm an eyesore to you, right?
It's a groundless suspicion, Hijikata-kun.
I don't think about that kind of thing.
That's good. It seems we have cleared
up any misunderstandings.
An eyesore...
It's even more than that.
Some time in the future, I'll kill you.
Toshi...
I heard about you from Ito Sensei.
That was a stroke of bad
luck. How's your injury?
Toshi...
Although we call ourselves samurai,
we're really just a bunch of country boys.
[Kyukuchu Hatto]
Even though that's what we
are, when facing death,
we're able to act more like
samurai than real samurai.
It was because of the Kyokuchu Hatto,
the strict laws you created,
that we can be like that.
It has 45 articles, encompassing everything
from daily behavior to manners,
and even battle preparation.
These are the strict laws that govern us.
If you break any one of those laws,
you'll have to commit seppuku.
That's your image of the ideal samurai.
We all agree.
Do you understand, Toshi?
You're the ideal samurai
model for everyone.
Everyone models himself after
you. Everyone watches you.
I'm not in a position to say this, but don't do
anything to betray the way of the samurai.
...He's quite a guy.
As quick as a flash, news of my
shameful behavior has spread.
Well, for him, it's the perfect opportunity
to defeat me and rise up the ladder.
Toshi, stop talking that way. Ito Sensei is
thinking about the spirit of the group...
I already told you to stop
calling him "Sensei."
Kondo-san, are you going to give
your position of Chief to him?
If that's not the case,
are you going to share your position as
head of the Shinsengumi with him?
Need I remind you that members are
unsure about how to treat him.
His former colleagues, who entered at
the same time, are already his allies.
Are you saying that Ito Sensei is trying
to take over the Shinsengumi?
Who knows?
But ever since he got here he's done nothing
but gather allies and influence.
...It's obvious he's up to something.
He's not as powerful as he wants
to be and he's not satisfied.
Kondo-san... If a snake has two heads...
...one either has to rot and fall off or the
ensuing feud will split the body in two.
I believe that Ito Sensei is a crucial
man for the Shinsengumi.
Hey, Toshi, we're not doing this
to ensure your own position.
We're doing this to protect Edo and
to stick to the ways of the samurai.
To get that wisdom, I'll ask for
anyone who can teach it.
It's natural to call the person
who teaches us "Sensei."
If you ask me to treat him
like a follower, I'll refuse.
I've never thought of you
guys as my followers.
As for the way of the samurai,
we're on equal footing.
Kondo-san, you don't
understand anything.
Pretty words won't help manage
the organization...!
Toshi!
Pretty Girl Samurai, Tomoe 5000 is here!
[Note: Parody of Sailor Moon]
Damn it! It's already started! I forgot
to record it! Tomoe-chan!
My body...again...
What am I watching?!
Punishment is complete.
Hey, hey, did you hear
about the Vice-Chief?
Hear what?
The Vice-Chief was attacked by Anti-Foreigner
Faction ronin the other day.
He was saved by Ito-san. But
you probably won't believe it.
The Vice-Chief knelt, bowed
and begged for his life.
It's impossible that something
like that could happen.
He would rather die than
do something like that.
He's the demon Vice-Chief.
The "demon."
But I heard it, too.
Hey, hey, cut it out already.
If this conversation is overheard,
we'll be in trouble.
It's against the Kyokuchu Hatto
rules to pass JUMP around.
"No reading of manga, except for MAGAZINE,
allowed in the headquarters."
[Note: MAGAZINE refers to "Weekly Shonen
MAGAZINE, a rival of Shonen JUMP.]
If someone sees us, we'll
have to commit seppuku.
Hijikata prefers MAGAZINE.
Let me see that.
Moreover, he liked yankee manga a decade
ago. It's hard for us JUMP fans.
[Note: Yankee manga is a genre
where bad boys fight others.]
V-Vice-Chief! Wh-When did you...?!
No, that's like nothing... That's...uh!
The thickness of the book is about the
same...so I bought it by mistake!
Hey!
Yes, sir!
"To Love-Ru" is really great.
[Note: "ToLoveる" is a manga in JUMP.]
I'm going to buy the manga.
"To-To-To Love-Ru?" Is
that the Vice-Chief?!
For argument's sake, "Boys be…"
[Note: "Boys be…" is a manga in
Weekly Shonen MAGAZINE.]
[MEETING ROOM]
These days, attacks by Anti-Foreigner
Faction ronin have increased.
So, make sure not to go off on your own.
Yes, sir!
Then, I'll assign today's
shift. Squad one is…
Damn it! My cell phone...!
You idiot!
If your cell phone rings during a meeting,
you'll have to commit seppuku
according to the Kyukuchu Hatto.
Hijikata-san! Nothing… I… My wife
is in labor, so she called me…
[Note: The Pretty Cure (a magical
girl series) song is playing.]
Hello, this is Hijikata…
Yes…right now? No problem.
Huh? The limited-edition DVD
BOX comes with a figurine?
Well, then…one to save, and one for
that… I'll need a total of two sets.
Hey! Spit it out! I'm asking you
where your headquarters is!
I won't sell out my own
comrades! Kill me!
I'd rather die like a samurai
than shame myself!
Hey, hey! Do you really think you
can die in a place like this?
We'll make you feel like you’re in a
hell worse than death from now on.
Vice-Chief!
Work him over! Please.
Get out of here, you guys.
Y-Yes.
He's a really scary guy…
When the Vice-Chief works a
guy over with his own hands,
the interrogation room becomes
completely silent.
However, five minutes later,
even the bravest men start crying
and spit out everything.
Wh-What's going on inside?
Just take a peek. You'll see hell on earth.
What? Is there anyone you like?
Not really. I don't have anyone.
Come on! I already told you,
so it’s your turn to tell me.
It's not fair! Not fair! You lied to me,
didn't you?! You did! You tell me!
All right! I'll tell you then! But don't
tell anyone! It's a secret.
Well, I don't know about that.
Oh, damn it! The teachers are on
patrol. Put out the cigarettes!
Is this a school trip or something?
…That's how it goes.
After I got this sword,
everything went wrong.
It looks like I’m really cursed.
That’s why I didn't want to tell you.
You don't believe me, do you?
There's no way you'll believe me.
Just like that, I had switched personalities
with someone completely different.
No, that wasn't someone else.
The weak side inside everyone
gets awakened by this sword.
Hijikata-san, you can't blame
being weak on the sword.
You were weak to begin
with, Hijikata-san.
That's right; I'm always like this…
Oh, my…this is really something strange.
Then why don't you just throw
away that cursed sword?
I would, If I could. I even find myself carrying
it with me to the toilet and bath.
I can't get rid of it, even if I want to.
And the old man at the swordsmith’s
isn't there anymore.
Then are you trying to say…that's the reason
you had a fight with Kondo-san?
…I wish I could say that…
Hijikata-san, if you don’t
pay attention this time,
Ito-san will take away your
vice-chief position.
No time for that now.
Since I became like this, I've already broken
more than ten of the Kyokuchu Hatto rules.
If Ito delivers a sentence for seppuku
tomorrow, I wouldn't be surprised.
As I am right now, I wouldn't refuse.
If you're with me, you'll
attract Ito's attention.
…Hijikata-san…
Wait, Hijikata-san!
[Note: Yakisoba pan is noodles in a hot dog bun.]
Go buy me a Yakisoba pan.
And JUMP, too. Of course,
you pay for them.
Toshi is late. It's already past the time.
This is a really important meeting…
Kondo-san.
This is a good opportunity. I was going
to bring him up for discussion.
I think you’ve already heard
about his recent behavior.
He broke the Kyokuchu Hatto
rules more than ten times.
And yet he created those
rules for the members.
Besides him being late for an
important meeting like this,
If we continue to let him act like this, we won't
be able to control the other members.
Sensei, hold on. I know Toshi well.
He must have something
exceedingly important…
I'm not only talking about
this particular case.
Of course, I fully understand what he
achieved for the Shinsengumi before.
That's why I want to give
him some candid advice.
If he's the symbol of the Shinsengumi,
and he downplays the rules,
other members will do the same.
A pack of wolves that has lost its discipline
will be like sheep without a shepherd.
He's the one who deserves
strict punishment!
Kondo-san, please make a firm decision!
Hold on! Toshi will definitely…
Hi! I bought your Yakisoba
pan, Okita Senpai!
I'm sorry, but they didn't have
JUMP, so I got MAGAZINE…
D-Damn it! I was trapped!
Those guys…were working together!
[To Be Continued]
[Preview]
I didn't expect anything
like that, Okita-kun.
That you would be on my
side. What do you desire?
Naturally…the Vice-Chief position.
["Otaku Are Talkative"]
[Hijikata knowingly broke the "Kyokuchu Hatto",
and has been exiled from the Shinsengumi.]
[He becomes a hopeless otaku and visits
the Odd Jobs with "a request."]