Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[Note: Spoof of Space Battleship
Yamato series anime.]
Gentlemen of the Yamato,
our Chief, Isao Kondo
has been safely rescued.
Victory is within our grasp!
[Note: Spoof of GUNDAM series anime.]
We shall get revenge on
that lawless bunch for besmirching
our Chief's name. Let me say this.
They are all scum!
In the name of the moon...
[Note: Spoof of Sailor Moon.]
we will punish them!!
Hey, who's that? Who's making
that silly speech?
Who am I? I'm Shinsengumi
Vice-Chief...
Toshiro Hijikata nari!!
[Note: Suffix "Nari" was used by Samurai and by
Korosuke in the Kiteretsu Daihyakka anime.]
Hijikata-san...
Mr. Kondo, we shall protect your life.
In return, you have an obligation to fulfill.
To not die. Do whatever it takes to live.
No matter how humiliating it may be...
No matter how many squad members
die before your eyes, you must live!
As long as you're here,
the Shinsengumi is not finished.
We joined the Shinsengumi because we
wanted to be with you...
You're an idiot.
Don't think about such difficult things!
You should live the way you want to live.
We just have to protect
you from everyone.
Kondo-san...
You are the soul of the Shinsengumi.
We are the sword that protects you.
Toshi...
You broke once before.
What can you protect?
Hijikata-kun, it seems we have
to settle things between us.
I have a sword right here.
One that cuts very well.
Odd Jobs, I heard your rotten sermon!
What is it?
Don't talk as if you're so high and mighty.
Draw it already!
Shut up!
I have one more thing to say to you.
Thank you!!
Hey, hey, it looks like the demonic sword
devoured him again... Toshi?
Is that Toshi?
I'm...
[Toshiro Hijikata has fought off the demonic
sword's curse and recovered all by himself.]
[The moment to settle things with his
rival, Kamotaro Ito, has finally come.]
["Important Things Are Hard To See"]
If you want to kill our boss,
you have to defeat me first.
I won't let anyone past me. I won't
let anyone disgrace our souls.
I am the final fort that
protects Isao Kondo.
I am the final sword that protects
the Shinsengumi.
I am Shinsengumi Vice-Chief...
Toshiro Hijikata!!
He fought off the demonic
sword's curse by himself.
Sorry, Gorilla.
Unfortunately, we can't take your request
no matter how much money you offer us.
He was our client first.
Didn't your job end already?
I'm going to be charging overtime pay!
Come on, Ito!
It changed... The rhythm of that
man's soul has changed.
It went from a childish anime song
to a sturdy rock-and-roll tune.
I guess the same goes
for you, too, Ito-dono.
You've gone from very dignified classical
music to fierce heavy metal.
That's a nice song... Play your beautiful
concerto to your heart's content.
Hijikata!!
Ito!!
The steering wheel...!
Hey, behind us!!
Kondo-san, move over
to this side already.
I overworked myself a bit... I'm
getting overtime pay for this, right?
Sogo?!
I'll make sure you negotiate with
the person in charge of our pay.
That's good. Also, make
sure to take care of him.
I'm a little tired...
Hijikata-san, if you come out even
a little behind, I'll kill you.
The next time you show
weakness, I'll take...
your position as Vice-Chief.
But are you saying that I should
just leave Toshi and run away?
Don't waste your time!!
Don't fight here!!
Why are you using me like
a bridge as if it's normal?!
Gin-san!
Hijikata-kun, you were the only
one who understood me.
Unfortunately, you knew and feared my
potential and we became enemies.
If you were Chief, I might have
never planned this rebellion.
This is just hypothetical, though.
But there's one thing you've
got wrong about me.
Just as you know my potential,
I also know your potential.
Toshiro Hijikata, bring it on!!
This is the final showdown!!
You have an interesting sound.
Your sound is haphazard, willful,
and vague. It's akin to jazz.
But it's undignified. If anything,
it's a drunk's humming.
You bastard... You're the guy
who was with Takasugi.
Hey, take your headphones off
when you talk to someone.
Gintoki Sakata... No, White Knight...
Why are you with the Shinsengumi?
You can hear me, can't you?
That man seems to be
under your influence.
Are you planning to spy on the Bakufu
once you take control of the Shinsengumi?
We're not generous enough to be allied
with those who easily betray others.
We also know that people will not gather
under a person who has been unfaithful.
So what of that man?
He is a pitiful man.
By the time he realizes his
capacity, it'll be too late.
It'll be after everything
breaks into pieces.
Go to sleep, Ito...
Along with the Shinsengumi...
Geniuses are always alone. I have
no one who understands me.
I shouldn't remain in a place like this.
No one understands that. No
one realizes my true worth.
In that case,
I just have to demonstrate my potential
to take control of the country.
I will take control of the Shinsengumi.
I will use that as a foundation
to take control of the country.
I, Kamotaro Ito, will take control of the
country as proof that I have lived.
I will etch that into people's hearts.
You don't mind acquiring
a bad reputation?
In order to achieve what you propose,
you have to wipe out Kondo,
whom you are indebted to.
Indebted? Kondo's the one who
should be indebted to me.
I'm working for an incompetent
man like him.
He should be thankful. He has no
reason to be dissatisfied with me.
Ito, you're the kind of person
who thinks that everyone aside from
yourself is stupid, aren't you?
But you're unsatisfied that those stupid
people don't understand you.
You want them to understand you.
You want them to acknowledge you.
You want to prove your worth?
It's not that difficult.
You choose to be all by yourself.
You don't want someone who
understands and accepts you.
What you really want is...
Where am I?
Hijikata?
I see... I won! I finally
won against Hijikata...
Shinsuke saw through Ito.
He is a show-off who has more
pride than anyone else
and doesn't know his own worth.
It was easy to provoke and use him.
As expected, the Shinsengumi members
fought against each other
and depleted their fighting potential.
You were planning to use him to crush
the Shinsengumi to begin with.
You acted as if you were helping
with Ito's rebellion.
While you were really planning
to annihilate the Shinsengumi
when it was exhausted after they
fought amongst themselves.
It's a death that suits that
man, don't you think?
The traitor is wiped out by the traitor.
S-Stop!
Stop!
I'm not meant to die in a place like this.
Stop. I can do much better...
Much, much better...
Mother!
Take a look! I got a perfect
score on a test at school.
Kamotaro, be quiet. It's bad for
your older brother's health.
I-I'm very sorry.
I've got to try much, much harder.
If I try harder, I'm sure she'll notice me.
Yes. That's wonderful, Kamotaro!
You are the first child prodigy
to come from our school.
Everyone, don't lose to Kamotaro.
Don't get cocky.
You're just a rich kid who
only knows how to study!
I've got to try much, much harder.
If I try harder, I'm sure that
everyone will accept me.
One point! Wonderful. You're
really something, Kamo!
Such an aptitude for swords at your age.
You worked hard, didn't you?
Kamo, go to Edo.
I'll recommend you to the dojo of the
distinguished Hokuto Itto Style.
Your brilliance will go to waste
out here in the country!
It's possible you might even surpass the
great swordsman Musashi Miyamoto!
Why?
[Letter of Recommendation]
Honestly. My heir, Takahisa is so sickly.
I wonder what's going to
happen to the Ito family.
Kamotaro grew up so healthily.
No matter how brilliant our second
son is, it's just a waste of talent.
Takahisa wasn't born to have everything
taken away from him by Kamotaro.
I'm sure Kamotaro took everything away
from Takahisa while he was in my womb.
I wish he was never born.
Hey! What if Kamotaro hears you?!
What's the matter with you?!
I feel so sorry for Takahisa.
When I see Kamotaro carelessly
running about...
You must be tired from taking
care of Takahisa.
Go to bed already.
Why? Why doesn't anyone look at me?
I've tried so hard. I'm not at fault.
Look at me. Praise me.
Don't leave me alone.
Stay by me. By my side.
Hold this hand...
K-Kondo?!
What are you doing?
Do you know what you're
doing right now?!
I'm the traitor who tried to kill you.
The boss is at fault if there's a revolt.
Soldiers will lose their lives if they
stay with an incompetent general.
They're not at fault for killing him.
Sorry. I'm not a good enough
general to be your superior.
I was never suited to be the boss.
You're far more suited to be the boss.
I can't stand by while squad
members are dying.
I can't ever use suicide squads.
Sensei, I'm not a soldier.
But I wanted you to be by my side as
a friend that I would pour drinks with.
There were still so many things I wanted
you to teach me, Sensei...
It's not my fault I'm alone! I'm not at fault!
They're incompetent!
They're completely incompetent!
We live in different worlds.
I was a chosen individual.
I couldn't accept my loneliness and
I blamed my loneliness on others.
I was afraid that people would
reject me, so I rejected them.
I was afraid I would get hurt, so
I acted as if I liked being alone.
I built a wall around my heart.
But my lingering desire for attention
grew stronger by the day.
I wanted to be accepted by others.
Even when I was accepted,
I wasn't satisfied.
I could do better. I'm not like them.
I'll show them who I am.
You don't want someone who
understands and accepts you.
I had forgotten what I really wanted.
It wasn't power, fame, military exploits, talent,
or someone who understood me.
I just wanted someone to be by my side.
I just wanted someone to see me.
I just didn't want to be alone anymore.
I just wanted...
Sensei!
Friends who would accept
me for who I was.
Hey, look over there!
What are you doing?!
Hurry up and run away!
Someone who would
look directly at me...
Someday, I'll kill you.
And take me head on.
I just...
Wanted friends.
The thing I wanted...
Was something...
I already had.
Hijikata-kun, I have something
I want to say to you.
What a coincidence. Me, too.
I hate you.
Someday, I'll kill you. So...
Don't die here.
The bond I wanted so much...
Was right here all along.
I can't see your swings or your rhythm!
Out of the way, damn it!!
Don't you understand that...
I'm telling you to get out of my way?!
I don't have the time
to deal with...
idiots like you!
Strings?!
You shouldn't push yourself.
Your arms and legs will rip off.
Even if you go to help
them now, it's too late.
Do you think your friends are still alive?
Even if they survived that explosion...
We've taken many measures.
The Shinsengumi will disappear.
I told you that your arms
and legs will rip off.
Who'd want to go and save their sorry asses?
I can't stop. My body won't listen to me.
It's being pulled forward.
Strings are pulling me from
the front and the back.
It annoys me to no end...
These strings are as strong
as steel, but still...
You can have an arm and a leg or two...
Even if these strings can cut flesh...
I'd like to see them
try to sever
an obnoxious bond!
Get down!
Sensei!
Ito!
[To be continued]
[Preview]
Hey, young man, clean out
your ears and listen up!
I've never once fought for the
sake of this cheap country.
I couldn't care less if the
country or samurai fell.
["It's All About the Beat and Timing"]
[What did he find when he tugged
on the invisible strings?!]
[The Shinsengumi Crisis Arc
ends in the next episode!!]