Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Can't you tell...?
I used to be a human, same as you guys.
Until that point, I had taken away many
things that could never be replaced.
But I would use this body,
the precious body he gave me,
to protect those things that
can never be replaced.
This town doesn't need a boss.
We're gonna live free!
An uprising?
I'm leaving the rest to you.
Hoichi!
What are you doing?! Hurry up!
We're leaving the rest to you, Odd Jobs!
Grant the stray cats of Kabukicho!
And their proud king!
True freedom!
["Kabukicho Stray Cat Blues"]
Well, that should do it.
We've captured most of
the strays in Kabukicho.
Thank you for your cooperation.
Well? Are there any to your liking?
B-Bro...
What's with the feeble old cat?
Moron! Don't make any
stupid comments.
The cats will rip you apart and eat you.
That's their king.
Huh?! That old geezer's the
king of Planet Catnip?!
Moron! You're too loud!
Why? Why's he here?
Wouldn't the king coming
to Edo be big news?!
I never heard a word about it!
He's obviously being discreet because he
doesn't want people to know he's here!
Doesn't want people
to know he's here...?
Meow!
Greetings, everyone.
What's with that old geezer?!
He can speak our language?!
Meow!
It is a pleasure to meet
you, cats of Earth.
Meow-yeow.
I apologize for any inconvenience
caused by assembling you here.
I must confess that I have
a favor to ask of you.
Hey, he's pretty talkative for someone
who looks the quiet type.
Mew.
We may come from different planets,
but we belong to the same race, which
is why I hope you'll be willing to help.
Meow.
I am actually the king
of a certain planet...
Purr.
I have grown old without
producing any children.
Meorw.
And I must say that my wife
is a dead fish in bed.
Of course, I love fish,
at least the edible kind.
I mean, I'm a cat.
Hey! That geezer's spillin' everything
to total strangers!
Mrrow.
She won't budge or make a
sound, no matter what I do.
Practically copulationless.
I've become a master at going solo.
And I'm used to a curved faucet,
so normal sex completely fails to...
Hey!
We don't want to hear this!
Why do we have to listen to an old
geezer's sexual preferences?!
Myao.
I took a new wife,
but by that time, I could
no longer get it up.
Meows.
My nation is currently in an
uproar over succession.
Meyow.
That is why I must ask a favor of you.
Hey, aren't we about to get lucky?
I heard something about losing
our souls, though...
Maybe this geezer brought us
here to pick a successor...
Meowzer.
Could you all please give me your balls?
Why?!
What kind of twisted logic is that?!
Meow-ow.
There is an ancient legend on our planet.
Nagas.
[Note: Parody of the manga "Dragon Ball".]
When the legendary "Golden
Balls" are assembled,
Meowes.
Shenlong will be awakened from
its slumber in the earth,
Meowlos.
Will you assist in awakening
Meow.
my slumbering Shenlong?
That king plans on extracting cat balls
to produce the potent aphrodisiac
Catnip Omega!
Don't talk about Shenlong,
you sick geezer!
Screw that!
Why do we have to give up our balls to
help wake up your withered Shenlong?!
Meowsus.
Your Golden Balls, brimming with
virility, are the ideal ingredient.
Meowgos.
But this isn't enough.
Meof.
Your Golden Balls can shine brighter.
Where are we...?
Meows.
Do you know when seeds have
the greatest survivability?
It isn't when you find a DVD-porn that
perfectly matches your tastes.
Nor is it when you encounter
a ravishing female cat.
It is when your life is in danger.
When faced with absolute death,
Golden Balls shine brightest in an attempt
to leave its seed in this world.
N-No way...
Is that geezer planning on...
Now tremble in fear!
You are currently faced
with imminent death!
Now, grant the Golden Balls light!
Fuel it with all your energy!
There's no need to worry!
If you end up as corpses, I won't
let your Golden Balls go to waste!
He's gonna kill us!
Eat us up, leaving only our balls behind!
I won't let you pass...
I won't let you get one step past me.
Any further and you're on the turf of
Hoichi, king of Kabukicho strays.
I-It's standing! On two legs!
Wh-What is that?!
What is up with that cat?!
It's the king.
That is the boss cat which
rules over Kabukicho...
Reigning over the stray cats...
Hoichi, the stray king.
M-Magnificent!
The vitality! Courage!
Brimming with virility!
Ho-Hoichi...!
Why? Why?!
Why is he helping us after
what we did to him?!
WHY?!
Come on...
Hold on a little longer...
Just a little longer...
Hang in there...
Don't fall apart on me...
This guy's the last one...
Lend me your body...
A little longer...!!
You awake?
So you're the stray who's been making a
name for himself in Kabukicho recently.
You're a fool to pick fights with dogs.
Good thing you only lost your ears.
You're quite a handsome one.
There's no need to worry.
The charge you were protecting
is fine as you can see.
Well, it ran off.
You're not very well-liked.
I was wondering why it felt like
this wasn't our first meeting.
You're exactly like him.
I once picked up another stray.
On the verge of death, just like you,
lying on the side of the road...
A stupid cat that was your
match in every way.
I don't know how he ended
up there though.
Always seemed as though he
were looking for something.
Butting in where he wasn't wanted
and pitting his own body
to protect the things that were
important for other people.
Almost like he was trying
to atone for something.
Meanwhile, he kept nothing for himself.
Didn't get close to anyone.
He was always alone...
Just like you...
Maybe he was afraid of enduring
the pain of loss again...
Maybe he didn't want others
to experience what he had...
Perhaps he was trying to punish himself.
But you know...
There were other strays who
were drawn to that idiot.
Soon he could no longer stay alone.
Maybe he just learned from them.
That fatalism won't make anyone happy.
Friends to protect, who protected him,
may have given him the strength to move on.
You protect and suffer losses.
You're protected and suffer losses.
But then you take on a new burden.
In the end, it's just a cycle.
That's life.
Rough, isn't it?
But you know, when I see the expressions
on those three faces,
I start to feel that it's not too bad.
Why am I saying all this to a cat?
When I saw you rampaging
around on your own,
I was somehow reminded
of how he used to be.
Live positively.
I'm sure you have friends
waiting to support you.
The ones you care for would
want you to do so...
I can't be positive, Granny...
I can't make anything happen
by being positive...
I don't deserve any friends when I
couldn't even protect my only pal...
I forgot how to make friends
a long time ago.
Still, even if I couldn't make friends,
I wanted to protect them.
I wanted to protect something with these
hands, instead of taking from others...
Sorry I couldn't protect you
all till the very end...
I'm a failure
of a boss cat...
Pal, I broke another promise...
Sorry...
Gi-
Gin!!
What is that cat?!
Th-That's...
The newbie!
Bastards!
Did you hear what he said?!
He just voluntarily gave up
his position as boss cat!
From this point on, Kabukicho
will be a city of free strays!
Kabukicho no longer has a boss cat!
From now on, you're free
to do whatever you want!
Live by your own rules!
Now that you're free, let's test those
free-minded idea of yours!
Think long and hard before you answer!
He's no longer the boss cat!
So who is this dirty rag-like Doraemon?!
Who is this pathetic Mr. Frieza who bled
for you, got beaten to a pulp for you?!
He's just another
pal!
I-Impossible!
The strays are uniting!
This is...! This is...!!
M-Magnificent!
Witness that swarming wave of virility!
That's it! That is what is needed
for Catnip Omega...!
There's no time for that, your majesty!
We must evacuate!
It's dangerous here!
No!
I want my Catnip Omega
so I can be nippy!
Nippy I tell you!
Did you know?
Naughty cats...
...learn to behave if you neuter them.
Oh, really?
I've never heard that before...
But it's just a myth, a myth.
That couldn't be enough to
stop my burning pathos...
Why don't we find out?
Huh?
Bro, is it okay to ditch the king?
Don't blame me if we get in trouble later.
Are you a moron?
How could that fool be a king?
This wasn't a bad job.
Turned a pretty profit, and we
got to watch a fine show.
Of a true cat king...
Gin, you've really done it now...
Instead of succeeding me as boss cat,
you abolished monarchy and turned
Kabukicho into a lawless land.
They'll run wild now.
They'll be fine without a boss cat now.
Since they understand the pain
their pal's been through.
And you can forget all the
tedious stuff and live easy.
I...
Fatalism won't make anyone happy.
Live positively.
Your buddy didn't give you his
body to help you survive
for you to atone.
Don't you think he wanted his chained
friend to live free like a stray?
So I should live by my own
rules, as you put it?
That would be the Kabukicho way.
Gin, I have a favor to ask.
Don't worry.
I won't ask you to succeed
me as boss cat again.
I just...
I want to be pals with...
I've been thinking...
The cats in this grave might
not have been cursing us.
Say, why are we back like this?
It's possible that they only wanted
us to save Master Hoichi.
Hey, doesn't something stink?
It's possible that they knew how
Master Hoichi was suffering.
Hey, you said something about
taking a dump here, right?
It's possible that I had diarrhea.
Possible, my ass!
It's damn obvious if you
were the one who did it!
Ah, it's true!
Katsura's really here!
Farewell, Gintoki!
Hey! Something weird's popped out!
Isn't this p-
Give my regards to Master Hoichi!
After him! After him!
It was just as Kondo-san said!
That's our commander for you!
By the way, where have you
been this whole time?
We were worried, Kondo-san.
Kondo-san, you look different somehow.
Oh, did you cut your hair?
Give my regards to Master Hoichi?
Even if we run into one another,
he won't recognize us.
And it stinks!
I see.
So the strays were safely released
from the embassy.
Yes.
But they're still running wild,
so the neighborhood association is saying
that they should still be neutered.
So?
Gintoki's come back, right?
Ah, yes.
He didn't give us any details,
but he was apparently in a rough situation where
he couldn't have anything sweet to eat.
Thank you very much.
Hey! Where do you think you're
pissing, you damn stray?!
Come on, what is this?
How long do you need to piss?
["Thanks, pal."]
[Preview]
Everybody, we'll be learning
how to cook next week.
What? I don't need to.
Me, a samurai, learning how to cook...?
Too much of a pain.
Line up right now.
We're very sorry!
The next episode...
"Cooking is About Guts."
[Set out to marry rich?! The GinTama girl
brigade attend the Kitaoji Cooking School.]
[Different people have vastly different approaches
when making egg and boiled rice, huh?"]
[See you next time.]