Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Life is just one important decision after another.
Go ahead and see how far your naive decisions can take you.
I told you, didn't I? I...
...hate killing my own kind.
["Those Who Stand On Four-Legs Are Beasts. Those Who Stand On Two-Legs, Guts, and Glory Are Men."]
H-He...
saved us...
Shinpachi...
Kagura-chan!
Thank god.
You're back to normal...
I...lost.
To my Yato instincts...
To my own self...
I tried to kill him.
After all that preaching I did...
In the end, I wasn't any different...
from them...from my brother.
That's not true.
Kagura-chan, weren't you fighting to protect us?
Sorry...
It's because I was weak that...
If only I were stronger...
I couldn't see anything...
I couldn't hear anything...
Inside that total darkness, I heard...
Your voice...
Shinpachi, you're the one who protected me.
I feel so frustrated.
I want to become stronger...
Strong enough to protect everyone.
Strong enough so that I won't lose to anyone, not even myself.
I feel the same way.
But, for now!
There are people who need our help.
There are things even we can protect.
Every time we protected something,
we became a little stronger, didn't we?
So let's wipe our tears and go.
I'm sure we'll become a little stronger.
Don't let them get to Hinowa-sama!
Hold them back!
So persistent.
It's not my style to kill women.
Women may give birth to strong children, right?
Well, I suppose I can't expect anything from your children.
S-Stop it!
What's so fun about killing people like that?!
How can you kill people and just smile like that?!
That's harsh. After all I did to bring you here.
Besides, they're the ones keeping your mother locked up here.
I don't remember asking for it!
I pay my respects with a smile when killing.
Regardless of how their life was, it's appropriate to send them off with a smile,
so they can die soundly.
You could even say that, I intend to kill when I'm smiling.
I'm kidding.
I don't believe in killing children.
After all, they may grow up to be strong.
Come here.
You should also smile.
You don't want to meet your mother with such a strained look on your face.
Mom is...here...?
Eight years ago,
when she was captured while trying to help you escape,
she traded her own freedom for yours.
She's only a courtesan in name.
Hosen locked her up here when he wasn't using her to attract customers.
She was allowed no clients nor freedom.
Hosen forced Hinowa to rot to death here.
No, I suppose you could say that Hinowa chose this for herself.
In order to protect you.
Yet you still came here.
Wasting Hinowa's years of hardship and resolve and putting yourself in danger...
But you still came to see her.
Which means you're resolved in your own way.
It's your job to go from here on.
Leave.
You won't find what you're seeking here.
M-Mom...?
Is that you, mom?!
Open up!
You know who I am, right?!
I'm your son, Seita!
Mo...!
I have no son.
I don't know any dirty brat like you.
Why do you know...?
Why do you know I'm a dirty brat?
You were watching me, weren't you?
Whenever I was looking up at you from below,
you were also looking at me, right?
You never responded when I shouted to you,
but that was so I wouldn't get involved.
You were struggling to keep your mouth shut, weren't you?!
Mom...
I had no idea...
that you were suffering here.
I always wondered why I was the only unfortunate one.
When I was living in poverty with Grandpa...
When I was all alone after Grandpa died...
I blamed it all on you for abandoning me.
I had no idea.
I didn't know anything at all.
That you were protecting me this whole time.
Now it's my turn!
Now it's my turn to save you, mom!
Now I'm going to protect you, mom!!
I won't leave you in there!!
This time we'll leave this place for sure!
Both of us are going up together!
So mom...
Open the door!
Please, mom!
Mom!!
Mo...!
Stop it!
Your mom isn't here.
Didn't I tell you that?
M-Mom...
That's not true.
If you want to see her so badly, I'll let you.
Personally...
H-Hosen!
Oops, we've been found.
Take her with you if you want.
Child, that is your mother.
Hinowa isn't your mother.
Your mother left this world long ago.
What are you...talking about...
You think a courtesan of Yoshiwara could give birth to a child unnoticed?
Eight years ago, a prostitute became pregnant with a child.
But becoming pregnant in Yoshiwara means death for both.
So a number of the women hid her and secretly assisted the birth.
Yes...
That was you, child!
Your mother was weak and died after giving birth to you.
Unfortunately, the woman over there isn't your mother.
Dreaming of becoming a mother, yet couldn't.
Just a pathetic women who immersed herself in playing a mother role.
Why...
Why did you come to this place?
Why did you come?
You should have just forgotten about someone like me.
Just knowing you lived up there for the rest of us would have been enough.
I'm not worth risking your life to protect.
You won't find your mother anywhere in this world.
Now that you understand, take that memento of her and get lost.
Of course, it's a different story if you wish to see your mother in the afterlife.
I have a mother!
Right here!
My mom is alive!
The one who delivered me from this eternal darkness to the surface!
The one who risked her life to give birth to me!
It doesn't matter if we aren't related by blood!
This person is my mom!
You don't know when to give up, child.
I have no choice.
Go meet your real mother in the underworld.
Th-This is...
Hey, I wasn't told about this.
I came cause they said the best woman in Yoshiwara was here.
But it looks like she's got a kid.
Those tears prove it.
M-Mom...?
Hey manager, get me a different girl.
One that can withstand some really rough SM play.
Who are you?
Nobody special.
Just a girl-loving playboy.
Gi...
Gin-san!!
What are you doing, dummy?
Just get going and don't worry about me.
But...
Is it okay for me to go?
Is it okay for a dirty brat like me
to call such a beautiful person my mom?
You called her that all this time and now you're asking?
Call to her.
Yell "Mom" from the bottom of your heart.
M-Mom...
Are you sure?
Calling someone not related to you...
a dirty woman like me, your mom?
Mom...
Are you sure?
Calling someone who wasn't able to do anything for you...
a woman like me, as your mom?
Mom...
Are you sure?
A woman like me becoming your mom...?
Mom!
Seita!
He was the one from when...
Wow, so he survived.
I see.
You're the ronin the child hired.
Are you the one who's been running wild around my city?
Running wild?
Don't make me laugh.
I haven't bought a single woman.
I see.
Then I'll prepare a banquet for you.
A banquet of blood.
I appreciate the generous gesture, but I'll have to pass.
I can't enjoy a drink while looking at an old geezer's receding hairline.
I can't enjoy a drink at a place like this.
Yeah, you did a fine job with bringing in this many babes.
But it doesn't matter how many beautiful women,
or how much fine liquor you have.
I won't drink a single drop in your place.
I can't enjoy a drink poured by women in chains.
I can't enjoy a drink poured by someone in tears.
I'd take a crappy snack joint full of old ladies instead,
if they serve me with a smile.
I'd take a bar run by a vicious cabaret girl instead,
if everyone could drink and laugh.
I'd take a field in the middle of nowhere with no women, wine, or even a roof instead,
if we could drink cheap liquor and watch the moon.
A woman's tears...
are too much to go with drinking.
So you came to shatter those chains?
To free Hinowa...the woman of Yoshiwara from the King of the Night?
It's not that big a deal.
I just want a drink.
And have the finest courtesan serve it to me with one great smile.
How amusing.
Picking a fight with the King of the Night for the sake of a drink.
Guess Earth has its share of amusing people.
Right, Boss Hosen?
Ooh, scary.
Don't be so angry.
Don't worry. I won't interfere with you anymore.
Kamui! What are you after?
After attempting to take my life, you help that child by taking him to Hinowa.
You want to interfere with me that badly?
Or perhaps...
Watching that child long for his mother brought back memories of the past?
You now feel like atoning for abandoning your sick mother?
What nonsense.
I was wondering what sort of woman could turn the King of the Night into a fool,
but she turns out to be a miserable wretch clinging to a dirty brat.
The sun of Yoshiwara? Yeah, right.
This isn't it.
The strength I seek isn't for some cheap crap like this.
Like not hesitating to kill your own sister or father.
Is that what you mean?
Talk about ironic.
If there's a brother willing to kill his real sister,
there are people with bonds stronger than those between a parent and a child.
Who knows which would be considered the real family.
Very amusing.
Why don't you show me how strong those bonds are?
Whether you can release them from my chains...
or for me to break through their bonds.
Let's see who will win!
Can a mere Earthling shatter the chains...
of the King of the Night?!
A chain made from a perverted old man's wet dreams?
I'll break it with a single strike.
Every night has to end eventually.
It's time for this city to see dawn.
The King of the Night can watch the sunrise,
and go nighty night!!
Gin-san!
G-Gin-san!
Ah...
So you blocked my attack?
What the hell...
One hit...
One strike and it feels like...
my body's lost all its energy and stamina!
Hosen, King of the Night.
This is the power of the man once known as the King of the Yato?
Oh, wow.
You lasted ten seconds against the King of the Night.
This is getting interesting.
Good luck, mister.
I feel like rooting for you now.
Don't look down on me, you damn kid.
Ten seconds? Hell, I'll last till I die of old age.
I'll die peacefully while surrounded by grandchildren, you bastard!
Your life has already ended.
The second you decided to oppose Yoshiwara...the King of the Night!
My bones are grating...
My muscles are crying in pain...
I can't relax a single finger, a single muscle!
I'll be crushed in the next moment!
No time to breath...or even blink!
A single blow forces my soul from my body!
Gin-san!
What, over already?
That's no fun.
It seems you're not just all talk.
Within Earth standards, that is.
Of course, you samurai wouldn't be able to shatter my chains,
when you couldn't even protect your own nation from the Amanto.
When a lion loses a turf war,
it must turn over its land and its females.
Do you understand?
You samurai no longer have a home,
or the right to hold women.
Because your lands and females all became ours long ago!
That's right.
This city, its women, and Hinowa all belong to the King of the Night!
They're chained up as my pets.
They cannot escape anywhere.
And you losers don't have the right to stop me!
It's your fault for being too weak to protect anything!
A loser should act like one and just suck on his thumb...
and watch as this nation and its women are violated by the stronger ones!
In the other world, where your comrades are waiting for you!
We haven't lost...
...I'm still fighting!
You son of a...!!
Gin-san!!
Stay back!!
What are you doing, idiot?
Get going already.
Take your mom and get outta here!
N-No!
Are you telling me to run away by myself and leave you behind?!
I can't do that after getting you involved in all of this!
Getting me involved?
I butted in on my own.
Get going.
If something happens to the two of you,
we'll have come here for nothing.
No...!
No way!
I may be useless,
but I'll help you!
I'll stay with you until the end!
You stupid...
You said so!
That there were bonds stronger than family, even when people aren't related by blood?
That's right.
Blood doesn't matter.
You all reformed me from being a thief.
You all taught me how to lead a respectable life.
You all kept me...from being all alone.
It wasn't very long, but it was fun.
Ever since Grandpa died, I never had that much fun.
Just like Mom...
Everybody...Gin-san...
You're all like family to me!
The one and only people who taught me what's important!
And you're telling me to abandon you here?!
To let you die in this place?!
Hearing you say that is more than enough...
Get going.
Don't make me into a loser again.
Gin-san...
Gi...
Gin...!
Gin-san!!
[Preview]
What a joke this is.
After all that big talking, look at you!
Where's that sun you promised?
I was a fool for expecting anything from you.
You...stinkin' big bluff!
[The next episode: "Don't Trust Bedtime Stories"]
[There was a heart-wrenching reason why Hinowa was stuck there.]
[Inspired by Gintoki's words, Seita sets out to rescue his mother all by himself.]