Edited at https://subtitletools.com
To celebrate the Gintama anime becoming a movie
and breaking roughly one million in DVD sales,
we held the second character
popularity poll.
However, a bloody ranking battle has waged
by those unsatisfied with the results.
Who will be in 1st place
at the end of this battle?!
[Popularity Polls Can...]
I look away for a second
and this happens.
There's a traitor among us.
Well then...
Who might it be, Shinpachi-kun?
I-It wasn't us!
Hasegawa-san was ranked
lower than us!
So why would we need
to lower his rank?!
That assumption may be a mistake.
If the perpetrator's goal
isn't to raise his rank,
but to take out people he doesn't like...
That's...
That's just...!
Sunglasses there may have
been a lower rank than you,
but I hear you two shared the running joke
of the glasses being the main body.
And I shouldn't need to mention
that Zaki's character
overlapped with yours in
terms of being boring.
Y-You're wrong...
It wasn't me!
I didn't do it!
I'll listen to your excuses when
you've reached 300th!
You'll be the one to drop
to 300th, Okita-kun.
Gi-Gin-san!
You've finally shown your
true colors, Boss.
But you're a fool.
You missed a piece when you
were dragging my pants down.
U-Underwear Daburu Feinto?!
A brilliant tactician assumes that he is going to
be betrayed before he starts betraying others.
There's nothing brilliant or tactical
about being in your underwear!
You're definitely embarrassing
yourself, aren't you?!
Odd Jobs!
You're going down to hell
with your underwear!
Gin-san!
Th-This is!
R-Reddo Roincuroth?!
Fool!
Didn't you see the sponsor message?
I normally wear boxers,
but just for this episode, I'm wearing
a special red loincloth!
No, we didn't see it!
And your butt's totally exposed!
You idiots have been doing nothing
but speaking in bad Engrish!
Damn civil servants!
It's over now!
He's fully exposed to begin with!
F-Fu-ri Expozed?!
Just say exposed!
It more or less sounds the same!
Hah, fools...
If having your underwear dragged
down will lower your rank,
then you shouldn't wear underwear
to begin with!
You're the fool!
Is this person really a police officer?!
His rank isn't going down after revealing
his dirty parts to a girl?!
As a parting gift, let me tell you
why before you all go to hell.
The whole dragging down the underwear
along with the ranking
only works on you losers!
I have danced with death
on a regular basis
and exposed my private
parts many times!
The audience is already sick
of seeing me fully expozed!
In other words!
My 13th place rank comes after
I've already been fully expozed!
I have no blind spots in this fight!
You won't conquer this castle,
no matter what you do!
I can see blind spots everywhere!
The castle is so broken-down that
there isn't anything left to attack!
You cannot take this impregnable fortress...
So what are you saying?
That as someone who used to be 17th,
I lost to a fully expozed 13th...
No...
I lost to that pathetic piece of crap?!
He's fallen...
The impregnable fortress has
fallen in a different way.
Boss Lady!
Kagura-chan, it's okay now.
I've destroyed that dirty devil.
There's nothing for you to be scared of.
We have a message for the higher-ranked
characters hiding in this hotel.
This place already
belongs to us, Diamond Perfume.
Throw down your weapons and electro-on with
our fake Kansai accent and fake robot dance.
Why am I in this mess...
If you refuse...
We'll crush you!
She switched sides in an instant!
She brazenly switched to the side
with the advantage in an instant!
I'll kill you good and dead, yeah?
What do we do with these losers?
There you go.
Women can't be trusted because
they do whatever benefits them.
But the same can't be said for men.
Boss, do you intend to break
out of this siege?
How are we supposed to do that...?
Cease your futile resistance.
Nothing good can come
from going against us.
Y-You bastards!
It appears that we don't have
time to fight among us.
As I said to begin with...
Terrible things would happen
if we didn't unite.
This is no longer a fight
over a popularity poll.
It's a war of the sexes.
War?
You're a funny man.
You think you crap heads can defeat us?
[Note: Spoof on the Japanese group Exile.]
Diamond Perfume vs. Crapxile!
We'll have a contest to see
who's the real number one!
[Popularity Poll Arc]
Diamond Perfume vs. Crapxile.
We'll have a contest to see who's better!
Wait, Miss Otae!
We should not continue this ugly fight.
This pointless conflict has already
dragged on for three weeks.
Popularity isn't the only thing at stake.
If we continue to drag out this ugly battle,
it's very possible that the sponsors
will abandon us,
and the show will end in March!
We should calm down and talk this over.
We should have a discussion on what
direction the show should head.
One of the more pressing matters
would be how I, Miss Kyubei,
and the newcomer, Miss Tsukuyo,
have overlapping characters.
We need to have a dead-serious discussion
about which one of us should continue
to play the dead-serious character.
G-Get...
Hmm? What is it, Miss Kyubei?
Do you have something to say?
Get...
Your hands off me!
Overlapping characters?
You lot don't have the
right to talk about that.
Because y'all are
mere ripoffs of historical figures!
Katsura-san! Hijikata-san!
You didn't earn your own popularity!
You only capitalized from
the original's fame!
Fake imitation characters like you guys,
could never beat us original characters
who've worked our way up!
You weren't supposed to mention that...
Damn woman...
She wasn't supposed to mention that...
Having to put up with complaints
about how we mislead people
to accidentally put Kotaro
on their history tests...
Having to put up with history buffs complaining about
how we're ruining the names of famous people...
You could never understand that pain!
Katsura!
A temporary truce!
I'll arrest you after we've
finished them off!
We need to show them our true strength!
Wait!
Hijikata-san! Katsura-san!
Wh-Whoa!
I see that you won't make
this easy, Miss Kyubei.
It appears that this battle is unavoidable.
I'd realized that our characters overlapped
since the Ryugu arc...
I should have dealt with you then.
I should be the only eggheaded character!
Change your character to the one-eyed
dragon this very instant!
[Note: Historical figure Date Masamune as portrayed
in the game "Sengoku BASARA."]
The leader of the Yagyu who randomly speaks
English, rides a horse like a Harley,
and goes, "Let's party!"
I refuse.
[Note: Dragon Shiryu from Saint Seiya.]
You and your long hair should jump off a
waterfall to learn the Rozan Sho Ryu Ha.
So you refuse to listen, head-chief...?
In that case...
Let's party!
Hijikata-han, don't you need
to go "let's party"?
Aren't you the one who really
wants to "let's party"?
Aren't you all excited about the
second season coming up?
[Note: Date Masamune in Sengoku BASARA
is voiced by the same actor as Hijikata.]
What are you trying to imply?!
Stop saying crap that'll bring
down the fourth wall!
As long as you're around,
the Shinsengumi, including Kondo-san,
won't be able to stand alone at the top.
As long as you're around,
Kondo-san's image as a perverted
stalker won't go away.
It all ends now.
This stupid mess and everything bad
in the Shinsengumi's history...
So you intend to eliminate the woman who is the
source of your boss's scandalous behavior?
I would expect no less from the
demon vice-commander.
You're used to doing dirty work.
However...
There's no point in worrying about
the Shinsengumi at this point.
Since your Shinsengumi
and everything else
will be absorbed by us!
Toshi!
Come to our side!
It appears that it's only a matter
of time before 3rd falls.
You've made a fatal mistake in
your push to reach the top.
What's that?
Don't be a poor loser.
See?
Our rank has changed.
3rd is now one of us.
What?!
This is...!
12th?!
Impossible!
Why did our rank suddenly drop?!
It was a brilliant plan to absorb
the higher ranked members.
But our commander isn't the
type you can hold down.
C-Could it be...?!
Him?!
He's so offensive that he's starting to drag
Diamond Perfume's ranking down!
Curses!
It was a terrible mistake
to absorb that gorilla!
Toshi!
Now!
Do me!
Embarrass me!
If my rank goes down,
so will theirs!
Kondo-san...
Don't tell me, you...!
You purposefully allowed yourself to be absorbed
so you could destroy them from the inside?!
Don't worry about me!
Defeat me along with them!
That's impossible, Kondo-san!
I can't do it!
Do it!
Do it, damn it!
You said the Shinsengumi will
dominate the top, didn't you?!
I'll catch up to you afterwards!
That's impossible!
I'm supposed to embarrass you more when
you're standing there fully expozed?!
I can't do it!
And hell, what would be more embarrassing
than being fully expozed?!
Stop wasting time!
Do you intend to waste Kondo-san's
good intentions!
Take this!
A waist pouch on a naked body!
That's it!
Keep it up!
I won't let that happen!
A waist pouch goes with chemical-washed jeans!
What?!
She brought my rank back up with by
perfectly coordinating to the waist pouch!
I'm not giving in!
How's this?!
Chain mail!
Chain mail goes with sickle and chain!
Damn!
I'll add in the Cursed Belt!
[Note: Dragon Quest Series items]
Then I'll give him the Shield of Ruin!
This can't be!
Then I'll throw in a double-edged sword!
You're going with her coordination?!
It seems that this is the end.
Will you voluntarily cooperate with
Diamond Perfume, Crapxile?
Let us cease this unsightly battle.
We can all be in Diamond Perfume.
Everybody in 1st place.
What's wrong with that?
Don't be ridiculous!
[Note: From the Anime Evangelion]
What's with the pseudo
Human Instrumentality Project?!
Commander Ikari may
accept it, but I won't!
Is there any point to achieving
1st place in such a manner?!
Do you intend to make all those
votes count for nothing?!
To be frank, I don't give a damn
about a popularity poll.
But there are people who
can't accept the results.
This is the best solution, right?
Hold it right there.
Hold it right there. What?
What did you just say, Tsukky?
Well, I don't give a damn about
the popularity poll anymore,
so let's get this over with.
Y'know...
Tsukky, I've been thinking...
Aren't you being a little unfair, Tsukky?
Hmm?
You seem to be the only one
separating yourself, Tsukky.
The whole "I don't care, but I came
because everyone else told me to."
What's with the facade?
You're going to be the only one who doesn't get
her hands dirty? Who stays clean this time?
Well, I really don't care...
Yes, yes. You're so cool.
The whole, "I placed 10th
even though I don't care."
Amazing, right?
You're probably so calm
because you're 10th.
It's different when you're 10th!
They seem to be fighting
among themselves...
What? Speak up if you have a problem.
That aloof attitude of yours
really pisses me off!
What? What is this?
Where are we?
Be more serious!
An all-girls boarding school?
Don't give me that crap!
We're doing our best to live
with our hands dirty!
We're wading through the mud as we
try to become something better!
You can't survive in this
world by being clean!
I never said anything about
being clean or dirty.
I'm simply not interested!
Cut it out!
Damn bitch pretending to be all innocent!
Say that you really want to be 1st!
Say it!
["Little girls should go home and
watch "Ainori" or something!!"]
[Note: A Japanese reality show.]
What was that?
Who were those old men?
H-He was standing, right?
He was walking on two legs, right?
Th-They headed towards where
Sis and everybody else is...
M-Monsters!
Elizabeth!
What are you... Abeshi!
Something's...
No, I don't hear anything.
I can't hear a thing.
I know nothing. Nothing at all.
Gin-san!
A-Above your head!
Wh-What is this?!
My ranking...
My ranking is dropping like a rock!
What's going on?!
I didn't do anything!
What's happening?!
W-We're too late...
Hasegawa-san!
We spent too much time fighting...
We let our greed get the better of us,
wanting to rank higher than others.
We displayed our ugly conflict
for the past three weeks.
The viewers, the gods punished
us for our sins.
Y-You must stop this fight now!
D-Don't let him have his way!
Him?
He was the one who used unnatural
methods to summon the gods!
He was the one who took me down
and set your fight in motion.
No, he was the one who caused the
mess across this entire world.
Return to the beginning...
Why was there such an uproar?
What started all of this?
Head to the roof...
To end this stupid mess!
You're late.
I've been waiting here
to show you this sight.
Look.
They're all desperately fighting
for their own rank.
Isn't that funny?
Their attempts to raise their ranking do
nothing but make them look worse.
All humans are the same on the inside.
Nobody is suitable to be 1st.
We're all dirty maggots.
Yamazaki-san...
So this was all your doing...
You pretended that you were attacked
to drag your own rank down and
cause an uproar in the rankings,
to spark everybody's greed
and create a mess
that triggered the rage of the gods...
You couldn't become 1st.
You didn't try to become 1st.
Instead, you brought everyone
else down to your level.
Yamazaki-san...
Are you satisfied now?
Flowers need a foundation of dirt.
But the flowers never try to understand
how the dirt feels...
They bloom without a care...
Despite the fact that they could
never bloom without dirt...
I wanted to let them know
how the dirt feels...
Our true worth...
Punch me if you want.
But your ranking will only drop further.
The gods have grown tired
of this ugly battle!
Invite their rage if you'd like!
That's fine!
I'll smack you good!
Toying with people like that!
Don't look down on us!
Shi-
Gin-san, I won't let you dirty your hands.
I'm...
Happy to be the dirt for my flower!
Yamazaki-san, it's true that people
like us are never noticed.
Nobody tries to understand how we feel.
But that's fine.
We just have to be there like it's the
most natural thing in the world.
That's what dirt does.
Yamazaki-san, that was the spirit of being the
stepping stone that you taught me about!
And are you really okay with that?
Spending the rest of your life downtrodden
without anyone noticing...
Don't say that nobody notices us...
I... I alone know!
Yamazaki-san alone knows!
Isn't that enough?!
What more do you need?!
Sh-Shinpachi-kun...
You aren't the only ones.
E-Everyone...
Up. Look up.
It seems that the gods
were also watching.
This is...
We're...
Okay!
Hooray! Hooray!
We'll be your stepping stones for today!
Zaki!
Thanks for supporting us
when we didn't know it!
Come on, you two!
Congratulations on being 1st
place stepping stones!
Yamazaki-san!
Shinpachi-kun!
Everybody understands...
Everybody underst...
Dirt should return to the dirt.
Why are you two in 1st?
You had us fooled, damn punks.
Allow us to ask one more time...
Are popularity polls...
...really necessary?
[The End]
[The Top 100 Characters]
[Preview]
What?
A request to get rid of a wasps' nest?
Hell, when was the last time
we had an actual odd job?
And so next time:
"The Whole Peeing on a Bee Sting Is a Myth.
You'll Get Germs, So Don't Do It!!"
[Next week is a two parter. Things kick off in the Shinsengumi with "Hometowns and boobs are meant to be far away."]
[Hijikata, the mayonnaise lover's dream comes
true as he tours a mayo factory.]
[See you next time.]