Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[Note: "Okama" means cross-dresser
or drag queen in Japanese.]
[Today, there'll be two episodes again. "OKAMA
in love" and "Kagura and the umbrella."]
[And "Katsura Enrichment Week" Part III, is going on.
You'll see more details after the show's ending song!]
We're doing this to earn back payments
on our rent, Gin-san.
It's not Gin-san. I'm Pako right now.
Today, I forget all about the pride of being a man
and the thing that hangs between my legs.
Hey, you two aren't smiling. Smile!
That's right. Right now you guys are...
...splendid butterflies
dancing in the night.
This special dancing team...
[Note: A parody of Exile, a 14-member Japanese pop music
band. And "Kama," short for "okama" (drag queen).]
You're a member of Kamaxile!
Hey! Dance better!
You shut up! I'll kill you, Baldy!
Hey, you, he's our customer!
["Definitely Do Not Let Your Girlfriend See
The Things You Use For Cross-dressing"]
[GIRLY BOY CLUB]
[PAYMENT]
Here's the payment for
both Pako and Pachie.
Thank you very much.
You were a mess, but thank you for helping
us out when we were short on staff.
You can officially join KAMAXILE and
be a real member if you'd like.
Shut up. Who would wanna
join your toad-ugly group?!
Hey, that's so rude of you!
Who's an ugly toad?
We know we're beautiful, so
stop being jealous, already!
That's right! He's jealous
of us! He's envious!
Hey, you guys, it's too late to think positively
after you look in the mirror.
What?!
Good work today.
Ah, Agomi-san.
It's not Agomi. My name is Azumi.
For some reason, she seems depressed.
She's been like that lately.
She's all right at work, but right after
she finishes, she gets like that.
Ah, I guess all her energy
goes right to her chin.
Maybe so.
Get home safe.
Have a nice night.
There's no scarier place than that.
That's true. It's like "Scary
Face Safari Park."
Hey, wait!
Agomi-san.
My name is Azumi.
I have something to ask you, Odd Jobs.
[RAMEN DAIGAKUIN]
...It was two weeks ago...
As usual, I stopped by my favorite
ramen shop after work.
Here's your boiling stone
bowl ramen special!
Wow! It looks so yummy!
Let's eat!
It's hot!!
Owwww!
Are you...all right?
At that moment, I realized it.
That's right.
It was love at first sight!
Hey! Are you listening to me?!
I guess I'm lacking sleep.
I feel dizzy, Shinpachi-kun.
Don't worry. I'm really
dizzy, too, Gin-san.
I feel like I'm pregnant. I feel like
throwing up so bad, Gin-chan.
Don't worry. I'm about to
throw up, too, Kagura.
His name is Jurota.
He's a rookie host at Takamagahara,
a well-known club in Kabukicho.
Takamagahara... That's
Kyoshiro-san's...
I'm just another hostess...
And he's a host...
That's right. An innocent young girl
like me is destined to play around.
I think I'm suffering from
auditory hallucinations.
It sounded like he described himself as
an innocent young girl, Shinpachi-kun.
Don't worry, he really did say
"innocent girl," Gin-san.
Are you all right, Kagura?
Kagura-chan.
I've never suffered so much over
a passionate love affair before.
So I need your help!
I'm really suffering. It almost makes me want to die.
All right, here we go!
Hey! Why are you going to kill me?!
Well, you said you wanted to die, so I
was going to help you on your journey.
I was going to be the travel agent for hell.
That's not what I meant!
I want you to help lead me to love!
I want you to put me on an
international flight of love!
That kind of international
flight is impossible!
[Note: Parody of Space Battleship Yamato.]
Even if you had a spaceship that
can travel at warp speed,
an old man's love would
never reach that host!
Who's the old man in love?!
It's you!
If I don't do something, I'll go crazy.
I feel like I'm going to turn
into a love monster!
Well, you already are a monster, I guess.
If you can't help me out,
comfort me at least!
No way! No, no!
Healing the loneliness of
an innocent old man
isn't on the list of the
Odd Job's job duties!
Then what do you think I should do?!
Gin-san...
I guess we have no choice.
[Three days later...]
We can try asking Kyoshiro.
Welcome to the host
club, Takamagahara.
That's right. I started working
as a new host
in a black suit under the
name Agonosuke.
I locked away my true self deep
in the bottom of my heart.
Of course, it was a painful choice.
I know... It doesn't mean the distance between
our hearts is getting any closer.
Hey, you look like you're down! A-go-mi!
Huh? Is that so?
You idiot!
Really... You showed your true colors
so quickly after I called you by name.
Are you even trying, you bastard?!
Hey, listen up.
We're gonna act like angry customers
and pick a fight with Jurota.
You protect him from us.
Then the distance between
your hearts will shrink.
Pako...
I...If I wasn't falling in love with him,
I would fall in love with you guys.
Please don't!
Hello, I'm Jurota, the person you
requested. It's nice to meet you.
Wow! You're so cute!
So true! I'm going to fall for you!
Hey, give us more services!
Hey, wait...miss!
We do get more, right?!
Agomi-san, now is the time!
You're using us as steppingstones to build
up a trusting relationship with him!
That smooth skin... I want to eat it...
You messed up!
We have no choice, Gin-san!
Let's go to plan B!
Well now, let's lighten the mood
a bit. Chug that!
Well, but this is too...
Show us how cool you are!
That's right. The customer who
forces a host to drink is...
...a real troublemaker!
Agomi, this is your chance!!
Excuse me, Jurota-san...
...let me have that drink.
Agonosuke-san...
Here we go...Azumi...
I can do this!
Men have courage!
Women are lovable! But cross-dressers
are the most passionate!
Agonosuke-san!
A-Are you all right?!
I'm so relieved...
You saved me, Agonosuke-san.
Thanks for coming.
Well, all kinds of things were happening,
but it was good for Agomi-san.
Sort of.
Wait.
Saigo-san.
Hey, Agonosuke, when you're free,
can you clean up the locker
room for your fellow hosts?
Certainly.
[HOST LOCKER ROOM]
What are you guys doing with him?
Nothing really.
It's what Agomi wanted. So we're
just giving him a supportive push.
But you do know, right?
In the end, Agomi's love won't
ever be reciprocated.
Besides, he's an ordinary host,
especially around them.
If you do something unnecessary, and
it hurts him, what are you going to do?
Don't tell me you think things
will work out between them.
No need to worry.
It's like Agomi is more a young girl
in love than a real girl right now.
Just looking at a man from a
distance gives him a fantasy.
But men in the real world
are always nasty.
And not only in the way
they treat woman...
...but also in their lifestyle, the
way they smell, everything.
If Agomi finds out about their real lives,
his fantasies will be crushed.
Then she'll...
...realize that she has to move
on for the sake of tomorrow.
Gin-san...
No!
This is...
...Jurota-kun's...
...smell!
Is this Jurota-kun's locker?
Oh, yes! Oh, sweet!
What's this? Nice smell! Oh, no! I'm
going up! I'm rising to heaven!
It's not like that!
Well, see you later!
Wow! Great!
Agonosuke-san must be working
really hard to clean up!
A-Agonosuke-san...
That's right... You found out...
And so I might as well...
It looks like Agomi-san quit the
club after disgracing himself.
It ended up being his hopeless love.
Serious feelings sometimes have
a cruel ending, you know.
But Agomi will move on for the
sake of a new tomorrow.
Thanks for waiting!
Oh, no! I didn't wait at all.
Well, let's go!
Yeah, Azumi-san.
Gin-san...What's...that?
Well, you know... He moved on for
the sake of a new tomorrow...
...with Jurota-kun.
What the...?!
It's raining today, too...
When rainy days come so often,
it makes my heart gloomy as well.
Rainy day, rainy day, more rainy days...
It makes my brain moldy, too.
It was already like that.
How many days have
we not seen the sun?
It looks like mushrooms are
growing on my crotch.
It was already like that.
There are no clients. I don't feel
like going out in the rain.
There's no money.
Sadaharu stinks and my feet stink,
too, and so does Shinpachi.
What do you mean, "so does Shinpachi"?
Don't compare me to your feet.
Why are you two being
so negative? Cheer up!
The rainy season will be over soon.
Then you can get as much
sunlight as you want.
...That's why I hate the rainy season.
I'm kind of dubious about the
name "Tsuyu," anyway.
[Note: Tsuyu means rainy season.]
Just hearing to it makes me feel down.
Just listening to it makes me feel down.
It can't be helped because
it's the rainy season.
Why don't we call it by a different name?
Something with a more exhilarating tone.
How about "Happy Birthday To You?"
[Note: Japanese pronounce "to you"
like tsu-yu. Tsuyu = rainy season.]
...Isn't that a little long?
[Note: Kagura refers to the day
of a girl's menstrual period.]
It's too difficult to say.
I prefer "Girl's Day."
No, that sounds like a different day.
That's even more difficult to say.
And it's not even an appropriate word
for a show in this timeslot.
Then let's adopt the middle viewpoint
and call it "Independence Day."
Why is that the middle?
From now on, call "Tsuyu"
"Independence Day."
Anyway...well... "Independence Day"
will be over soon, so let's cheer up!
Man, I really hate "Tsuyu"!
I don't feel like doing anything.
...Huh? Aren't you going to
use "Independence Day"?
I felt a bit embarrassed saying that.
Huh? Shinpachi-kun, did you just say
"Indepen...something"? What's that?
No-No, I didn't... I didn't
say that! What's that?!
Yeah, you just said it. "Indepen...something."
Isn't it popular right now?
Is it something cool?
I didn't say that! I don't
even know what it is!
You guys are too noisy!
Stop annoying me and just shut up!
Who do think is the most
annoying person?
You guys are just taking
your stress out on me!
Not really. I don't take
my stress out on you.
I'm not annoying at all, either.
Don't talk! I'm so annoyed
listening to you guys talk!
You're the one who shouldn't
be talking! What's that?
Those mini gongs on your head! There's
something ugly on your head!
Oh? Why do you wear only
one sleeve of that robe?!
Why don't you wear it properly?!
Good grief! I give up! I don't care
about you guys anymore!
Shut up!
Shut up, Four-eyes!
Who you calling Four-eyes?!
["There's Almost a 100% Chance You'll Forget
Your Umbrella and Hate Yourself For It"]
Why do I have to go out with you
guys on such a rainy day?
When we stay in the house and
brood, we get depressed.
We should go out at such times.
And this isn't so bad, you know.
An Edokko should enjoy each
season's highlights.
[Note: Edokko is a Japanese term referring
to a person born and raised in Edo/Tokyo.]
For example, look! Here come some
girls walking with umbrellas.
Aren't they pure and beautiful?
We see girls with umbrellas
all throughout the year.
And girls with wet see-through
T-shirts are more...
Hey, what are you doing?
Kagura-chan, you'll catch a cold.
...It's broken.
Huh?
My umbrella is broken.
Just leave me alone.
Women sometimes want
to walk in the rain.
Hey. Your head is what's broken!
What's with her?
Just leave her alone.
Brats like rain, storms, typhoons
and all that kind of stuff.
By the way, we ran out
of laundry detergent.
[OEDO STORE]
Gin-chan, did you buy
my pickled seaweed?
Buy it yourself, brat.
Here.
I-I don't want it.
That umbrella is too flashy.
Who said it was for you?
This is for me. Just use that dirty one.
Wow, nice umbrella, Gin-san.
It looks cool and chic.
This is nice, isn't it?
Even though it only costs 100 yen.
Hey, wait! That's weird. It's weird if a
man uses it! I can take it if you like.
That's all right. It's all right
if women walk in the rain.
It's raining again today...
Whenever it rains,
Kagura-chan goes out.
She really is a girl at heart.
Humph. Brats like rain, storms, typhoons,
and all that kind of stuff.
That reminds me, the rain is supposed
to get worse today.
I wonder if she'll be all right.
It's raining again today...
Kagura-chan is out today again?
After all, she's a girl.
Brats like rain, storms, typhoons
and all that kind of stuff.
By the way, the 7th typhoon is going to
hit Edo. I wonder if she'll be all right.
Kagura-chan.
...What?
The weather was really rough,
so we were worried about you.
You're all drenched. Are you all right?
Kagura-chan, make sure you completely
dry off with a towel, okay?
All right.
Hey, young lady. Young lady!
You have such a cool umbrella.
Would you mind letting us under it?
Because ours broke.
Boy, "Independence Day" makes me feel
really gloomy. That's why I hate it.
No, I think "Independence
Day" isn't all that bad.
[ANTI-FOREIGNER FACTION EMPLOYMENT
EXAM MAKEUP TEST]
[Because my birthday will be next week. -Kotaro]
Then, here's the question.
In today's episode, I showed
up four times.
[Note: Opening, Ending. This
part won't be counted.]
Which parts were those?
You'll see the answer in
next week's episode.
[Preview]
Gintoki-sama, I have
some vacation time.
But I have no idea what I should
do during my vacation.
Well, days off mean not doing anything.
The next episode... "Lucky Is a Man
Who Gets Up and Goes to Work."
[Next week, after a long absence,
robot maid, Tama, appears.]
[The origin of the name "Tama" is from the
egg-cracker. Will you remember that?]
[See you next time.]