Edited at https://subtitletools.com
History is written by the victors.
But even if the radiant sunlight hides
the lights of the smaller stars,
even if those lights never
reach the people,
there exists a star, who risks
its life to shine brightly.
This is a story about one such star.
Quitting the business to
live in retirement, eh?
Not bad.
But I wouldn't be able to stand
such a backwards place.
["NAGAI"]
What would a reporter
want with me now?
Well, I was hoping to talk a bit.
I shouldn't need to tell you that I'm
researching the Anti-Foreigner War.
I would love to hear
your perspective as a military reporter
who was embedded with the Amanto, Bakufu,
and the Anti-Foreigner Faction during the war
and saw many different sights while
surviving many perilous situations.
I saw nothing...
No, you would know, Nagai-san!
As a journalist during the Anti-Foreigner War,
you must have encountered that enigmatic figure...
Only rumors remain...
Now considered a myth...
You would know about that man...
You're not one to leave even
if I told you to, are you?
["It's better to take care of this year's business within the year, but once the year is about to end, you figure that you might as well put it off till next year for a fresh start. That's how the end of the year goes."]
It began twenty-some years ago.
The Amanto ships arrived in
Edo and began their attack,
using overwhelming military force
to compel the opening of Edo.
A number of unequal
treaties were signed.
The samurai lost their patience with
the Bakufu's soft foreign policy
and sensing the crisis at hand,
they gathered under
the Anti-Foreign ideal.
They fought,
but their actions only led to much death.
However, the war unexpectedly
reached a stalemate.
The Amanto had an overwhelming
technological advantage,
but the efforts of the Anti-Foreigner Faction
allowed them to at least put up a fight.
That was largely because they avoided direct
battles and adopted guerrilla warfare.
But the main reason was
because they were samurai.
Even if their weapons
were clearly inferior,
they fought without any fear.
The highly advanced Amanto were unable to
understand the desperation of the samurai.
Samurai...
The Amanto feared their existence.
But that served to prolong the
war as it became a quagmire.
That's right.
A very long period of war existed, during which the
Anti-Foreigner Faction were labeled traitors,
but there was still hope.
This was when a group of young people
began distinguishing themselves.
The unstoppable noble, Kotaro Katsura.
The leader of the Kiheitai,
Shinsuke Takasugi.
A master swordsman,
Tatsuma Sakamoto.
An impressive bunch.
The Faction regained their morale as they
saw these men risk their lives in battle.
Soon, a large number of young men
had assembled around them.
On the surface, correct?
How much do you know?
Technically, I know nothing.
But I have confirmed that he existed.
An enigma, who wielded
unparalleled influence
for a person who never appeared
in the pages of history.
Blazing across the battlefield in a flash
of white as he cut down sturdy
Amanto with one swing.
Admired by allies as a pillar of support
while instilling terror in his foes.
He was known as the "White Devil."
The White Devil...?
Yes.
'Course, he was called by many names.
So you do know of him!
Please tell me about him!
What will you do with that knowledge?
You should understand.
As a journalist, I wish to know the truth!
The first time I saw him was back then...
I didn't expect an ambush here!
We must retreat immediately or
there will be more casualties!
Are you insane?
We'll be wiped out if we
turn our backs and run!
However!
Are we out of options?
Don't be foolish!
We still have him!
He will surely come!
Him, huh?
What was that?!
Ships 3, 6, and 7 have been shot down!
He has come!
Th-The White Devil...
Yes, he was the White Devil...
Gundam!
Wait!
Gundam, my ass!
You've got the wrong show!
I-it's for the 30th anniversary!
[Note: 2009 is the 30th anniversary of Gundam.]
That doesn't matter!
Are you just making up a story so
you can talk about Gundam?
[Mobile Suit Gundam 30th Anniversary Special Extra #2]
I-It wasn't me!
It was the staff of this show!
That's even worse!
Kabukicho radio exercise #1.
Ready...
I'm off!
["Radio Exercises are Socials
for Boys and Girls"]
Okay, we're done.
I'll stamp your card, so line up.
[Kagura]
That's impressive, Kagura-chan.
You have perfect attendance so far.
But if you keep barely showing up on time,
you'll miss out one of these days.
Sleep deprivation really
hurts your beauty.
Women need every minute
of sleep they can get.
I can see how you're able to walk around
in public with that haystack on your head.
But you're really amazing.
The kids in Kabukicho have become
know-it-alls and don't even bother coming.
We only get health freaks
and senior people.
You're the only kid who comes.
Oh, there was one more.
That's Hisashi Hongo-kun.
He also has perfect attendance so far.
I heard that he's participating for health
reasons since he's not very strong.
He's a good kid.
He always shows up fifteen minutes
before the exercise begins.
Well, that will come to an end today.
Today's Friday night movie slot
is "Kiki's Delivery Service".
A kid could never ignore
Kiki and go to bed.
Stay up all night to dreams of Kiki.
Kabukicho radio exercise #1.
Ready...
Lift your arms up and stretch your back.
1, 2, 3, 4.
5, 6, 7, 8.
Less people are showing up.
I guess they all went on
vacation for Obon break.
Kagura-chan, are you going
anywhere during Obon?
Kagura-chan?
You have bags under your eyes.
It's nothing.
It's just the baker's husband
being so awesome.
What baker's husband?
You watched it?
You watched Kiki?
You stayed up late then?
Lift your arms up and stretch your back.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Bend your knees with your arms at your side and
motion like a ca[beep]ret girl pouring liquor.
3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Now drop to the ground like a
sxxp girl greeting a customer.
5, 6, 7, 8.
Welcome.
Now spread your legs like a str[beep]er.
Then we'll see you again tomorrow.
["Visiting my family. Please stamp
the card yourselves." - Tanaka]
U-Uh...
The stamp...
I heard that he wasn't coming
today, so I brought one.
If you'd like, I could stamp yours.
You aren't going anywhere
for summer vacation?
Is your family also poor?
It's not so much money as...
I have health problems so I have to
visit the hospital on a regular basis.
I can't take any extended trips.
I see.
You have the money, but your body
won't do what you want it to.
Nothing works out in this world.
My body's perfectly fine,
but I have no money.
It's better that way.
With my health problems,
I can't do anything very long.
I don't even get to go to the
temple school as much.
That's why I wanted to see this
through to the end of summer.
It would be sad if I wasn't able to accomplish
anything after being born into this world.
Anything will do.
I just wanted to see
something to the end.
That's pretty ominous.
You sound like you're about to die.
S-Sorry...
I have a bad habit of being
pessimistic about everything.
But I'm glad that you're here.
I would have been lonely all by myself.
Kagura-chan, will you come
again tomorrow?
Of course.
Once I've made up my mind, I'll come
if it's raining cats or dogs or spears.
If you're a man, stop whining and
finish what you set out to do.
You'd better come, even if you
have to drag yourself here.
I can't be motivated if I don't
have any competition.
Y-Yeah.
Thanks, Kagura-chan.
Let's do our best together.
Yeah!
Kabukicho radio exercise #2.
Ready...
Relax your entire body while hopping.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Stick your right hand in the air
while hurling like a drunk.
5, 6, 7, 8.
Can't you tell that I have a hangover?
That's our Gin-chan!
He's like the real thing!
[Sakata]
Spread your arms and flex like a gorilla.
That's our boss lady!
Looks just like a gorilla!
[Shimura]
Wave your arms and legs while sprinting
like an Anti-Foreigner Faction man.
Wait!
That's our Zura!
Catch him already!
It's Katsura, not Zura!
[Katsura]
Get on all fours like a [beep]
waiting to be punished.
Smack me!
Smack me all you want!
[Sarutobi]
Lie flat on your back on the ground,
like a man without a job.
This isn't exercise!
I'm not doing anything here!
[Hasegawa]
Kagura-chan, I never knew how fun it was to
accomplish something with someone else.
What are you saying all of a sudden?
I always blamed my inability to do anything
on my illness, my poor health.
If only I had a normal body...
If only I was healthy...
I was being jealous of other people for it.
But that wasn't what I needed.
I'm glad I joined in these radio exercises.
I learned that the hard things can
be fun when you're with others...
It's all because I made a friend like you.
A-Are you stupid?
Why are you so happy?
Your card hasn't been
completely stamped yet!
A field trip isn't over until you've made
it home and greeted your parents!
Radio exercises aren't over until you've gotten
your last stamp and gone home to take a nap!
Don't relax until you've gotten through
the last spurt, goody two-shoes!
Right!
Canceled?!
What do you mean?
I didn't hear anything about that!
What is there to hear?
What kind of fool would
go exercise in this rain?
This fool right here!
A little rain won't be enough to stop me!
The radio exercise itself is canceled.
Kids don't do radio exercises
when it rains,
just as girls don't participate in swimming
class when it's that time of the month.
B-But after I got all these stamped...
I'll stamp it for you later.
Doesn't count if it's raining.
Like an unearned win.
That's not the issue here!
We want to see this through!
Doesn't change the fact
that it's been canceled.
This is a good opportunity for you to rest.
Isn't that kid unhealthy?
Don't push him too hard.
Kabukicho radio exercise #1.
Ready...
He collapsed?!
Why?!
He was fine just the other day...
He was exercising with me!
Our son doesn't have long to live...
That's what the doctor said.
Though we never told him.
He must have realized...
He suddenly said that he wanted
to accomplish something.
The doctor said to have him rest,
but he kept begging us
to let him go exercise.
But I never thought that he would
have gone out in that rain...
He said he'll go even if it's raining
cats or dogs or spears.
That was the promise he
made with his first friend.
I broke our promise...
I said I would come if it was raining
cats or dogs or spears.
I promised...
Sorry... If I hadn't said that...
It's okay.
I would have gone, even
if you hadn't promised.
It would be frustrating for rain to get in the
way of everything we've accomplished.
But I guess it was no good.
It was no fun exercising by myself.
It wasn't any fun without Kagura-chan.
Sorry, you helped me this far.
But it looks like I won't be able to
see this through to the end.
That's not true.
You can't give up yet.
I'll keep exercising and getting
stamps until you come back.
Did you know?
You can get a stamp on a rainy day
because it's like an unearned win.
So...
So come back.
We can exercise together again.
It won't stop raining until you come back.
I'll be waiting...
The whole time...
Kabukicho radio exercise #1!
Ready!
Hey, I said ready.
Stand.
Or I won't stamp you.
Gin-chan...
First, lift your arms up
and stretch your back!
Yes!
1, 2, 3, 4!
5, 6, 7, 8!
1, 2, 3...
Okay! Now line up!
No cutting!
Hey, kid. What do you
think you're doing?
Want me to brand you
instead of a stamp?
It stopped raining...
[Preview]
Hey, hold on.
We're just here to catch Hoichi,
the boss of Kabukicho stray cats, right?
So why?
So WHY?!
Why do I look like THIS?!
The next episode...
"When Looking for Something,
Try Using its Perspective."
[We'd like to believe that pure, young children
who believe in Santa Claus watch this anime.]
[Next episode, the Kabukicho Stray Cat arc begins.
Gin-san is cursed and turned into a cat!?]
[See you next time.]