[Last time on GinTama:]
Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[Input the damn resurrection spell]
[Note: Parody of Dragon Quest game.]
Uh, wait. What is this?
Can't you tell?
It's a "resurrection spell," okay?
We're picking up where we
left off last week, right?
So we need one.
Why?!
Why do we need a "resurrection spell" for an
anime flashback of the previous episode?!
Nobody uses a password system
in this day and age!
And a spell was never mentioned
at the end of last week's episode!
What? You didn't write it down?
There wasn't one!
You're so useless.
Then I'll just enter something random.
Uh, I'm pretty sure it's a bad
idea to put in random stuff.
It'll be fine.
[KAGURA SHINPACHI GINTOKI
AMACHI HIDEAKI HORI RYUUJI]
[Note: HORI RYUUJI is a parody of Yuji Horii,
creator of Dragon Quest.]
There's usually a pattern to these things.
Like an Up, Up, Down, Down, Left,
Right, Left, Right, B, A kind of thing.
[Note: The famous Konami Code to get 9
extra lives in Nintendo's Contra.]
Uh, that'd be a totally different game.
And doesn't this spell
look awfully familiar?
And aren't you including people who
have nothing to do with GinTama?
Okay, all done.
[Tama: I am your subordinate
Please call me Tama]
Hey!
A different game has started up!
[Tama: We are in Edo in the vicinity where the incident
occurred How do you wish to begin the investigation?]
How ancient is this thing?!
Kids nowadays wouldn't be
able to recognize this!
[(Selects Confession)]
[Tama: Then I shall confess first]
And what the hell is Tama-san doing?!
[Tama: Forgive me I did it Tama was the culprit]
[Tama: I'll never do it again Please forgive me]
Okay, all clear.
Tama's the killer.
[Tamatopia Murder Case
The End]
Tama was the culprit.
That was fast!
And that's not even possible!
That had nothing to do with
last week's episode!
Where the hell is Tamatopia?!
[Note: Parody of Portopia Serial Murder
Case. Created by Yuji Horii.]
Can't you be serious about this?!
[The real recap from last episode.]
The computer virus "Tapir."
A brand-new virus that infects the program,
consumes it, and multiplies.
Once it infected Tama, who
is a highly advanced robot,
it must have evolved a great deal.
And it's been there for a while.
Nobody can do anything about it.
It's evolved into the strongest
and worst virus ever.
But there's still a way to save Tama.
Shouldn't that be obvious?
We're going to eliminate the virus.
You midgets are doing it.
Best of luck to you.
["The Human Body is Like a Little Universe"]
[Note: Leukocytes are the white blood cells
that defend the body from infections.]
Welcome to Leukocyte Kingdom.
If you head north, you will
find Leukocyte Castle.
Head east to find Bifidus Village.
Head south to find E. coli town.
[Leukocyte Kingdom]
But stay away from the Capillary
Caves to the west.
It's crawling with viruses.
At your current level, you'll
be instantly wiped out.
Huh?
What?
What's with these people?
Huh?
What's with this place?
What is this?!
Why are all these people in bodysuits wandering
around inside Tama-san's body?!
Why is there an entire nation
inside of Tama-san?!
Why is there a weapon shop?!
Why is there an inn?!
Why is this like an RPG?!
Uh, Gin-san?
Where are you two going?
Shouldn't that be obvious?
The first step when you come to one of these
places is to put together a war chest.
That's why...
Why did you head straight
for the casino?!
I just said we needed a war chest.
I don't want to deal with a riskily run adventure
where we're always strapped for cash.
I'm the kind of person who spends hours
on the mini games whenever
I play an RPG.
You can't make any progress that way
because you always get off track,
in-game and in real life!
The next thing you know, you've
forgotten the main story!
We don't have time to play around here!
Tama-san will be taken over by more
of the virus if we don't hurry!
Calm down, Shinpachi.
You realize that without any money,
you'll have to stay equipped with
those Cypress Glasses?
[Note: Parody of the Cypress Stick (starter
weapon) from Dragon Quest game.]
What the hell are Cypress Glasses?!
Don't you want to buy Steel
Glasses at the next town?
Now, now.
Calm down for now.
It's a waste to rush through everything.
It's important to prepare well before setting
out on an adventure in an RPG.
Don't blame me if you leave the safe town
and run into a really strong enemy.
Now confess what you've
done before God.
We're saving right now?!
We haven't done anything yet!
All we did was go to the casino!
What's your beef?
I see.
Shinpachi's the type who always
rests up at an inn before saving?
You're a real stickler.
You people are the sticklers! Who
bothers to save at this point?!
Just move on with the story!
Were you listening to me?
We need to hurry.
If we don't pick up the
pace, we'll be too late.
I know that.
But y'know?
We're completely clueless right now.
There's no point in floundering around.
Do you know what we're
supposed to do?
See?
After all, we're completely
out of our comfort zone.
We have no idea if these guys
are allies or enemies.
You have a point...
Do not worry.
They all serve me.
Ta-Tama-san!
Allow me to guide you.
Could you please follow me?
What?!
Tama-san showed up inside Tama-san!
I apologize for taking so long.
I created an offshoot from a sector
in my system that is still safe.
I shall provide you with support.
Provide us with support?
Is your body okay?!
There is no problem.
I cannot lie around shamelessly while
everyone else is fighting for my sake.
Er, sorry about that...
We've only been to the casino, so we
haven't actually done any fighting.
I shall redirect the remaining operational
systems to support you.
Does that include these guys?!
Yes, they are components of the original
security system in my body.
The anti-virus program, Leukocyte.
Security?! These men in bodysuits?!
Their job is to expel the viruses
that infiltrate my body.
And as they protect me, they've also
built a home inside my body.
Protect you...?
Are they actually protecting you?
It looks more like they're pretending
to be in Dragon Quest.
There is no problem.
Their program has been rewritten to recognize
you as saviors from another world.
They should all assist you
in destroying the viruses.
We should start by meeting with the Leukocyte
King and asking for his aid.
It will be impossible to defeat
the Tapir without it.
Oh, yeah.
Now that you mention it, we were asked
to deliver a message to the king.
It saddens me to say that our Leukocyte
army has fallen to the Virus army.
I pray that our king takes flight.
And searches for the legendary
warriors from another world...
Search for the midgets...
Let's go, Gin-san.
Tonnelat, how could you die on me?
[Note: Character name from Dragon Quest.]
No, he isn't dead.
Don't kill him off like that.
And Tonnelat is one lame name.
Tonnelat only needed 1,008 love experience
points to reach the next level.
What are love experience points?
How many times does a girl have to fail
at love before she grows stronger?
And who's Tonnelat?
[Note: Fictional name from Dragon Quest.]
Suke-san needs 5,466 more
summer experience points.
What the hell?!
How many summers has
he been through?!
And why Suke-san?!
Would you like to learn the
resurrection spell for love?
Only weak men would
be interested in that.
Women are always looking
forward to their next love!
When did this game turn
into a romance RPG?
Are you completely influenced
by your memories of love?!
Ow! Ow!
Her parting words are piercing my heart!
Like I care!
What did you say?!
You mean our Leukocyte army was
defeated by the Virus army?!
Yes.
That was the last message
from the injured soldier.
He wished for Your Majesty to escape before
your foes reached your kingdom.
But running away from love
will only lead to regret.
Can you drop the crap
about love already?!
Are you a sophomore in high
school or something?!
Escape and abandon the leukocytes who've
been injured while fighting for this kingdom?
How could I do such a thing?
Travelers...
A legend has been passed down
in this kingdom from olden days.
When a great disaster befalls this land,
heroes carrying toothpicks will travel from
another world to save our world!
Perhaps you all are...
No, I say no more.
How could I ask someone else to fight for the sake
of a kingdom on the verge of destruction?!
Except you just said that out loud.
This old man's got no shame, and I'm
not just talking about the bodysuit.
Hey, you're pretty slow, old Spe**.
[Note: Bleep covers "sperm."]
Enough introductions. Just hand
over your remaining soldiers.
And give us whatever's in your treasure
vault for our war chest.
We sound more like thieves than heroes.
Amazing.
Are you offering to fight on our side?
My eyes did not betray me!
You must be the heroic
midgets of legend!
But our kingdom has suffered from the long
war and we have no soldiers to offer you.
Don't give me that bull!
There are two guards here, plus you!
I'll abuse you like a workhorse.
Hey! Stop that, Gin-san!
I shall offer one of the
strongest soldiers of the
Leukocyte Kingdom to aid
you in your journey.
Really?
Come forth!
The strongest pair around, feared
as the Leukocyte Double Dragon!
[Note: Parody of Ortega and Despisaro
from Dragon Quest III.]
The warrior, Bortega!
The fighter, Despigaro!
Take whichever one you want.
We don't want either of them!
Hey!
How can you call them Double Dragon?!
How can you call them
the strongest pair?!
Why is there someone who looks like
the prince crying behind Bortega?!
You're obviously trying to get
rid of a dog the prince took in!
Are you taking it...?
We aren't! We aren't taking it!
So you don't want Bortega...
Then take Moth-
I mean, Despigaro
Mother?!
You were about to say "Mother"!
You called Despigaro "Mother"!
Hey, you've got some nerve, old man.
You trying to ditch your mother
off on the party of heroes
because you don't want
to take care of her?
Unbelievable. He's worse
than those viruses.
We should eliminate him first.
Wait! Wait! Wait!
No! No!
That's wrong! You've got it all wrong!
Give me a break, big guy.
You know how people accidentally call
their teacher "Mother" sometimes?
That's what it was! For real!
You're not even acting
like a king anymore.
More like a common thug!
It's true that I've been fighting with my
wife about how to take care of Mother.
It's true there was an uproar because
Takeshi brought home a mutt.
But none of that has anything to do
with what we're discussing here!
Except it does.
It's obviously related!
You're obviously trying to dump
your problems off on us!
No! You're wrong!
These two, you see...
They may look like this now,
but that's because they were
cursed by the virus!
If you can find the Poof Mirror
that reveals the truth,
[Note: Parody of Rah Mirror
from Dragon Quest series.]
they'll return to their original
forms and serve you well!
Very well! Please give it a try!
What's this Poof Mirror crap?
Your head's gone poof!
No! I'm serious!
If you had the Poof Mirror!
I could show you!
We have it.
The Poof Mirror is right here.
What?
Where did you get that...?
We are inside my body.
Searching for an object is like
going through my pockets.
I've heard the Tapir are especially
skilled at mimicry.
You cannot defeat the Tapir if you
believe everything you see.
Now, let us see what truths
shall be revealed,
be it Bortega, Despigaro,
or something else...
Everybody look closely.
Th-This is...!
The King... The King...!
His nipples...are huge!
Nobody cares! I swear!
No! Wait a sec!
The King's nipples ARE getting bigger!
Yo** **o...
[Note: Word play on "Oh no."
Bleep covers "Yoko Ono."]
No, even bigger!
This is... This is...!
Not too shabby.
[Leukocyte]
[Tapir]
Not too shabby.
I never expected you to see
through this Tapir disguise!
This is...
Hey! Don't tell me this is a Tapir!
He's just wearing a black bodysuit
instead of a white one!
This isn't the time for that!
If they've already gotten the Leukocyte
King, that means...
Exactly.
You came to this kingdom seeking aid,
but are too late.
The Leukocyte Kingdom, from
the king down to the soldiers...
Even Mother...
Even Prince Takeshi...
The entire kingdom is in black bodysuits!
You have no allies here!
We will consume all!
Until all are dressed in black bodysuits,
we will continue to consume!
The toothpicks.
Everyone take hold of your toothpicks!
Those toothpicks were specially
made by Gengai-sama.
They take advantage of the Tapir's
nature to consume data
by sending large quantities
of data at high speeds!
Huh? What?
And the data is rotten enough
to cause food poisoning.
If you continue to send poison to their stomachs
after they've been poisoned once,
their stomachs will not have enough
time to digest the data
and they'll explode.
That sounds just fine!
These toothpicks can't remove leftover
food stuck in your teeth,
but they can kick stinking
virus butt, huh?!
Gin-san! There are too many!
We can't deal with all of them!
Hurry! This way!
We need to retreat for now!
Don't expect to escape!
You're all going to die here!
What are you...?!
This is...!
Poof Mirror, reveal the truth!
Return the sword to the hero who
protects me as no other can!
That's...!
The dog is...!
Turning into a person...
Y-You're...!
That is not a person.
That is...
The ultimate security program that
has destroyed many viruses
and kept the peace in my body.
The one and only true...
Leukocyte King!
Gi...
Gin-san?!
Find them!
Were they there?
Where'd they go?!
Damn! Where did they go?
Find them! Even if you have
to split nose hairs!
Looks like they're gone.
Lady Tama, they will find us here.
We should move at once.
I believe B-29 in the large
intestine would be safe.
That place is a maze.
Perfect for hiding out in.
Leukocyte King, we did not
come here to escape.
We came to fight.
Though you may only be a copy,
I cannot allow Lady Tama
near those filthy viruses.
I can handle the fighting alone.
Leukocyte King.
This time we are up against
the strongest virus ever.
The battle will not be as simple
as it has been in the past.
Even someone as accomplished as
yourself will have no chance alone.
We must work together and fight.
So you were the one who rewrote my
program and turned me into that dog.
You restricted my ability to act so I wouldn't
attempt to face them alone.
Is that correct?
Your death would be an inconvenience.
When the right time finally came...
Yes, I wished for you to survive
to fight alongside us.
What's your problem?
Keep that virus-infested face
away from Lady Tama.
You wanna get sterilized?
No, sorry.
I couldn't help but stare at
such a handsome face...
Not!
I don't recall ever having a Transform
spell cast on me.
You've got nerve to do that embarrassing
cosplay with my face!
You think you're Loto?!
[Note: Loto is the legendary hero from Dragon Quest 3.]
A lot of people in this world claim
that DQ3 was the best one,
but I won't accept that!
There are two Gin-chans.
Ta-Tama-san, what is that?
Why does that guy look like Gin-san?
All internal systems are affected
by my memory banks,
thought patterns, and various other data.
I would assume that image
was influenced by my mind.
Meaning...?
The security program Leukocyte, which
combats all sorts of viruses,
is a reflection of the strongest
person I know.
That would be the most
accurate conclusion.
Hey!
Two of the strongest have
been assembled.
There is nothing to fear now.
I see. So you're my...
Though the significant difference
in personality between us
suggests she doesn't think much
of what's in your head.
What was that?!
Though that's a given, considering
how much of a coward you are.
You won't be able to protect Lady Tama
with those virus-infested hands.
I shall be the one to defeat the Tapir.
There is no need for you to step in.
I am the only one who can
protect Lady Tama.
[To Be Continued]
[The next episode...]
My lord, Archfiend Tapir.
I just received word that Bifidus Castle
and E. coli Castle have been taken.
Is that so?
The areas of greatest resistance
now belong to our forces.
Very soon, the system of this world
will fall completely into Tapir hands.
The super science and technology poured
into this robot meant nothing.
Nothing can stop us now.
Excellency!
What is all the fuss about?
The third Tapir general was somehow
destroyed in the Leukocyte Kingdom.
What? That's impossible.
The Leukocyte Kingdom was
completely under our control
without a single Leukocyte left to resist.
Nobody left in this world
can stand against us.
According to our information,
there was an incredibly strong Leukocyte
dressed up like he was in Dragon Quest.
Along with three human-like creatures
carrying toothpicks
and a pixel robot to fill out the party.
D-Dragon Quest, you say?!
C-Could it be?!
He's... He's still alive?!
Deliver this order to all soldiers
in this robot!
Return to the Archfiend
Tapir's castle at once!
Abandon any conquered
castles if necessary!
Concentrate all forces at his castle immediately
and tighten the defenses!
Sir!
Is it him?
Yes...
He's coming...
The Leukocyte King,
with a party of heroes from the outside
world, is headed towards this castle!
["A Group of Fools are Led"]
[The five fools are led to and storm
the Archfiend Tapir's castle!]
[Will Gin-san and the Leukocyte King
work well with one another?]
[See you next time.]