[Teach us!! Ginpachi Sensei]
Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Teach us!
Ginpachi Sensei
Pen name "Catherine's cat ears are the worst-ever,
strongest-ever weapons" writes...
"What is "GinTama" trying to do?
I don't understand what they're doing.
I don't see any kind of goal in this anime."
Okay, here's your answer.
I don't know, either.
It's sad that after two-and-a-half years,
we're still getting postcards like this.
We shouldn't keep dragging
on and on. I mean really.
[Note: Parody of ONE PIECE.]
Maybe I should've said something like "I'm
going to become the Samurai King!"
So let's use that.
And so, "Catherine's cat ears are the
worst-ever, strongest-ever weapons,"
[Note: Gintoki is wearing Luffy's
costume from ONE PIECE.]
the goal of GinTama the anime is:
"to become the Samurai King!"
[Cattle abduction. In essence: the
kidnapping of livestock by aliens.]
[Oh, scary!! Aliens are so scary!!]
["Novices Only Need a Flathead and a Phillips"]
Look at the center of your screen.
Our camera is too far
away to see it clearly.
But you can see what
appears to be a cow
flying through the air as if it's
being sucked into the sky.
[Livestock farmer Zenshichi Toyobe (Age 72)]
I was working, when all of
a sudden, the sky lit up.
A glowing saucer came flying down,
sucked up my cow and flew off.
I hear Hikohachi over yonder
had all of his pigs taken, too.
Who could be doing such a thing?
The Bakufu suspects these to be
cases of theft by Amanto thieves
and is conducting an investigation.
Currently, the only damage has been
to livestock in farming villages,
but for anybody living in the city-we urge
you to lock your doors and be on the alert.
In other news...
How troubling. No telling where thieves
will strike from these days.
Cattle abduction in this
day and age isn't cool.
A long time ago, before anyone
knew Amanto existed,
human beings were abducted and their
bodies altered against their will.
Because of incidents like that, people
talked about being "spirited away."
The problem was the victims had their
memories of the experience erased
so they can't remember
what was done to them.
But there were a rare few who did remember
and that's why we have these stories today.
There's no telling what
those bastards did.
For all you know, you may have
already been abducted
and had some strange thing
embedded in your body.
After all, you seem like an easy target.
Stop joking. I'm not a kid, so
you're not going to scare me.
Gin-san, the TV's acting up again.
This thing is hopeless...really.
That didn't fix it.
Maybe its time has come.
Guess we'll have to open it up to fix it.
Gin-san, if you're going to fix it,
I have a screwdriver...right here.
Want to use it?
W-Wh-What is t-th-this?!
W-Wh-Why is my finger
a Phillips screwdriver?!
C'mon Shinpachi, I know
your character is weak,
but that's not the way to go.
If you're going to upgrade your character,
at least give yourself a Psycho Gun.
[Note: From the anime Cobra.]
That's so half-assed.
That's not what happened!
Who'd do something like this
to upgrade their character?!
You saying you don't remember
doing that?
Of course not! Who would choose
to do such a thing?!
You're saying you have no
idea how it got there?
Did you get abducted?
Could...it be...
That wasn't a dream?
Tonight, I'm having Pacific
saury for dinner.
[Note: Pacific saury (mackerel
pike) is a type of fish.]
Nothing beats saury in the fall.
Wh...What is that?
It's...
so bright!
How's this one?
No good again.
The size is too big.
It doesn't fit the screw.
Good grief, now I can't fix my PS(P).
[Note: Short for PSP game Monster Hunter Portable.
Sold as Monster Hunter Freedom in US.]
The analog controller broke while
I was playing Mon-Hun.
I'm positive it'd be an easy
fix if I took it apart.
I don't think an amateur
should disassemble it.
[Note: Parody of Sony.]
Let's send it to Zony for repair.
I don't want someone taking my money.
But I heard if you disassemble it yourself,
they won't accept it for repair.
What? Seriously?
What'd you do with the warranty...
that came with it when you bought it?
I probably...
threw it out with the box, uh-oh...
W-Wh-What are you?!
Wh-What is this place?
Uh-oh, he's awake. It's because
you talk too loud.
That was you, Senpai.
What...did you do to my finger?!
We don't know anything about that.
What do you mean you don't know?!
You...it's...a Phillips screwdriver now!
It was like that from the start.
Don't lie! You did this!
You modified my body!
We didn't. I didn't want to.
Then Senpai said he wanted
to take apart the PS(P).
PS(P)?!
I told you not to say anything!
Hey, what do you mean by PS(P)?! Is that
the reason why you...?!
No, that's not it at all. We didn't
have the right screwdriver, so...
That's totally it!
You could've bought something
like that at any hardware shop.
Why did you have to modify my body?!
No, you misunderstand.
We had no time to lose...
After all, I knew you'd
try to get ahead of me
in Mon-Hun while I couldn't play.
You'd defeat Paoshanron all by yourself
to get an awesome item
[Note: Paoshanron is a Parody of Lao
Shan Lung from Monster Hunter.]
and give me the "I'm better
than you" Senpai look.
I wouldn't do that.
I'd never be able to defeat
Paoshanron by myself.
You told me that last time.
Then you defeated Purin alone
and got a nice item.
[Note: Parody of Kirin from Monster Hunter.]
Seriously unbelievable.
Who cares?! What're you going
to do about my finger?!
Return it to normal! I'll sue you!
I'll definitely file charges!
What should we do, Senpai?
I'll give up on the PS(P).
There's supposed to
be a new model out.
The one that's Net-enabled.
Let's play that one.
You're supposed to be able to
transfer your PS(P) data to it.
What'll we do about him?
Throw him out onto the road.
So you're saying they abducted
you to modify your finger
into a screwdriver just so they
could repair their PS(P)?
Hey, look at me.
It's not funny! How am I supposed
to live with a finger like this?
I can't pick my nose or
hug the person I love!
You'll be fine.
You'll be able to tighten the screws
to the heart of the person you love.
That's just lousy smooth talk.
What do you mean "screws
to the heart"?
Forget it. You have ten fingers.
I'm sure it's more convenient that
one of them is a screwdriver.
I've got to pee.
Don't say irresponsible things because
it's someone else's problem!
'Morning.
Oh, Kagura-chan, look what
happened to my finger...
I had a weird dream and
didn't sleep very well.
Gin-san! It's Kagura-chan!
Kagura-chan's entire body's been
turned into a flathead screwdriver!
C'mon! Are you listening?! Gin-san?
Gin-san?!
...Gin-san?
Not you, too...!
G-Gin-san...n-not you, too?
Patsuan, it's not a crime to kill
aliens from outer space, right?
They did it to him! They messed
with Gin-san's analog stick!
[Net Cafe]
Unfortunately, the information we have
on them is extremely limited.
We don't know what planet those Amanto
are from, or where they are now.
All we know is that they're
obsessed with Mon-Hun.
Our only hope is to find a clue
and trace it back to them.
What is "Mon-Hun"? Is that short
for Mongolian hamster?
It's a very popular game throughout
the galaxy right now.
[Note: Parody of the game, Monster Hunter.]
Monkey Hunter, a.k.a. Mon-Hun.
It's a game where the player enjoys
being a hunter on a planet inhabited
by many types of monster monkeys.
They were playing the PS(P) version
and wanted to switch to
the latest online version.
That's fortunate for us.
The online version allows gamers
from all over the galaxy
to access a playing field
created on the Net.
No matter where those aliens are,
if we conduct our search inside the game,
we're bound to meet up with them.
So we'll have to search for
them inside the game
where gamers from across
the galaxy come together.
That'll be troublesome.
We don't have a choice.
We don't have any other clues,
so this is the only place we can be sure
those game-playing aliens will be.
Huh?
We don't have to go through
all that hassle.
It'd be faster if we hunted down
every single Amanto.
I'll give everyone of them
a slow and painful death.
Gin-san's losing it.
Do something, Kagura-chan.
Damn right, I'm losing it!
Shinpachi, you were lucky.
Of your ten analog sticks, only one
got turned into a screwdriver.
I, on the other hand, have only
one in the entire world,
an extremely rare analog stick...
No, joystick...and now it's useless! Eh?
Gin-san, you're too loud.
And what's worse, they changed
it into a kind of screwdriver
I've never seen before!
What is that? Huh?
It's probably a hex socket screwdriver.
Where am I supposed to use this?!
I have no idea!
They could've at least made
it a Phillips or a flathead!
Your stick never had any use, anyway.
It would've been better if it had
corroded and fallen off.
A flathead like you would
never understand
how a hex socket like me feels!
They won't get away with this...
I'll drag them out of cyberspace and
tear their analog sticks apart!
I swear...I swear I'll get my stick back.
Let's go, you guys!
Right!
It's crowded here, so I'll go that way,
and Kagura-chan, you go that way!
We'll meet at the designated place!
Roger!
And so began our battle
to restore our bodies.
The curtain is about to rise...
A spectacular battle for survival.
A hunter trusts only...
Himself.
Beat them down...
Or dazzle them with your technique.
[Note: Parody of a Monster Hunter
online TV commercial.]
Monkey Hunter online!
Risk your life to hunt them down!
[New Game
Load]
Welcome to the world of Monkey Hunter.
This is the adventure of your dreams where
hunters from all across the galaxy gather.
Please exercise proper Netiquette
to ensure this is an enjoyable
experience for all.
All right, please create your
avatar for this world.
I see. I have to start by creating
I wonder if Gin-san and
Kagura are doing okay.
I shouldn't use my real name.
My avatar needs...
Oh yes, glasses.
Okay, I'll go with this.
Sure looks like me. How common
is my appearance?
Wow, there sure are a lot of people.
They're all players of this
game. Awesome.
Those aliens are definitely
in here somewhere.
I'll find them and restore my body!
Gin-san and Kagura are late. I told
them to meet me at this spot.
Hi.
Someone approached me.
It's a girl.
Are you a beginner at this game?
I'm a beginner, too.
What do you say? Would you
like to go hunting with me?
Wow! She invited me. What'll I do?
What is this awkward feeling?
It's as if she's asking me out.
What should I do? I feel
kinda happy, though.
No...but Gin-san and
Kagura are here, too.
I can't go girl-hunting.
I don't have a choice.
I'm sorry. I'm expecting someone.
I see. Too bad...
Oh, by the way, I'm in a bind right now.
Would you mind giving me an item?
I wouldn't mind, but I just started the
game myself, so I don't have much.
That's all right. It's an item everyone has.
Give me your balls!
Gin-san?!
Are you still hung up over
your analog stick?!
Give them to me, I said!
Hey! He keeps punching
me in the crotch!
Stop it! Gin-san, we're
comrades! Come on!
This is a game where we
defeat the monkeys
and take their items to strengthen
our armaments!
What're you trying to take?!
Shut up, four-eyed monkey!
You're totally in a "take-your-anger-out-on-anyone" mood, dammit.
Pisses me off.
How long are you going to
feel sorry for yourself?
You lost your analog stick, so
now you're an online tranny?!
Are you stupid or something?
I didn't create this avatar because
I was down on myself.
Listen, we're not here to play around.
We're here to find those
rotten Amanto, right?
Isn't this form more suitable
for gathering information
than some shabby dude?
I see! Just what I'd expect
of you, Gin-san!
Gamers are gonna be kids who
are wet behind the ears,
desperate for girls, and stuck
in a room littered with tissues.
I figure if I went with a sexy
look, they'd be pushovers.
Now then, time to gather
some information.
How 'bout this?
Lets look for strong-looking veterans who've
been playing this game a long time.
Oh!
That guy over there looks good.
He looks really strong.
He's probably played over 100 hours.
Excuse me, can I ask you a question?
What is it?
It's you!
That you, Gin-chan?
Why does someone who just started playing
look like a veteran warrior?
What's that scar on your face?
Who gave you that?
Kagura-chan, where'd you
get those fine weapons?
I'm a hunter. I get what
I want from the hunt.
Hunt? But you just started.
How did you...?
Excuse me.
I'm sorry. We've already
formed our party.
We don't need any more members.
No, we're the administrators
of this game.
We received a report that
a hunter was attacked
and stripped of his clothes and equipment
in a back alley nearby.
Do you know anything about it?
Ugh!
Don't rob them!
Mmm... Looks Tasty!
[Note: Parody of Monster Hunter. "Mmm... Looks Tasty!"
voice is heard when player barbecues a well-done steak.]
Don't barbeque him!
What're you doing?!
This is a game where you hunt monkeys!
It's not a game where
hunters hunt hunters!
First-rate hunters aren't picky
about their targets.
You guys aren't hunters!
You're nothing but bandits!
Ack! Trouble!
The administrators are trying to oust
us because we broke the rules!
If they catch us, we'll never be able
to play this game again! Run!
A very interesting group
has joined the game.
What should we do?
[Patsuan - Hunter's knife wielder]
After what we did, we can't
return to the town.
[Ginko - Great sword wielder]
How're we going to gather information
about the alien gamers?
And we're out in a field where
[Kaguura Jasuanto - Dual sword wielder]
there's no telling when the
monkeys might attack.
Do you understand? Now that the
game administrators are after us,
if we lose and the game ends even once,
we'll never be able to access
this game again.
Shut up. I know that.
Kagura, your long sword has been
bumping against my knees.
It's getting in my way.
I'm not Kagura. I'm Kaguura Jasuanto.
[Note: Probably a wordplay on
Giant from André the Giant.]
What's a Kaguura Jasuanto?
Are you serious?
Sounds like a name a middle-schooler
would think of.
That's totally the failure pattern
of a novice sending in their entry
to a manga competition.
You know, the way they over-think
things to the point where
the readers can't remember
the name of the characters.
Shut up, Mr. No-balls!
What do you mean "Mr.
No-balls"?! Huh?!
I swear I'll restore my body
to the way it was!
Come on, both you-stop it.
Anyway, since we can't go back to town,
we have no choice but to
keep moving forward.
We'll keep hunting to the very end.
Hunt?
That's right. This is a game where the
players enjoy hunting the enemy.
If we go to a high-level area, we'll
find equally high-level hunters.
In other words, we'll be able
to meet all kinds of people
who've played this game
for tons of hours.
We're bound to find hunters who
know about the alien Gamers.
Hey, aren't you the one who said
we're done for if the game ends?
Then we should become allies
with the hunters we meet.
We'll get information, and kill
two birds with one stone.
And if all goes well, we might even
bump into the alien Gamers.
Yes! We should start by making allies.
Excuse me. We're novices at this game.
Won't you play with us?
Not that one! That's the enemy!
Run!
Hurry! Hurry!
Gin-san! What item do we
need to get past him?
This was amongst the things we
took from the security squad!
A tainted banana?!
[Note: Parody of Tainted Meat
from Monster Hunter.]
I get it-if we throw this at the
monkey and get him to eat it,
he'll be paralyzed.
Okay, here!
Eat this!
[Note: Now Loading background
is a parody of Monster Hunter.]
Why'd you eat it?!
It was a trap.
It's not a trap for you! It's a
trap meant for the beast!
Never mind me. Go quickly.
Become a good...hunter...
Kagura-chan!
Gin-san, at this rate, the game is
going to end for Kagura-chan.
Lure the enemy this way.
What's that...?!
A pit. We'll use these bananas
as bait and then pummel him.
Over here, you stupid monkey!
Come here! That's it!
Yeah, we're right here!
What are you doing here?!
How'd you get here when
you're paralyzed?!
What is this obsession you
have with bananas?!
At least in the game I get to eat my fill.
What a sorry thing to say.
You make me wanna cry!
I'm sorry...it's all my fault.
I'm so sorry.
Gin-san! The enemy!
Who's that...?
[Teach us!! Ginpachi Sensei Encore]
Teach us!
Ginpachi Sensei
This time, we have a question
from pen name
"I can't watch in real time in Shizuoka city, so
I buy the DVDs and watch them instead."
"Who is the person that brush paints
the titles for each episode?
I looked in the credits
but couldn't find him.
They're beautifully written!"
Okay, here's your answer.
They're painted by a producer
at Sunrise named Wakanabe.
He studied calligraphy
when he was younger,
but then drank too much liquor.
That's why he can't write
the titles in a straight line.
Just FYI, he says he wouldn't mind
getting a hug from Joe Odagiri.
[Note: Joe Odagiri is a popular young actor.]
[Correct: "There's a Thin Line Between
Strengths and Weaknesses"]
In the preview for episode 102, he
made a mischievous mistake.
[Incorrect: Good Points and Bad
Points Are Hard to See]
Okay, Wakanabe,
so you don't get bigheaded because
someone praised your calligraphy,
go and stand out in the hall!
[Preview]
Yo! Kaguura Jasuanto here.
Next time, the sad story behind
the scar on my face and
the cursed bloodline that became
the reason for this journey of
revenge will be revealed!
No, it won't!
The next episode... "Imagination
Is Nurtured In the 8th Grade."
[In order to find hunter allies, the group
travels through the world of Mon-Hun.]
[There, they find the legendary hunter, "M."]