Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[GinTama the anime is entering its final chapter!]
["Entering the Final Chapter!"]
[Odd Jobs Gin]
Well, it looks like the GinTama anime
is finally entering its final chapter.
I never expected this to happen
in the middle of the third year.
Lately, JUMP anime just drag on
and on, and when they end,
[Note: Refers to D. Grayman,
which ended like that.]
it's like "Our battle has only just begun."
D. [bleep]man was just like that.
Well, It's unfortunate that the
GinTama anime is ending,
but let's do our best until the very end!
All right!
So how long do we have?
Huh?
How many episodes is the final chapter?
When is the final episode?
Oh, well...
What? It hasn't been decided yet?
What? What's the big idea?
Well, how should I put this? Umm...
the final episode is...in about
half a year from now.
What?!
We're half a year from the final episode?!
How long is this final chapter?!
That's enough for about two seasons
of a late night anime!
[Note: Three months is the usual length
for one season of late night anime.]
Is it that the type of thing they've
been pulling in TV dramas lately-
that scam, where they keep saying
they're going to end?
When you look at the TV schedule, you
think it's going to be the final episode.
But when you watch it, it's
not the final episode at all.
It's the first half of the last chapter,
or the second part of the final chapter,
or the conclusion of the final chapter.
Is it that ploy where it keeps
dragging on and on?
Well, umm, that's right...
The third year of this anime
is getting kind of dull,
so I thought we should
get a little enthusiastic.
Aww... I don't feel like doing
anything anymore.
You said it was the final chapter,
so I was getting excited.
Hey, you two...
Let's end for today.
Yeah.
What? No way!
Anyway, GinTama is over for today.
See you next week, uh-huh.
[Preview]
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What
should I do?
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-Wh-What should
I write in a l-l-letter?!
What are you getting all flustered
about, Shinpachi?
Just leave this to me!
The next episode... "Some Things Can Only
Be Conveyed Through the Written Word."
Next is the King Kong twosome. Thanks.
[NOTE: King Kong is a Japanese
standup comedy team.]
H-Hey!
It's only been six and a half
minutes since we started!
Shut up. We've already done the
ending credits and the preview.
We can call it a day, can't we?
If we end here, it'll be dead air!
No, we've shown only this background since
we started. It's already like dead air.
Still...
Anyway, GinTama is over for today.
Everyone, we won't do anything
even if you keep watching!
Next is the King Kong twosome. Thanks.
No, no, no, no, no, no. This is bad.
Our superiors will be furious.
They're already mad at us
for a lot of other things.
The producer has already written
several apologies this year.
Mu-san was moved to a different
department, too.
[Note: Mu-san is now the producer
of an Ad agency.]
We can just write another apology.
We can't do that.
If I say it's over, it's over.
After this, watch [bleep]
until Konkon Hills starts.
[Note: Bleep covers Nintama Rantaro, a ninja anime for
little kids. Kinkon Hills is a Japanese variety show.]
Next is the King Kong twosome. Thanks.
I'm sorry! This is my fault!
Let's do this properly.
Okay? Okay? Okay?
Oh well. Let's fill up the time.
Phew...
Thank goodness.
But I don't feel like doing
anything anymore.
For times like this, we'll do that thing
with that thing like we always do.
Oh. If we do that thing with that
thing, they'll all do that thing.
I-I feel a sense of déjà vu...
Anyway, we're going to
a commercial break.
We'll be dragging on like this even
after the commercial break.
Anyway, we could have ended the episode
with thirty minutes of only that background,
but we were told we couldn't do that.
So we're going to make due
with a mish-mash recap.
All right, Shinpachi, you can start us off
by looking back on the GinTama anime.
Well, if you're talking about GinTama, there's
one episode that you've got to mention.
Back then, I...
The land of samurai. The
time when our country...
Hey! Why do you have to start
all the way back there?!
Well, this is the fateful episode
where we met.
Last year's recap episode
started from there!
We don't need that.
Let's go to my first appearance, next...
We already did that, too!
Reminisce about other things!
But when I try to look back on GinTama
and take a look at the list of titles...
["Nobody With Naturally Wavy
Hair Can Be That Bad"]
["You Only Gotta Wash Under Your
Armpits, Just the Armpits"]
It's difficult to remember anything
because a lot of the titles
["Watch Out for Conveyor Belts"]
make it impossible to tell what
the episode was about.
["You Know What Happens if You Pee on a Worm"]
["Do Cherries Come from Cherry Trees?"]
That's right.
["A Dog's Paws Smell Fragrant"]
The episode I first appeared in was
["The Manga Writer Becomes a Pro.
After Doing a Stock of Manuscripts"]
"Watch Out! Weekly Shonen Jump Sometimes
Comes Out on Saturdays!"
["Watch Out! Weekly Shonen Jump Sometimes
Comes Out on Saturdays!"]
What's that supposed to mean?
Oh, I think that's just being considerate.
Oh well. Then let's decide
on a theme and reminisce.
For example: Gin-san's
top ten touching lines,
or the top ten battles where
Gin-san looked cool.
Wait, why are they all
about you, Gin-san?
Then why don't we do the top
ten episodes that received
the most complaints from the viewers?
We can't do that!
Oh yeah. Why don't we say that we're going
to reveal all of the unaired scenes
and air them without the bleeps?
In that case, we should remove
the scrambled parts, too.
We'll be immediately cancelled!
Anyway, it's difficult to make
a recap about GinTama
because there isn't a continuous storyline and
the main character doesn't have a goal.
[Note: Parody of Dragon Ball and ONE PIECE.]
For example, searching for seven
balls that grant wishes,
or trying to become the pirate king...
We did that a month ago.
Oh...
Don't say "Oh." What are we going
to do? This is not even a recap.
If we don't cut it out, management
will be furious again.
Really?!
I'm serious. This time, they're going
to haul another person away.
What?!
This is an official police bust!!
What's your problem?
Prince of Planet Mayo Maniac,
why are you here, mayo?
We got word there was a suspicious secret
discussion going on here, mayo...
I didn't mean to say "mayo"! What
in the world were you doing?!
If you don't confess, I'll haul you in!
I won't tell you, mayo!
Anyway, who do you think you are, barging
into someone's house, mayo?!
Stop with the "mayo"!
So what were you all
talking about, mayo?
Well, the GinTama anime is finally
entering its final chapter,
so we thought we'd drum up some interest
by looking back on our past episodes.
Tsk. Is that all? A recap episode, huh?
Don't say, "Is that all?"
We need it to help keep GinTama going
for the remaining six months.
There are lots of things
we need to preserve.
If we don't reminisce on cool scenes
and beautify them in our memories,
we won't last six months.
Hmm... Cool scenes, huh?
["Make Friends You Can Call by Their Nicknames,
Even When You're an Old Fart"]
He's finally exposed himself...
Yamazaki.
Yes!
Track down their base, at all cost.
Sir!
With all the Amanto in the world now,
even the hero of the Amanto
war is just another criminal.
It takes real guts to still be fighting
the Amanto these days.
Hey, Okita, wake up.
I'm surprised that you could sleep
through that explosion.
Explosion? Did you let the
terrorists attack again?
What's your problem, Hijikata-san?
You need to apply yourself.
You wanna sleep permanently?
They can blow up all the
Amanto for all I care.
I'll let those fishies swim for a bit before I'll
reel 'em in, line 'em up and cut their necks.
It'll be a proud moment for the Shinsengumi.
I'm looking forward to this fight.
Hey, that was the episode
when you first appeared!
Ahem...
Then shall we look back
on Kondo-san next?
No, we don't really need to
look back on Kondo-san.
No one wants to see that.
Our ratings will drop.
No, no. Right now, I'm
a gorilla-like character,
but I was cool when I first appeared.
["There Is Butt a Fine Line Between
Persistence and Stubbornness"]
It's not gonna happen... Besides,
my butt hair is too thick.
There's no way a girl would
go out with me.
I'm no good.
That's not true. You're just very manly!
And that's attractive, isn't it?
Then let me ask you this...
If your boyfriend's...
rear end looked like an afro with
a part down the middle, what would you do?
I would love him, butt afro and all.
What a goddess!
She purifies unclean things
just like a Bodhisattva.
Butt-butt-butt-but will you marry me!
Huh?!
[Otae-san]
[Otae-san, go out with me for a hump.]
[Otae-san, marry me.]
Otae-san!! Marry me!!
I'm not the kind of man who takes
"No" for an answer twice!
My mom says women find more happiness
in being loved than in loving someone!
Otae-san!
Won't you just show your
angelic face at least?!
Otae-san!!
Right?! Right?!
Otae-san!
Kondo-san, you seem to be mistaken...
You've been nothing but a pathetic stalker-gorilla
since you first appeared!
In order to avenge Kondo-san...
Our Vice-Chief fought you once
again, mayo... Mayo...
["Fighting Should Be Done with Fists"]
What's the big idea?!
He may be a gorilla, but to us,
he's our beloved general!
He built the Shinsengumi up from
nothing with just one sword.
He's my brother-in-arms!
I won't let anyone shame our unit...and who
so ever crosses that line, my blade...
...shall taste
his blood!
Got him!
What?!
Parried! He got me.
Thus, Hijikata-san miserably lost, mayo.
Stop talking like that! It's annoying!
Gin-chan really does steal
the cool scenes.
But this isn't the only grudge between the
Shinsengumi and the Odd Jobs, mayo.
Huh? Did something happen?
Oh! That episode where Otae-san
and I were united!
There is no such episode.
There was an episode where the
Odd Jobs had a full-scale battle!
["Even if You Aren't Drunk, Pretend You
Are and Steal Your Boss's Toupee"]
Here you go, a bento box lunch.
Sorry for barging in on a family outing.
That's all right.
It wouldn't be any fun viewing the cherry
blossoms with just the two of us.
Right, Shin-chan?
When our father was still alive,
the three of us used to party like
crazy under the cherry trees.
Now, eat up.
Well then, I'll dig in.
What the heck is this-a sculpture?
I can only make omelets.
This isn't an omelet. This is a burnt egg.
No matter what state it's in, as long
as the egg is cooked, it's an omelet.
No, it's not. This isn't an omelet.
It's an innocent, abused egg.
You're a man, so shut up and just eat it!!
If I don't eat this, I'll die.
If I eat this, I'll die.
You don't need to convince
yourself to eat it!!
Don't eat it. Your eyes
will go bad like mine.
You guys really are pitiful.
C'mon, give it to me... I'll eat it.
Just scoop some into this
Tupperware container.
Why are you sitting here as if you're
a regular customer, you gorilla!
What rock did you crawl out from under?!
Whoa. Geez, is that stalker still after her?
Maybe you should talk
to the town magistrate.
No, apparently he's a police officer.
It's the end of the world...
Sorry about that...
Uh-oh. What do all you
ugly guys want with us?
Are you hunting for mushrooms?
Move out of our spot.
That's a special spot the Shinsengumi
uses for cherry blossom
viewing every year.
What kind of excuse is that?
Every spot is the same. What are
you, the 24-hour police thugs?!
It's not the same! The cherry blossoms
look extra special from there!
Isn't that right, guys?
Well, I don't really care so long
as I can get smashed.
I don't mind if we sit on
the asphalt or wherever.
Even sitting on asphalt, I can get in the
flower-watching mood if I have a drink.
Shut up!! I actually couldn't
care less either.
But I don't like the fact that we have
to move because of this jerk!
Anyway, we sent Yamazaki
to save our spot, didn't we?
Where did he go?
He's playing badminton.
Yamazaki!!
Well, anyway, that's the case.
We use this spot every
year, so just move.
We want everyone besides
Otae-san to leave.
No, Otae-san leaves with you.
No, Otae-san stays.
Who the hell do you schmucks think
you are, ordering us around?
If you want to do something about
us, then bring a bulldozer.
Bring a dozen cartons of Bäagen-Dash.
Bring some fried chicken.
You move pretty easily, don't you?
Oh that's rich...talking back to
the bakufu government, eh?
It looks like we'll be watching blood
swirl, instead of cherry blossoms.
It looks like we're destined
to do this every year.
I'm going to pay you back
for what you did last time!
Hold it!
We can't have you guys sword
fighting out in the open
with innocent civilians nearby.
Let's settle this in a Cherry
Blossom spirit.
The First Annual... Mallet and Helmet-style
rock paper scissors contest!!
That has nothing to do with
cherry blossom viewing!!
[Mallet and Helmet-style
Rock Paper Scissors]
[You need: a helmet, a toy hammer]
Let me explain. In Mallet and
Helmet rock paper scissors...
You play one round of
rock paper scissors...
The winner gets to hit the loser.
The loser is safe if he blocks
it with his helmet,
but the winner wins the
game if he gets a hit in.
Anyway, it's something like that.
It's a wild and aggressive game.
Go, Chief!
Die, Vice-Chief!
Who just told me to die?!
Seppuku for you, damn it!
Umm... This challenge
will be decided by...
three representatives from each side.
To be fair, Shinpachi-kun and I, Yamazaki,
will be the judges.
The winner wins the right to view cherry
blossoms from here and gets Otae-san.
What kind of rules are those?!
What are you, kidnappers?!
We don't gain anything
by winning or losing.
Then we'll give you a Shinsengumi sausage.
It was in the headquarters' refrigerator.
In other words, it's just an ordinary
sausage! We don't need that!!
A sausage, he says. Let's go for it.
All right.
Idiots!! You guys are total idiots!!
[Round One:
Chief Kondo vs Otae-san]
Let's begin the first round!
Chief Kondo versus Otae!
Sis, don't push yourself.
I'll take your place.
No, there's no honor in this
unless I do it myself.
That man keeps popping up no matter
how many times I crush him.
I'm sick of it...
I'm going to end to it right here and now.
This is bad. That look in her eyes...
Well then...
Get ready to play...
Rock, paper...
Scissors!!
Whew, I'm safe!!
You're not safe! Run away, Kondo-san!
Huh?
Spirits of heaven and hell,
give me strength!
Huh? Huh?
Use me as an instrument
of divine judgment!!
Hey, Otae-san, I already
have the helmet on...
That's not in...the rules.
[That's not in...the rules]
Chief!
What the hell did you
do, you evil wench?!
Oh... So you want to fight, too?
We're very sorry.
Shinpachi-kun, you have
it rough, don't you?
I'm used to it.
Umm... The Chief is unable to continue,
so the first round is a draw.
For the second round,
both contestants please try to
at least follow the rules...
Whoa!
They've already started!
They're fast!! They're super fast!!
They're so fast it looks like they both
have a hammer and a helmet.
Oh? She's evenly matched
against Sogo?
Who is that girl?
Sogo's got no brains,
but he's got the strongest sword
arm in the Shinsengumi.
Evenly matched?
You think a human can
stand up to Kagura?
She's a member of the nearly
extinct race of warriors,
the Yato clan. She's amazing.
What? Well, our Sogo...
Well, our Kagura...
Hey, knock it off!
You sound ridiculous-like little kids
bragging "my daddy is a pilot"!!
Never mind that. Did you guys
start drinking already?!
Huh? Our round started already.
Okay, next up tequila.
Bring it on.
Man, they're in their own world
with that drinking contest.
Wow. The battle on this side
has become ever fiercer.
Huh? Wait a minute...
Both of them are clearly
wearing a helmet.
And they don't have hammers.
They're not even playing
rock paper scissors.
They're just beating the
crap out of each other!!
I told you to follow the rules!!
This is so out of control.
Oh well. We have to decide
this with the final showdown.
Gin-sa...
Hey! What are you doing?
You two can't fight like this!
Don't worry. I can still do
this. Let's settle this...
Bring it on, damn it!
It would be boring to settle
things normally.
Why don't we play some
"Cut and Parry-style
rock-paper scissors" using real swords?
Bring it on, damn it!
"Bring it on" is all you've been saying.
I feel weird asking you this,
but are you all right?
Bring it on, damn it!!
Yamazaki, give him a sword!!
Huh?
Sure! Sure!
You shouldn't have given him a sword.
Huh?! But...
Let's do this!
Bring it on, damn it!
Ready?
Cut and parry-style rock paper...
Scissors!!
I win!!
Don't worry. I used the back of my sword.
Well, I hope you've learned your
lesson-don't mess with me.
Hey you! You throw "rock" every time!
Are you trying to make a fool of me?!
What's wrong? You aren't
saying anything.
Are you trying to make
a fool of me, huh?!
We both have pretty strange bosses.
Yeah...
Father, cherry blossoms are really best
when viewed with a large group.
This is the most fun I've had
viewing cherry blossoms
since you passed away.
Come on, Shin-chan...
Oh, that's umm...
Huh? Where am I?
And so, we managed to fill
up thirty minutes of time.
Well, it really was just a recap episode.
Will the producer have to
write another apology?
[Note: Bleep covers Code Geass.]
It's all right. This happens
a lot with [bleep] as well.
It's Sunrise's usual problematic pattern.
Well, anyway, we'll finally be entering
the final chapter next week!
We still have half a year, so let's not
exert ourselves and drag it on.
We might extend into our fourth year!
That won't happen.
Oh, we forgot the cast credits.
[So anyway, we'd like to drag
on until the final episode.]
[Also, we won't be doing these crappy
recaps or whatever anymore.]