Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[Slightly Feverish Continent]
[Note: Parody of Passionate Continent,
a Japanese documentary program.]
[Singer: Tsu Terakado]
[Slightly Feverish Continent]
The singer Tsu Terakado.
When she was an amateur, she played
live performances on the streets.
She made her pro debut when she
caught the eye of a talent scout.
Soon after, she was wrapped up in a
scandal and her popularity declined.
For a while, there were rumors
she was going to retire.
But she made a miraculous comeback
under the production of Tsunpo,
[Note: Tsunpo is a parody of Tsunku, a Japanese
record producer, songwriter, and vocalist.]
a mysterious hit-maker who never
revels himself to the media.
She is truly a first-rate pop
idol in name and in reality.
We covered her closely as she
composed her new song.
[Shibuya Regretful Hall]
[Note: Parody of Shibuya Public Hall.]
[June 12]
[Thank you in advance,
attack of the hornet.]
Our coverage of her began on the
last day of her national tour.
I like it... I like drinking...
I like it... I like drinking with you...
Liquor, liquor, liquor, liquor...
No drinking today.
Liquor, liquor, liquor, liquor, liquor...
Drunk with you and P-chan...
Everyone, thank you for
coming, corn poop!!
Corn poop!!
Today, I have a very important
announcement, Mas Oyama!!
[Note: Mas Oyama is a famous karate master.]
Mas Oyama!!
The truth is...
[Note: Tamba (old province of Japan) is famous
for producing high quality black beans.]
The release date for my new single
has been set, Tamba black beans!!
[Q: What do you think about the announcement
of her new single?]
Well, this is the first time I've been excited
since her last single came out.
I'm definitely going to buy it.
I think it's important to know
whether it's edible or not.
Well, I might be a bit hesitant
to buy it if they end up
releasing several different versions
of the single like they do
[Note: Japanese pop idols often release several
versions of a single to boost sales.]
with other pop stars' albums.
[Q: Who are you?]
I'm Tsu Terakado Fan Club Captain
Shinpachi Shimura!!
Sergeant, recite Article 7 of
the Fan Club Regulations!!
[Q: What is Article 7 of the Fan Club Regulations?]
Owowowow. "Members are to buy
four of each of Otsu's CDs:
one for storing, one for looking
at, one for propagating,
and one for actual use."
That's right!!
Sergeant, even though you
are one of our leaders,
your comments go against this rule!!
[Q: What do you mean by "actual use"?]
Therefore you will be punished with the
Nose Hook Destroyer
Second Illumination!!
The night the album was announced,
excitement continued to rage on.
News of it immediately spread
throughout Edo.
[Tsu Terakado's new single!! On sale soon!]
[Tsu Terakado's new single,
the long awaited debut!]
[One day in June]
[AnipleX (Note: Parody of Aniplex)]
But on a certain day in June, the situation
took a turn for the worse.
[Q: What sort of business do you have here today?]
Well, I'm not sure. I was suddenly
called in for an important talk.
Good morning, Otsu-chan.
Good morning.
Well, I think they probably
just want to tell me
the demo for the new song came in.
Huh?
We're going to postpone sales.
Hey! Why?! Why is this happening?!
We don't have a song written.
It can't be helped.
[Ichi Terakado (Otsu's mother and manager)]
Tsunpo-san made the decision himself...
That's right!!
[Toba-san (Employee from
AnipleX in charge of Otsu)]
Yesterday, we suddenly got
a call from Tsunpo-san...
He said...
"I was playing my shamisen,
when a man with naturally
wavy hair hit my helicopter
with a wooden sword and
it crashed into the ground.
"I sprained my finger. I'll get serious
next year, so wait for a while"...
So he says...
That's the stupidest reason ever!!
We can't postpone the sale of my important new
song because of a crazy reason like that.
Anyway...
"I was playing my shamisen,
when a man with naturally
wavy hair hit my helicopter
with a wooden sword and it
crashed into the ground"?
That could never happen!!
This isn't an anime!!
This isn't... an anime...
I just thought of a nice song.
Otsu-chan, that's probably plagiarism!!
[Note: "This Isn't An Anime" (Anime Ja Nai)
is the opening theme song to Gundam ZZ.]
Otsu already made a
public announcement
about the release of her new song...
To postpone it because of some nonsense
about playing a shamisen
and his helicopter crashing
into the ground...
There's no way he'd only have
suffered a sprained finger.
Is that all you care about, Mom?!
There was a good deal of conflict
at the last-minute meeting about
postponing Otsu's new single.
We asked everyone for their thoughts
about Tsunpo, the producer...
and the cause of this problem.
[Q: What kind of person is Tsunpo?]
Huh? Tsunpo-san?
He's an amazing guy.
His bold, yet delicate, skills keep
others from getting near him and
puts him in a strong positing
to keep climbing to fame.
He sells and still causes
a stir on the scene.
He's a true samurai.
[Q: Tell us about Tsunpo-san.]
Well, ever since he's been producing
her, Otsu's been a gold-record artist.
But I can't accept this. I never expected
he'd sprain his finger.
[Q: That really bothers you, doesn't it?]
[Q: What do you think about Tsunpo-san?]
I think it's important to know
whether he's edible or not.
But Toba-san, I don't want
to postpone this!
You can bring in a different producer!
I can make my own song for
the first time in a while!!
Well, I understand your feelings about
your first new song, Otsu-chan.
But I don't have anyone who
can take Tsunpo's place...
And your own songs never
really sold, anyway...
Shut your face...
Shut up and bring me
Akimoto or Mackey...
[Note: Yasushi Akimoto and Mackey (Noriyuki Makihara)
are Japanese songwriters and producers.]
Anyway, do you even want to do this?
Realistically speaking, when
am I going to get an album,
or a karaoke release? I've been
waiting all this time...
Huh?!
O-Otsu-chan, what's wrong?
Oh my. I lost my temper,
tanuki balls.
Well, excuse me.
I don't remember raising
her to be like that.
I-I'm all right, Mrs. Terakado.
Is that so?
[Q: Are you going to wait for Tsunpo-san?]
Our staff asked Otsu what she thought
about postponing the release
of her new song.
I'll manage by myself!!
I'm still somewhat of a musician.
I wrote my own songs before Tsunpo-san
became my songwriter,
I should be able to make an amazing
song that's as good as his.
Then...
[Three Hours Later]
I can't write anything!!
Why? Is it because I
made some money?
Or is it because I don't
have a clear goal?
Is it because I lack concentration?
Is it because I'm hungry?
Is it because I can't remember
what I ate yesterday?
Is it because I haven't been in an episode in a while and
I can't remember the last time I was in one?
Or is it because...my talent's dried up?
No! No!
This isn't a matter of talent!!
Masterpieces are difficult to create!!
In that case...
[Q: Why are you suddenly going on a trip?]
I was spoiled by my situation.
I have to go to a place where no one
knows who I am, reexamine myself,
and get back the feelings I lost.
Nakata went on a trip to find himself.
[Note: Hide Nakata is a Japanese soccer player.]
I must do that, too...
Ah... This is heaven...
[Q: Is your song done yet?]
No! I can't be doing this!
You can't!
But...
Long time no see, Dynamite Otsu...
Yes, same here, The
Demoness Haruna...
[Wild Pro Wrestling]
How many years has it been
since out last fight?
If I close my eyes, I remember
my memories with you...
[The Tsu Terakado Story - The Musical]
[Note: Japanese pop stars often make
their success story into a musical.]
[Big Success Story]
[A touching and randomly cast...]
When Otsu returned to Earth, she was...
...unable to make the time to write a new
song because of her busy schedule.
Friendship! Dynamite!
Friendship! The Demoness Haruna!
[Note: Friendship in Japanese is "友情." (yuujou)]
It's friendship! The two letters
that spell friendship...
Duwa!!
[Q: Can you complete your song?]
[Slightly Feverish Continent]
Please come in.
Today, I'm opening Tsu Terakado Productions'
new Japanese restaurant.
Everyone, please come in.
Her new song was to be
released the next day…
Please come and eat here!
Right now, we have foie
gras at 30,000 yen!
But Otsu's busy days continued.
[Q: It doesn't look like people are
impressed with the restaurant…]
Well, of course. I don't
feel like eating there.
[Simple Dishes
Fukinoto Corn Poop]
Not at a place with a name like that…
[Q: What do you think?]
I think it's important to know
whether it's edible or not.
Everyone, please come in.
Putting aside this campaign for a restaurant
that closed after a month,
Please come and eat here!
the deadline for the release
of her new song is…
Please come in.
Getting closer and closer.
Yeah! I'm gonna win!
Wait!!
I can't make it… I really am no good.
I can't do anything by myself.
I'm a manufactured pop idol.
I couldn't even write a song by myself.
In the end, all my struggles were in vain.
Yes. Tomorrow, I'm going to apologize
in front of everyone.
I thought that was the case.
M-Mom!
It's not just me.
E-Everyone… Why?
I know you.
You got stubborn and tried to handle
everything by yourself, didn't you?
Mom…
Your mom asked me to bring
over everyone you knew.
Toba-san!
I'll bet no one expected
me to show up again.
The Demoness Haruna!
I caused you a lot of trouble when
you were Chief for the day.
I'm going to repay you, tax thief.
Kondo-san!!
I was forced to come, but I want to
see an Elephas namadicas's poop.
[Note: Elephas namadicus is
a small prehistoric elephant.]
Hijikata-san!
Now I’ve done it…
I've done it again…
Makoto-chan!
And Corpse-chan!!
Huh? Come to think of it,
where's the Captain?
You're right. He's not here.
It's not a bad thing to be stubborn
and stick it out on your own.
But you're not alone.
Otsu, everyone's gathered
here for your sake.
In order to help you…
Yes. Tsu Terakado is supported
by all these people.
Have confidence. Everyone supports you.
There's still time until the release!
We'll help you!!
It's not like you to give up, Otsu-chan!!
Since you've come this
far, you've got to do it.
Everyone… Thank you. I'll give it a try…
I'll do it!!
I will!
I'll write an excellent song!!
Well said, Otsu. Let's go and
compose that song.
We've managed to secure
a meeting room.
Then let's get over there right away!
Yeah!
[Later, that night]
["Otsu is composing a song.
Keep out" - Mother]
I did it!!
Everyone, sorry to keep
you waiting for hours.
Thanks to you, I'm almost
finished with my song.
Actually, there's still one problem left…
The lyrics don’t feel right.
It kind of doesn't have much punch.
That's not true! These are good lyrics!
I'm not afraid. That's
because you're here.
I've made up my mind. So
I'm not turning back.
To hell with those who act
as if they're important.
It's risky if you get too used
to really nasty jokes.
Now free yourself from control.
Go anywhere. Fly to an
unseen new world.
Who cares about broadcast regulations?
You don't need brakes.
My heart is always dressed in white.
[Note: White traditionally worn at funerals.]
Hmm…
Oh! I thought of something great.
This doesn't…
…have any punch to it.
So if you do this to it…
Gin-chan, I also thought
of something cruel!
Hey! How could the two of you
do that to Otsu-chan's lyrics?!
Make that part cute like this!!
Oh! I also thought of something!
Hey, that's not fair, Toshi! In that
case, I also thought of something!
I also have an idea!!
Do you think it would sell
better if we did this?
No, if we do this…
Amazing…
Everyone's pouring their
ideas into my song.
This is amazing. Yes, this
is the energy I wanted!
This is good…
This is definitely good!!
[September 18
(New song announcement concert,
Tamba black beans.)]
[Shibuya Kokaido]
Everyone, thank you for coming
today, corn poop!!
Corn poop!!
A lot happened, but I finally
completed my new song…
Please listen to it!!
This is my new single!!
"Who Cares About Broadcasting Regulations"!
The thing I'm afraid of is…
[Bush].
[Note: Most of the [*bleep*] words are not allowed
to be broadcasted on TV in Japan.]
That's because he's [insane].
The [methamphetamine] is working.
So I won't be able to [sleep]
for three [days].
[Day laborers] with bad [backs]…
Those people, [f**k you]!!
I'm making jokes out of [madness]. I'm
beginning to [see] [hallucinations].
Come on!!
[Trample] on the [eyes of the law].
[Go] anywhere. Fly to a [crazy] world…
Who cares about broadcasting
regulations!
A thirty-minute discussion
on [going commando]!!
Who cares about broadcasting
regulations!
I don't [care] if I become [limp].
[I don't] care about [broadcasting
regulations].
Am I not allowed to say [which planet]?
I don't [care about broadcasting
regulations].
They're probably not going to air it.
[Censored]
If I die, I'm taking you all with
me, got that necromancer?!
[Tsu Terakado's New Single]
["Who Cares About Broadcasting Regulations"]
[Sale Discontinued]
[Slightly Feverish Continent]
On the next Slightly Feverish Continent,
we're featuring a charismatic,
homeless, Musashi-like man.
His unrestrained and eccentric lifestyle
gains the sympathy of today's youth.
We will be uncovering the secret to his
marvelous cardboard collecting skills.
[Slightly Feverish Continent]
On the next, next Slightly Feverish Continent,
we're featuring Prince Hata of Midland Star.
His philanthropic spirit, which
he only shows to animals,
gains the sympathy of today's…
[Slightly Feverish Continent]
On the next Slightly Feverish Continent
after that, we're featuring Viper.
The lifestyle he leads after being downsized
gains the sympathy of…
I'm not afraid.
That's because you're here.
I've made up my mind.
So I'm not turning back.
To hell with those who act
as if they're important.
It's risky if you get too used
to really nasty jokes.
Now free yourself from control.
Go anywhere.
Fly to an unseen new world.
Who cares about broadcast regulations?
You don't need brakes.
My heart is always dressed in white.
If I die, I'm taking you all with
me, got that necromancer?!
[Third Year, Group Z Ginpachi-sensei]
Third Year, Group Z…
Ginpachi-sensei!
If this doesn't go in, I'll die.
No, if this goes in, I'll be revived.
If this goes in, I'll get another
chance to revive myself.
No, that was a joke. This is for real.
Actually, this one is the real one.
That was just for practice.
If this one goes in, all those
other ones are nullified.
No, this is my last chance. If
I miss this one, I'll go to hell.
How silly…
[Third Year, Group Z Ginpachi-sensei]
Third Year, Group Z…
Ginpachi-sensei!
Alien 1 and 2 were great,
but 3 was horrible.
[Note: Schwa-chan is Japanese nickname
for Arnold Schwarzenegger.]
Also, Terminator 2 was also good. I cried
when Schwa-chan was sinking.
I don't remember 3, though.
Anyway, we've reached the middle of
the third year of the GinTama anime.
Sensei, don't start us off
by making us look bad.
Anyway, this world is structured in
a way that the 3rd one always fails.
“You can only get carried away until 2.”
This is going to appear
on the test. Take notes.
Sensei, Home Alone 2 was horrible!
How do you explain that?!
Macaulay Culkin-kun got carried
away in 2 as if it were 3.
He acted like “I'm Macaulay. So what?”
“What do you think? My face
is sickening, isn't it?”
When child actors get carried away, sometimes
number 2 gets turned into a 3.
This will be on the test. Don't be tricked.
Wait!! Then what about Dragon Quest 3?
I thought 3 was a masterpiece.
In 3, Ortega was like, “I fell
into a volcano. So what?”
“What do you think? I showed up, didn't
I?” It's been upgraded to 4. It's not 3.
Sensei, Ortega isn't a child
actor. He's an old man.
From Zoman’s point of view, Baramos
and Ortega are child actors.
[Note: Ortega, Zoman, Baranis are
all characters from Dragon Quest.]
Hijikata, why don't you advance a year
and become a fourth year student?
Okay!!
I'm going home to watch
Karate Kid, Part III.
[The End]
[Preview]
This is terrible! In this episode, we'll be
entering the final chapter of GinTama!
What?!
GinTama is ending?!
But didn't we just say we were
in the middle of the third year?
Anyway, it means you should keep
watching from now until the end!!
[GinTama, the Anime]
[Entering… Its final chapter!]