Edited at https://subtitletools.com
This school was in the same
district as Gintama High,
but it tended to attract students with a notorious
reputations during middle school,
and the rundown building was dubbed
a concentration camp by some.
The Metropolitan Yato
Industrial High School.
This is the story of one man who arrived
in this school full of savages...
I'll kill ya.
Bebop.
Kamui-kun!
[Kamui - Episode 1]
Starting today we have a new student,
Kamui, joining our class.
Be nice, everyone.
I'm Kamui, from Harusame High.
I only have interest in
those who are strong.
I'll take over this class before
the day's over, so cheers.
What's that?!
You dissin' us?!
I'll show you how fearsome
Yato High can be!
If you get in my way again, I'll kill ya.
Hey! What do you think you're
doing on your first day here?!
You bastard! You don't get
to push my buddy around!
Be nice, or I'll kill ya.
Bastard's got cheek.
Abuto, do something!
You read that as "Kamui"?
[After School]
Hey.
I said hey.
Can't you hear me?
Are the things protruding from your
head supposed to be doorknobs?
Eh?
How about a contest?
Huh?
7x1=7, 7x2=14, 7x3=21.
Wait, that's...
7x4=28, 7x5=35, now 7x6 equals?
The sevens, the hardest
part of the times table...
Uh, six sevens would be 45...
No, that's not it...
In this case, it'd either be 38 or 48...
Ungyo!
Lend me your fingers!
I think I'll transfer...
[The End]
Teach, I don't get why we have to study.
Is this going to help us
out in the real world?
I was spewing a typical adolescent question after
failing this important juncture in life eight times.
Yes, I was the only one held back at the metropolitan
Yato Industrial High School eight times.
I no longer show up for New Year's gatherings 'cause
I can't stand all the stares from the relatives.
Never show up!
That was when one particular
man arrived before me.
I'll kill ya.
Bebop.
Kamui-kun!
[Episode 2]
Hey, look at that.
It's the three stupid crows from Yato
High that've been getting cocky.
The new kid who took control of the
third-years on his first day, Kamui.
The member of the old guard who's
flunked eight times, Abuto.
The fatty's who's seventeen,
believe it or not...
What's his name again?
Beats me...
I think I'll transfer...
[The End]
Say, did you know?
That scene from the current
ending sequence.
It has me set up as the only one
who flunks and doesn't graduate.
How mean is that?
That was when one particular
man arrived before me.
I'll kill ya.
Bebop.
Kamui-kun!
[Episode 3]
Bah, those bastards from
Yoshiwara Trade School...
Well, just sit back and let your leg heal.
Don't worry about anything else.
Hey! Nincompoop!
Don't tell me you're going to go
off to get payback by yourself...
I won't allow you to do that.
This is my problem.
Got nothing to do with you!
I'll be back.
Hey, wait!
Don't give me that shit!
Hold up!
Bah, damn idiot.
Mommy, peel a pear for me.
I think I'll make him transfer...
[The End]
[The showdown at Hotel Ikezuya: The Kagekiha
Anti-Foreigner Ronin Faction versus the Shinsengumi.]
[The fate of Edo rests on what
Hijikata saw happen to Kondo...]
The enemy is hiding in Hotel Ikezuya.
They plan on executing an armed
takeover of the terminal tomorrow.
They're meeting up at Ikezuya
to discuss their plans.
I would assume that they're building morale for
the upcoming battle with a feast of some sort.
This is our only chance to stop their
plan and to bring them all in.
It's a showdown...
Squad 1 will join me in attacking
from the front.
Squads 2 and 3 will follow their captains
and attack from the back.
Don't let a single rat escape.
Got it?
The fate of Edo rests on our blades.
Every battle we fight may be our last.
Our backs are against the wall.
Never look back.
Focus only on the enemy.
Open a path to the future
with your swords.
Let's go!
Excuse me...we're booked for the day...
We're here on official business.
We'll need to have a look inside.
Huh? Uh...
Toshi, I'm trusting you to watch my back.
Yeah, I got you.
["Whenever I Hear Leviathan,
I Think of Sazae-san. Stupid Me!!"]
Oh...
He's got snot coming out...
Nah, it can't be.
He wouldn't have snot coming out now...
Nope, that's definitely snot.
It's clearly snot.
Should I tell him?
But...
I don't want to do anything that would
affect our morale right now...
But still...
If I leave it alone and the men notice,
that'll also affect the squad's morale...
Let's go!
Yeah!
Huh? Snot?
No way! Seriously?!
Crap... I had better tell him...
What's wrong, Toshi?
Why the funny face?
Kondo-san... Well...
Even you feel nervous
before battles, eh?
But there's no need to be ashamed.
It's far more shameful to grow
accustomed to killing.
We have no choice but to
swing out swords in agony,
hoping that we will be able
to bring peace one day.
Humans are the only ones who
can set other humans straight.
Don't let yourself become a monster,
no matter how much blood you shed.
Th-Thanks...
That helped me snap out of it.
Kondo-san...
That was a nice speech, but your
snot is going Tarzan on you.
Report!
Squad 2 has reached the 12th floor!
Squad 3 is on the move!
Very well. Squad 1 will head out
once squad 3 is in position.
Yes, sir!
No...I can't tell him...
I'd rather die than tell someone who's being
serious that he's got snot going Tarzan.
Tarzan would fall into the ravine...
Can't do it...
I have to prevent that from happening...
I'll have to make him aware of the snot in
passing instead of pointing it out directly...
What options do I have...?
Hey! You lot!
Yes, sir!
We'll have a piss break
before we charge in.
Listen up.
You won't have time once
the battle starts.
Take care of your business now.
If you don't piss now, you'll have
to hold it in for at least an hour.
Hijikata-san, we didn't come
here on a picnic.
Shut up!
You're the type of kid who make them stop the bus to
piss in the bush, crying, while all the traffic goes by!
Hijikata-san, we're not on a bus.
Shut up!
I told you to piss, so piss, damn it!
Man, this is such a pain.
There goes all the tension.
I already squeezed out every
last drop before coming here.
Kondo-san, why don't you join them?
Nah, I already took a piss.
You should go wash your face.
It'll help you focus.
Really?
I'll be gone for a bit then.
Stay on your guard.
Yeah, don't worry.
Okay, it's all good now.
Once he looks in the mirror,
he'll notice Tarzan yelling.
I can only pray that Tarzan will return
to the forest before anyone notices.
Okay, I'm focused now.
Let's get going!
Yeah!
T-Tarzan's come out to New York!
Why?!
What's going on?!
He washed his face, yet his snot's
gone from Tarzan to Leviathan?!
[Note: Referring to the Leviathan from the
"Final Fantasy" video game series.]
Hey, check out the commander...
Isn't there something on
his nose? What is that?
Isn't it Leviathan?
This is bad... They're starting
to notice Leviathan...
Fall off!
Leviathan, that isn't where you belong!
Back you go to the Feymarch!
[Note: From Final Fantasy IV for the Nintendo DS.]
There it goes!
It's definitely gone now!
What? Did I catch a cold?
N-Now Bahamut's been summoned!
Crap!
I didn't expect Bahamut to be
renting the room next door!
Squad 1 has reached their floor!
Very well. Squad 1 will also move out.
Yeah!
I-It's impossible to hide now...
Bahamut and Leviathan...
They won't stop until
everything's destroyed...
What do I do?
So-Sogo!
What is it?
Take squad 1 and use the
emergency stairwell.
I'll join the double dragons, I mean...
Kondo-san in attacking from the front.
Will the two of you be
okay by yourselves?
The goal is to confuse the enemy.
You don't need to worry.
I'm willing to die to protect Kondo-san.
Toshi?
Let me handle this.
I managed to get rid of the men,
but the problem now is how to proceed.
If we charge in, the enemy will
see these double dragons.
Huh?
Hey, this guy's dripping snot!
You should take care of your nose
before taking care of patriots!
Stop!
Don't look!
I have to do something before
the situation gets ugly...
Eliminate the double dragons without messing
with Kondo-san's serious manner.
Toshi, check that out.
The enemy has people on patrol.
If we're spotted, the enemy will
be alerted to our presence,
and our ambush will fail.
Yeah, you're right...
There's no time to get hung
up about cleanliness.
I'll just use my hand.
There's no other way to bring
down those giants.
Bahamut and Leviathan...
Which to go for first...
Given the way he's turned,
Leviathan will be difficult...
Guess I'll start with Bahamut.
Okay!
Bahamut just?!
What?!
Did it sense the impeding danger?!
Leviathan's doubled in size instead!
What's going on?!
Come on! Don't tell me Bahamut and
Leviathan are connected in the back?
They're a couple?
That makes this easy then.
Grab one and they're both goners!
That's it!
[Note: Odin's trademark attack from FF series.]
I'll go for Zantetsuken!
My eyes! My eyes!
Hey, Toshi!
You okay?!
Sn-Snot came flying out!
Snot came flying at me like a Flare spell!
What's going on?!
Hey! What're you doing?!
Whoa! What's with that sno...
Whoa!
Nice one, Toshi!
That was instant!
Th-That was close...
He was about to find out.
Hey, wasn't that guy saying
something about sno...
He wasn't!
No, pretty sure I heard sno...
He must have been talking
about snowbells, yeah.
He realized he was about to die, so he wanted
to request snowbells at his grave.
Snowbells...
Damn, that's loud!
What's all the noise about...
What the hell is that s-...
Socrates!
I-It's the Shinsengumi!
Onward!
Wh-What's with this guy?!
He's got all that sn-...
Soul Society!
Hey! That's s-...
Son Goku!
Whoa! S-...
'Nothing to worry about!
The hell's up with this guy?!
He's a monster!
Run!
You won't get away!
Zaki!
Crap!
Huh?
Commander, what's with that s-...
Yamazaki!
You okay?!
Who did this to you?!
A vase suddenly...
Zaki...
Damn them!
They won't get away with this!
Wait!
Hold on!
Here.
Your face is covered with the blood
that's been splashing around.
Use this to wipe it off.
Your face is the one that's
covered with blood.
I said to wipe it off, damn it!
You won't be able to fight
if it gets into your eye!
Yeah, sorry...
It's true that you're as good as dead if
you lose your eyes on the battlefield.
Right, you're done now.
It's over for you this time, damn snot.
H-Hey!
What is that?!
Why is his snot wiping his face?!
Why is the dirtiest part of his face
trying to wipe his face clean?!
Okay, I'm ready to go.
Let's do this, Toshi!
You aren't ready!
You're a complete mess!
Damn villains, it's on!
He has total control of his snot...
No, I would say that the
snot is controlling him...
What the hell?
What is that thing?
Stop it.
Stop abusing Kondo-san...
Get the hell out!
Look out!
Toshi!
Kondo-san!
The snot is gone...?
I'm sorry.
For deceiving you this whole time...
Toshi...
N-No way...
You're kidding me, the snot... You...
I am the true identity of Isao Kondo.
Snot Nebula 28...
[Note: Spoof of the Japanese hero Ultraman
and his home Nebula M78.]
That is my home galaxy.
I came to investigate Earth,
so I commandeered the body of a gorilla,
and altered my appearance to allow
me to live amongst humans.
That would be me, Isao Kondo.
Once my investigation was done, I was supposed
to be blown into a tissue and thrown away.
But before I knew it, five years,
ten years had passed...
The next thing I knew, I was
a middle-aged man.
I had so much fun with you guys...
Sno...
Kondo-san...
So everything I was trying to do to help
you would have destroyed you?
That's how it should be.
It's the fate of snot to be blown
into a tissue and throw away.
But...
I've lived too long...
I've grown too ugly and fat
to be kept inside a nose...
I wanted you to send me off...
Toshi, I wanted to be blown
into a tissue held by you...
Can you do me this favor...friend?
I'll come after you...
Next time, I'll also become snot...
I'll be waiting...
I'll be waiting in Otae-san's nostrils...
Like hell I'd follow you there!!
Talking snot is damn disgusting!
Toshi...
Your fly was open...
We're here, Toshi.
This is Ikezuya.
This will be an intense fight.
Stay focused.
Kondo-san...
Hmm? What is it?
Your snot's going Tarzan on you.
Oh, you're right.
[Teach us!! Ginpachi Sensei]
We have a question from someone
with the pen name Mutaito.
[Note: Based on the Master Roshi's
master from Dragon Ball.]
I have an uncle in his late 30s, a Madao.
The other day, he came
over to my house
and ended up staying in my room.
That night, around 2 AM,
[Note: Master Roshi's technique.]
Madao got completely naked and used a
full power Evil Containment Wave on me.
Mr. Ginpachi, please help him.
Okay, here's your answer.
He's beyond help.
Please get completely naked and use a full power
Evil Containment Wave to seal your uncle.
It's sad, but I believe it's the best
thing you can do for him.
So Mutaito-san, men in their late 30s are
a lot more childish than you realize.
They get worse as they age.
I would love to show you what's going on inside the
minds of the staff members who make this show.
[Preview]
A sunny and bright smile.
A demeanor soft as a spring breeze.
Ana Ketsuno, I turn to this channel every
morning just to see that smile.
I'll brave any danger to
protect that smile...
Whoa! But not this kind of danger !
The next episode...
"Not Losing to the Rain!"
[Gin-san is a huge fan of Ana Ketsuno,
the once divorced weather girl and face of Edo.]
[However, she has a surprising
other face as well.]
[See you next time.]