Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[Note: Parody of the Monster Hunter game.]
[In order to track down the alien gamers, Odd Jobs
dives into the popular "Monkey Hunter" game.]
[It's not "Monster." It's "Monkey," so
it'll be okay! At least it should be...]
["Imagination Is Nurtured In the 8th Grade"]
[Internet café]
He's here! A hunter is here!
He's here! He's really here!
He seems incredibly strong! He's without
a doubt, a first-rate hunter.
We've got to recruit him!
Thank you. You saved us. You're
very strong. Do you hunt alone?
I have no friends (lol). Won't
you join me in the hunt (lol)?
He wants to join us! He looks scary,
but he seems to be nice enough.
Yes, by all means!
We're novices and don't have
a clue. I'm Patsuan. (lol)
Ginko here. (lol)
I'm Kaguura Jasuanto. (cry)
Why (cry)? Why're you sad?
I'm on a quest for revenge. It's
going to be a hellish journey.
Cut out that 8th-grader storyline.
Ahahahahaha (lol).
Forgive me. (lol) This (lol)
is a habit of mine. (lol)
He puts (lol) after he laughs. Hilarious.
He's an awesome guy.
There was an argument
about this on the Net.
It's often difficult to convey
feelings in text.
So we write in our emotions
to avoid misunderstandings.
Forgive me. I got sidetracked and
haven't introduced myself. (lol)
I'm Fruit Punch Samurai G. Pleased
to meet you. (Katsura)
(Katsura)...you mean?!
This guy reveled his identity
right from the start!
What're you doing here? Get back to
your Anti-Foreigner Faction activities!
What do you all do in real life?
(It probably can't be anything good seeing
as you're playing games in the afternoon.)
Hey! You're being way too
honest in the parentheses!
You're writing feelings
you shouldn't write!
We're just gamers. (pilot)
Don't lie! Don't lie in the parentheses!
I'm just a traveler.
(But when my back is against the wall,
my second personality awakens and
I become a hard-nosed berserker...
My mortal enemy, the shining Knight
Shezard, is actually my older brother.
He gave me this cross-shaped
scar on my face.)
Stop explaining your 8th-grader storyline!
When did that happen? When
did you get that scar?!
What are you in real life,
Fruit Punch Samurai G?
I'm totally on to you, but
I'll ask as a courtesy.
Me? I'm...
a screwdriver. (+)
[Note: (+) stands for Phillips screwdriver.]
You, too?!
I was subjected to alien abduction
by a mysterious UFO.
My body was modified
without my consent.
I'm playing this game to pursue the alien
gamers. Do you know anything?
Huh?
Just a minute... (sad)
He's a nuisance. Let's kick him out
and find someone else.
Gosh. There were other
victims besides us.
Just a minute. Let's hunt together...
Hey, I thought I told you not to
show your face around here.
If you're going to come here, I told
you to change your name first,
Fruit Punch Samurai G.
You're... (anger)
Fruit Chinpo Samurai G!
You're still in this game?
How many times have I told you to change
your confusing name? (anger)
[Note: "Punch" is "ponchi" in Japanese. "Ponchi" spelled
backwards is "Chinpo" which means "penis."]
You're the one who has
to change his name.
I will not allow anyone to
use the name "Fruit."
[Fruit Chinpo Samurai G]
[Bow User]
[Fruit Ponchi Samurai G]
[Cannon User]
[Note: Refers to Ep. 34]
I think I've seen this scenario before.
Let's do this!
You missed! Where are you aiming,
Fruit Punch Samurai G?
Your arrows look like they're not even moving
to me, Fruit Chinpo Samurai G!
What are you in real life anyway?!
I'm a screwdriver.
You, too?!
What...?! Chinpo Samurai G...not
you, too...?! (surprise)
Fruit Punch Samurai G...you, too?!
Th-That's impossible! There were others...?
There were others who entered the transporter device
not knowing a screwdriver had fallen inside,
[Note: Reference from the movie "The Fly".]
and had their body fused with a screwdriver
at the genetic level?!
That's totally different! Only you were
involved in "The Fly" accident!
That's shocking... (I have no
idea what he's talking about.)
He's going with the flow!
At any rate, we're both fighting
the wrong enemy.
Totally wrong! This is a
totally different incident!
Did it happen to you people, too?
Well, yeah. Anyway, let's capture the alien
gamers-they're in here somewhere.
They can help him.
No, they can't! Not him! What
an irresponsible thing to say!
Don't slow us down.
(I say such spiteful things, but Kaguura
never ignores people in need.
However, when my back
is against the wall,
my second personality awakens and
I become a hard-nosed berserker.
You were a hard-nosed
berserker from the start!
You say you're going to find
the alien gamers...but how?
This game is filled with gamers
from all over the galaxy.
Besides, their appearance will be totally different
from how they appear in real life.
How will you find and recognize them?
We need to find M. (passion)
M...? That's impossible!
He's just a myth!
Even if he is, we have no other
way out of this difficult situation.
We have to find M. (passion)
But...
Just a minute. Just what is M?
You don't know? (ass)
(Ass)?! Are you saying I'm stupid?
You better not mean that!
Codename M.
He has existed since Genesis.
He is all-knowing and has hunted
throughout this entire world.
The legendary hunter...M.
If he's all-knowing, he must know
where the alien gamers are.
There's no guarantee, but I've heard
rumors that someone resembling M
was last seen in Area D-51.
Area D-51? That's the lair of mythical beasts
that even top-class hunters fear.
So this is Area D-51...gives
me the creeps.
Be wary. The monkeys that live
here are of the highest level.
If you encounter one, don't fight
it under any circumstances.
We'd be no match for it. (fear)
I can't believe anyone would be in
such a frightening place like this.
Exactly. Only monsters dwell here.
So if you see a human-like shadow,
you can assume it is M. (resolve)
Did you hear something?
A howl...like that of some kind of beast.
Could it be the enemy?!
No, it sounds different!
Look! A human-like form!
No, it can't be! Could this
be M? Is this really M?
Th-That's...!
Oh no! Someone's been strung up
to roast! Hurry and get her down!
She's still breathing.
She must've been captured by the monkeys
and was about to be eaten.
Hey, pull yourself together! Can you
speak? What happened?! What...
Why'd you cut me down?
It's you! This is just
an ordinary M!
[Note: M stands for masochist.]
Some "legendary hunter"!
What did you bring us here for?! Huh?!
Let's string this guy up next.
Stop it! If you're going to do
that, do it to me. Please!
You keep quiet, perverted woman!
What? If you've got a problem with that,
let's hear it! C'mon, say it! Say it!
M-Monster!
I-Impossible!
He defeated the mythical beast, Paoshanron,
a monkey of the strongest class...
[Note: Parody of Lao Shan Lung
from Monster Hunter.]
In just one shot...
Don't even think about
touching my guests.
Yo.
I'm M.
[GinTama Monkey Hunter Arc]
There's no doubt about it.
Only one person in this world
could do such a thing.
One who is all-knowing; one who has
hunted all over the entire game...
This is the legendary hunter...M!
C-Cool!
I was expecting a much older, rugged
sort of guy, but he's way cooler!
Did you appear in FF? He
appeared in FF, didn't he?
[Note: Refers to Cloud from Final Fantasy VII.]
I want your autograph.
What're you getting so excited about?
That's not the reason we came here.
Excuse me, M-dono, would you mind
taking a photo with my kid and me?
What did you come for?! Who's your kid?
Forgive us. We're...
You don't have to say anything.
Who do you think I am?
I am the all-knowing M.
I know why you're playing this game
and why you came in search of me.
I know everything.
I've been waiting for you.
People who can face any crisis, who
hunt for the hope that is tomorrow...
I have been waiting for true
hunters like you to come.
Recently, there has been an increase in
some rather odd hunters coming
to the Mon-Hun world.
They're not here to enjoy hunting.
All they do is search for people.
And they all say the same thing...
Do you know anything about
the alien gamers?
I-It can't be...
Yes. You're not the only victims
of alien abduction.
Others like you, who wish
to restore their bodies,
are coming one after another
into this world.
Didn't you people know?
It's become such a crisis that the
Bakufu is taking action.
I was asked by certain higher-ups
in the Bakufu
to infiltrate this game. I'm here to string
up and arrest the alien gamers.
No, you strung up yourself,
indulging in M play.
But the majority of players gave
up and tossed their controllers.
It is nearly impossible to
find specific individuals,
whose names you don't even know,
in the huge world, known as the Net.
You are the first ones
to have reached me.
You'll find what you're looking for here.
Inside this temple is the monkey
who stands above all others,
the mythical beast...
Seiten Taisei. The aliens
plan to hunt it down.
[Note: Seiten Taisei is the self-claimed name
of Son Goku in Journey To The West.]
They will come here for sure.
You are people whom I recognize
as true hunters.
Will you fight with me?
I cannot stand by and watch anymore
as people trample on
this hunters' paradise
with their soiled feet.
Let us go together. Let us reclaim
our hunters' paradise.
Oh M...!!
Keep it down!
Oops, sorry.
M is way cool! Finally,
we got someone decent to be...
a member of our party!
Are you okay with getting involved
in such a problem?
Hmph.
Games are all about the enjoyment
of solving problems.
Don't worry. I'm not doing this on
a whim or just for the fun of it.
I have to restore my own body, as well.
Not you, too?!
Well, yeah. Though I'm not in
as bad shape as you people.
A light shined down on me from the sky
and by the time I knew what was
happening, it was too late.
I had been rendered completely
unemployed.
That's not a modification!
Why are you blaming aliens
for not having a job?!
You were that way before
they showed up!
I was turned into a spiritless, filthy dude
with sunglasses named Hasegawa.
That's who you are!
You're just trying to escape your real life
self by pretending to be someone else!
No way...the legendary hunter...was
Hasegawa-san?
I see.
He has so much free time that
he escaped into this game
and became the strongest hunter here.
His life inside the game and his real
life are in inverse proportion.
Often, the heroes who have
influence inside a game
are good-for-nothings in the real world
who have too much free time.
The legendary hunter is a legendary
good-for-nothing.
In that regard, our party
is the strongest ever.
We're all good-for-nothings.
Will we be okay?
Oh...someone's there...!
There they are!
It's them! No mistake! They look
almost the same as in real life!
Those jerks! I'll finish them off!
Wait!
We're inside the game.
Capturing them in here won't
restore our bodies. (anxiety)
Punch Samurai G is right.
Unless we capture the guys
playing the game,
any victory in here would
be meaningless.
Then...what can we do?
There's the offline meeting.
Offline meeting?
Yes. An offline meeting is a "land party",
where people who met on the Net,
via a bulletin board or chat room,
can meet face-to-face and get
to know each other better.
We'll help them with their hunt
and become Net friends.
Then we'll invite them
to an offline meeting
and drag them out of the cyber world.
We don't have time to go
through all that trouble!
This is already the second week!
We've already spent two weeks
on this ridiculous subject!
It's our second week, so we need
to approach this rationally.
And it's part B, so we need
to calm down and think.
Okay! Then let's hold an offline
meeting to plan our strategy.
You're too calm. That's an "I'm
relaxing at home" calmness!
I-It's here!
Senpai, the final boss appeared.
Oh, it's huge.
Whatever we do, make them
feel indebted to us.
Our enemy is the strongest in Mon-Hun.
Don't get yourselves killed.
Let's go!
I think they killed it.
Just a minute! What're you doing?!
We haven't done anything yet!
Ah...we've killed the final boss.
I guess we're done with Mon-Hun.
Oh no! This isn't good!
We've got trouble!
They're planning to quit the game!
If they leave, it's over for us!
An enemy! We have to give
them a new enemy!
Where are we going to
find another enemy?!
I'll think of something!
Keep them in the game until then.
I think our only choice is
to use womanpower.
Suit yourself.
You never did find it, did you?
You mean the rare item?
No...that.
You go and approach them.
Oh no! Because Ginko, you told
me his antennae was too risqué.
You go, Ginko.
Oh my, they're looking this way.
Uh, excuse me... The two
of us are on a hunt.
She wants to know if you'd
like to come with us.
Oh no, that was her. She said it.
Terrific! They've got the high-school
co-ed thing down pat!
No man can resist that!
I really didn't care, but Ginko here said...
C'mon, stop that! Saruko,
you were saying those body
tights turned you on.
Oh no, that was you, Ginko.
No, you did, Saruko.
No, I said that.
Why's an old man joining in?!
Don't you think it's seriously risqué?
Those body tights are so risqué, don't
you think? Aren't they risqué?
You're not a girl right now!
The problem is you, the creepy old man!
Sorry, but we already defeated
the final boss.
Wow! Awesome!
You're so strong, aren't you?!
I so respect that!
Well, I guess. It took only one shot.
But did you know there's a hidden
boss inside that temple?
There's a super-strong hidden boss called
Smegmamon or Masta Bayter.
Masta Bayter?! Oh, come on now!
Senpai, what do you think?
They want to come with us.
I don't care.
Just a minute! There's no Masta
Bayter anywhere in this world!
What are we going to do?!
They just lied to convince
them to go with them!
This is bad.
That Senpai dude is totally
stricken with 8th-grade-itis.
He's fully aware of the opposite sex,
but can't deal with them face-to-face.
He acts disinterested.
You see? He's part of the group,
but notice the distance.
The sex-appeal tactic is backfiring.
They won't be able to invite
them to an offline meeting.
Let's use his 8th-grade-itis
to our advantage.
People with 8th-grade-itis have a thick
AT Field towards the opposite sex,
[Note: Absolute Terror Field from
Neon Genesis Evengelion.]
but they're defenseless against
those of the same sex or race.
What's an AT Field? Aren't you
the one with 8th-grade-itis?
I'll force open a hole in his AT Field.
You guys use that opportunity
to get close to him.
How're you going to force it open?
That guy won't let anyone
in except his Kohai.
I'm sure he'll open up if we
show him we're his friends.
Is there anything they identify with?
That!
Senpai, is something the matter?
You've been really quiet lately.
It's nothing.
This isn't working. He hasn't
opened up to us at all.
He's at a difficult age.
But he keeps ogling us. So irritating!
Don't lose patience. We'll
seduce him in time.
Oh?
Aren't you...
Senpai?
It's me. Me! I was two grades
below you in middle school.
Don't you remember me? This antenna?
Awesome! A new species of monkey!
A rare monkey. Let's
quickly take his stuff.
Did he say something just
now? Do I know him?
He's nobody you know. He's just
a monkey. A genuine monkey.
I obtained a truly rare item.
I want you to have this as
a token of our friendship.
[Obtained: A filthy antenna]
You mean it?
That's great, Senpai. You can use
it to create powerful armaments.
No, I think it probably has no use at all.
No, you can use it in a cursed knife.
Fruit Chinpo Samurai G!! (lol)
What's the (lol) for?
That strategy was a total failure,
but the awkwardness has lessened a bit.
Fruit Chinpo Samurai G! Your death
was not in vain! (roflmao)
Why are you laughing?
Fruit Chinpo Samurai G taught me that
people must bare themselves and confront
each other head-on. (naked)
No, that guy was simply vulgar.
There was no hope of opening
up that guy's heart
by whispering secretly between
ourselves over here.
I've made up my mind-I'm going to bare
myself and confront them. (resolve)
I will tell him everything I
feel with open frankness.
We may live on different planets,
but I am sure we can understand
each other!
Just a minute, Katsura-san!
Hey! You guys!
The truth is, I sometimes urinate
when I take a shower,
but you all do that, too, don't you?
He's revealing something
that's totally irrelevant!
A-Awesome! Rare monkeys
keep appearing here!
No, he's your friend, right? They
were both your friends, right?
No, these monkeys aren't our friends.
They were genuine monkeys.
I obtained a very rare item.
I want you to have this as a token...
[Obtained: Golden water]
I don't want it!
Look I didn't say anything earlier,
but that's enough, you guys.
You've been sneaking about
trying to check us out.
What're you up to? Are you with them?
Huh? What're you saying?
I'm asking who you people are!
You should identify yourselves first
before asking us questions.
Huh? We are...
[Senpai]
[Gun User]
[Kohai]
[Whip User]
We are screwdrivers.
[Preview]
How many weeks is it going
to take to get my dick back?
We're having an offline meeting
next week?! Who cares!
Come back, my Shane!
[Note: Parody of the Western movie, Shane.]
The next episode... "Always Keep
a Screwdriver In Your Heart."
["Always Keep a Screwdriver In Your Heart"]
[Due to not making any progress, the Mon-Hun
party holds an offline meeting.]
[Will Gintoki and friends finally be able to restore
their modified body parts next week?!]