Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[The Odd Jobs head to Ryugu Palace. Kamenashi,
whom they saved, leads them there.]
[The summer vacation special project:
The Ryugu Arc... Begins this week!!]
Gin-san...
What is it?!
Did you find the suspicious person?
He's not here.
People who are not wearing swimsuits
and wandering around with cameras...
are suspects. He's probably been secretly
taking pictures of girls in swimsuits.
I see.
I hope you're really looking
for him. Really, I beg you.
The peace of the beach
rests on our shoulders.
That aside, everyone sure makes a big fuss
about the beach opening every year.
What are they, stupid?
They say that all life forms
came from the sea.
Apparently, everyone's unconsciously
yearning for mother ocean.
[Coast Guard Headquarters]
An annual return to Ryugu Palace, huh?
I'd like someone to take us there.
[Note: Ryugu Palace is the undersea palace of the dragon
god of the sea according to Japanese mythology.]
Huh? Come to think of it,
where's Kagura-chan?
She probably went to look for a turtle.
Huh? People are gathering over there.
It's Kagura-chan, isn't it?
It looks like she got in a
fight. Let's take a look.
Huh? Don't think...
I'll let you get away with this.
Stand the hell up! That was
for Krillin. Next is...
[Note: Refers to Krillin from Dragon Ball.]
Kagura-chan!
What are you doing?!
Are you all right?!
Are you all right?! Is he a turtle?
What are you thinking, Kagura-chan?
How could you pick on a turtle
at the beach? That's abusive!!
Is he really a turtle?
You've got it wrong. This turtle has
been filming us all this time.
Is he really turtle?
This girl helped us.
So did you film them?
I wasn't filming them.
I was just filming kelp.
Liar!! You were only following
around girls!!
I wasn't filming them. Honestly, could
you stop making things up?
It's really annoying.
All right. Then, excuse me,
but may I check the contents
of that video camera?
No. I told you that I didn't film them.
This is an invasion of privacy.
H-Hey!
If you didn't film them, then you
can show it to us, can't you?
It'll clear you of any suspicion.
Gimme that!!
Umm... I usually only film kelp, but there
may be girls on the sides of the videos.
That's safe, right?
That's okay, right?
No, that's not it. That's not it.
Actually, I was just filming
a swimsuit commercial.
It's a company camera, ya know.
[Coast Guard Headquarters]
Where do you live?
Umm, I'm sorry. Could you
please not not tell my family?
My wife is going to be laying eggs soon.
She's very sensitive at the moment.
She'll just have to shed tears
as she lays her eggs.
I really am sorry. I really
won't do it again.
It's the truth! I swear on kelp!! Really!
What kind of oath is that? Is that
popular in the turtle world?
If something were to happen to the
eggs in her belly because of this...
Even kelp can be washed
away by the river currents.
What is that, a proverb?
Are they all kelp related?
I wish I could eat kelp!!
Is that like "I wish I could
crawl into a hole"?
I have some pickled seaweed.
Oh, thanks.
Oh Gin-san, he has a license
amongst his possessions.
It's a boat license.
If you're a turtle--just swim!
3-chome, 2-5-3,
Maison Kelp, Room 305...
Ryugu Palace?
Ryugu Palace? You live
in Ryugu Palace?
Oh... Yes. Actually I'm a guide
at the Ryugu Palace...
Really?! Huh?! It exists? Ryugu
Palace really exists?!
Huh? It ordinarily exists...
["Summer Vacation is the Most
Fun Right Before It Begins"]
[Note: Urashima Taro is the story of a fisherman who rescues a turtle and is rewarded with a visit to Ryugu Palace under the sea.]
Long, long ago... Urashima
caught a voyeuristic turtle...
When he went to Ryugu Palace...
Could you stop that? Could
you stop singing that song?
It would be bad if it became folklore.
Yahoo! We get to spend summer
vacation at Ryugu Palace!
I never thought Ryugu Palace
actually existed.
Does that mean Taro Urashima
actually existed?
Yes. I don't know him,
but a guest the first turtle brought
over was called Urashima-san.
We've called all of our guests
"Urashima-san" ever since.
Did you hear that, Gin-san?!
We're Urashima-san!!
Isn't that amazing? We've
left our mark in history!!
This isn't really important, but you've
been referring to us as guests.
You're not going to take money
from us, are you?
Of course not!!
Ryugu Palace is indeed a paradise that
only chosen celebrities can visit.
It's the sea's holy land and
cannot be entered no matter how
much money you pay. But...
Turtles, despite their looks, are honorable
creatures that fulfill their duties.
Repaying favors like the surging and
receding waves is the law of the sea.
"Despite their looks"? There
aren't any turtles like you.
As a special offer...
I'll give you a complimentary
all-you-can-drink voucher...
Make it free!!
All right. As a special offer...
I'll double the stamps on your point card.
Make it free!!
[Note: He's holding erotic massage lotion.]
All right. I'll rub lotion on you for free!
What kind of shop are you?!
Anyway, how long will it
take to get to Ryugu?
We've been drifting in the ocean
for about two hours.
You have a boat license, don't you?
Don't you have a faster boat?!
I got into an accident and killed
a dolphin. I'm on trial now.
How many times have
you been convicted?!
Come on. Give me a break.
At this rate, I'll become an old man before
I even open the treasure chest.
Hey, what's with that cruiser?
Th-That's...
Sis!! Kyubei-san!!
Oh, Shin-chan, what are you doing
out in the middle of the ocean?
You, two! Why are you here?
I thought you were out shopping
with Kyubei-san.
Otae-chan...
[Note: Parody of Japanese
actor, Tatsuya Umamiya.]
Kyu-chan...
I caught a nice swordfish.
Shall I clean it...
on our way to Ryugu?
Wh-What kind of turtle is that?!
He's really cool!! He has
a golden sheen to him!!
He caught a swordfish!
He has chest hair!!
Is he really a turtle?
S-Sis, could it be that you're also...
We happened to save his
daughter from bad men.
He was insistent on inviting us to Ryugu Palace
even though we said he didn't have to.
They were a rare brand of wicked men.
Let's get going. Ryugu Palace
gets crowded around this time.
We must hurry.
Oh, yes.
Well, Shin-chan, I don't know what you all are doing,
but it's dangerous and you should return to land.
H-Hey, wait...
Sis, let us on, too!!
Sis!!
Hey!!
What's the meaning of that? Why
is there more than one turtle?!
I thought it wasn't that easy
to go to Ryugu Palace!!
What's the deal with that turtle?!
Why is there such a difference?!
Gin-san, now's not the
time to be saying that.
He said that Ryugu Palace is going
to be crowded!! We've got to hurry.
Damn it!!
We can't let them outdo
our summer vacation!!
Wh-What the hell is this?!
Oh! That's...
It's Madao!!
Hey, what's with that turtle?
No one would ever pick on that turtle.
Hey, Gin-san, this turtle saved me when
I was about to jump off a cliff.
He's taking me to Ryugu Palace now.
He didn't save the turtle,
but was saved instead.
Hasegawa-san, I caught
a nice Shikao Suga.
[Note: Wordplay on Kajiki Maguro (swordfish)
and Suga Shikao (musician).]
Why don't we clean it
on the way to Ryugu?
What's a Shikao Suga?! How
are you going to clean that?!
Captain!!
There's something flying above us...
What?!
I-Impossible. That's... It can't be...
It's a giant turtle.
That's a soft-shelled turtle, isn't it?
It's a soft-shelled turtle.
That's slightly inaccurate.
No, wait, we're riding in a rowboat
for transportation. His guide is...
No, that's totally inaccurate...
[Note: Refers to Momotaro, a
hero from Japanese folklore.]
That's the wrong folktale.
Gintoki, I never expected to see
you here. What a coincidence.
[Note: Millet dumplings are from the Japanese folktale of "Momotaro" and Tianzhu is from the Chinese legend "Journey to the West."]
In return for giving them millet dumplings,
they're taking me to Tianzhu.
What country is that folktale from?!
Fire!!
Hasegawa-san's the one who's
going to go to Ryugu Palace!
Madao has lost hope. I'm
going to give him a light!!
Who'd want to go to Ryugu Palace?!
We're going to Tianzhu!!
That doesn't exist!!
You bastards!!
I'm the feared Emperor of the Sea.
You've got some nerve, getting
rowdy in front of me!!
[Note: "Tatchan-zuke" is a brand of Japanese pickles
owned by Tatsuo Umemiya, a Japanese actor.]
I'll turn you all into weights
for making Tatchan-zuke!!
H-Hey, wait!!
Why?!
We just wanted to go to Ryugu
Palace. Why does this...
have to happen to us?!
Is this...
Ryugu Palace?
This wasn't Ryugu Palace.
Everyone! Gin-san, Kagura-chan,
Kamenashi-san!
Here...
There wasn't any extravagant food, beautiful
dancers, or Otohime-sama.
My...
worst summer vacation
was about to begin.
[Gorilla News]
Hey, look at that!
We have determined that the
person who was rescued
from the deserted island the other day
is Shinpachi Shimura-san,
who had gone missing sixty years ago.
[Current]
[Shinpachi Shimura-san]
[60 years ago]
Excuse me, Shimura-san, but how did
you survive on that deserted island?
What did you eat?
What did you think about?
Wasn't there any way to escape?
What do you want to do
the most right now?
I want to see Gin-san and the others.
[Odd Jobs Gin]
[Lingerie Pub]
Hey, sir, want to come in?
We have a lot of cute girls.
You'd like to have some
fun, wouldn't you?
There isn't anyone...
Everyone's gone...
They're not anywhere...
I'm alone...
I'm alone in the world...
I was alone even when I
awoke from my nightmare.
Taro Urashima grew old while living
the fast life in Ryugu Palace.
But I'm going to grow old alone in this place
without ever reaching Ryugu palace.
No, I'm not sure I can even
survive, let alone grow old.
Furthermore, there's no guarantee
that anyone will rescue me.
No, no. I get depressed
when I'm by myself.
I need to think positive!!
You need to think positive at
times like this, Shinpachi!!
I'm sure that Gin-san and
the others are alive.
I'm sure they'll come to save me.
Until then, I need to do
my best by myself.
Think positive, Shinpachi.
The world is just a reflection
of your heart.
One thought can change the
way you see the world.
If anything, enjoy this predicament,
Shinpachi.
This is a deserted island!!
There aren't many opportunities to experience
such complete solitude.
My heart suddenly feels lighter.
I realized that it wasn't clothes I had discarded,
but rather my mental armor.
Our daily lives wear us down.
We end up placing heavy armor around our
hearts in order to get by without being hurt.
What are we afraid of?
Now that I've removed my barrier,
now that I've let everything loose,
my naked heart tenderly
accepts everything.
My heart melts in the wind.
My body melts into nature.
The trees, the water, and the
sun were all within me.
Yes. I am a part of this planet,
and this planet is a part of me.
Before I knew it, my sense of
loneliness had slipped away.
I had nothing to fear.
I'm...
Not alone...
I really wasn't alone.
S-Someone was here.
Y-You washed up here, too,
huh Hasegawa-san?
Let's ignore what we
were doing just now.
Yeah.
I thought that I was completely alone.
I just let loose as if I was the
only person in the world.
Well, opportunities such
as this don't really exist.
Ka-me-ha-me-ha!!
[Note: Parody of Dragon Ball]
Something's wrong. Maybe I should
do it with a little more oomph.
Ka-me-ha-me...
We didn't see anything.
Thanks. I thought I was
completely alone.
I thought I could practice
to my heart's content.
Yeah!!
That girl is a lovely angel from
the sun! Just a little wild! Say!
[Note: Lyrics to the B'z (a Japanese band)
song, Taiyo no Komachi Angel.]
Umm... Everyone likes B'z. There's
nothing to be embarrassed about.
Th-They're always at
the top of the charts.
I understand. She wanted
to show that to someone.
That was miraculous, wasn't it?
[Note: Refers to Laputa: Castle in the Sky.]
That cloud... Laputa's got to be in there!!
Everyone thinks that when
they see a huge cloud.
There's nothing embarrassing about that.
That girl is a lovely angel from the sun!
What's this?
That cloud... There's got to be a crystallized
Crystal Takigawa in there.
[Note: Christel Takigawa is
a Japanese newscaster.]
Oh no. I stopped in the middle of "SOS"!
What the-?!
I can't understand any of his actions!
I can't sympathize with
him. What is this?!
Why was he trying to save this?
It's miraculous isn't it? It looks
exactly like Crystal Takigawa.
What do you mean by
Crystal Takigawa?!
What's miraculous is your idiocy!!
I ran out of piss halfway.
Does anyone have to
go to the bathroom?
Why does it have to be in piss?!
Anyway, how much did you piss?
I'm surprised you drew
something this big!
I was influenced by Inoue
sensei's commercial.
Inoue sensei would never do this!!
This is terrible.
Our boats headed to Ryugu
Palace were destroyed
and we ended up on this deserted island.
It's Tianzhu, not Ryugu.
You be quiet.
It's great that everyone's all right.
What's so great about this?
We don't have a boat to escape
in or any way to call for help,
not to mention food and shelter.
What are we going to do?
With this many of us, we'll manage
on this deserted island.
For now, we need to think of a way
to get off this island and
how to survive until then.
Before we do, you should probably
choose me as your leader.
Why are you already the leader?
First, we should choose a leader to
decide how we'll choose a leader.
Then first, we should choose a leader
who will choose the leader who will
decide how we'll choose a leader.
Hey, this is really tedious!! Our world
will become filled with leaders!!
This is a bother, so Hasegawa-san
is good enough, right?
He's the oldest.
We should let him do what he
wants on this deserted island.
Don't say that in such an annoying
way! I don't want to be the leader!!
That's right. Madao is best left in charge
of opening and closing curtains.
Why am I in charge of something
that doesn't even matter?!
There aren't even any
curtains anywhere!!
You're in charge of closing
the curtains on your life.
Are you telling me to die?!
This girl is telling me to die!!
What we need right now is
food and a place to sleep.
Also, we can't do anything unless
we explore this island.
For today we shall split into four groups:
the food team, the shelter team,
the exploration team, and
the curtains team...
We don't need anyone
in charge of curtains!!
I want to be on the food team.
I'll cook with the utmost care.
All right, make one more team-the
chemical poisoning team.
Poison!
Look. I caught these.
Oh my! That's amazing, Hasegawa-san!!
I may not look it, but
I'm a man of the sea.
As long as I have a pole
and bait, this is nothing.
That's amazing!
God gives merits to even the
most worthless of people.
So you were praising God...
But even if we have ingredients,
we can't cook...
We can't start a fire. I've tried everything.
Tried everything? Looks more
like you were fooling around.
You were playing go.
When my father was still alive,
we'd gather around the othello
or go board and start a fire.
You can't start a fire that way!!
Oh yeah, you were smoking, weren't
you? Do you have a lighter?
Sorry, I dropped it in the ocean.
I was desperate to save
these sunglasses.
I see. That's problematic.
I really want a cigarette.
Do something, Otae-chan.
Oh!! I know.
Hasegawa-san, could you
lend me your sunglasses?
What? What are you going to do?
I just got a great idea... Just watch.
Just to let you know,
it's probably impossible to start a fire
using those lenses and sunlight.
You were going to break them?!
Furthermore, you've got matches!!
We were supposed to have a wonderful
summer vacation at Ryugu Palace.
Why did this have to happen to us?
Things like this are nice once
in a while. It's like camping.
Camping? We might not
be able to get home.
Just as I expected of our leader.
She isn't upset by any predicament,
and, if anything, she's got
the guts to enjoy it.
You're a true samurai!!
I'm not a samurai. Don't touch me!
Gintoki, why don't you learn
a little from our leader?
You always complain about silly things.
If you're really disappointed
with the status quo,
you should join the Anti-Foreigner
Faction! Honestly...
Why are you suddenly trying
to get me to join you?
Why are you talking to me
as if you're my mother?
Hey, what's that?
It's a giant box.
It looks manmade. Why is
this on a deserted island?
Leader, don't touch it!!
Courage and recklessness are
two different things, leader.
If you're a samurai, don't
charge in blindly.
You need to have the strength
to stand up to your enemies
with the knowledge of how
terrifying they are!!
You already touched it!!
Run away...
Kagura!!
Gin-chan!! Zura!!
I'm not "Zura." I'm "Katsura"!!
What is this smoke?!
Hey, are you all right?
I'm not "All right." I'm "Katsura"!!
Gin-chan!! Zura!!
Are you all right?
Who are you?!
[To be continued...]
["The Older, The Wiser"]
[Gintoki and Katsura have turned into old men...
Because of the smoke from a treasure chest (?).]
[Otohime, ruler of the Ryugu Palace, has a plot that is slowly coming to fruition. Can the elderly group stop her?!]
[See you next time.]