Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I never expected...
Ito to be allied with them...
I need to tell the Vice-Chief immediately.
The Vice-Chief!
Please...
The Shinsengumi... My...
Our Shinsengumi...
Protect it.
Please...
Kondo-san, I'm sorry.
Your flag has become pitch black.
As expected, Sensei...
You say interesting things.
We've become pitch black?
I don't know about those around you...
But they're different.
They can't be called a color.
If anything, they're grime.
They're stains that you can't remove,
no matter how much you wash.
They can't be colored or
affected by anything.
Okita-kun, what are you doing?
You're supposed to be keeping watch.
What are you doing?
I'm asking you what you're
doing, you piece of shit.
Okita-kun...
How dare you talk like that to Ito Sensei?!
Let go.
I said, let go of him!!
[Ito's faction plans to assassinate Kondo. Upon discovering
this plan, Gintoki and the others chase after the train.]
[Hijikata has become a hopeless otaku.
Is there any way to save Kondo?]
["There's a Thin Line Between
Strengths and Weaknesses"]
Sogo...
Okita-kun, so you really were
part of Hijikata's faction.
You were a spy who got close to me
to find out what I was going to do.
Your betrayal of Hijikata was
all an act to fool me.
That wasn't an act.
I told you... All I want is to be Vice-Chief.
I'll crush anyone who gets in my way.
Hijikata disappeared... You're next, Ito Sensei.
I don't want to work under him
or you. I have only one boss.
Out of the way! That spot
by his side is mine!!
How ill-natured. You used
me to get rid of Hijikata.
And, now that I'm of no use,
you're going to get rid of me.
Why not? I have the same idea as you.
Kondo-san!! At this rate, Kondo-san
will be assassinated!!
It's none of my concern...
Hijikata-san!! Get a hold
of yourself, Hijikata-san!!
It's none of my concern...
It's of no concern...
At this rate, you may lose all
the people and things...
You hold dear!!
It's of no concern... It's
none of my concern...
Gin-chan, what should we do?
Please protect...
Our Shinsengumi...
Kagura, patch us through to
headquarters and all cars.
Aye, aye, sir.
Umm... Hello? Can you hear
me you tax thieves?
I'm not sure if it's the Ito faction
or the Mayonnaise faction...
But I'm saying this to
all of you tax thieves!
Immediately leave your posts and
go after the train that Kondo's on.
If you waste time, your boss...
Might be killed.
This is an order. Those
who ignore this order...
Will have to commit seppuku for
not standing by their bushido.
Is this a prank?! Who are you?!
Who do you think you're
talking to? Who am I?
This is Shinsengumi Vice-Chief
Toshiro Hijikata, damn it!!
Humph!
Gin-san...
I'm sick of seeing that cowardly face.
This is convenient.
If the Shinsengumi is going to disappear,
you can disappear with them.
I'll send you to your grave.
No way! I'm not going!
I wasn't talking to you!!
Hey, are you listening? Are you?
Don't retreat and shove your
problems onto other people!!
Are you the type that asks
things of others?
Are you the type that
shoves the fate of your Shinsengumi
onto someone else?
If you're going to die,
die while swinging your sword along side
the things that are important to you!!
That's who you are!!
That hurts...
I told you, that hurts!!
Could it be?
Could it be?!
Ito Sensei, the train is on fire! It's
dangerous for us to stay here!
Don't stop the train!! If we
stop, Kondo will escape.
Everyone on this train aside from
those two are our allies.
As long as this train continues
moving, they're trapped like rats.
Sorry, Sogo. It's all my
fault this happened.
How can I make it up
to you? How can I...
apologize to you...to Toshi?
How can I apologize?
Sogo!!
What are you doing, Sogo?! Open up!!
Kondo-san...
If our boss is killed, we'll lose this battle.
Please stay here.
No way!!
Kondo-san, I've constantly told you
that the bad thing about you is
that you're too good a person.
You believe anyone and
never doubt them.
In the end, a fox like him
ended up by your side.
Well, I expected this would
happen sooner or later.
But because you're like that,
we gathered around you...
Because you're like that,
we fought with you.
Because you're like that...
You're worth risking my life to protect.
Sogo! Wait!!
If you die, I... I...
Sogo!!
Okita-kun, I thought you
were smarter than that.
Do you plan to fight us all by yourself?
You let Kondo escape and remained
behind with the enemy.
Do you plan to die a heroic death?
Unfortunately, Kondo is going
to die according to my plans.
We aren't the only ones
on this battlefield.
The Kiheitai, huh?
Sorry, Ito-san. Actually,
I'm not alone either.
Impossible... That's...
This is a raid!!
All of you surrender quietly!!
Hijikata?!
Why is he here?!
Can't you act cool for just a little longer?!
I can't, I can't! It's impossible
for me! I'm scared!!
In order to raise the morale of your allies,
you need to show them that their
Vice-Chief is still kicking!!
You've got to be kidding me! You only
reverted back when you hit me?!
Tsk... A bunch of eyesores
have crawled out...
But an army isn't enough
to take them down.
Hijikata...
What can he do by showing up now?
I'll wipe them all out, including Kondo.
You're the ones who are
going to get wiped out.
I see some faces I know.
I hope you're prepared to
die for joining that side.
Shinsengumi Regulation Article 21...
Those who have been secretly conspiring
with the enemy shall be punished!
I'll take down all of you.
Don't you see the situation you're in?
Here, I'm the faction in power.
You're the rebel.
The laws that he created have
no meaning anymore.
Your Shinsengumi will disappear.
Get rid of him.
Yes!
As the First Squad Captain
of the Shinsengumi,
I shall give you your final lesson.
When faced with an enemy who
is considerably more powerful,
it is best to overcome that power
with sheer numbers.
Synchronize your breathing.
Build up spirit in your heart and body.
When you are at your peak...
Attack all at once!!
And...!!
Die.
Are those Anti-Foreigner
Faction members?
Jeez... It looks like it wasn't
just an internal squabble.
Kondo-san...
Where in the world is Kondo-san?!
There!
That car that's moving
far behind the train!
All the enemies are headed there!
That's the situation, Mr. Hijikata.
Take care of the rest yourself!!
Hey, wait, Mr. Sakata!
Are you planning to leave me here?!
[Note: Parody of Dragon Ball. Yamcha
is thought of as the weakest character.]
That's as reckless as sending Mr. Yamcha
to Planet Namek by himself.
And leaving him to decide
the fate of the universe!!
It's all right! You're Vegeta!!
You can do it if you try!
[Note: Parody of Dragon Ball. Vegeta
is one of the strong characters.]
Mr. Sakata!!
Vice-Chief!!
It's the Vice-Chief!
The Vice-Chief is all right!!
No matter how you look
at this, I'm not all right!!
So you've finally come.
I was getting sick of taking care
of him. Take him already.
He's caused us a lot of trouble.
Have the shogunate transfer the
reward into my bank account.
Ito, that bastard, has finally
shown his true self!!
But we're all right now that
the Vice-Chief is back!!
Hey, are you listening? Transfer my
reward into my bank account...
Vice-Chief, we shall confront the enemy.
You save the Chief in the meantime.
Let's go!!
Hey, wait!!
Hey, wait, damn it!
Something weird has happened
to your Vice-Chief.
Listen to me, baldy!!
Those guys... Why?
Why?!
You idiot... Why are you...
Why are you here?
I treated you so badly.
Why did you come all this way for me?
Toshi!
Why did you come?
You idiot!
Huh?
Kondo-san, are you all right?
It's no good. He's not here.
What the hell do you think you're doing?!
Oh, there he is! Are you all right?
Hey, it seems that people are really
trying to assassinate you.
No, I was almost killed by you just now!!
Could it be that you dragged
Toshi all the way here?
This is impossible. You help us?
It was his last request.
His last request?
His soul was devoured
by a demonic sword.
Right now, he's just a hopeless otaku.
He won't return ever again.
A demonic sword?
Toshi?!
Pretty Samurai Tomoe 5000 is here!
Damn it!!
If all of Toshi's unexplainable actions were
the result of the demonic sword...
To Love-Ru is really great, isn't it?
While in that state, what
did Toshi ask you to do?
He asked us to protect the Shinsengumi.
It would be a pain to do that, so I brought
him here and told him to do it himself.
Our job ends here. I want you
to transfer the reward to me.
I will... I'll give you all of my savings...
But, Odd Jobs, I have a request for you.
Consider this a last request as well.
Take Toshi and run away.
It's my fault this happened.
I don't want Toshi to get involved
in this battle in his current state.
I ignored Toshi's advice to be wary of Ito.
Furthermore, I punished Toshi for
a petty blunder on Ito's advice.
I never even knew that this
was happening to him.
I didn't know that he was trying to protect
the Shinsengumi, even in his condition.
I didn't know that, despite his
pride, he lowered his head...
And entrusted the Shinsengumi to you.
I'm sorry, Toshi... I'm sorry, everyone...
I...I'm...a big idiot...
Tell all the cars to immediately
leave the battlefront.
Isao Kondo has died in battle.
I don't want my friends to fight
each other any more.
Gentlemen of the Yamato,
our Chief, Isao Kondo...
[Note: Spoof of the Space Battleship Yamato anime series.]
has been safely rescued.
Victory is within our grasp!
We shall get revenge on
[Note: Spoof of GUNDAM series anime.]
that lawless bunch for besmirching
our Chief's name. Let me say this.
They are all scum!
In the name of the moon...
[Spoof of Sailor Moon.]
We will punish them!!
Hey, who's that? Who's making that silly speech?
Who am I? I'm Shinsengumi Vice-Chief...
Toshiro Hijikata nari!!
[Note: Suffix "Nari" was used by Samurai and by
Korosuke in the Kiteretsu Daihyakka anime.]
HIjikata-san...
Mr. Kondo, we shall protect your life.
In return, you have an obligation to fulfill.
To not die.
Do whatever it takes to live.
No matter how humiliating it may be...
No matter how many squad members
die before your eyes, you must live!
As long as you're here,
the Shinsengumi is not finished.
We joined the Shinsengumi because
we wanted to be with you...
You're an idiot.
Don't think about such difficult things!
You should live the way you want to live.
We just have to protect
you from everyone.
Kondo-san...
You are the soul of the Shinsengumi.
We are the sword that protects you.
Toshi...
You broke once before.
What can you protect?
Hijikata-kun, it seems we have
to settle things between us.
I have a sword right here.
One that cuts very well.
Odd Jobs, I heard your rotten sermon!
What is it?
Don't talk as if you're so high and mighty.
Draw it already!
Shut up!
I have one more thing to say to you.
Thank you!!
Hey, hey, it looks like the demonic
sword devoured him again...
Toshi? Is that Toshi?
I'm...
Shinsengumi Vice-Chief
Toshiro Hijikata!!
[To be continued]
[Preview]
It changed... The rhythm of that
man's soul has changed.
It went from a childish anime song
to a sturdy rock-and-roll tune.
I guess the same goes
for you, too, Ito-dono.
["Important Things Are Hard To See"]
[Hijikata fought off the demonic sword's curse
by himself. He goes to fight Ito one-on-one.]
[Meanwhile, Gintoki is in a fateful confrontation
with Bansai Kawakami.]
[See you next time.]