Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I saw a spider.
A spider tattoo on that man's neck...
A spider, huh?
Not much to go by, but oh well.
I'll have to let myself be caught.
In the spiderweb.
I'm the one who brought
you into this mess.
Go, quickly!
I'll follow behind shortly.
Sorry, but I try not to take a woman's
last minute nonsense seriously.
Please go, I beg you.
I wish to stay as your equal.
When I'm with you, my resolve weakens.
Give up on being a woman, Tsukuyo.
Don't shake up my feelings any further.
Pay attention, you idiot!
You're the one
who's not paying attention.
["Once You're Entangled in a Spiderweb,
It's Hard to Get It Off."]
Gintoki!
Bastard!
You need to shut up.
Tsukuyo!
I knew you would come, Tsukuyo.
You've become so beautiful.
I almost didn't recognize you.
However...
Your soul has become
repulsive to behold.
A tragedy.
Who... are you?!
You must be the one
who ruined the moon.
The one who soiled my beautiful moon.
It must have been you.
I see...
Your movements are still sharp
despite the injuries.
I can see how you were
able to defeat Hosen.
Who the hell are you?!
Someone you can trust
to watch your back.
Someone who would protect you,
instead of being protected.
Did that bring back the womanhood
you thought to have given up on?
Or could it be...
You've fallen for this man?
Gin-san and Tsukuyo are really late.
They should have returned by now.
I hope that they weren't caught
up in any trouble.
Don't worry. She's with Gin-chan.
Though the fact that she's with Gin-san
gives us something else to worry about.
Anyway, sorry about today, Hinowa-san.
We checked all over but we weren't
able to learn anything.
It's fine.
I'm sorry about forcing you to do this.
To be honest, I was more worried about
her than this whole drug deal.
Are you talking about Tsukky?
Yes, Tsukky.
You're the only ones who
would call her that.
Does it sound dumb?
No, it's wonderful.
I'll call her Tsukky from now on.
She always tries to bear
the burden alone.
I'm always so worried.
Protecting me and Yoshiwara for so
long, when she's only a woman...
Yet she never tries to rely on other
people when something happens.
She's so focused on protecting others that
she doesn't allow others to protect her.
It was the same this time.
She was thinking of how to deal
with this problem by herself.
Acting recklessly without considering
the danger to herself...
I wish she'd be willing to rely on
me when there was trouble.
It's because I'm so useless like this...
But it's different with you people.
When she's with you, she's able to relax.
Able to face you on equal footing
and ask for help or offer help.
Able to forget that she's the leader of the
Hyakka and become an ordinary girl.
You people are a true marvel...
Any heavy burden, any
attempt to shun others
feels stupid when we're around you.
Hinowa-san...
Was that a compliment? Or an insult?
It makes me happy to see
Tsukuyo look that way.
It doesn't have to involve business.
Please come to see her when
you have a little time.
She needs people like you.
Ever since he died...
He?
Who do you mean?
A long time ago, there was a person
she was able to rely on.
A person who would protect
her no matter what.
Tsukuyo, I made this clear.
One who can't give up on being a woman
couldn't possibly protect a thing.
Have you forgotten the pain
which came with that scar?
Tsukuyo.
If you wish to become one who protects
instead of one who is protected,
give up on being a woman.
How can you protect someone or something
if you're busy ensuring your own safety?
Devotion can only come
from sacrificing the self.
But devotion to what?
Not the Bakufu, not the
Shogun, not your lord.
It is to what you believe in,
what you must protect.
Yes, he protected Tsukuyo.
And Tsukuyo respected him in return.
However, it wasn't Tsukuyo
that he was protecting.
Tsukuyo turned out this way because...
Who are you talking about?
You may not be the sun which
shines above the people.
But I alone know of your lunar beauty
which secretly illuminates the land.
I alone shall watch over you.
I alone will protect you.
That's right...
I've come to protect your former beauty.
He was one of the strongest
Ninja in Edo.
Yet he was banished from the
Oniwabanshu for his sins,
and ended up in Yoshiwara.
Nobody knows his real name.
He's known as...
Jiraia.
The original head of the Hyakka.
And Tsukuyo's...
Ma-
Master?!
Master...
So you weren't able to see
through my disguise.
It's ironic.
I gave up my face when
I gave up my identity,
yet now that very face serves
as the only proof of my existence.
The face of my identity...
Master...
How can you be alive?
Why are you doing this?!
Isn't it obvious?
To see you, Tsukuyo.
He was the one who trained
Tsukuyo from a young age
to create a hardened warrior.
He was the one who made Tsukuyo
abandon her life as a woman.
He was the one who created
the Tsukuyo we now know.
And as a final lesson, he sacrificed
himself and died.
Died?
There was a great fire in Yoshiwara
four years ago.
He died to protect Tsukuyo.
He was never trying to
protect Yoshiwara.
He was protecting his beloved
student, Tsukuyo.
I'm grateful to him for risking
his life to protect her.
For providing her with support
this whole time...
But she remains reluctant
to depend on others
because she's walking in his footsteps.
And he probably wasn't even protecting
Tsukuyo as a person.
He was protecting Tsukuyo
as his creation.
Tsukuyo, you were a masterpiece that
came from my blood and sweat.
I have been watching you, ever since I feigned
my death and vanished from Yoshiwara.
And you alone...
After losing your only source of support,
you were desperate to protect Yoshiwara,
Hinowa on your own.
You were beautiful to behold.
Just like the moon.
Humans acting in selfless devotion can
transcend flesh, good, and evil...
Only your beautiful soul remains.
You would have never been perfected
as a creation without my aid.
But my existence was also
preventing your perfection.
A weak human who had someone to rely
on could never sacrifice her sense of self.
Once your heart is strong enough to bear
the loneliness of having
no one to depend on,
you are able to abandon
your sense of self.
You were perfected when you lost me.
Yes, that should have been the end.
Until you all appeared!
Tsukuyo, you understand nothing.
You do not need anything
to rely on, depend on.
You only need solitude and
an enemy for your blade.
Look, Tsukuyo.
You will watch as one who
protects you vanishes.
And a new enemy will be born here
to replace your King of Night.
I, Jiraia!
Gintoki! Run!
You won't get away.
You are already caught in my web.
He's floating?!
Gintoki!
The threads!
He's strung up threads all around!
We can't beat him here!
Run!
Threads?!
He's using imperceptible
threads as a foothold?!
The first set of kunai was
for setting this up?!
By the time you notice
that you're caught in a spiderweb,
it's already too late.
Gintoki!
Now, to finish you off.
With your death, the moon
will become whole again.
Gaze at my beautiful moon
from the afterlife.
No matter.
He won't survive those wounds.
Gin...
Gintoki...
Not my problem.
I didn't see a thing.
I've been reading JUMP the whole time.
Because Ninjas can read
JUMP even in the dark.
I have nothing to do with this.
Gin-san!
Hang in there, Gin-
Thank goodness!
I thought you were gonna die!
Are you stupid?
It'll take more than this to kill Gin-chan!
But he was unconscious
for three whole days!
And these injuries are terrible.
Hey, why am I alive?
How did I make it back here?
[Ugly Girls Club]
C'mon! Drink up!
You're a good man.
But aren't you going to run out of
money if you come every day?
Oh, it's fine.
I got a bunch of coupons
from the Hinowa lady.
Besides, I'm rich.
I actually used to work for the Shogun.
You're such a kidder.
Why would someone from
a fine background
surround himself with fuglies
in a rundown club.
I find more beauty in ruined buildings
and funky caverns than
shiny skyscrapers.
You're a real wreck.
A rare breed.
What happened here?
Were you attacked by a Giant Warrior?
What are these two caverns?
Why are they pointing up?
Can I stick it in?
Can I stick an electric plug in?
Ow...
Bastard!
Is this how you treat the man
who saved your life?
Do you have any idea how hard it was to fish you
out of the ocean and drag you down here?!
What the hell are you babbling about?
You have no right to talk when you stood
by and watched while I was almost killed.
Why would I come to your rescue?
Besides, I have no interest in pretty girls.
What the hell were you doing there?
What happened to Tsukuyo?
Had a little business to take care of.
The pretty girl was taken.
Where'd they go?
Beats me. I said that I have
no interest in pretty girls.
Hey, where are you going?
Just to be clear,
you don't have a chance against him.
Even if you weren't all beat-up.
So you have no interest in pretty girls,
but you seem to be very interested
in fuglies and old men.
Jiraia the Spider...
He belonged to the last generation.
His power was said to rival my old man's,
the strongest of the Oniwabanshu.
However, despite his abilities, he was
banished from the Oniwabanshu...
Because of his dangerous nature.
I'm trying to be helpful.
Give up on the woman.
If you've been caught in his web,
you're beyond saving.
Are you awake?
How do you feel?
Master...
No, Jiraia...
You no longer wish to call me master?
That's fine.
You only need solitude and an enemy.
So I'd been struggling in your
web all these years?
I believed you.
I wanted to follow in your footsteps...
But it was all a lie?
What was it that you believed in?
The kind master who gave
his life to protect you?
Or the harsh master who taught you
the meaning of selfless devotion,
to give up your identity, to give
up on being a woman?
In that case, it wasn't a lie.
Even now, am I not sacrificing myself
for the sake of creating you?
Creating me?
You killed him just for that reason?
That's right.
If you hadn't grown weak,
I would have left Yoshiwara alone.
If you hadn't learned to rely on others,
I wouldn't have killed that man either.
You are the one who killed him, Tsukuyo.
And the tragedy that will soon play out
will all be your fault.
What do you intend to do?!
Wait! Jiraia!
Abandon your sense of self to
protect Yoshiwara and Hinowa.
That was the oath you
swore on that scar...
But Yoshiwara has become more
than a place for you to protect.
It has become a place where you belong,
where you can rely on others.
None of that is necessary.
I shall burn
the cobwebs and roots in your heart.
Wait!
Jiraia!!
[Preview]
Screw that.
Screw that to hell.
I'll die before I let that son of a
bitch call himself her master!
["It's the Irresponsible One Who's
Scary When Pissed."]
[Jiraia's spiderweb cloaks all of Yoshiwara.]
[Feelings towards the master, who misses Gintoki...]
[See you next week.]