Edited at https://subtitletools.com
My, my. What an unexpected guest.
The Harusame Seventh Division Commander,
Kamui-dono.
Earth food sure is good, Sir Housen.
The Seventh Division... Harusame's feared and unrivaled Lightning Spear.
What business could one who has achieved so much at such a young age
have at my humble abode?
You're too much, Sir.
You're the one who created the Seventh Division,
and then you left me with all the responsibilities...
so you could retire here peacefully.
It's unfair.
As people age, their bodies and hearts change.
What relieves the body is sake.
What relieves the heart is women.
Perhaps you're too young to understand?
No, I understand.
Oh? So you've learned the taste of things other than food since I've last seen you?
Do you want sake? Women?
Just tell me.
In that case...
One night with Hinowa.
As you can see, I've come prepared with a gift.
She'd be glad to serve me, don't you think?
You don't want Hinowa to be tainted by someone else?
You don't want this boy to take Hinowa away?
You don't want to be parted from Hinowa?
Be silent you-!
I wouldn't want to grow old...
It seems the one known as Night King Housen would be inept if it weren't for that one woman.
Yoshiwara - a woman's hell, yet a man's paradise.
Well, not quite.
This place, Sir,
is a paradise you built for yourself.
Kamui, I said to be silent.
It's a prison where a pitiful old man whom nobody pays attention to...
keeps cute dolls chained to his side.
Can you not hear me, Kamui?
A man drunk on sake is distinctive,
but a man drunk on a woman is just unsightly.  Right?
You old pervert?
Did you bastards come to check up on me?
Did you think I wouldn't notice?
They're orders from above, aren't they?
Have those old bastards finally begun to fear the great strength of Yoshiwara?
Is the Night King that hangs out in Yoshiwara becoming a nuisance?
Do you think you can defeat Night King Housen?
Well, you may be correct, but you wouldn't want to take on Harusame head on, would you?
It would be in your best interest to think before you act...
That would be a problem.
If you do that, then what do I do about this thirst of mine?
Women and sake don't cut it...
I don't need things like that.
They wouldn't be able to quench my thirst.
Blood...
The blood of Asura.
Only when I'm with someone of equal or greater blood than mine,
does my soul cry out in ecstacy.
I heard that you rebelled and tried to kill each other...
but you can't deny your blood.
Your eyes are just like his...
Long ago...
When I, the Night King, reigned atop the Yato, only he ever refused to swear allegiance.
The man who challenged me all by himself...
Your father,
Umibouzu's eyes.
I remember those three days and nights like they were yesterday.
He was the first to last that long against me.
He was also the first person I was unable to settle a fight with.
And then...
Excuse me... but I need to take a dump.
It was the first time I had ever ended a fight like that as well.
Kamui, can you surpass your father?
I've surpassed him long ago.
Tied up by trifling issues like his obligation to his family and whatnot..
A frail man like that who loses his arm to his own child...
cannot obtain true strength.
Sir, you are similar to that man.
Even though you look strong, there is nothing but sake and women inside you.
A true warrior needs a strong body in addition to a strong soul.
I have nothing holding me back and only strive for power.
You guys can't beat me.
Keep talking, brat!
Don't do it, commander!
I'm sorry.
If only I had let you go sooner...
There's no need to apologize.
Are you going?
If we don't go, Seita-kun will die.
If you go, you'll die too.
There are four Yato.
An entire army wouldn't be enough.
I have to do something about him.
For whose sake are you going?
Is it for Seita? Hinowa?
I'm going out for a bit to get some sun.
The same one that everyone's forgotten about...
after living their lives out in this dump of a place.
No matter where you are,
no matter how scared you are,
the Sun is there.
It's neither Hinowa nor Tsuji-chan's husband.
Your sun...
is often covered by clouds.
But if you continue to watch the sky, it will eventually make its way through the clouds.
That's why... we must never lose sight of that.
We must never stop staring at the sky.
Stand up straight,
watch the heavens,
and continue to live your life.
Tell everyone you see who looks depressed...
to watch the skies.
In this filthy, lead-colored sky...
we're going to put up a ridiculously huge sun.
Sorry, but I refuse.
Because I'll be going with you.
We can't bring someone who belongs to Yoshiwara to a fight against Yoshiwara.
You'll become a traitor.
I've told you already.
I protect Hinowa.
Not once have I sworn loyalty to Yoshiwara.
For me, it is even more treacherous to stand by and watch Seita die.
Besides...
Instead of continuing to depend on others, I'd rather look for it myself...
this so called sun you speak of.
Don't blame me if you have nowhere to return to.
It's alright.
You're going to crush Yoshiwara anyway, right?
Commander, stop it!
Did you forget our objective?!
Stop, Ungyou!
Com-
Stay put.
I'm having fun right now.
If you interfere again,
I'll kill you.
Commander!
I told you...
The commander's bad habit's taken over him again.
Once he gets like that, nobody can stop him.
As expected of Night King Housen, the man who once stood atop the Yato.
It seems like succeeding you isn't a simple task.
Succeed me?
Don't make me laugh.
Kamui, you don't believe in hierarchies.
You only believe in the difference between the strong and the weak.
You don't bother yourself with the weak.
But against the strong, it doesn't matter who it is.
You would even bare your fangs against your master.
That's just how the Yato blood is.
While you were happily drowning yourself in sake and women,
did your blood dry out?
Beating you as you are now would be no fun at all.
Please try to remember...
the blood of Asura that flows through you.
Silence.
You don't belong in a place like this.
I said to be silent.
You belong...
That's right...
We belong on the battlefield.
There it is again. It's from Housen-sama's room!
Shouldn't we go check it out?
Our friends are already on the way.
It's at times like this that we can't loosen security.
You don't know if an intruder will infiltrate through the gaps, right?
Exactly.
Boss!
That's enough. Both of you need to calm down.
My arm and his life were worth stopping your fight.
Please don't let his death be in vain and forgive our commander's misconduct.
Killing what few clan members we have left makes me uneasy.
We didn't come here to start a war with you.
We came to strengthen our relationship.
Why don't you just admit that you want this town?
The higher-ups are scared as well...
As one of us, we know your strength the best.
The old men just want proof that you won't betray them.
Quite the friends they are.
They're extorting a retired old man trying to peacefully live out the rest of his life.
I've lost interest.
Sir...
If money is what you want, take as much you want.
Things like that are worthless to me now.
However...
This town...
If you try to steal my country,
I will show you the true strength of the Night King.
I'm the one who has lost interest.
Is the toy you've made that precious?
If so, you should just wither away here.
It's not even worth killing you.
Wither away?
I started withering away long ago...
How have I shriveled so much when the Sun doesn't even reach me?
Where have you been this whole time?
Removal operations for the collapsed pipe.
But I'm glad. We can relax now that you're here, Boss.
Leave Housen-sama's matter to me.
I'll count on you guys to guard this place.
Roger!
Listen up. Don't let even one conspicuous person through.
If they're even a little suspicious, call 911.
I give you permission.
There won't be any mercy if you mess up.
Boss, they're suspicious.
Actually... no, they're not.
They're... um... new recruits.
New recruits?!
These suspicious people are?!
I'm Paako.
I'm Pachie.
I'm Gurako.
The three of us combined...
are the Three Bursting Peach Best Friends!
Boss, they're suspicious.
No... I said they're new recruits.
Are you sure you want to bring them?
Housen-sama is going to burst!
From his crotch?
No way!
Look in a mirror, Three Silicon Best Friends!
Bringing such useless people is dangerous!
It'll be okay. It's Chinhou-sama we're talking about.
He's just slipping into another woman. Don't get so worked up.
Who's Chinhou-sama? It's Housen-sama!
How would "slipping into someone" create a racket like that?!
Well, he is called the Night King, right?
He's got to have a loaded bazooka, right?
That's not what it means!
They may be new recruits, but they're skilled.
You don't need to worry.
If you say so, Boss.
Please go through.
We did it. It looks like we fooled them!
Please be careful...
on the journey to your next life!
It seems...
that whole act was a waste of time.
They saw through everything.
Boss...
To think you would assist the intruders...
You should know best what happens when you betray Yoshiwara.
Is that so?
What happens? Please tell us.
There are so many of you gathered here, are you guys throwing a goodbye party?
Gin-san, it really is goodbye.
What is?
What do you mean "what is"? How many times have you been hit?!
Is there a black hole on your forehead or something?!
What is? Nothing hit me.
You were hit!
Your face is obviously turning red. You're embarrassed!
Oi, get it together.
If you're gonna do it, do it right.
You were hit, right? You were obviously hit there, right?
If you guys start out like that, I'm worried about what's to come.
You guys... at this rate, you won't be able to beat the Night King in a hundred years!
I'm just not going to comment.
I should probably leave her be, right?
It's better she doesn't know, right?
Death to traitors. That is the law here.
You should give up your life in order to protect our laws one last time!
This is great...
Everybody working together to get the job done is more than a man like me deserves.
However...
If you're all flat-chested, I'll lose interest.
A woman needs...
giant melons!
Now then, let's kick off this party with a bang!
You guys go get the children!
We'll head towards the intruders!
Quite the commotion.
Better than the one you started.
What? You're still mad?
If you don't learn to let go, you won't live a long life.
Well, one of us is already dead.
Hey. You intended to mix it up with Housen from the start, didn't you?
Was it obvious?
"Was it obvious" my ass! Dammit.
Thanks to you, our bargaining chip got away during the confusion.
Oh, you mean that boy? I totally forgot about him.
Getting away in the middle of that is quite a feat.
I look forward to his future.
Now's not the time for admiration.
We don't need a bargaining chip.
If we want Yoshiwara, all we have to do is kill Housen.
Are you an idiot?
If our actions cause a war between Harusame and the Night King,
the higher-ups are going to kill us!
If that happens,
I'll slaughter the higher-ups too.
And after that, are you going to become the Pirate King?
That sounds nice.
If I move up, I'll be able to meet people just as strong.
Yeah, yeah.
We're blessed to have a commander with such... great aspirations.
God dammit.
Where are you going, Abuto?
Let's leave already.
Then go.  Go home before that scary old man kills you.
I can't just leave while I still owe Housen a favor.
We underlings are responsible for wiping the commander's butt.
No, maybe I'll go pave the way for the Pirate King.
Good luck.
This is... a smoke bomb?
They're looking down on us. Are they saying they can't cut down women?
Over there!
I'll hold them back here for a while.
Go on ahead.
Tsukuyo-san!
Do you want to die?
The boss needs to discipline her subordinates.
Hand over your pipe.
It'll be a problem if it disappears with you.
I won't be able to use this.
It may be my last, so one last dra-
No, hand it over.
Gin-san, are you really going to leave her behind?
If you want to smoke that much, come back for it.
Make sure you come back to smoke it.
If you don't make it quick, I'll drool all over it.
Gin-chan...
Hurry, you guys go on too.
Don't make me repeat myself.
Hinowa is the only person I'd ever give up my life for.
I don't have enough lives to throw one away protecting the likes of you.
Go quickly.
That's right.
I'm a guard dog that lays down its life to defend Hinowa.
My sun...
Yoshiwara's sun...
The guiding light of Yoshiwara.
I'm prepared to die.
Come at me however you may,
but I won't let even one of you pass me.
The Guardian Dog of the Sun, Tsukuyo!
Here I go!
Out of the way, dammit!
Hurry! To the Night King!
Seita-kun must be there!
Kagura-chan!
What a surprise.
I was wondering who it was, so it's you guys.
I see you survived.
If the commander heard, he'd be elated...
that there are Earthlings that actually have some muscle in them.
You finally show yourself.
One, two, three.
Assuming I just killed that one, you're still missing one person.
Oi, stop daydreaming!
Who's an Earthling?
Don't compare me to these country bumpkins.
I was born and raised a city girl.