Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I wish you had told me this sooner.
I wish you had allowed me
to share your burden.
If the master's duty is to shoulder
the student along with their pain,
what is the student's duty?
To grow strong enough
to shoulder the master.
You're light...
So light, Master...
I never knew you were so light...
Can you see, Master?
Yes...
I can see...
A moon more beautiful...
than any... I've ever seen...
That's one helluva student.
A student's duty is to grow strong enough
to shoulder the master, huh?
I was always relying on my old man,
so I was never able to do that.
...Same here.
Reconstruction is coming
along smoothly.
Boy, that's a relief.
At this rate, Yoshiwara will be
back to the way it was in no time.
We were able to keep the
damage to a minimum.
And miraculously, there
were no casualties.
Oh, I need to thank that ninja, too.
Will he be coming by again?
He's probably drinking at some
cabaret full of fuglies.
In any case, how has Tsukuyo-san
been doing?
She's recovered from
her physical injuries,
but her emotional scars, well...
She's been in her room
since the incident.
Who can blame her?
She went through so much.
And she also feels responsible.
She believes it's her fault
that this happened.
But it isn't Tsukky's fault.
Should we go cheer her up?
Just leave her alone.
She's been working nonstop
this whole time.
Probably feels like taking
a break for a change.
That's true...
Oh, that's it!
Since she's taking a break,
we should take her out.
It'll be a good change of pace.
Why are you coming up with ideas
that mean more work for us?
I won't do it.
I'm gonna hit the pachinko parlor.
That's a wonderful idea.
Please.
She was always working so she's
never been to the surface.
Introduce her to a place
where she can relax.
Say, Hinowa-san...
Weren't you listening to me?
You're pretty abusive, huh?
Rattling off request after request.
Tsukuyo-chan!
Let's go play!
Hey, wake up, damn it.
We're hitting the pachinko parlor.
You probably got a bunch
saved up, right?
I'll blow it all for you.
Huh? She isn't here?
Forget it. Just leave her alone.
I'm leaving.
I feel like I'm gonna hit
something big today.
...Jackpot?
The hell are you doing?!
["Watch Out For A Set of Women and A Drink"]
I see...
You all thought I was feeling
down from the incident.
Looks like I made everyone worry.
Sorry to cause unnecessary concern.
But as you can see, I'm fine.
You don't need to worry.
Yeah, no kidding.
Too fine, if you ask me.
Great to hear.
Really, that's great to hear.
Uh, we heard that you were too
depressed to leave your room.
Yes, I was somewhat injured.
Hinowa would give me an
earful if I went out to work.
I did a little acting and
pretended to sleep,
before sneaking outside
through a side exit.
Huh?
You were still working after that?!
In that condition?!
Of course.
Yoshiwara has taken a big hit.
I can't be resting, just
because I'm injured.
Besides, even if the illegal
drugs have disappeared,
crime is still a problem in Yoshiwara.
I don't have time to sleep
or be depressed.
Well, I made Hinowa and the
others worry unnecessarily.
I've recovered from my injuries.
I should start working in the open
and show them that I'm doing fine.
There you have it.
Sorry to cause you trouble,
but I don't need a vacation to rejuvenate.
I'm fine now.
Thank you for everything.
I'm too busy right now,
but at some point, I'd like
to properly thank you.
I can't provide much service,
but enjoy your stay.
Tsukuyo-san hasn't changed.
She's still the same.
Never letting anyone else
see her weak side.
She just doesn't know how to open up.
I thought she would have changed
after everything that happened.
I guess people can't change so easily.
She'll let us know when
she's really suffering.
She just puts that off considerably
more than the average person.
But Gin-san...
That just means she's pushing
herself too hard.
Leave her alone.
There isn't anything for us to do.
I wanted to let her take a break.
Guess that won't happen
if she would rather work.
But she'll ruin her health if she
keeps pushing herself like that!
If she won't take a break, we just have
to help her rejuvenate on the job.
There wouldn't be any problem
if it was that easy.
Are you telling her to play around
or drink while working?
What kind of job...
Oh...!
Welcome, savior of Yoshiwara!
Thank you for coming.
Now, come this way.
Um...
I came because I was told there'd
be free drinks, but is that for real?
I'm flat-out broke.
Since I lost at pachinko.
Yes, it's our way of saying thanks.
You've saved Yoshiwara so many times.
Please enjoy yourself tonight.
Whoa, is this for real?!
Are you saying I can have free drinks,
AND also try some seaweed sake?
Oh, don't just stop at seaweed, sir.
Anything from dancing clams
to picking chestnuts.
Hold it! You shouldn't get nuts involved!
I'll end up with a Mont Blanc, you know?!
Cook myself some rice with nuts!
Is that really okay?!
That's fine!
Enjoy yourself all you want.
You know, call me if you ever
need any help again.
I'll come flying at a moment's notice.
I'll cook nut rice at a moment's notice.
Yeah, it's a good thing I didn't
bring Shinpachi and Kagura.
You'll be in this room.
Then please enjoy yourselves.
W-Welcome.
Ah, hello there.
I am the Courtesan of Death, Tsukuyo.
Please enjoy your...
Change!
Change please!
Get me a girl who's more friendly!!
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
Why are you here?
That's my line!
Why are you...!
Nobody mentioned this!
Any drink will taste bad when served
by such a grumpy woman.
Hinowa requested me to perform
this important job.
She said that an important customer
would be coming.
The other girls are busy with Yoshiwara's
reconstruction so they can't help.
Please, Tsukuyo.
Could you at least pour a drink for him?
I was told that this was an important job.
T-those bastards got me good...
So much for providing me service...
They were just using me to
help rejuvenate this woman.
It looks like Gin-san's figured
out what's going on.
I'm sorry, Gin-san.
Tsukuyo isn't the type of girl
to rest during her time off.
I have to use the pretense of a
job to allow her to take it easy.
Please help her relax.
I'm sure that Gin-san can do it.
I can't be sure,
but I assume that Hinowa was
trying to say that serving you,
someone who's saved Yoshiwara
many times,
was also an important job.
That I represent the women of
Yoshiwara in thanking you.
No, I'm pretty sure it's
nothing that formal.
No matter, I also wanted
to show my appreciation.
Is this good enough?
Do I look like a corrupt politician to you?!
What kind of appreciation is that?!
Hinowa would never tell you to do that!
But she told me to provide service.
Not THAT kind of service!
For someone so pure, you
sure know your stuff!
You really are a woman of Yoshiwara!
What am I supposed to do then?
I've never been in one
of these rooms before.
Guess I don't have a choice.
For now, just drink.
A lot's happened,
but for today, just forget it all and drink.
That's your job today.
That's our Gin-san.
He knows what to do.
Oh, she drank.
Mom, she drank.
That's wonderful. This is how
it should be, Tsukuyo.
You can hold your liquor, huh?
She looks like a normal girl now.
You should relax and rest every
once in a while, Tsukuyo.
Hey, don't drink it all. Pour me some.
Man, who's serving who here?
Huh?
Pour.
Pour!
Huh?!
I said there ain't enough liquor!
Bring the whole damn barrel!
Wha-
W-who the hell is THAT?!
She's turned into a completely different
person after one shot?!
She's not just cutting loose anymore!
Something more important just got loose!
Hey, damn it!
How long you gonna lie there?!
Hold it, hold it!!
That definitely isn't a normal girl!
She's acting like a drunk old man!
Gin-chan!
She's gonna kill Gin-chan!
Hey, wake up.
It's too early to get smashed.
The night's only begun.
Yeah, s-sorry...
I suddenly lost consciousness.
Maybe I drank too much.
Th-That's odd.
Maybe I should l-l-leave.
You come to my house and think that
you can leave before the sun rises?
I'm joking. Please forgive
me, Lady Tsukuyo.
I'll accompany you till morning.
I'll kill all the morning birds and
accompany you till morning,
But um, Lady...
When did we start drinking together?
Was there a change at some point?
I was with the Lady to begin with?
You're the Lady, right?
Obviously!
I dressed up and prepared
all this liquor for you today!
I'm gonna kill you, bastard!
I-I never knew...
That she had such low
tolerance for alcohol...
Come to think of it,
I've never let her drink before.
This is way beyond low tolerance.
The alcohol is releasing some
kind of unknown power.
Okay, I'm gonna entertain
you good today.
We've had plenty to drink,
so let's play a game.
Look thataway.
N-No, it's okay.
I'm happy just to drink by your side.
Don't you know this game?
The loser has to remove
an article of clothing.
No, it's okay.
You don't have to push yourself, Lady.
What's that? You don't
wanna see me naked?
You have no interest?
No, that's not true.
But you're drunk right now,
so you'll regret it later.
So you wanna see.
Perv.
Gintoki's a perv.
Such a pain! This lady is
such a pain in the ass!!
Then if I lose, I'll take something off,
so if you lose, you also
take something off...
Like your skin.
Lady, look up the word "fair"
in the dictionary and circle it!
Here we go!
Listen!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Look thataway!
Lady, this is already punishment enough!
Again!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Okay!
Look thataway!
Lady, I still lose when I win!
Rock, paper, fist!
Look thataway and bam!
One more time!
Stand up, damn it!
Rock, paper, scissors!
Tsukuyo's having so much fun.
She looks like an ordinary girl now.
How?!
Okay, let's play cards next.
Hey, the people hiding over
there should join in.
I'll kill you if you don't show yourselves
in three seconds.
Ready? One, two...
No more, please...
Going on patrol?
In the end, you never change.
Say, if...
If I didn't have this scar...
Could I have lived a different life?
You wouldn't be any different.
That's the path you've chosen,
your way of life.
There's no need to regret it.
There's no need to feel any shame.
You, and nobody else, chose
this path yourself.
Walk tall.
Your face isn't ugly.
It's a pretty face carrying a clean soul.
Gintoki...
I'm glad to have met you all.
[Trailer]
[In response to calls from passionate fans,]
[we finally have]
[a movie!!]
[That sword-]
You... That sword...
I wasn't the one who cut him down.
is said to suck human blood.]
Right, Benizakura?
[GinTama the Movie: Benizakura Arc]
[Danger creeps toward Gintoki.]
Gin-san!
[Their name is-]
You think you can win against
Matako Kijima's quick-draw?!
[The Kiheitai]
I don't have a Lolita complex.
I'm a feminist.
What's with this girl?!
[Go quick.]
Elizabeth!
[Shinsuke Takasugi returns]
Don't ever call them my chums again.
There are no warm feelings
between us anymore.
When did our paths diverge?
[Their beginnings were the same...]
We may have started
from the same place.
But we've been looking to
different things ever since.
[Original Story: Hideaki
Sorachi (Weekly JUMP)]
[He's the dumbest samurai
in the universe, bastard.]
The intense fight is bringing back the fighting
skills his body still remembers!
[The excitement returns to the big screen!]
So that is Gintoki Sakata
and Kotaro Katsura.
They are strong...
I'd like to face off with them some time.
Takasugi!
We'll do everything to take you out!
[GinTama the Movie: The New Benizakura Arc
New Translation
Nationwide - Golden Week 2010]
[Note: Golden Week falls under the first week of May]
Uh, what is this?
What? A trailer for GinTama the Movie.
GinTama can finally join the
other popular Jump anime.
Uh, no!
This is that fake movie preview
we used last time!
So after the fake ending scam, we're
going to have a fake movie scam?!
Well, the decision came so suddenly
that there wasn't any time,
and then we were like,
we can just use this.
You're still making excuses?!
Might as well skip the effort and reuse
footage for the movie itself.
Toss in a few new scenes
and you'll fool them all.
That won't work!
Really?
Most of Sunrise's movies
are recompilations.
Like XXXX and XXXX and XXXX.
Those are all Gundam series!
Oops, he said it.
And there you have it.
GinTama the Movie:
The New Benizakura Arc.
Come shake my hand in the theater!
Who's gonna believe that?!
[And so, we have a movie coming up.
Sorry that it isn't a Hollywood production.]
[Adding "New Translation" will make it work.
That's what a certain someone said.]
[See you next time.]