Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Please turn on the lights and keep your distance from the television when watching Gintama. You got thaaaat?!
The Universe, vast and limitless, is filled with many life forms.
As one star dies, another gives birth.
The breath of the vast Universe is passed on from one life to another.
A never-ending cycle.
The mysteries of the vast Universe can never be completely revealed.
At times, it can even bring upon horrific dangers that defy the human imagination.
["Beware of Food You Pick Up Off the Ground"]
Hmm... He's not eating again.
Gin, Sadaharu doesn't have an appetite lately.
He's hardly eaten anything for two days.
He might not be feeling well.
Maybe he's just on a diet.
Males his age do silly things like that just so they can get girls.
Sadaharu's not like that. He's the stoic type.
The last time you said that, he was aroused over some female dog, remember?
[Odd Jobs Gin]
But he usually eats a lot. I'm worried.
Maybe we should take him to the hospital.
Leave him alone.
He's tough. Sprinkle some salt for him to lick and he'll recover.
[Kabukicho Animal Hospital]
It seems there's a shadow in his stomach.
Shadow? Is it something terrible?
Who's behind this?
Is it a shadow ninja, of the Tokugawa...or the Yagyu?
No, not Tokugawa shadows. There's something in his stomach.
Does he have an illness?!
Is Sadaharu sick?!
Will he recover?!
He will recover, won't he?!
Calm down.
He's not sick. There's a foreign object in his stomach.
Foreign object?
Yes. Did you make Sadaharu eat anything odd?
Huh? We haven't fed him anything except basic dog food.
I see.
Then he probably ate something off the ground when you took him for a walk.
Dogs put unbelievable things in their mouths when their owners aren't looking.
Especially since Sadaharu is a large breed, anything can go in.
You need to be careful.
So, this is the shadow.
What could this be? I can't really tell.
Anyway, I'll get him to vomit it out. That'll make him better in no time.
No! Never mind!
Huh? Why?
No, it's because, you know!
If all we have to do it make him vomit, we can do it ourselves.
We're...going home.
No, if it gets stuck in his throat as he vomits it out, it could be trouble.
And depending on the situation, he might require surgery.
We can manage!
We're good at slitting our bellies. We're samurai, you know.
No, not yours.
No, really, it's all right. Just let us go. Don't call the police.
The police?
What're you doing? Hurry and come with us, Sadaharu!
Do you want to be caught?
It's coming out of his mouth!
Gin, from his mouth.
Push it back in!
Sadaharu, open wide.
For now, there doesn't seem to be anything else.
But to be safe, they say he should stay overnight at the hospital.
I see.
I'm worried, so is it okay if I stay with Sadaharu overnight?
Oh, okay.
Why're they so tired?
If it isn't Leader...
Huh? Zura?
Not Zura. Katsura.
What're you doing here?
Don't tell me Sir Sadaharu is not well?
Not as sick as your mind. Don't worry.
I see, I'm glad to hear that.
Zura, what brings you here?
Did you come to an animal hospital because regular hospitals won't touch you?
No, Elizabeth's been lacking energy.
I came here hoping to have her looked at.
The X-rays showed a disturbing shadow.
No, it's just an old man.
Seems she ate something that looked like an old man off the ground during our walk.
No, you're the one who picked up the old man, I bet.
So that's why she'll be having an operation to remove the old man soon.
Taking out the old man means the whole body.
It's no wonder I thought she was behaving strangely.
When I go near her, she smells of aging body odor.
Hey, don't deny the truth.
What you were keeping as a pet is just an old man.
Well,
it's a good thing neither was life-threatening.
Yours is threatened.
After all, you always want to have your pet smiling at your side.
That's true.
I did everything I could, but he was, after all, an old dog.
I don't think his body can withstand any more treatment.
I see.
Kintaro...looks like I won't be able to take him to my Dad.
Is your Father's condition that bad?
Yes. Seems he's not going to make it, either.
Imagine a pet dog and its owner falling ill at the same time.
I see. Your father was really fond of Kintaro.
An old man and his old dog.
They both lost many things, until all that was left at the end was their friendship.
Those fools, are they planning to die together as well?
Doctor, I've got to go see my Dad.
Please look after Kintaro.
Please see to it that he passes on peacefully.
Sorry... Kintaro, I won't say good-bye.
Thanks.
I can't fall asleep.
Zura?
What, are you trying to get in my way by sleeping there?
Huh? No.
I was having a bit of trouble falling asleep.
Here there's a breeze and it seemed like a good place to sleep.
That's true. I'll crash here, too.
I'm sure he wanted his master to be at his side when he dies, not us.
Who knows?
I heard it from the doctor.
It's almost a miracle that he's still alive despite being ravaged to such an extent by disease.
This animal is apparently a loyal dog that supported his master who lived alone for all these years.
He nestled up next to a stubborn old man
who wouldn't even have anything to do with his own children after his wife died.
He hung on until he was this ragged.
When the old man collapsed,
it seems he just flopped down as if to say his job had ended.
No, maybe he is trying to follow his master into the afterlife.
If that's the case, then maybe this is what he wanted.  This tiny samurai.
Zura, that's why they send you to the animal hospital.
What?
I've made up my mind.
I'm going to let this dog see the old man, after all.
Wait, Leader. What're you talking about?
You plan to take a dog in this condition with you?
It can't wait.
You're the only ones who'd be happy that he died
all by himself in a place like this and became a noble tale.
Have you forgotten?
We can try to get them together, but the old man is on the brink of death himself.
That's why I'm sure he's hoping to see each other, too.
Hope to see him? He's already lost consciousness.
It's all he can do just to breathe.
He has no strength left.
The doctor said so himself.
Instead of needlessly making him suffer, let him peacefully...
You...you're...
Does it...mean that much to you?
When a dog is ragged, and writhes in agony, desperately trying live a long life,
the reason why he won't leave his master's side is obvious.
It's because he wants to stay at his master's side forever.
It's obviously because he doesn't want to leave.
Then there's just one final thing we can do for this dog.
I see.
Little Mr. Samurai, I have underestimated you.
A true samurai does not die for his beliefs. He lives for his beliefs, doesn't he?
Okay!
Let's head to where the old man is.
Like hell I will!
After eighteen years of suffering while sealed in by that despicable old man, finally...
Finally, the chains have rotted off!
The time for the resurrection of the King of Terror has come.
Earth has come to an...
Uh-oh, it hurts... Call an ambulance!
[18 Years Prior]
We go back in time eighteen years.
From beyond the far reaches of the vast Universe,
a frightful beam bringing disaster is approaching Earth.
Parasite X.
Feared as the "Planet Eater."
X splits into infinite beams, raining down on the planet.
Parasitically attaching to all life forms,
it controls the central nervous system
and manipulates its hosts' genes, evolving incredibly quickly,
to create a powerful invasion force in the blink of an eye.
Every planet invaded by X is left with a huge scar, as though torn off by a huge jaw.
This is how they got the name "Planet Eaters."
Earth.  Looks like quite a lovely planet.
I tremble with excitement when I think of sinking my fangs into such a juicy planet.
So, which creature should I attach myself to this time?
Looks easy, so this time, I'll go with my eyes closed.
Whatever happens, I'll probably be fine.
I've entered a mongrel that almost died in its mother's womb.
Idiot! I'm an idiot!
Why did I get so carried away like that!
With my eyes closed!
Even my senpai told me the real climb begins just before the summit.
As a result, I was cooped up in a dog house for eighteen years,
spending peaceful days without being able to start on world conquest.
Even then, though, I tried so hard.
Fiddling around with the genes and such, you know?
I tried to evolve, you know?!
But in the end,
all I could do was learn to do the front raise on a bar!
As a final measure, I waited for the old man to die,
but just when I thought I was finally free...
My life reached its limit, as well.
How cruel!
Is there no god or King of Terror in this world?!
All I've ever done is a front raise.
I haven't even learned the glider yet!
Give me back my life!
So what happened is, you attempted to take over the Earth, but failed,
and you were kept as the old man's pet this whole time?
Then the reason you desperately tried to live a long life
wasn't because you wanted to stay by the old man's side and support him, but...
...to conquer the Earth.
I waited vigilantly for the old man to die so I'd be freed from that stupid doghouse.
Excuse me.
Yes?
Nuke this Amanto in the microwave and make a hot dog out of him.
Nooo!
I'm sick of this.
My motivation's down. I'm going home.
Now, wait, Leader.
It's true there's nothing to be gained by helping this dog.
But I'm sure the old man wants to see this dog, despite what it is.
We should finish what we started.
What've we got to lose by letting them see each other?
Planet Eater...
You've done a whole lot of evil. At least before you die...
I've finally found you!
What's going on?
[18 Years Prior]
We go back in time eighteen years.
From beyond the far reaches of the vast Universe,
an intense celestial light is approaching Earth.
Parasite Z, revered as the Planet Pukers.
Z splits into infinite beams, raining down on the planet.
Parasitically attaching to any life form,
they evolve incredibly quickly, exterminating the Planet Eaters and saving planets.
They are, so to speak, the Planet Eaters' counterbalancing force-the allies of good.
When Z saves a planet, it leaves covered in the vomit of its host as it is expelled.
This is how they got the name "Planet Pukers."
Earth.
So the Planet Eaters are trying to eat away this beautiful planet.
We must never allow that to happen.
We will protect this planet without fail and cover it with vomit!
But the question is, what animal shall we counter with?
Looks easy, so this time, we'll go with our eyes half-opened.
Whatever happens, it'll be fine.
Planet Eater... I've finally found the last one of you.
I will...kill you for sure!
What's that? More strange creatures?
That's...
The Planet Pukers!
Charge!
[Oedo Hospital]
I see. Poor Kintaro.
He supported Dad for so long, but I couldn't be there when he dies.
With Dad in this condition, it can't be helped.
Besides, Dad's the one who most wanted to be there when that dog dies.
He was so fond of him.
Not to worry. They'll meet again in the afterlife.
Hey, that's imprudent.
You guys are stressing too much.
You're exhausted because you've been tending to Dad all this time.
Why don't you take a break?
Looks like Dad will be okay for a while.
Are you sure you'll be okay?
Don't worry, don't worry. I'll keep a close watch.
Okay, I'm counting on you.
Alrighty.
This isn't getting anywhere.
What are they? Why're they attacking us?
Planet Pukers...
They're parasites that drive out Planet Eaters like me and protect planets.
Quickly, quickly, get away.
If they catch me, I'll be eliminated.
I had no idea.
I wouldn't have believed that cats and dogs
battled over the fate of the world since ancient times.
No, that's not how it is.
It's just coincidence that I parasitically attached myself to a dog, and they attached to cats.
What should I do?
Dogs...and cats... Both are difficult to forsake.
They're both cuddly balls of flesh and fluffy soft.
Oh...what should I do?
I don't' want either of them to disappear.
Hey, are you even listening?!
All right, I'll make a peace offering.
They're both cuddly balls of flesh-
if they discuss things, they should reach an understanding.
Hey, why're you wasting time talking. Hurry and run.
Listen to me, courageous cuddly balls of flesh.
We have no intention of conquering Earth.
Even without your help, this dog is at the end of his life!
However, we want to let his owner see him once before he dies.
As those who are also of flesh and blood, I'm sure you can understand!
We're strays!
Planet Eater! You came to conquer Earth.
What're you doing living a leisurely life as a kept pet?!
What's the idea of getting them riled up?
I failed to convince them, huh?
Well, that's okay.  At least I got to touch some cuddly balls of flesh.
What're you so happy about?!
What is it with you and cuddly balls of flesh?!
We have no choice.
Now that it's come to this, I'll draw them to me.
During that time, Leader, you go to the old man's place.
Zura, you'd do all that?
I don't want to see cuddly balls of flesh fighting among themselves.
Take care of the rest, Leader!
I have discovered Bushido in a death surrounded by cuddly balls of flesh!
All right, come at me, you cuddly balls of flesh!
With your cuddly balls of flesh...at me...
They ignored him!
[Special Prizes Stefan Goods!! A chance to win 2 weeks in a row!!]
Good grief...
My body's not gonna last if this keeps on.
If you're going to die, Dad, hurry up and get on with it. I mean really.
This is no good.
Time for my walk.
[To be continued]
[Tell me! Ginpachi Sensei!]
Tell me! Ginpachi Sensei!
Okay, today, we have a letter from someone a bit unusual. I'll read it now.
It's a question from Amachi Hideaki of Tokyo.
This is about something that happened a while back.
When I saw an ending where Kagura was running along the beach in Summer,
I wondered about something, so I wrote this letter.
If I'm not mistaken, Kagura is an Amanto belonging to the Yato Clan,
who are supposed to be vulnerable to sunlight.
Basically, wasn't it a given that she always uses a parasol?
I draw a lot of manga myself, and often forget to draw in the parasol.
But is it all right to do that?
It bothers me so much, I can't get on with my manuscript.
Okay, here's the straight answer.
Yes, I do remember.
It's the one where the voice actress of Kagura said
"Who is this cute girl who appears in the ending?"
when she first saw it, right?
That certainly was Kagura running energetically under the sun with her skin exposed.
But she's fine.
Huh? Why is she fine, you ask?
Okay.
Actually, that was filmed in studio.
Adults play so dirty, don't they?
They explain everything that's not going their way after the fact.
Well, then, Amachi! Don't worry so much about details.
Have a manuscript by tomorrow.
[Preview]
Hey, Gintoki!
This one's a multi-part episode, so how about we call it the Bark-Meow arc!
But the Fuzzy-Wuzzy arc is hard to disregard, too.
But there's the Fluffy-Wuffy arc... Maybe the Cuddly Balls of Flesh arc, after all.
Don't bother. It'll end next week.
What?!
The next episode:
"Cat Lovers and Dog Lovers Are Mutually Exclusive"
[To reunite with Kintaro (Planet Eater), the Old Man (Stubborn) makes an implacable comeback.]
[But the Planet Pukers (Cat) hand of pursuit (Cuddly Balls of Flesh) goes dauntlessly after the Planet Eater (Cuddly Balls of Flesh) to corner him (pinch)!!]