Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[You never thought the day would come...]
[Live-Action GinTama!]
[Up next!!]
Man...
After making it to our fourth year,
I've gotten to the point where I want to
throw up every week in April, y'know?
Next thing I know,
one cours is up and done.
[Note: One cours refers to three months
of scheduling. In practice, 13 episodes.]
We managed to continue on despite
all the pain and suffering.
We had to walk home from the station
while holding in a big one,
but we somehow managed to make
it out of the shopping district.
But y'know...
It's a long ways getting home
from the shopping district.
I wanted to give up when
we passed by the park.
The whole "Just use a public bathroom"
idea started to sound pretty tempting.
Oh, not that there's anything wrong
with using a public bathroom.
But it's all about overcoming the temptation
and reaching the washlet bathroom at home.
Right, Shinpachi?
Huh?
Gin-san? Is that Gin-san?
That's right.
It's Gin-san.
Uh, what is this?
What do you mean?
This is GinTama.
Same GinTama time. Same GinTama channel.
The same old GinTama.
Uh, doesn't this seem a little different?
Oh, is this live-action?!
When did GinTama turn
into a live-action show?!
What?! They're mannequins?!
Ah, I thought someone told you.
We're going to become an anime
that transcends anime.
Starting this week, we'll be showing
"Live-action GinTama Revolution:
Love will save Hollywood."
[Note: Parody of the movie
"Dragon Ball Evolution."]
We are not!
[Note: Parody of the movie "Titanic."]
This will leave Shueisha in Titanic status!
A surreal world anime with thirty
minutes of talking mannequins.
"Oh! Gintamikey."
[Note: Parody of mannequin comedy show
"Oh Mikey!" aka "The Fuccons."]
No, this can't be considered
anime anymore.
These are just still-frame photos!
Well, this is basically what happened.
We tried a number of different detours
and then someone said
"Ah, that's right. We haven't
tried doing live-action yet."
So we're doing this on
the whim of the staff.
Got it, Shinpachi?
Seriously?
[Note: Parody of 20th Century Fox.]
I was expecting 20th Century
Box to show up behind us.
Right, Shinpachi?
Geez, why do you purposely
take these risks?
It's pretty damn scary.
You're such a spoilsport, Shinpachi.
That's why you can never
stop being Shinpachi.
Learn your lesson already, Shinpachi.
Uh, what's that even supposed to mean?
And why am I just a pair of glasses?!
Okay, it's starting to rain,
so we'll move indoors.
This show is pretty damn random.
We're going to visit Sunrise's fifth studio
where they make the GinTama anime.
Excuse us, murder license.
[Note: Parody of manga "Murder License Kiba".
Shueisha title serialized in Super Jump.]
Oh. This is where they make
the GinTama anime.
Looks like a dirty place.
This is what is known as the
modern-day sweatshop.
No, it isn't!
Don't ruin their reputation!
What if everybody believes you?!
There isn't much difference.
This is a modern-day sweatshop.
Cancer Beam!
[Note: Parody of GUNDAM W.
anime created by Sunrise.]
There's no cancer or
beam involved here.
The boss is going to be pissed at you!
Uh, Kagura-chan?
What's with the horns on your head?
They're antennas.
[Note: Parody of Chidejika (Digital deer), Japan's official mascot to promote transition to Digital terrestrial television.]
Starting today, I'm the digital conversion
mascot, Digi-Kagura.
That's a complete rip-off!
Okay. Then I'll pitch in.
Don't take your clothes off!
What the hell is this scene?!
This is nowhere near acceptable
for showing on TV!
Then we'll move on to today's main topic.
All analog broadcasting will end in July of
2011 and switch to digital broadcasting.
After that, analog televisions without a digital
tuner will be unable to receive a signal.
There you have it.
Huh?
That's it?
This was just another digital
TV ad, wasn't it?
Why do I have to catch
a cold this time of year?
I'm completely out of sync
with the rest of the world.
[Note: "15 no Yoru" (Night at 15)
is a Yutaka Ozaki song.]
Is my body in 15 no Yoru or what?
I feel like I'm racing along
on a stolen motorcycle.
[Note: A lyric from "15 no Yoru"(Night at 15).
A song about an unruly teenager"s life.]
Hello.
Are you okay, Gin-san?
Honestly...
How could you catch a
cold this time of year?
Hell if I know.
My body went off and picked up some hitchhiking
germs from who knows where.
Y'know?
Since my body's all kind and considerate.
Don't let that hitchhiking
germ spread to me.
In any case, a cold in this
season can be a real pain.
You have to take good care of
yourself or you won't get better.
Gin-chan.
I made some rice porridge.
Eat this and get better soon.
No, he's going to be feeling a different
kind of sick if he eats all that.
That isn't even a normal portion size.
Guess I have no choice then.
I'll help out.
Are you sure you don't just
want to eat it yourself?!
This just sucks.
I feel so crappy that I don't
even care anymore.
How can you say that after a little cold?
Think back.
That newtype influenza was much worse.
Influenza?
That's right.
This cold is nothing compared to that.
Yes... Compared to that...
["If It Works Once, It'll Work Over and Over Again"]
[Winter]
The current outbreak of influenza in Edo
is believed to be a newtype
virus from Planet Onishi.
[Note: Onishi was the first GinTama manga editor.]
We expect the outbreak to
get extensively worse.
Everyone please take care of yourselves.
Sis, I'm coming in.
Yes...
It's starting to snow.
We'll probably have some accumulation.
Are you okay, Sis?
Let me know if you're cold.
I made some rice porridge.
Eat plenty so you get better soon.
Th-Thanks, Shin-chan.
I'll be fine now,
so go to work.
Ah, it's fine.
I just called and he was like,
"You're probably infected already so
don't bother coming, you sicko."
Honestly, that Gin-san...
It's so terrible of him to call you a sicko.
They were probably trying
to be considerate.
That's not possible.
There probably isn't any work.
I'll take the day off.
I also let "Hostess Club Smile" know
that you'd be taking the day off.
I can look after you the entire day.
But it would be terrible
if you caught my cold.
Don't worry.
It's my turn to take care of you.
You look kind of happy.
Ah, uh... Sorry.
That's not it.
I'm sorry.
It's disrespectful to feel this
way when you're suffering.
It's just that, well, we haven't had a chance
to be alone like this in a while.
I-I'm really sorry.
Honestly, you're so hopeless, Shin-chan.
Then I guess I'll depend on you today.
Will you listen to my whims?
Y-Yes!
You can ask for anything!
I'll do it all.
Ah, then I'll go get some more water!
It's dangerous to run.
I'll be right back so sit tight.
Yes? Eh?
I caught a cold.
It hurts...
My head is splitting...
I'll probably...
I'll probably feel better if I
eat some rice porridge...
No, you gotta add egg.
[Note: Takuan is a traditional Japanese
pickle made from daikon radish.]
Pretty sure I won't get better without
rice porridge with egg and takuan...
Uh, why did you come all
the way to my place?
Shouldn't you rest at
home if you're sick?
Why did you come here?
Don't be so cold.
Neither of us can move.
Like, you know, in DQ when a party
of jesters have been paralyzed.
[Note: Parody of Dragon Quest III video game.]
[Jesters - Helpless beings that just play around during battle. But, they never run out of laughs; they're just creepy, popular guys!]
Jesters?
That's a strange analogy,
but in the game, jesters have their minds paralyzed
the second they go on a journey.
[Kintoki suddenly collapses!
Kintoki: *Snore Snore*
He somehow manages to breathe normally!
Kintoki: Ahh... Ahh... I can't move.
Kintoki is bound by evil spirits.]
We used the last of our
strength to make it here.
There can't be much difference between
looking after one person or two or three.
[Note: Spoof of manga "Yoroshiku Mecha Doc" (Mechanical
Doctor). Serialized in Shonen Jump in the 80s.]
I leave the rest to you, Mecha Doc.
Uh, this isn't a church or inn or anything.
[Note: Parody of game "Dragon Quest."]
You won't restore HP or recover from status
effects by staying in a commoner's house.
My body is burning... I'm gonna die...
It hurts...
I might...
I might get better if I eat
some ice cream...
All you've been thinking about is food!
Shin-chan, I'll give you a hand, so let's
make rice porridge for everyone.
No, no!
You just rest!
Aren't you sick?
But I can't just lie down in this situation.
You fool!
Don't push yourself!
Your cooking will lead to death!
For us!
You should take better care of yourself!
That's right.
We just want Sis to live.
We're not asking for anything else.
You two care about me that much?
Fine!
I get it!
I just have to do it, right?!
I just have to take care of
all three of you, right?!
S-Sorry...
Could you make it four?
Sorry...
Could you add another one...?
I didn't think it'd be so contagious...
I came here to take care of Otae-san,
but now I'm being taken care of!
The biggest mistake I've ever made!
But I'm so happy to contract
a virus from Gin-san!
Wreck me hard, why don't you?
Have your way with me, Ginfluenza!
What are you talking about?!
This virus is from Otae-san!
Violate me, Taefluenza!
Harder, Ginfluenza!
Squeal, Taefluenza!
Indulge yourself, Ginfluenza!
Deeper, Taefluenza!
It burns! It burns!
You're too damn loud!
You sickos wanted to take
care of them, my ass!
You were just stalking them!
Why do I have to take care of stalkers?!
Calm down, Shinpachi-kun.
It's long been said that you'll recover from a
cold if you give it to someone else, yeah?
I intended to sacrifice my
body to save Otae-san...
Sis, you okay?
She isn't any better!
She's even worse because the
air's all contaminated now!
Why do all these people have
to gather at our house?!
Nobody will get any better with this much
virus concentrated in one place!
It's fine, Shin-chan.
Sis!
Everybody feels lonely when they're sick,
like they're the only one
suffering in the world.
It feels reassuring to have so many
sick people in the same room.
What are you talking about, Sis?!
These people are sick in a different way!
Their way of life is fundamentally sick!
That's right!
I'm infected by the disease
known as Gin-san!
I can't leave him, until death do us part!
What?!
That means I'm infected by an incurable
disease called Otae-san!
I won't be able to leave
her after I'm dead!
Couldn't you people at least
pretend to deny it?
Shin-chan...
We may fight all the time,
but we're all sick and in
the same boat now.
Let's work hard together to beat this cold.
Yes, Otae-san.
Let's work hard together, Otae-san!
We'll get better and run around
the fields like we used to!
When did that ever happen?
There's a folk remedy I'd like to try.
It involves this green onion...
Ah, green onions are supposed to be
effective against coughs and phlegm.
My mom wrapped one around
my throat when I was a kid.
So what are we going to do?
Otae-san! How much longer
do I have to keep this up?!
Until your fever's gone
and you're frozen stiff.
Sis, he's going to die.
That should help clear up the air.
But the air's too dry.
The virus is going to multiply.
That's it.
I'll water the yard.
Otae-san?!
The snow turned into rain?!
Sis, he's really going to die.
Hey...
Could you shut the door?
It's cold.
I can't stop shivering.
Oh, you're cold?
Then I'll sleep with you.
Huh?
You're supposed to lie naked
together when it's cold.
Ah, wait, hold...
Gin-san...?
Wait, Gin-san!
Y-You can't!
Not that I don't want to...
But you can't!
Not here!
They're all watching!
This... This...
Makes me so excited!
Gin-san!
Do whatever you want!
Shinpachi, don't let any
more sick people in.
Uh... That was really important to me...
Th-That's...!
A large amount of virus is sneaking
in through the door cracks!
O-Otae-chan...
I'm here to see how you're doing...
Now we have someone whose very existence
could be considered a virus!
Huh?
Oh? What's this?
You guys are here, too?
What's this?
You're all sick together?
Honestly...
You're such a weak bunch.
I'm used to living on the streets,
that's why I'm fine as you can see.
What the hell?!
You just threw up blood!
You've got something worse than a cold!
As you can see, I'm just fine.
I don't feel cold at all when
I'm practically naked.
He's wearing the virus.
He's posing with the virus
like it's a winter trend!
This is just a small token,
but please eat it together and get better.
It's a Nagoya delicacy...
What is this stuff covering the Uiro?!
[Note: Uiro is a steamed cake from Nagoya.]
Are you trying to poison us?!
We appreciate the thought,
now scram.
I'm feeling worse.
Don't be like that.
Zura-chi said he'd drop by later.
We can all chat together.
Huh? Katsura-san?
Give me a break already.
Don't bring any more virus in here!
Don't worry.
Despite his looks,
Zura's tougher than I am.
He doesn't catch colds.
That may be true,
but just think, Gin-san.
Kondo-san is here.
Won't it be a problem if he and
Katsura-san see each other?
Man, it's working!
It's really working, Otae-san!
I'd say it's having more of a spiritual
effect than a physical one!
Since I almost lost my dignity
as a human being!
Oh my...
I'm surprised to hear that Kondo-san
had any dignity to begin with.
In any case, it would be bad for
Katsura-san to show up right now.
You have a point.
Excuse me!
Shoot!
We're too late!
Oh, you're here.
Over here! Over here!
Zura-chi!
I'm not Zura-chi.
I'm Ill Smith.
[Note: Wordplay of actor "Will Smith" and "Virus." Japanese
pronunciation of "Virus" sounds like "Wills."]
He's not just sick! He's
turned into Ill Smith!
He's obviously been infected!
Since he's Ill Smith!
Sick to his very genes!
And who the hell is Ill Smith?!
How pathetic of you all to catch colds.
Yes, we can.
[Note: Parody of President Obama's
campaign slogan.]
What country are you the president of?
"Yes, we can," he says.
His character's so random.
That's totally somebody else.
You were infected by this virus because
of the sloppy lifestyle you lead.
Yes, we can.
I don't want to hear that from someone
who's sick to his very genes!
An unbreakable will leads
to the prevention of colds.
[Note: Title of popular song by Namie Amuro.]
Can you celebrate?
What are you saying?
Did the virus get his brain?
Well, I doubt the half-gorilla will
recognize him with that face.
Y-You're right.
Huh?
But that's odd.
Katsura-san's infected to his very genes,
yet he looks perfectly fine.
And there isn't any virus around him.
Hey! Look at that!
That's...!
The virus around Hasegawa-san
is vanishing!
Could it be...?!
Katsura-san is absorbing
Hasegawa-san's virus?!
I-I see...
Damn Zura...
I thought he never caught colds because
his body resisted viruses,
but it's the opposite.
His body absorbs viruses,
which means his immune system
was strengthened to the point
where he can never catch a cold!
That's why he became Ill Smith.
Which means...
M-My body...
I feel better.
Th-This is...
Huh?
A-Amazing...
He cured everybody's cold in no time.
I-It's like he's...
Yes, we can.
A messiah...
A messiah sent from the heavens
to save us from the virus.
Katsura-san, I mean, Ill Smith...
You were actually helpful!
Otae-san!
The green onions worked!
My fever's completely gone!
It's amazing!
You're so amazing!
You should all give it a try! Come on!
That's...!
All of the pent-up virus
is blowing out his ass!
Oh...
It was just a dream...
That's a relief.
Yes, we can.
That was a tough ordeal!
Right?
Like hell!
What's with the forced flashback?!
Why did the flashback start with the
opening and finish with the ending?!
The eyecatch was even
part of the flashback!
Didn't you screw up the timing for starting
and ending the flashback?!
We can't do anything about that.
This chapter was in JUMP in February
Volume 10.
Don't mouth off to me!
Don't snap at me!
And this was too much of a stretch!
[The End]
[Preview]
Why?
Why you?
That's what I should be saying, dimwit.
Shut up! Zip it, mayo baldie!
No, you shut up, poop curls!
The next episode...
"Two Is Better Than One!
Two People Are Better Than One!"
Man, that's good. That's good.
We managed to make it through
this week somehow.
At this rate, we'll make it through
the fourth year in no time.
That won't do, Kagura.
We're only through one cours.
If we relax now, we won't be able to
make it to the washlet toilet at home.
I don't think I can hold on
another three seasons.
Forget it.
I'll just go right here.
So why am I just a pair of glasses?
[Welcome to Anime Town.
It's just outside the Kami-Igusa train station.]
[Note: "Ai Senshi" was an ending theme
from the GUNDAM anime.]
[By the way, the song the music box plays
at noon is "Ai Senshi" (Soldiers of Sorrow).]
[See you next time.]