Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[Toshiro Hijikata has become a hopeless otaku
because of the curse from a demonic sword.]
[What is Kamotaro Ito's ambition?! And
what is Sogo Okita's true intent?]
[NOTE: "NEET" is an acronym that stands for "Not currently engaged in employment, education, or training." In Japan, it refers to unmarried 15 to 30 year-olds who are unemployed, not in school, not training for a job, and not seeking work. A growing problem in Japan.]
The NEET problem, the
hikikomori problem...
The number of apathetic young
people is steadily on the rise.
The people known as "Otaku" are said to
be NEETs and hikikomori in the making.
Today we have gathered one hundred
self-proclaimed otaku.
What do they think when they withdraw
into their inner world?
We will find out what they're really like!!
Otaku Summit: A Live
Debate Till Morning!
[Otaku Summit - A Live Debate Till Morning]
[Note: Spoof of Japanese TV discussion
program "Asa Made Nama TV."]
As usual, we'll be going on until morning.
Oh no! It's started...
Huh? This is odd...
What are you doing?
I've got to tape Shinpachi's gallantry.
Shinpachi?
Come to think of it,
he hasn't come over today.
First off...
I'd like to correct the notion that all otaku
are hikikomori and NEETs in the making.
[53 Idol Otaku - Captain Shimura]
There are otaku amongst us who
work and function in society.
What is he doing?
Ah, I see...
Umm...
Number 31, what's your opinion?
Well...
This show attempts to criticize and blame otaku
for causing Japan's current problems...
All right, all right.
I just want to get other people's
opinions, too...
What's this? He's become
a really annoying guy!
I'm sure the viewers definitely hate him!
First off, it's weird to group
all otaku into one category!
Oh no, it's getting heated! Come
on, where is that piece of junk?!
Now, now... A-Anyway, sit down, okay?
We're supporting a pop idol,
something that's real.
But what I don't understand is...
People who are in love with two-dimensional
girls from anime and games.
Hey! What do you mean
by that, Number 53?!
A two-dimensional girl can never be attained
even if you're in love with her.
It's a waste of time.
No way! Shiori-chan is alive in my heart!
Oh, I have an objection. May I speak?
Go right ahead.
[7 Anime Otaku - Toshi]
Umm... In short, Number
53 is trying to say
that three-dimensional otaku are more realistic
than us two-dimensional otaku.
But let me ask you this...
Do you think supporting a pop idol
will help you get one to marry you?
Well...
You can't, can you?
In other words, us two-dimensional otaku
and you three-dimensional otaku
are both in love with something unattainable.
We're in the same boat.
No, no, you're wrong!
Indeed, it's impossible to marry a pop idol.
But it's not 100 percent guaranteed.
It's 100 percent impossible for you.
No, it's definitely impossible for you.
No, it's not! That's because
pop stars exist in real life.
No, thinking about things beyond
your grasp like that
is absolute proof that you're
not being realistic.
Number 7 sure is annoying.
Go, Shinpachi!!
How dare you talk to
our captain like that?!
What did you say?!
Whoa! The two-dimensional fans and the three-dimensional
fans have begun fighting each other.
It's done.
It's nicely melted!!
You were toasting bread?
Weren't you supposed to be taping this?
Huh? That guy...
I've seen him somewhere...
["Otaku Are Talkative"]
[Shinsengumi Headquarters]
Hey, did you hear what happened
to Hijikata-san?
He was placed under suspension
indefinitely.
He broke one of the Kyukuchu Hatto.
Ito-san insisted that he commit seppuku.
But the Chief and everyone else
persuaded him otherwise.
He's really being forced out, isn't he?
He probably won't be coming back.
Ito won't forgive him. Those two were
always at each other's throats.
It's finally his time to shine, huh?
According to rumors, Okita-san
has sided with Ito's faction.
No one can oppose Ito anymore.
How unexpected.
Okita-kun, I never expected you
to come over to my side.
I heard that you two knew each other
before the Shinsengumi was formed.
I completely thought that you
were part of Hijikata's faction.
Hijikata's faction?
I wasn't aware that such
a faction ever existed.
You're a smart man.
What do you want?
Naturally...
the Vice-Chief position.
As long as you stick with
me, I promise to
grant you that wish.
Is that all right?
It doesn't matter.
I'll give him the position of Vice-Chief.
But if you do that, it'll defeat the
purpose of getting rid of Hijikata.
Shinohara-kun...
Do you think I've started this silly
power struggle with that man
just so I could become Vice-Chief?
[Odd Jobs Gin]
Umm... I'm sorry.
I never expected you to be there...
H-Hijikata-san.
No, it's all right.
I'm just glad my limited-edition figurine...
Tomoe 5000 is safe.
Th-Thank you very much.
Umm... What? Are you
really Hijikata-san?
What are you saying, Mr. Sakata?
[Note: Otaku often call each other by their
last names and the suffix "shi"  (Mr./Ms.)]
"Mr. Sakata"?
As you can see...
I am the real Toshiro Hijikata de gozaru.
[Note: Ending sentences with "de gozaru," (archaic form of "desu") was common amongst samurai and is popular speech among otaku.]
[Shogunate Special Armed Police, Shinsengumi
Vice-Chief Toshiro Hijikata]
"Gozaru"?
Oh, Miss Kagura...
That Chinese outfit!
Are you dressed up as Magical
Girl Chinese Papaya?
[Note: Refers to "Maho Shojo Chukana Paipai."
A live action girly series from the late 80's.]
That's incredibly accurate.
Could I take your picture?
Nice. That's good. One more.
Why are you bashful?
Hey, what's the meaning of this?
He's the real Hijikata-san...but
he's like a totally different person.
Anyway... Hijikata-san...
What is it, Mr. Shimura?
Umm... What happened to work?
You're hanging around here
in the middle of the day.
Work?
Oh, the Shinsengumi fired me.
What? You quit the Shinsengumi?!
Why?!
Well, I started to hate trifling
human relations.
The job was dangerous, too.
Besides, I'm not suited for it.
I originally wanted to become
an anime voice actor.
Really?! Is that true?!
Well, I guess, right now, I'm looking
for a way to get by without working.
I think working is for losers.
He's a NEET!! He's thinking
like a NEET!!
Oh yeah! Come to think of
it, you're like NEETs, too!
Who are you calling a NEET?
Don't group us with them.
How about it? Do you want
to form a group with me?
Right now, I'm writing a
To Love-Ru dojinshi.
Mr. Sakata, you know a
lot about JUMP, right?
Want to make some money
at the Summer Comiket?
[Note: Summer Comiket is a Convention
for dojinshi (amateur comics).]
This won't sell!! This looks
like a kid drew it!!
I'm stumped. I used up most
of my savings on a figurine.
I guess I have to sell my sword.
He's really pathetic! He's trying to sell
his samurai soul to get a figurine!!
I've tried to sell it many times,
but I can't seem to let go of it.
The guy at the store said that it was a cursed
demonic sword, but that can't be...
Oh! Do you think that maybe I'll
wake up in the morning to find
this demonic sword has changed into
a beautiful girl sleeping next to me?
Oh! I'm beginning to love that idea...
[Swordsmith]
This blade pattern on the
front and the back...
There's no mistake. This is Muramasha.
[Note: Spoof of legendary evil sword "Muramasa."]
Muramasha?
[Note: Spoof of legendary swordsmith
"Senko Muramasa."]
It is a famous sword forged by Muramasha Senko,
a swordsmith from the Muromachi Era.
It is said to cut incredibly well.
It is also known as a demonic sword
that devours human souls.
A demonic sword? Is it really
a demonic sword?!
Will a beautiful girl come out of it?!
Well... Umm...
A demonic sword?
What kind of demonic sword is it?
It apparently harbors the grudge
of a hikikomori boy
who was slain by his mother
with the Muramasha.
What kind of demonic sword is that?!
According to legend, the son
never went to school...
And always watched anime. But he said
he wanted to go on a school trip.
As expected, his mother snapped.
Muramasha is the sword she used.
What a realistic legend! That
happened recently, didn't it?!
That sounds like it was on
the news, doesn't it?!
Those who carry Muramasha
at their sides
will become possessed by the
grudge of the hikikomori son.
Their interest in anime and two-dimensional
media will increase,
and their interest in work and fighting
will decrease proportionately.
In other words, he'll become
a hopeless otaku.
But there are many counterfeits
of this sword.
Even if it is a real sword,
there's an even lower chance that
it's the sword of legend. But...
If this is the real demon sword...
There may not be anything left
of that man's original soul.
It's likely the demonic sword has devoured him
and he's already become a different person.
He'll probably never return
to his former self.
Do you understand me, Shinohara-kun?
What do you think is the greatest
misfortune for a warrior?
It's the misfortune of not
being understood.
No matter how much skill you have...
No matter how hard you try, you
will never be judged properly.
You will never be given food
that is suited for your stature.
There is no greater misfortune.
Like Li Mu of Zhao and Yue
Fei of Southern Song...
There were many great generals who
faded away along with their skills...
While serving stupid rulers.
I also never had someone
who truly understood me.
Even when I was called a
child prodigy at school,
or when I mastered the distinguished Hokuto Itto,
I went along with the times and even associated
with Anti-Foreigner Faction members.
But wherever I went, nothing
was satisfying enough.
I never thought that I
would find it here.
That man understands me the most.
That man knows I'm too good
for the Shinsengumi.
He knows that I will not end
up serving the likes of Kondo.
He knows what I thirst for...
My greatest misfortune is that the person who
understands me the most is my enemy.
Well, that's fine.
If there isn't anyone who understands me,
I just have to make everyone recognize me.
The most dangerous man is gone.
All that's left
is to kill Isao Kondo and make
the Shinsengumi mine.
That man... It's as the Vice-Chief said...
I need to tell the Vice-Chief... I need to
let the Vice-Chief know immediately.
You... Could it be?!
My, my, I came to smoke
my last cigarette.
Of all the people to last see...
I've become a total degenerate.
Oh well... This is it for me... I'll cling
onto anything, even straw...
[Note: From the proverb, "A drowning
man will grasp at a straw."]
Listen up. This is my first
and last request for you.
I never expected...
Ito to be allied with them.
I need to tell the Vice-Chief
immediately...
The Vice-Chief ...
Please...
The Shinsengumi...
My... Our Shinsengumi...
Protect it...
Please...
Y-You're...
The Kiheitai... Swordsman...
Bansai...Kawakami...
I-Ito...
You bastard...
You were secretly associating
with the enemy.
Yamazaki-kun, the world won't change
if we keep on sword fighting like you.
We must be smarter.
No matter how much we swing our swords,
we cannot stamp out crime.
Furthermore, you mustn't forget
that if they weren't around,
there would be no use for us police.
I'm sure it would be better for
us to work with each other.
We can become partners who work for each
other's profit and maintain balance.
The Shinsengumi won't become
any stronger if we
continue to do things the
way your superior does.
I will change the Shinsengumi.
It'll become stronger and bigger.
And I, Kamotaro Ito, will become the
spear that shows our potential
to take control of the country.
Do what you want...
But let me say this.
We may be uneducated and can't
tell how skilled you are...
But no one will follow an empty vessel
with no bushido or principles.
I'll follow them...
Until the end...
You'll continue on struggling to inform them
of what you've discovered until the very end.
As their spy, are you saying
that is part of your bushido?
Bansai-dono, I leave the rest to you.
I'll give you the honor of dying in a battle
against an Anti-Foreigner Faction member.
Aren't you glad? You can maintain
that bushido you love so much.
I'll be sure to tell that to your superiors.
No...
I suppose there's no need for that.
They'll be headed to where
you're going soon enough.
There's something going on within
the Shinsengumi right now.
Is that it?
Do you think Hijikata-san was fired from
the Shinsengumi because of that?
Who knows? Well, whatever happens,
it's none of our business.
Let's avoid getting involved any further.
But Hijikata-san asked us
of all people to help him.
Hijikata is very prideful.
For him to put aside his
shame and self-respect,
and ask someone to do something for
him... It must be pretty serious...
Umm...
Excuse me, Mr. Sakata, but...
A rare limited-edition figurine
is going on sale tomorrow.
It's limited to one per customer.
But I want to buy three: one to preserve,
one to look at, and one to use.
So I order you to come with me...
You should get some shame
and self-respect!
"To use"? What are you
planning to use it for?!
I feel stupid for worrying about you!!
[Shinsengumi]
Vice-Chief ...
We finally found you.
Bad news, Vice-Chief!
Come back to the squad immediately.
What happened?
Yamazaki-san... Yamazaki-san...
Someone killed him.
Y-Yamazaki-san?!
We found him on the ground, covered
in blood just outside the headquarters.
By that time...
We still haven't found the killer.
Anyway...
Come back with us to the headquarters.
Huh?
But I was fired...
Now's not the time to be saying that.
Come on, quickly...
Vice-Chief...
Come join Yamazaki...
Damn! They got away!
After them!!
Ow,ow,ow,ow,ow,ow. Mr. Sakata,
the shoulder portion of my denim
jacket is grinding into me!!
My arms feel like they're going to
rip off just like Guts from Berserk!!
[Note: Guts is the main character of Berserk,
a popular manga from Hakusensha.]
Shut up!! You be quiet!!
What was the meaning of that?!
Why is the Shinsengumi after Hijikata?!
Mr. Sakata!
Whoa, Miss Kagura. That was amazing!
[Note: Dr. Slump is a manga by Akira
Toriyama, author of Dragon Ball.]
This is like the return of Miss
Arale from Dr. Slump...
Shut up!! Someone shut this guy up!!
This is Third Squad. This is Third
Squad. Come in. Over.
Did you find Hijikata?
We found him, but we were no match
for his incredibly cute and strong ally.
Over, uh-huh.
"Uh-huh"?
Do whatever it takes to kill him.
Even if we kill Kondo, it'll be
meaningless if Hijikata's still around.
Get rid of all the dangerous elements
before we assassinate Kondo.
Once Kondo and Hijikata are both gone,
the entire Shinsengumi will become
faithful to the Ito faction.
They're planning to assassinate
Kondo-san and Hijikata-san?!
Don't let any other squad members
aside from us find out.
Make it look as if Anti-Foreigner
Faction members did it.
If Ito-san's plan is exposed at this stage,
the Shinsengumi will be split in two.
Kondo's assassination
looks to be a success.
Right now, he's on a train
heading to an expedition
to recruit squad members,
just as Ito-san planned.
All of the squad members
with him are allied with us.
He's by himself...
Kondo is
going to hell.
[Note: Also known as Musashi Province. Today, it
comprises of Tokyo, Saitama and part of Kanagawa.]
It's been a while since I've
gone back to Bushu.
That's where Toshi, Sogo and I grew up.
It was a rough place where
there were always fights.
Come to think of it, it's no different
from what we're doing now.
Sometimes I get anxious.
I could have been a better
guy back then.
I could have advanced a little.
You're a wonderful samurai.
I've never met a person
more honest than you.
I suppose I could call you immaculate.
You're like a white cloth.
You accept anything and
are colored by all colors.
The Shinsengumi
is a flag made of a white cloth onto which
everyone may project his colors.
In comparison, my color is black.
I'm not colored by anything,
and I turn everything black.
Only black remains, no matter where I go.
Everywhere I go becomes my color.
Kondo-san, I'm sorry.
Your flag has become pitch black.
As expected, Sensei.
You say interesting things.
We've become pitch black?
I see. That would be true
if I were a white cloth.
But I'm...
a loincloth that's full of frizzy hair. A white flag?
I'm not that naïve.
I don't know about those around
you, but they're different.
They can't be called a color.
If anything, they're grime.
They're stains that you can't remove,
no matter how much you wash.
They're persistent and can't
be removed by washing.
I ended up becoming attached
to them. It's a real bother.
But the stains began to gather, and as
time passed, they became visible.
Before I knew it, they'd become
a splendid flag.
They're uneducated and have no ideals.
They act according to emotion
more than logic.
I don't often know what they're thinking.
They're mysterious guys.
Sensei, you...
can't control them.
They can't be colored or
affected by anything.
Okita-kun, what are you doing?
You're supposed to be keeping watch.
What are you doing?
I'm asking you what you're
doing, you piece of shit.
Okita-kun...
How dare you talk like that to Ito Sensei?!
Let go.
I said, let go of him!!
[To be continued]
[Preview]
Hijikata-san!! Get a hold
of yourself, Hijikata-san!!
It's none of my concern...
It's of no concern...
At this rate, you may lose all the
people and things you hold dear!!
["There's a Thin Line Between
Strengths and Weaknesses"]
[Ito has been in contact with the Kiheitai. His plan
is to assassinate Kondo, the Shinsengumi's Chief.]
[Hijikata has become Toshi. Gintoki and the others
drag him along as they chase after the train!!]]