Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I can no longer see...
Doman, it appears that I've
lost sight of myself again.
I no longer have a need to watch over all!
I only want one thing...
I only want to see her smile...
That's all.
Come get me, Doman!
I shall show you the true power of the head
of the Ketsuno clan, Seimei Ketsuno!
["Never Losing That Smile"]
What incredible power!
Seimei has gathered the power
that was used to protect Edo!
Team Shirino's shikigami
was instantly eradicated!
Soan has lost his will
to fight and run away!
Only Doman remains!
Doman!
Seimei...
Seimei!
Rin, Pyo, To, Sha, Kai,
Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen!
Mystic counter!
Mantra of Victory!
Mystic seal!
Spell return!
A furious exchange of blows!
The arena is falling apart!
It's like we're watching Dragonball!
Seimei, I will not lose!
I will never lose!
It's futile, Doman.
Your power alone will not
be enough to defeat me!
namaH sarvatathaagatebhyaH
sarvamukhebhyaH, sarvathaa traT...
But Doman is already chanting
another spell!
You have a bad habit of getting so excited that
you lose sight of everything else, Doman.
I'm going to wake you up!
Silence!
Acala Vidyaraja!
Wow!
Doman is surrounded by
a swirl of flaming wards!
To cast so many wards simultaneously!
Such an amazing display of power!
Seimei...
I shall incinerate you with an
infinite number of flames!
Doman.
Don't make up numbers.
Rounding 103 wards wouldn't
give you an infinite number.
I should mention that I'm using 1,562.
Nowhere near infinity.
What an incredible number!
Seimei has surpassed Doman
by controlling an infinite...!
Correction, by controlling 1,562 wards!
It's almost like a giant wall of fire!
Seimei... You...
Doman, this is the difference
between our heart's wish!
Overwhelming!
Now that Seimei has unleashed
his true power,
Doman is unable to fight back!
Doman has been swallowed
in a giant flame to burn!
Is the match over?!
Doman...
Doman, what are you doing?
You're so hopeless.
Staying up late again.
But I can't fall asleep.
Very well.
I shall tell you another old tale.
Yay! What are you going
to tell me about today?
Kintaro slaying Gedomaru?
Or Momotaro?
No, I have an older story to tell you.
Long, long ago, an evil
god lived in the capital.
The brutal god, Antenmaru, shrouded
the capital in dark clouds
and tortured the people
with an eternal rain.
However, Antenmaru was sealed by the
mysterious power of two travelers.
The skies cleared above the capital and the emperor
showed his appreciation for the brothers
by granting the name Mikado, as protectors
of the capital, and made them his servants.
The Mikado brothers were very close,
and they were able to drive away
all forms of wickedness.
Their strong bond kept the capital safe.
But something happened to fracture their bond,
where demons had been unable to strike.
The younger Mikado brother was in love with
the emperor's sister, the lovely princess.
However, the princess lived in a different
world from the Mikado brothers.
The younger brother's love was
a sad one that could never be.
The younger brother kept his feelings
for the princess secret
as he could only watch
over her from afar.
That was when a shocking piece
of news reached his ears.
The princess had been kidnapped.
The kidnapper was...
His older brother.
Yes, the older brother was also
in love with the princess.
Sadly, they had fallen in love with each other
without the younger brother knowing
and eloped, abandoning their
position and prestige!
The emperor was absolutely furious
and declared that the older
brother be tried as a traitor.
And the younger brother was
chosen to track him down.
The younger brother set off on
his search with a heavy heart...
But his older brother was living
happily with the princess...
And when he saw their baby, his heart
was overcome with darkness.
The next thing he knew, the two of them
were on the ground before him.
The two people he loved most.
He spared the baby because he could not bear
for his heart to be blackened any further.
Once he returned to the capital, he was named
to a high position in the government.
But despite his prestige, despite his beautiful
wife, his heart remained clouded.
Rain continued to fall on the
capital, as it did in his heart.
And the younger brother finally realized.
That he was causing the rain...
That he had become a demon...
The darkness had spread from
his heart to the rest of his body,
transforming him into the evil god he
and his brother had once sealed,
Antenmaru!
Antenmaru had been biding his
time after they sealed him,
before possessing the younger brother through
his jealousy, hatred, and negative feelings,
all while plotting revenge.
However, it was too late
by the time he realized.
An arrow was fired into his hideous face.
There stood the son of his brother,
whose life he had spared.
And thus, the clouds which had
shrouded the capital cleared.
However, a new dark cloud was born.
The son of the older brother
slew the revived Antenmaru
and entered the Emperor's service,
founding the Ketsuno clan.
[Ketsuno]
And the children of the younger brother
who were chased from the capital
and had their name taken,
the Shirino clan.
[Shirino]
The holy gate, Mikado, which
had once guarded the capital,
was split in half like a dirty ass.
And thus began the long struggle
between Ketsuno and Shirino.
A spiral of growing hate...
How am I supposed to fall asleep
after hearing all that melodrama?!
Now listen, Doman.
No way!
You're going to tell me to
fight Seimei-kun again!
So it's true that you've become
friendly with the Ketsuno boy.
I don't care about the past!
Don't force your family feud onto us!
Seimei-kun's a really nice guy!
He taught me how to curse
my enemies today!
Once the two of us take over, the Ketsuno clan
and Shirino clan will get along together!
We made a promise!
You fool!
Can you not understand the grudge our ancestors hold
for having their position and prestige taken away?!
Get along together?
That will never happen!
If you have time to learn how to curse
your enemies from an enemy,
curse that boy to death.
If you don't end your
relationship with him,
our relationship as father
and son ends here.
What's that?!
The mystical mark on Doman-san...!
It's too bad.
I thought we could become best friends.
Hey, you hear?
Our young master was beaten
up by the Ketsuno kid again.
No chance there.
That kid's said to be the greatest prodigy
the Ketsuno clan has ever seen.
Adults can't even beat him,
and he's still young.
Man, what a terrifying kid.
Completely different from
our craven young master.
I have to worry about our future when
our next head is so pathetic.
Honestly, I envy the Ketsuno clan.
You fool!
You have the nerve to crawl
back to this house!
You have shamed our clan!
I told you not to return
until you defeated him!
Hate him!
Envy him!
Despise him!
We are armed with a millennia of malice!
Change that hatred into power!
Take everything back, even if it requires
you to become a demon!
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
My brother doesn't know
how to hold back.
Oh no...
You're bleeding from your butt.
You can use mine.
Help one another when in need, right?
["Rorie"]
[Note: This is a play on "Laurier",
a woman's sanitary napkin brand.]
What is this?!
The writing on Doman's
face is spreading!
That's?!
Doman.
Surrender your body to me!
The ones who banished your family from
the light to the dark should be hated!
Should be destroyed!
Why do you hesitate? Why do you wait?
Surrender your body, just as it happened
a thousand years ago!
I'm sorry...
Today's that day...
Recall!
The magma of hatred
sleeping deep within!
Hey, Christel.
We're out of paper.
Okay, then I'll leave some out here.
That's all you ever have!
Never forgive the ones who
took everything from you!
If you can never have what you want,
destroy it all!
Soak into darkness!
Doman...
Did you channel yourself
into a shikigami?
No.
That is not a mere shikigami.
Lord Seimei, that man...
Has allowed his hatred to drive him
into summoning something terrible.
Don't tell me that's...?!
The most evil of gods, sealed by
the Ketsuno and Shirino clans
a thousand years ago
after a desperate fight.
Antenmaru.
Antenmaru, you say?!
The demon who almost destroyed
the capital a thousand years ago...
The strongest of the wrathful gods which
was sealed by our predecessors,
the Mikado, after many battles...
Why is it here?!
It was revived.
That man was driven by negative
feelings to seek power
and dabbled in the forbidden arts.
He's awakened the slumbering Antenmaru
and given his own body.
Turn his own body over to a demon...
How could he do this?
You intend to repeat the tragedy from
a thousand years ago, Doman?!
Lord Doman! Get a hold of yourself!
What's going on?!
No! He can no longer differentiate
between friend and foe!
Everyone run!
Wake up! Doman!
My spells don't work!
Lord Seimei!
Shinpachi! We don't have
time to worry about rules!
Darkness...
Overwhelming darkness capable of even
swallowing Lord Seimei's spells...
It consumes Doman's negative
feelings to grow stronger.
It can no longer be stopped...
It won't stop until it has shrouded
everything in darkness!
Lord Seimei!
Stay back!
Gedomaru! Kuzunoha!
Take that man and his
friends and escape!
Lord Seimei!
Gedomaru?!
It's too early to give up.
This man has yet to play his role.
What are you saying?!
Continue treating him.
His right ball is more or less healed.
Lord Seimei wasn't able to
stand against that thing!
What could this man with
no balls possibly do?!
It's true that he has no balls...
But this man...
...has a soul that can never be crushed.
What are you doing?!
Don't push yourself!
Your left ball is still crushed!
It's just as she said, I'm good to go...
Help keep my balance...
Speaking of which,
it's time for me to use this baby.
Got a rendezvous with a demon.
Spruce it up a bit.
Something flashy enough
to stick up its dirty ass!
What are you doing?!
There isn't time to worry about
which side you're on!
At this rate, the Ketsuno clan, Shirino
clan, and all of Edo will be wiped out!
Help him out!
You may have had your differences,
but you were all trying to protect Edo!
Didn't I tell you to escape?!
Sister lover!
Hold on!
We're coming to help!
This is the fate of those born
to Ketsuno and Shirino.
We may struggle, but we cannot
escape a millennia of karma.
Our ancestors destroyed one
another over a woman.
Our ancestors took from yours,
and threw you into the darkness...
And I have repeated that mistake.
However, Doman...
I can not allow a woman to
die because of our fight!
And Doman...
I won't let you die!
I am the only one who needs to die.
Doman, I knew that you
had fallen for Christel.
That you were suffering from the mess
created by your feelings for her,
animosity toward me, pressure
from your clan, and whatnot.
I thought I could ease your suffering...
A time would come where the three of us could
laugh together, that's what I thought...
But in the end, I only hurt
Christel and you...
Fate is beyond our control, Doman.
I may know a thousand different spells,
but I don't know a single way
to make up with a friend.
I was the one who pushed
you into that state.
It is my duty to take it all in.
Throw me all your hatred, sadness...
I'll accept all of your darkness.
My life would be a cheap price to pay to
end this stupid thousand-year-long fight...
Let's end this, Doman.
You must not lose yourself like your
ancestor and attempt to destroy all!
Come back to us, Doman!
Remember!
Was the woman you loved meant to
stand in the rain under a dark sky?
Was the Christel you loved...?
The Christel we loved...?
Seimei-san!
Descendant of Mikado.
It is too late.
Your voices cannot reach him,
now that I have swallowed him.
I laugh that a weakling consumed by darkness
would ever think to control my power.
However, his negative
feelings served useful.
I'll gladly be taking them.
And thus, Ketsuno and Shirino, the two despicable
Mikado bloodlines, have been destroyed.
However, my thousand-year-long
curse will not end!
I will not allow a single
drop of Mikado blood,
responsible for sealing me,
to exist in this land!
What?!
Who are you...?!
Just a fan.
[To Be Continued]
[Preview]
Not losing to the rain.
Not losing to the wind.
Not losing to the storm.
All while never losing that smile.
"That's How I Wish To Be,
Beautiful And Strong."
[Gintoki, blast away Antenmaru and the feud
between the Shirino and Ketsuno clans,
to get Ms. Ketsuno smiling again!!]
[Next time, the conclusion of the Onmyoji arc.]
[See you next time.]