Edited at https://subtitletools.com
I came after hearing about
a corpse-eating demon...
Would that be you?
A rather cute demon.
Did you also take that from a corpse?
A single child stripping corpses
to protect himself, is it?
That's very impressive.
However, you no longer need that sword.
A sword that's only swung in self-defense,
while fearing others,
should be thrown away.
I shall give you my sword.
If you wish to learn how
to properly use it...
Then come with me.
Hey...
Get your hands off her.
Get your stinkin' hands off this woman.
Y-You're...?!
Gintoki...
Why did you...
come here...?
["The More Precious the Burden, the Heavier
and More Difficult It Is to Shoulder It."]
Look at yourself...
I told you to run...
You fool...
I won't be dying.
Nobody will be dying.
I won't let anyone die in Yoshiwara.
You see...
We aren't gonna leave you all alone.
You followed my threads
to find this place?
Commendable.
[Note: A reference to Ryunosuke Akutagawa's
"The Spider's Thread"]
They say one climbs the spider
thread to reach for paradise...
Instead, you climb up to reach for hell.
Your idiocy would leave Buddha
and Enma both speechless.
Wait, Gintoki...!
Don't bother telling me to run again.
Trying to shoulder the burden
all by yourself?
Don't be such a stranger.
Weep and ask for help.
Lean on me with your runny nose.
Cry when you feel like crying.
Laugh when you feel like laughing.
When you're tearing up with an ugly face,
I'll give you a good cry
with an uglier face.
When you're laughing so
hard your stomach hurts,
I'll laugh in a louder voice.
That's how it should be.
It's far better to get dirty while
living true to yourself,
than to throw away yourself
and die a clean death.
You offer to carry her burden?
You will help carry Tsukuyo's burden?
Don't you understand?
You are Tsukuyo's burden.
You people are the reason Tsukuyo
has suffered so much.
The reason she's grown so hideous.
Tsukuyo, you must be hungry.
I shall prepare you a top class meal.
Of the pathetic worm who followed
the moon into my web.
I don't give a damn about
who you've betrayed.
Do whatever you like to the
Shogun or any other lords.
But you called yourself her master
and then you betrayed your student...
who's believed in you
since she was a kid...
Who's followed in your
footsteps for so long...
You made her your prey.
You don't deserve to call
yourself her master...
You don't deserve to
call her your student.
Get lost.
Don't ever show your face around
her again, you sick son of a bitch!!
This man...
His eyes aren't that of a prey.
Nor the eyes of a meal.
My threads are quivering.
My web is reacting to an
unprecedented invasion.
That's...
Those eyes are...!
Jiraia...
You're the one who's been
caught in a web.
My web.
Now that you've made
a mess of my place,
don't expect to leave alive.
Spill your rotten gut as you die!
A battle between hunters?
Amusing.
I'll show you who the
master of this web is.
Any place with my threads, be it the
six realms, shall be part of my web!
You cannot catch me with those injuries.
Do you intend to escape outside?!
Fool!
You're the fool.
Gotcha.
Now, time for supper.
Let's dig in!
If you wish to learn how
to properly use it...
Then come with me.
From now on, you will swing that sword.
Not to cut down your enemies.
Not to cut away your weaknesses
and protect yourself.
But to protect your very soul.
Gintoki!
How...?
How can you have power that rivals mine?
By someone unable to abandon
their sense of self...
By someone who can't even sever their ties,
just to have a place to return to...?!
I have sacrificed everything...
My sense of self, my home,
even my comrades...
All for my prey...
For you...
Yet why...? Why?!
You still can't understand?
Some of the things you sacrificed
were too important.
You abandoned your comrades?
No.
You were afraid of losing your comrades.
You fought alone?
No!
You wouldn't have to feel the pain of solitude
if you'd been alone to begin with.
You abandoned your sense of self?
No.
You were running away from the pain
you caused and the pain you endured.
You're just a coward!
She's far stronger than
you could ever be.
A coward is enough to deal
with another coward.
I'm enough to take you.
Silence!
You don't have the right to
call yourself her master!
You don't have the strength to shoulder
a student and their pain!!
Gintoki...
Let's go back.
To your home...
Jiraia! Stop!
Give up already.
There's nothing in your web.
This whole time, there was only
ever a pathetic little spider,
spinning threads into the sky while
gazing at the distant moon.
What are you babbling about?
I already knew that long ago.
Stop! Jiraia!
Yes...
This is how...
How it should be...
The spider will disappear
in a pool of blood.
It doesn't...
feel as good as I expected...
to be killed by myself.
I want to kill myself.
Jiraia, were you...?
Jiraia, your final prey...
was you yourself, huh?
Your goal wasn't to kill the clone
you'd raised and trained.
It was to be killed by your beloved
student, as yourself.
Th-The boss's son, is it...?
We met once before.
Have you come to avenge your
father and comrades again?
I lost interest in revenge a long time ago.
I have no interest in crushing a spider
who's fallen to earth.
...Danzo.
So you've done your research.
Jiraia the Spider.
Real name: Danzo Tobita.
Born to a country samurai in Iga and mastered
ninja techniques at a young age.
Your natural aptitude had people
calling you a prodigy.
The samurai in Iga were
fighting year round.
The Tobita family was one
of the larger families in Iga.
With such a talented son in line to take over,
its foes weren't going to stand by idly.
The only survivors were you
and your still young sister.
You felt ashamed of the skills which kept
you alive while everyone else was killed.
With the life of your only remaining
family hostage,
you were forced to swear fealty to your hated
enemy, what would have been your prey.
That gave birth to your twisted
sense of devotion.
Sacrifice oneself for the country.
You literally sacrificed your sense
of self to devote yourself to work.
No, you had no choice.
Your only escape from the hate,
sorrow, and shame of serving the ones
who exterminated your family
was to forget your identity and focus on mechanically
carrying out mission after mission.
You used that intoxication
to escape the pain.
However, your sister couldn't bear
seeing her older brother like that.
No more... No more.
Stop pushing yourself for my sake.
Dear brother, live your own life.
Live freely for yourself.
Your sister took her own life.
After all the prey you took,
all the pain to your body,
you still couldn't protect your sister.
To this very day, you're still
haunted by that fact.
And so you attempted to kill yourself
in the worst possible way.
You would become the enemy of
the beloved student you'd raised,
and die by her hands.
That was your self-inflicted punishment
for failing to protect your sister.
No...
I was just scared.
Just as you said,
I was scared of losing anything else...
A coward who was too scared
to bear the burden.
That is why I became drawn to her.
I wanna protect Yoshiwara and Hinowa!
The child who tried to shoulder
everything on that small back...
That was why I taught
you everything I knew.
I didn't want you to be hurt...
The way I was...
If we are doomed to experience
the suffering from a loss,
then why shoulder the
burden to begin with?
No need for a home or comrades...
But you defied my expectations...
You've managed to find
friends... a home...
You possessed a strength I never did.
The strength to not run away from the pain
you caused, the pain you endured...
I was scared of losing
someone else again...
You were headed somewhere
far away from me...
I...
...was trying to draw you back...
To the same fate I suffered...
In the end, I wasn't protecting
you or my sister...
I was only protecting myself...
And I became tired of myself.
That was all...
I planned on never shouldering
another burden,
yet I'd managed to do it again.
I planned on never forcing anyone
else to shoulder my burden,
yet I'd managed to do it again.
Tsukuyo, I forced you to shoulder
a worthless burden.
I am sorry...
I wish you had told me this sooner.
I wish you had allowed me
to share your burden.
We would have been able to
arrive at a different answer.
If the master's duty is to shoulder
the student along with their pain,
what is the student's duty?
To grow strong enough
to shoulder the master.
You're light...
So light, Master...
I never knew you were so light...
Can you see, Master?
Yes...
Yes...!
I can see...
A moon more beautiful...
than any...I've ever seen...
That's one helluva student.
A student's duty is to grow strong enough
to shoulder the master, huh?
I was always relying on my old man,
so I was never able to do that.
...Same here.
[Preview]
Tsukuyo-chan!
Let's go out and play!
Hey, wake up, damn it.
We're hitting the pachinko parlor.
You probably got a bunch
saved up, right?
["Watch Out For A Set of Women and A Drink"]
I'll blow it all for you.
[Ohh! JUMP-san!! Don't use profanity
in the important parts!]
[See you next time.]