Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Prisoner 3-2034.
Kohei Tanaka.
A vicious serial killer who murdered
35 Bakufu employees.
Also known as Kohei the Manslayer, a leader in the
Akatsuki faction of the radical Anti-Foreigner Faction.
Surrounded by over forty Bakufu officials,
with a dozen cuts on his body,
he didn't bat an eye as
he killed seven officials.
After being captured, he has
yet to respond to torture,
and we haven't been able to
get him to open his mouth.
No, that would be the
wrong way to put it.
His mouth is definitely open.
In fact, it's been open the whole time.
He never stops smiling, regardless
of the torture he's going through.
He's always smiling like
he's enjoying it all.
["It All Depends On How You Use
The 'Carrot and Stick' Method"]
The suits have given us
a real pain to deal with.
There have been reports of a large-scale terrorist
attack in the works by the Akatsuki faction.
He must know the details.
And we're supposed to
force it out of him?
Yeah, pretty much.
Can you do it?
I doubt we'll be able to make
him talk through torture.
Look at that masochistic face.
Does he look like someone in a desperate situation
after being captured by the enemy?
He isn't thinking about how
to get out of this situation.
He's enjoying the situation.
He must have been trained
to take torture.
He doesn't reject pain.
He's probably learned
to seek and relish it.
We could cut off an arm or leg,
and he would keep on smiling like that.
So it's impossible to pressure
him through pain.
Still, what do we do, Toshi?
There's more to an interrogation
than going on the attack.
We'll use the "carrot and stick"
technique to make him talk.
Lose the mindset of forcing
information from him.
We're going to get close
to him and snatch it.
So you want to win him over...
How exactly are we supposed to
get a serial killer to warm up?
If someone like him had been in my class, I
wouldn't have wanted to be friends with him.
I would have graduated without
saying a word to him.
It's fine.
When you're about to graduate, the people
you couldn't stand all look like nice people.
Uh, how is it fine?
What are we graduating from?
Hijikata-san, this is your chance
to make a friend.
Do you intend to end three years of school
without ever lifting your head off your desk?
Don't talk about me like I'm
some sorry, lonely guy!
You'll never make any friends if you
aren't willing to approach anyone.
Physical exams are a great time
to try, with everybody hyped up.
"Oh? You wear briefs?"
You know, something along those lines.
Who are you accusing
of wearing briefs?!
Go for it!
Be brave, Toshi!
Open his heart!
Open his briefs, Toshi!
Hey! Why are you trying to
push the dirty work on me?!
Yamazaki, you go.
You wear briefs, right?
Get going.
No, I wear boxers!
Shut up.
You might as well be wearing briefs.
You ooze lameness...
No, wait...
We don't even know if he wears briefs...
Stop wasting time and get going!
Open!
Open his briefs, Zaki!
Ow-ow-ow...
S-Scary!
This guy's really creepy up close!
Like he's going to jump me at any time!
Zaki, carrot and stick.
Mercilessly pressure him, while offering
gentle words of comfort.
Use the tsundere principle
to catch his heart!
[Note: A character archetype, where a rough person suddenly becomes sweet, under certain circumstance.]
Calm down.
His arms and legs are chained
together so he can't move.
And everybody's watching me through
the two-way mirror behind me.
I'll start with a threat.
He's looking down on the police.
I won't be able to accomplish anything if
I can't get that smug smile off his face!
Fuck it, patchwork baldy!
How long you gonna keep playin' it cool?
Don't mess with the police, mothafucka!
We don't have all day here!
The anime's on its fourth year, with our
stock of original material running out!
We get manga manuscripts
faxed over every week!
We're on the ropes!
Everybody's stressed out to the limit!
We don't got time to waste on
a guest character like you!
So cut to the chase and spill your guts!
What's he talking about?
[Note: Refers to the recently released "Dragon Quest IX".]
I wanna play DQ too!
I haven't beaten it yet!
But I'm sucking it up and
working my ass off!
I have to deal with people like you
instead of doing what I want to do!
Hey, isn't he just bitching now?
Damn it!
Why can't I get a job like the one
Kochikame's Akimoto has?!
[Note: Osamu Akimoto is the manga artist of "Kochikame (Kochira Katsushika-ku Kameari Koen Mae Hashutsujo)," a very popular police manga/anime.]
What is he doing?
He's not even looking at the suspect.
He's just channeling the author
of this manga now.
I watched Binetsu Tairiku!
[Note: Binetsu Tairiku is a parody of the Japanese TV show "Jyonetsu Tairiku."]
I was all pumped up to
work after watching it,
so I sat down at my desk,
but it was no good!
I can't be like you! I'm worthless!
Yeah, we don't care.
Cut it out.
This isn't a place for Sorachi to repent.
[Note: Hideaki Sorachi= original
manga author for Gintama.]
I'm just... I'm just...
This is the theme from Binetsu Tairiku...
The Taro song...
You...
You are certainly a failure of a human.
What?
Like you're one to talk.
I'm not referring to your
tardy work habits.
I'm talking about how you gaze at the
top of the mountain in servitude.
The path to the top will only grow
longer if you belittle yourself.
A mountain peak does not exist
to show how small you are.
It's there to provide you with a goal.
If you have to wander down a side path,
you should take your time
to slowly climb up.
The mountain you call Akimoto-san
was the product of thirty years.
[Note: Tanaka is using a mountain metaphor to describe the Kochikame manga artist. "Kochikame" has been in Weekly Shonen Jump since 1976. ]
It won't be an easy climb for you.
You must be prepared
to spend thirty years.
Step by step, as steady as a turtle...
[Note: Part of the manga title "Kochikame"
is "kame", which is turtle.]
It's possible that you'll
never reach the top.
You may burn out halfway.
However, you'll still have a better
view than you do now.
Thank you very much.
If you'll excuse me.
What did you go in there for?!
Why did you fall for his carrot?!
Why did you let him use
the stick on you?!
Why were you the one
who spilled his guts?!
You're supposed to get the
suspect to spill his guts!
Still, I was able to get close to him.
He burned me a DVD of Binetsu Tairiku.
He's the one who won you over!
Hey, Yamazaki.
Lend me that.
Now, I'll always be able
to see the rare scene,
where the interviewers ask kind Mr. Akimoto
what he's most angry about right now,
[Note: Refers to the documentary Jyonetsu Tairiku (Passionate Continent - Documentary). Osamu Akimoto was featured in February 2009.]
and he gives his long answer in the interview.
How could you enjoy that?!
It must have been a really long interview
to make Mr. Akimoto say that.
Rewatch the part where he's
interviewing the interviewers!
Yamazaki, you let him
pull a fast one on you.
I can't believe you let yourself
be lectured by that murderer.
Pathetic...
He'll be a tough nut to crack.
Okay. I'll go next.
That's enough threatening.
I'll go with carrot.
[Note: Parody of the police TV drama "Hagure Keiji
Jyunjyo-ha (Rogue Detective Naïve Type).]
Just like the rogue detective.
Detective Gorilla: Empathy Type.
I'll use empathy to sway him over.
It says Detective Gorilla. You're a gorilla.
You've strayed from the human race.
Chief, take care of my daughters
if anything happens to me.
Where's the chief or your daughters?
Detective Kane.
[Note: Parody of Kane Kosugi, the son of martial art star Sho Kosugi. He appeared in many physical challenge shows.]
You should learn to act
before you learn action.
Yeah, whatever happened
to Detective Kane?
You're probably sick of the prison slop.
I've brought you something
special today.
Eat as much as you want.
It's Gorilla's special katsudon.
[Note: Katsudon (Fried pork cutlet and egg on rice) is often used in Japanese police TV dramas as a prop to convince hungry suspects.]
The katsudon might be
considered empathetic,
but the way he's feeding
it to him is anything but.
Eat up.
The exact opposite, in fact.
All right now...
Fact is, I have a son your age.
Hey, Detective Gorilla!
How old are you supposed to be?!
That makes your son an old man!
You remind me of my son.
I wonder where he is now...
He said something about studying
action in America...
How did Detective Kane
become your son?!
There was a period when he
went down the wrong path...
He'd be immersed in dangerous
bodybuilding shows every night
[Note: Kinniku Banzuke (Muscle ranking) and SASUKE are names of physical challenge shows in Japan.]
like Muscle Ranking and SASUKE...
Yeah, that sure is dangerous, but...
Murofushi, Shoei...
[Note: Koji Murofushi is a Japanese gold medalist hammer thrower who appeared in the 2004 Olympics. Shoei is a Japanese actor who competed on Sasuke in early 2000s.]
Those were the nameless muscle
freaks he joined with,
as they snorted muscles,
and raced around in stolen muscles.
[Note: Kondo is using "muscle" in
lieu of "drug" and "motorcycle".]
It was awful...
What the hell are stolen muscles?!
How would that work?!
Eventually, my wife collapsed
because of her muscles.
What?!
You're not even making any sense now!
Enough! Enough about Detective Kane!
She must have been worried
about our son's muscles...
Stop talking about muscles!
But our son never came to the hospital,
despite his mother's condition.
He had been locked up in the slammer!
Hey!
Why are you giving Kane
a criminal record?!
Illegal possession of muscles.
[Note: Kondo is using Muscle to refer to drugs here. Yukio Iketani is a gymnast and Olympic medalist.]
He'd been secretly growing
Iketani in his closet.
How would that even work?!
He might have avoided arrest if
it had been the younger Iketani,
but the older Iketani assures
you of a sentencing.
[Note: The Iketani brothers. Yukio Iketani and his younger brother, Naoki Iketani are both gymnasts.]
What's the difference?
I was enraged, despondent...
I considered cutting ties with him.
How could I call him my son when
he hadn't come to see his mother
on her deathbed because
of his muscle addiction!
But as I sat there in despair
and regret, my wife told me.
Don't run away.
If it's the duty of a parent to praise a child
and rejoice when he does something right,
it's also the duty of a parent to curse and
mourn when he does something wrong!
Once my son was released, I beat him
to a pulp... Till he almost died...
However, when he repented his
old ways and stood up,
I embraced him as tight as I
could... Till he almost died...
It's the job of a parent to accept their
child, no matter what they become.
However, no parent would
want to hate their child.
If it's the parent's responsibility
to love and hate their child,
what is the child's responsibility?
I'll make this simple.
Don't make your parents suffer.
Please don't make them go
through what my wife did.
You have committed many sins.
It's too late for you to erase them.
Your parents will have to bear that
burden for the rest of their lives.
But there are still sins that
you can make up for.
It's still possible for you to lessen
the burden on your parents!
I'll spill...
I'll spill everything...
You...
D-Don't tell me he actually
convinced that murderer?!
Did you see that, Toshi?! Sogo?!
It's all about heart!
My heartfelt carrot was able to
soften this hardened criminal!
Touch this killer deep down...
He spilled something else!
[Note: Spoof of Police drama TV series "Taiyo ni hoero! (Howl to the sun!)" from the 70-80's. G-pan(Jeans pants) detective played by Yusaku Matsuda died in the series using this line.]
What the hell is this?!
Why did this turn into a Detective
G-Pan death scene?!
Weren't you a rogue detective?!
Why are they playing the death music from Howl
to the Sun for a scene where he got barfed on?!
Ah, I'm sorry.
I believe this katsudon is spoiled?
H-Hold on...
It hasn't spoiled yet.
Please wait...
Don't throw this away...
It's only three days old!
I was saving it to eat later!
No, the katsudon's definitely spoiled.
So is your head, for that matter.
Forgive me.
After you went through the trouble
to prepare that for me, well...
I'll take responsibility
by eating all of it,
so please leave it here.
What the hell is this?!
Wait... Please wait!
Don't take this from me!
Don't overdo it!
I don't want to become a killer!
Hey, could you drop the
crappy imitation?
Please set your mind at ease.
You've done nothing wrong.
I have faith in you.
If it's the parent's duty to
bear the child's sins,
the "friend" should take the duty of having
faith and fighting by your side.
Gorilla-san!
Weren't you going for G-Pan?!
What happened to the rogue detective?!
Gori-san! Hang in there!
Hey!
He got me...
I was soundly defeated...
After I suspected him and
fed him this pig feed...
He called me friend... He
still believed in me...
Yeah, why a pork cutlet?
Shouldn't that be a cigarette?!
[Note: Spoof of Police drama TV series "Taiyo Ni Hoero! (Howl to the sun!)". Each detective was given a nickname for the way they dress and their personality.]
Detective Mayora...
Detective Sadist...
The rest is up to you...
Gori-san!
What's going on?
Our attempt to convince that murderer
is backfiring...
Hijikata-san...
He seems to be much better than
us at using carrot and stick.
[?-kun]
Your concept of carrot and stick
[?-chan, you're too close!]
is basically where someone who's
always beating you from behind
[It's embarrassing when people are watching]
[What~ That's not true~]
[On the other hand]
[Geez, I can't believe you, stupid ?-kun]
says something kind or righteous,
[Sorry, XX-chan...]
you appreciate it more than if it
came from someone normal.
[I love you, ?-kun]
What you might call the gap principle.
What's with the really dumb visual aids?
[...is more of a turn-on]
However...
What? We're not done with
these weird visuals?
He's already known to be a vicious killer,
so you could say that we've already
experienced his stick.
By the time we try to give him the stick,
he's already finished.
[Mr. Akimoto is wonderful...!!!]
He just has to spew some
nice-sounding crap,
[Oh... My friend...]
to accomplish the carrot and stick effect.
We will always be behind in the score,
which is why we aren't
getting any results.
If we want to win, we have to achieve
carrot and stick before he does.
Can we do that?
It's impossible to do it alone.
But...
I see!
Don't make yourself too comfortable!
Your torture's about to start!
A top-class sadist who's aiming
for his superior's life!
And...
Are you okay?!
Are you hurt?!
The follow-up master who cleans up after
superiors and subordinates alike!
If the two of us work together,
we can form the best carrot and stick!
Now...
It's over.
Uh, sorry...
What are you doing?
Wh-What?!
Carrot and stick isn't working!
Impossible!
That should have been a clean hit!
Are you okay?
Why don't you have a
seat so we can talk?
I was feeling lonely because
everybody had gone.
A murderer feeling lonely...?!
This guy has brought out
a real carrot bomb!
We can't hold him off!
Hijikata-san!
We've had this completely
wrong from the beginning!
Think back!
This guy is a masochist!
Which means a normal carrot
and stick won't work on him!
I-I see!
A masochist won't feel any
pain from the stick!
So his carrot would be the stick!
We had the order wrong!
Using the stick and then carrot in that
order didn't have any effect on him!
We have to hit him with
the carrot, then the stick!
No, wait...
My carrot shouldn't have
lost its effect yet.
Which means we need one more...
One more lash with the stick to
complete our carrot and stick!
But he's so far away...
I'm losing my will to fight...
It's no use...
I can no longer...
fight...
Toshi.
Toshi...
Toshi!
Vice-Chief!
You guys!
I can...
I can feel power surging through me!
I see...
Carrot and stick isn't
limited to the enemy.
Our plight was the stick.
And the comrades who are able
to rise up out of this plight
serve as the greatest carrot!
Go!
Uh, this might be a bad
time to interrupt you all.
Uh, there was a mistake.
That person isn't Kohei Tanaka.
He's not a killer either.
He's Kahei Tanaka, a good citizen
who helped catch a shoplifter.
He crashed into a store window when he
caught the shoplifter, and hurt himself.
so we brought him to the
station to get treatment,
but there was a mix-up since
his name was similar.
I'm really sorry about this.
I'll bring the real Kohei now.
Combine the carrot with the stick...
My katsudon is starting to spoil...
Mr. Akimoto works so hard...
He was just a smiling nice person...
What the hell is this?!
[Preview]
Uh, Eli, was that how you always looked?
Was that how you always were?
The next episode...
"It's What's On The Inside That Counts."
Plus another one.
[Preview]
["It's What's On The Inside That Counts,
But Only To A Certain Extent."]
[Two parts starring the GinTama mascots,
Elizabeth and Sadaharu.]
[Why are the titles similar? You'll find out next week.]
[See you next time.]