Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Smoking increases a person's risk of
developing pulmonary emphysema.
In addition, smoking by minors
is forbidden because it leads to severe
health issues and nicotine addiction.
Never smoke, even if asked to by others.
...Do you understand?
[Inhale, puff puff... Inhale, puff puff...]
[Hijikata-san, too much smoking is bad for your health.]
10 votes in favor, versus 1 against.
Everyone except Hijikata-san voted
in favor, so this bill is approved.
The Shinsengumi headquarters
will no longer allow smoking
in all areas starting today.
H-Hey, the whole headquarters
is going too far.
It's like you're purposely keeping
smokers out of here.
At least make arrangements for
a designated smoking area.
What are you saying, Hijikata-san?
Smoking is worse than athlete's foot.
Even though it's not prohibited by
law, nicotine is actually a drug.
A drug!
Everyday, you inhale and
exhale, inhale and exhale,
you become addicted.
So, what's wrong with that?
Even if this is a personal matter for you,
you can't run with this line of argument.
Anyone near a smoker is forced to
become second-hand smokers.
But... But...
You're Vice-Chief of the Shinsengumi.
Please think about the other
people around you.
If a Vice-Chief can't even quit smoking
or halt a nicotine addition,
it sets a bad example for everyone else.
H-Hey, Harada. You sometimes
smoke, don't you?
Are you all right with this smoking ban?
Yeah...I completely quit smoking,
so it doesn't matter to me.
It's already been decided.
Man, even with Okita-san's proposal,
that was a productive meeting.
Yeah. Speaking of smokers,
Vice-Chief was the only one.
It was so smoky and awful in there.
My clothes are covered in
that stinky smoke odor.
Any person who practices a martial
art knows smoking is unhealthy.
["Within Each Box of Cigarettes, Are One or Two
Cigarettes That Smell Like Horse Dung"]
...gimme a break.
Is he seriously intending to keep
me out of the Shinsengumi?
Damn it. I might as well inhale as much
nicotine as possible while I'm outside.
[Smoking on the street is prohibited.]
[BATTLE ROYAL HOST]
Ah, excuse me.
Do you have an ashtray?
I'm sorry. This restaurant prohibits
smoking in the whole facility.
What's with this city?
Signs everywhere say "No
Smoking," "No Smoking."
I'm sorry, but smoking
isn't allowed in here.
Hey! Your cigarette!
Cigarettes are...
Oh, no! What's he doing?!
Don't stare.
Let me smoke!
Damn it.
I didn't even notice but
now I can see there's
no places for us smokers to go anymore.
I want to smoke even more
when I'm told not to.
It's hopeless. I can't stand it anymore.
In this situation... I... I...
[SMOKING AREA]
That's it!
I found it! I finally found an oasis!
Here's our next story.
The universal environment
conservation meeting
will be held one week from today.
It'll talk about environment-related
issues in the whole universe.
And the Bakufu is taking this opportunity
to ask the nation to start thinking about
the environment as it launches the micro-environmental
protection campaign for one week from today.
Let's put aside the big problems of ozone
depletion and global warming.
It's important for each person
to do their own part,
no matter how small, to
help the environment.
All your small efforts will start to pile up
into one big push to save the earth.
Yeah, right...
What this old man is trying to say is, before
you go saving the huge Earth...
...you should first save yourself.
Someone who can't even save himself
won't be able to save the earth.
and is disliked by his daughter...
...won't be able to save the earth.
Well, we'll explore all of
that a week from today.
All of Edo...
...will assist in helping implement
the smoking ban.
We repeat.
Currently, an emergency smoking ban
is in effect throughout all of Edo.
Smokers are asked to please throw
away all cigarettes immediately.
Ci...Ciga...rette...
Also, please never approach cigarette
vending machines or smoking areas.
It'll lead to sever punishment.
We repeat...
Are you taking a trip through
the universe, too?
Man, times are sure changing.
I never thought we'd see the day when
we could travel between planets.
So, which planet are you going to?
[Note: Parody of Planet Namek from Dragon Ball.]
Planet Hamek.
Planet Hamek? There's nothing
to see in that countryside.
It's nothing but tobacco fields.
Why are you going there?
...Naturally...
...to smoke some cigarettes!
Don't underestimate a smoker.
[Note: Cigarette images were removed from
GinTama manga vol.8 and vol.16 covers.]
They claimed the cigarette was edited
out of the manga cover because
I looked like a high
school student smoking.
They also said it was never a good
idea to show smokers on the cover.
And they ended up not using
someone smoking.
And we deceptively said it was a pocky chocolate
snack when it was really a cigarette,
or else we'd be forced to give up airing the
show in prime time in North America,
or be stuck with an R rating.
And yet I still haven't given up smoking!
Once the smoking ban starts,
I'll smoke outside Earth!
If cigarettes run out, I'll even
travel to their place of origin!
Don't underestimate a smoker!
I see, I see.
I'm so glad to hear that
you came all the way to
Planet Hamek to smoke our cigarettes.
Unfortunately, this planet
has been turned into
a scorched field by the evil
emperor, Breeza.
[Note: Parody of Frieza from Dragon Ball.]
So cigarettes are no longer...
This is the last one.
Is that all right? Just one...?
Stop it, Grandpa!
Hey, Delde! Take your hands off me!
[Note: Parody of Dende from Dragon Ball.]
That's...! That's the last
cigarette my dad made!
It's a memento of my dad,
who was killed by Breeza.
Dad! Dad!
Dad!
Delde!
...Da...Dad...
Da...! Dad!
Dad!
Dad...
Da... Dad's...
Shut up, Delde!
Cigarettes exist to be smoked.
Cigarettes that you can't smoke shouldn't
even be called cigarettes at all!
What do you think would please
your father the most?
To let the cigarette get moist in a
drawer or let someone smoke it?
Da...Dad's cigarette...
...please enjoy smoking it...
Oh! What a coincidence!
Well, were you able to smoke?
Are you on your way home?
No.
What? Where are you going then?
I'm going to defeat Breeza!
Huh? Breeza? What? Aren't
you going there to smoke?
There's no way I can smoke
something like that!
What?!
I'll kill Breeza and smoke afterwards!
He definitely has cigarettes.
Next time, I'll definitely smoke
cigarettes, damn it!
I never suspected that
you were against me.
But I admire your rashness.
Hijikata's quest to smoke
a single cigarette started
[Note: A parody of Master Roshi's
narrations from Dragon Ball.]
because of the Shinsengumi's
smoking ban.
The trip has been full of hardships.
Well, we'll explore all of
that a week from today.
All of Edo will assist in helping
implement the smoking ban.
But finally he heads off into the universe.
To smoke some cigarettes!
However, when he arrives
on Planet Hamek,
he finds it was turned into a
scorched field by Breeza.
Da...Dad!
Dad!
The young boy Delde's tears...
Hijikata channels his anger into power
and he heads toward the final battle.
Hey! Why am I suddenly having flashbacks
of the previous episode?
This isn't Dragon BLEEP!
It's taking too long! I'm in a hurry!
Let's get to the main episode now!
I never suspected that
you were against me.
But I admire your rashness.
But when you see my power, I wonder
if you'll still have the same attitude.
Well, I'll show you.
My full power!
How about that? You look like
you're scared speechless.
Get ready for it.
Here I come.
Hey, give me a cigarette.
I know you have some.
You destroyed Planet Hamek,
didn't you? Where are they?
I, Breeza-sama, was knocked down
by a monkey like you.
It can't be...you're a legendary
Super Earthling.
[Note: Parody of Super Saiyan from Dragon Ball.]
Shut up, already. Just
give me a cigarette.
I'm grumpy now thanks
to nicotine withdraw.
You're the Super Earthling
who woke up irritated.
Don't tell me you're the
son of that Earthling
who was the only one to
challenge me back then?
Huh, who's this? I don't
look nothing like him.
You're totally wrong.
Can it be that you're searching
for the same thing I was?
Huh?
Whatever. I praise you for defeating me,
the emperor of the universe,
so I will give you this.
Here, take it.
That's not what I asked for!
I said, give me some cigarettes!
What's this ball? It's so disgusting!
It's an Ooey-gooey ball.
[Note: Parody of Dragon Ball from Dragon Ball.]
When you collect all seven of those balls,
the Ooey-gooey dragon will appear
and make everything you want
turn Ooey-gooey.
It's a really mysterious ball.
Why Ooey-gooey? I think
you're lying to me!
If there's anything you
want but can't find,
you should collect six more balls
and have your wishes granted.
Hey! Why are you making that kind
of face made by the super villain
right before he dies in the big scene
at the end of the episode?
Anyway, why do I have to do all
of this just to get a cigarette?!
Give me a break.
It'll be a lot faster if I just
go to another planet
and buy a pack of cigarettes
at a vending machine.
That's right. I should've done
that earlier. I'll go do that.
Grillin! Open your eyes, Grillin!
[Note: Parody of Krillin & Goku from Dragon Ball.]
Damn it! If only I had
all the Ooey-gooey balls!
Grillin!
...Hey, what are you doing?
I'm trying to revive Grillin.
Who the heck is Grillin?!
You came to smoke some
cigarettes, right?
And who's that sitting right next to you?!
Yo! I'm Kobayashi! I'm so excited!
[Note: Parody of Goku and
Yamcha from Dragon Ball.]
Kobayashi?! I'm not excited
about that name at all!
[Note: Refers to Bulma from Dragon Ball.
She dated Yamcha in the series.]
You're Bulma's ex-boyfriend,
aren't you?
Shut up!
You know, Grillin might
have some cigarettes!
I'll definitely smoke next time, damn it!
[Note: Parody of Cell from Dragon Ball.]
I'm Celo!
That's enough! You're so persistent.
I know it's going to take a long time.
I get bored easy. Hey, just give me
some balls. You have some, right?
Why? Why does he have
so much power?
Shut up!
Hurry up and give me some balls so I can
revive Grillin and smoke a cigarette.
I can't believe I lost after taking
cells from the Super Earthling...
[Note: Parody of the scouter device from Dragon Ball.]
Who is this guy? What's with the
scouter rip-off? It pisses me off!
You defeated me, the perfect form, after
I took in every cell and powered up.
Your attack deserves to be rewarded.
As you wish, I'll give you my balls.
Take these.
You hid these in there?!
They're disgusting and dirty!
Use these balls to summon the dragon
and make a wish for me.
My wish is
"To graduate from being a virgin..."
Why are you making it sound like
I'm helping you grant your wish?!
And why did you make
such a useless wish?!
Anyway, now that I've collected
all seven balls.
Hurry up and revive Grillin
so I can smoke a cigarette!
What's this? Can I eat this?
There's no way you can eat that disgusting
thing! What about Grillin?
Oh, that's right!
Hurry up and summon the dragon
so it can revive Grillin!
Come out Ooey-gooey Dragon!
Please make my wish come true!
...Huh?
Nothing happened. There're seven
balls all together. What's going on?
Oh? Taking a closer look, this one
isn't an Ooey-gooey ball at all!
What?
The other six balls are real Ooey-gooey
balls. But this one is...
...a Sticky-icky ball!
It's pretty much the same!
What's the difference between
that and an Ooey-gooey ball?!
Yo. It's a Sticky-icky ball!
That's just a technicality!
See?! Something is coming out!
They're all Ooey-gooey balls, after all.
Great job in collecting all
the Slimy-grimy balls.
It's not Ooey-gooey, nor Sticky-icky!
That's the least of our problems.
Hey, hurry up and save Grillin.
I see. It's not Ooey-gooey.
Then I don't care.
Why?! How much loyalty do
you have for Ooey-gooey?!
How badly do you want to
make Grillin Ooey-gooey?!
Just ask him! It doesn't matter
if he's Slimy-grimy!
He's your friend, right?
If it's Slimy-grimy, I prefer
something else.
What do you mean, something else?
Give me some gal's panties!
[Note: A famous line from Dragon Ball when they
first met Shen Long, the dragon.]
Hey!
A gal's Slimy-grimy panties?!
That's such a gross wish!
Don't request a pair of dirty panties
and give up your friend!
Never mind! Forget it!
Hurry up. Or the Slimy-grimy will dry up.
Wait! Hold on a second!
If I have a Slimy-grimy cigarette,
I can't smoke it.
What should I wish for?
I'm about to dry up!
I know!
I'll get the last one.
You're...
Why are you here again?
I've changed my mind...
I want the last cigarette.
I know that's an important memento
from your dad. But...
...you don't need a memento anymore
if you have your dad back.
Don't tell me... Da...
Yeah. It's your dad.
Whose dad is he?!
What's with this Ooey-gooey?!
No, it's not Ooey-gooey, it's Slimy-grimy!
There's a limit to disgracing the dead!
No, it's true. Even if it's
Slimy-grimy, he's real...
It's you again.
Were you able to smoke
a cigarette, after all?
Where will you go next?
I've decided...
...to quit smoking.
After Hijikata returned to earth,
he wasn't able to give
up smoking, after all.
In order to get the legendary cigarette,
Hijikata works hard at training.
And a new powerful enemy appears before him.
Next episode will be Ooey-gooey
ball, episode 120.
Cut it out! This can't be right!
[Note: Parody of next week
remark from Dragon Ball.]
Everyone! Please watch it!
I said, shut up!
[Preview]
Oh, good for you, Hasegawa-san.
I heard you'll head up the conveyor belt sushi
restaurant all by yourself, after all.
The next episode... "Once you've chosen
a dish, you can't give it back."
Have some sushi!
[Actually, there'll be two episodes next week. The other episode... "Japanese Restaurants Abroad Taste Pretty Much like School Cafeteria Lunches"]
[The plan is to sneak into an Amanto restaurant,
but for some reason, Prince Hata was working there.]
[See you next time.]