["Previously on GinTama"]
Edited at https://subtitletools.com
"Land of the Samurai." The days when our
country was called that are long past.
What's with the intro? Didn't we
already do that a year ago?
Have we run out of new material?
No, actually, TV-Tokyo's ratings
have been pretty good,
so we thought it'd be nice to explain the
GinTama world to our new viewers.
So after a year and a half of hard time,
spring has finally come to this anime!
I heard it was because reruns of "The
Prince of Tennis" that started in April,
in the time slot before GinTama,
are doing extremely well.
Eh?
He was lavish in his praise
for "The Prince of Tennis."
[Note: Parody of "You've got ways to go" famous
phrase by Ryoma Echizen from Prince of Tennis.]
We've got ways to go...
[Thanks to capitalizing on another show's popularity,
"GinTama" continues its successful run!]
[So in response to the good fortune of a certain
sports series... This week we try soccer.]
Here we go! We're in stoppage time
in the second half!
This is FC Oedo's last chance to score!
Come on...
Go.
Do it!
It's up to you!
Now!
Kick it!
This is it!
Kick it in, Amarao!
[Two hours and 40 minutes earlier...]
Strikers are beasts that
live to score goals.
What waits at the end of the road
for those who seek to score?
If I remain true to what I believe,
even in this match that marks the end
of the road...I will see everything.
[Locker Room]
The new world...
that awaits me after a
life of scoring goals!
Okay!
Here we go, team!
Huh?
What?!
["Love Is Often Played Out In Sudden Death"]
[Oedo Stadium]
Hey!
What is this?! What's going on?!
Who are you? Who are you people?!
Wh-Who are we, you ask?
Well, we're like beer vendors.
We came here to sell beer,
but they said they couldn't
drink beer before a match.
They said they only wanted Bocari,
[Note: Bocari is a wordplay on Pocari Sweat,
a Japanese sports drink, available in powder form.]
so I went looking for Bocari powder
and made some for them.
No! That wasn't Bocari powder!
That was the powder they
use to mark the field lines!
The game's about to start!
What have you people done?!
What am I going to do now?!
Shinpachi, who is this guy?
He's, you know, FC Oedo's star
player, Daisaku Amarao.
Amarao-san, you don't have
to make such a big deal of it.
[Note: In Japan, August 31st is the last day of
summer vacation for elementary school kids.]
It didn't bother me one bit that I waited until
August 31 to do my summer homework.
Today was...my final
game before I retire.
Your retirement game?
Yes...and I'm the symbol of
this team. Its best player.
For the past 20 years, I've remained with
FC Oedo and scored countless goals.
And above all, I'm an ace
striker who has made
a massive amount of scores every night.
My fans call me the "night-on-the-town's ace"
and the "command tower of group dates".
No, I think they're looking down on
you. What kind of ace is that?
During my prime, I scored countless
legendary goals. I'm a fantasista.
[Note: Fantasista is an Italian term
for a superstar soccer player.]
Are you a fool or something?
What're you fantasizing about?
I can't lose my retirement
game by forfeit.
I'll disappoint my fans.
No, I think you've already
forfeited your life history.
I realize that...
But today is different!
Today...I wanted to make my precious
little boy's wish come true!
You wanted to score a goal
today for your little boy?
That's right! That's what
I planned on doing.
But look what you've done!
Forget it, I'll just die!
I should just die right now! Sis, hand
over some of that Bocari! A big cup!
Coming right up.
W-Wait! Wait! Just a minute!
There's no need to die!
Then what're you people
going to do about it?
Are you to going to take
responsibility for this?!
Gather up some people, do something!
Just set things up so we
can play the game!
If you don't...my little boy will...he'll...
All right, all right. I'll take care
of this. Give me some time.
Really?!
Thanks for waiting.
It was rather sudden, but I think
I rounded you up quite a group.
Look! These are the new
FC Oedo team members!
Jesus Christ!
What is this?! Who are these people?!
What costume party did you find them
at?! All that's missing is Kin-chan!
[Note: Refers to Kinichi Hagimoto who
used to host a costume contest.]
Where is he? Where's Kin-chan?!
We need Shinya, too.
[Note: Shinya Yamomoto is a judge in the
Kinichi Hagimoto's costume contest.]
Where is he? Where's the director?!
This is ridiculous!
[Note: Director is Shinya Yamamoto's nickname.]
What're you so flustered about?
[Note: Katsura is wearing a Nankatsu team uniform that says "Tonkatsu" (Pork cutlet). Elizabeth is dressed as Kojiro Hyuga from Captain Tsubasa]
Now that we're here, there's no problem.
As you can see, we've studied up
perfectly on the game of soccer.
[I'm Morisaki.]
[Note: Refers to Yuzo Morisaki from Nankatsu FC.]
Quiet! The one next to you
is wrong from the get-go!
[Note: Captain Tsubasa is a soccer manga.]
You probably just read Captain Tsubasa.
I'm not Captain Tsubasa.
I'm Captain Katsura.
Who cares!
Excuse me, what're we doing?
It's been a long time since
I made an appearance.
I was asked to come to a contest where you
roll balls around without using your hands...
How freaky.
That's fine with me! Gin-san,
take out your balls.
Tiger!
[Note: Tiger shot is a special move of
Kojiro Hyuga from Captain Tsubara.]
What?
I heard we were doing a sport
that involved a lot of kicking,
[Note: Otae is wearing a Thai kickboxing outfit.]
so I came dressed like this.
What?!
I heard it was a sport where everyone
watches all the cool things
you can do with your balls,
so I came like this.
What?! I heard the person who makes the
most unique Inari zushi was the winner,
[Note: Inari zushi is a tofu pouch packed
with rice. Looks like nuts.]
so I came like this.
Hey! Every one of you guys
thinks this is about nads!
The game's about the start!
How're we going to play
soccer with this group?!
Gin-san, all of us together make
only ten. We're short one.
Huh? Is that so?
Don't just say "Is that so?" Soccer
is played with 11 people!
We're really in trouble
now! There's no time!
What're you going to do?! Come on!
There, we have everyone.
You just slapped this team together!
You sure this old geezer is any good?
Well at least he's not deaf.
Wait a minute, what's going
on, Amarao-san?
Huh?
The opposing team...
They all have the same face.
They were 11 kids born
at the same time.
What?!
Today's opponent is the
Oedo Ambivalence.
All positions are played by
the 11 Matsuno brothers.
I'd like to see their mother.
Amarao! Make sure you score today!
[Go, Go Amarao!]
Go! You're the night-on-the-town's
top scorer, right?
We're counting on you, Amarao!
At least look good in your last game!
I'm finished.
There's no way we can play a decent
game with these amateurs.
Go for it! Amarao!
Could that be the little boy
he talked about earlier?
That's right...I mustn't give up.
No matter how inexperienced they are, with
proper directions, we might pull it off.
The game is about to begin.
I'm Nakano, and I'll be your
announcer for today.
The Oedo Ambivalence starts things off.
Sannan Matsuno dribbles and
slashes into the defense.
Defenders! Stay on your mark, man-to-man!
Don't let them move freely!
Gotcha!
I have my man!
I have mine!
Hey! You're guarding your
own teammates?!
Shut up! When you go after
the one you love...
You always go man-to-man!
Otae-san!
I won't let you go!
Now Sannan Matsuno...
makes a sharp pass towards the
goal right through the defense!
Clear! Just clear it!
Clear!
Shin-chan, I did it. I cleared two balls.
Sis! A girl shouldn't be
talking about two balls!
The ball is grabbed by Juichinan Matsuno.
He races toward the goal.
He's coming your way, goalkeeper!
Okay, I'll guard this side of the
line, and Elizabeth, you...
That's not fair! That side's
bigger than mine.
What're you talking about?
This boundary is absolute.
Hey! What're you setting territories for?!
What do you mean by absolute?!
I swear to God, they are absolute!
Why are there three goalkeepers?!
Okay, above the line's okay.
Above the line is still out of bounds! You're
gonna get penalized! Definitely penalized!
I dare you! I dare you to penalize me!
You get the death penalty!
Definitely the death penalty!
What?!
You'll definitely get five whacks!
What'd you do that for?!
Elizabeth...
[We should all share this space...]
[We are...]
[...teammates!]
You...
Elizabeth...
Okay, let's do this!
Right! We're teammates!
Teammates!
[That's right! That's right!]
Hey! Hey!
Goal!
The visiting Ambivalence scores first!
It's all right. We'll have
many more chances.
No, we won't.
Only you people here should hear this.
My body is a wreck from all my battles
on the field over the years.
These knees,
this back,
have all reached their
limits a long time ago.
I don't know how many more times I can
shoot for the goal with all my might.
That's why...!
I'm not asking for repeated chances!
One...just one shot is enough.
Give me one chance at a goal!
You say that, but we're amateurs...
But we'll do what we can.
Shin-chan, Kagura-chan.
Okay.
Right.
...Everyone...
The game continues with FC Oedo
in possession of the ball.
I'm counting on you.
Oh... Having said that, we've
never played soccer before.
Sakata has it stolen away!
We don't have the guts!
[Note: Famous phrase from a Captain Tsubasa video
game. Displayed when Energy (guts) is low.]
This is going to be easy!
They're nothing but amateurs!
I'll increase our lead!
He shoots!
The ball is headed straight
towards the goal!
Elizabeth is their only goalkeeper!
After the last goal, it seems they decided who would
be the goalkeeper using rock-paper-scissors!
The ball is in the air. But will Elizabeth's
physique get in the way?!
It's a spectacular save!
Elizabeth makes a spectacular,
unexpected save!
Makes you wonder what
sort of creature it is!
The front line has raced deep into
the opponent's side of the field.
Goalkeeper! This is our chance
to counterattack!
Kick it out in front of their goal!
The goalkeeper makes a nice feed!
Amarao!
With this...
I can make his wish come true.
Damn! Why does this
have to happen now!
Are you okay, Amarao-san?
Don't worry! It's a badge of
honor I got during a game!
Yes...it was during a hard-fought
game like today!
[Cabaret Chic Hostess Bar]
C'mon, Ohana-chan, why won't
you go out with me?
What should I do? I'll consider it if you do
the Amarao Dance you do at the game.
Is that all? Okay, here goes.
Hora, hora, hora.
One fruit plate, please.
Here comes the signature pose!
I never imagined that "game" would
force me into retirement.
A...ma...ra...o...!
Huh?!
From start to finish...
You totally got...
what you deserved!
It's your own stupid fault!
Shoot!
...not today...
That concludes the first half.
Hey! What're you doing?!
What, Shinpachi-kun? Balls
always go with bats, right?
Shut up! Can't you people even remember what
sport you were playing just a second ago?!
No. My memory went splat after
I got kicked in the balls.
Are your brains in your balls?!
Gin-san! I want the bat between
your legs right now!
That's enough!
You stop that, too!
Sarutobi-san, a woman must never say such
vulgar things such as bats, poles, and bleep.
Hey! You're more vulgar than she is!
Why're all of you panicking?
In the second half, I, Misugi,
the prince of this field, shall?
[Note: Jun Misugi is a player with heart disease from Captain Tsubasa. Uniform says "Kakashi" a wordplay on his team "Musashi FC."]
M-My heart. Stay back, manager!
I can still play.
[Misugi-kun!]
I will get them all with an off-side
trap in the second half...
Cut that out! How long are you going
to keep playing Captain Tsubasa!
Gin-san, this is totally messed up. How'll
we manage in the second half?
How would I know?
You're talking about the guy who did
nothing but stupid things out there.
Maybe we should do as we please, too.
But that's...
Amarao-san...
The second half is about to start.
In the first half,
FC Oedo managed to keep the score
at 0-1 despite missing their regulars.
Can they catch up in the second half?
The ball goes to Amarao.
Amarao-san!
I'd forgotten. I always did things myself.
For my own sake, using
my own strength!
Amarao races deep into the enemy's
side of the field all alone!
No you don't!
He draws a yellow card!
FC Oedo gets a penalty kick!
Yes...
All Right! Go!
This is how it should be...
Huh?!
What're you doing?!
[Note: Famous phrase by Kinichi Hagimoto,
from the costume contest.]
Wh-Why do things...turn out this way?
What happened to...
The match!
Ambivalence adds another point!
Looks like Amarao who was out with an
injury is coming back into the game.
Amarao-san...we're sorry.
No, I'm to blame for getting
you involved in this.
All we have left is stoppage time.
It's true that I did nothing but stupid
things during my soccer career.
That came back to haunt me today.
But I won't give up on scoring
a goal until the very end.
That's the sort of person a striker is.
During the time that's left, I'll score
a goal even if I have to do it alone.
My little boy...is waiting for a goal.
But isn't your back and knees a wreck?
They give me more of a chance
than relying on you amateurs.
You realize it now, don't you?
Soccer is not a game.
The field is a battleground.
Soccer is war!
War?!
What's so funny?!
Amarao-san, you son-of-a-gun.
All of us here are definitely
amateurs at soccer.
But, if it's war, we're talking about...
Everyone here is a battle-hardened pro.
Huh?
Just watch.
All that remains is stoppage time.
With the outcome already decided,
the only question is whether or not Amarao
will score a goal in his retirement match.
Amarao speeds in alone once again!
Tsk! That pain again...
The ball is taken away!
And it goes back...
the other way!
Crap!
Don't come here!
You go for a goal, nothing else!
We'll set you up!
You're not scoring any more points!
Fools! Amateurs shouldn't rush in!
You're wrong! He's not just any amateur!
He's...
Is that?! A foot soldier?!
One who rushes in with
no fear for his life?!
I'm used to diving in and
sacrificing myself!
He's just a foot soldier, after all.
Look closely!
The foot solder was a decoy!
The real defenders are the
spearmen behind him!
Let's do it, Otae-san!
That figure going after the ball
in mid-air has to be an archer!
Go! Sky Love Gorricane!
[Note: Parody of "Sky love Hurricane", special attack
by the Tachibana Brothers in Captain Tsubasa.]
Look out! There's a defender
in the path of the pass!
This one's mine!
Do you know...
who the fastest person on
a battlefield is?
It's...
the shinobi!
Shinpachi! Let's do this with a
back-and-forth pass attack.
Right.
Here's the pass!
Pass.
What a combination!
It's the Takeda Cavalry! The strongest
during wartime Japan!
What?! I'm a horse?!
What're you guys doing?!
There's only Amarao left! Defend him!
What?!
Samurai-san, leave this guy
to me and go on ahead.
Score a goal for everyone.
Hey! You're way too cool!
Gin-chan!
Go, Amarao!
Score!
[Go!]
For the sake of your little boy!
Thank you, everyone...
And...!
Amarao!
Ohana-chan!
What?!
Go out with me for the
sake of my "little boy"!
Shoot!
I-It...snapped...
And that's the end of the game!
C'mon, let's go home.
Daddy!
Strikers are beasts that
live to score goals.
The next episode... "Kids Don't Understand
How Their Parents Feel."
[The Odd Jobs are summoned to a splendid mansion owned
by their client Kaguzo Mashiroi, boss of the Mashiroi Gang.]
[His son, Utsuzo, had become reclusive. Can
Gin-san and friends coax him out of his shell?]