Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Funnuraba!
Hey, you can't do your business here...
Your excretion is bigger than
a naughty monk's dreams!
Damn it!
That's why I didn't want this...
She's the one who said she'd
take him for a walk later!
But in the end, your mother
has to do all the work!
Wait, I'm the mother?
You can't even keep a
pet in line... Pathetic.
How can you change this nation when you
can't even hold an animal in check?
And you call yourself a samurai?
What is that next to you?
["It's What's On The Inside That Counts"]
[Battle Royal Host]
Honestly, you're such a pain.
How long have you had Sadaharu-kun?
You still haven't established a
master and pet relationship.
Right, Elizabeth?
A true bond of trust between a master and
pet must be deeper than the Sea of Japan
[Note: Riki Choshu is a professional
wrestler known for his mullet.]
and longer than Choshu's mullet.
Right, Elizabeth?
What is it, Gintoki?
You aren't going to eat that parfait?
If you aren't, would you
mind if Elizabeth had it?
Right, Elizabeth?
Yeah... That isn't Elizabeth, is it?
Gintoki, that was a pretty
witty American joke.
I wasn't telling a joke!
And how was that even American?!
Hell, that thing's the one
that looks Americanized!
["I'm Russianized"]
How would I know that?!
[Note: Parody of Nintendo DS]
And why are you using a Bentendo
TS to talk to me?!
Use your usual sign!
Anyways, are you okay?
Did you eat something rotten?
Did you eat something off the floor?
As you go through life, it is always
possible to find hope lying around...
That's not what I asked.
This is bad. Definitely bad.
You were bad to begin with, but you've taken
it to a whole new level today, Zura.
It's Katsura, not Zura.
In any case, we don't have time
to listen to your foolishness.
Let's go, Elizabeth.
Th-Thank you very much...
[Note: This is a 10,000 yen bill. 10,000 yen
is equivalent to USD $100.]
Th-Thank you very much.
I'll go get your change.
["Keep the change"]
Thank you very much!
Thank you so very much!
Elizabeth, you seem to have forgotten
how to use chopsticks.
No matter. I'll teach you
from the beginning.
Since we live in a land of chopsticks.
I-Indeed...
It's just like Gin-san said.
It's no longer the Elizabeth we know.
That's no simple makeover.
Doesn't even look like a fake.
It's something completely different.
I wonder what happened
to the real Elizabeth.
Hey now...
Why are you getting all gloomy?
Why wouldn't we?!
I might not be able to compare
with Katsura-san,
but I have my own share of fond
memories with Elizabeth.
Me too!
All of the memories are so beautiful.
No, there's nothing beautiful about that.
And wait, why are you remembering
last night's dinner?
That has nothing to do with Elizabeth.
I'll find a way to wake Katsura-san up!
Katsura-san will surely be sad when
he realizes what's happened!
Right on!
That fake can't hold a
candle to Elizabeth!
But Zura usually won't listen
to anything we have to say.
No choice then...
We'll try to wake him up.
Excuse me, you two.
Why hello there...
What's with you people?
Well, we happen to belong
to a pet-loving society.
There's been a rise in the number of people
keeping illegal animals as pets
or stealing other people's pets.
What was that?!
Are you implying that I'm one
of those evil villains?!
More stupid than evil.
No, no, no! That wasn't our intention.
We simply wanted to check
if that was really your pet.
Please cooperate!
I have no choice...
So what am I supposed to do?
Could you start by providing
some form of ID?
For the pet.
Uh, it'd be pretty odd for
a pet to have any ID.
What?! It does?!
Isn't that odd?!
Isn't this pretty odd?!
Himeka...
Rise...
Hazuki...
How many different hostess
clubs have you been to?!
[Note: Girls at hostess clubs usually have their own business cards for their customer to call. More business cards implies more hostess clubs.]
Elizabeth is so hopeless.
But where did you get those things?
Isn't that obvious?!
They came from society's nighttime outlet where
money and the lust of old men come together!
But this is perfect, Gin-san.
The normal Elizabeth would
never go to those places.
One more push and Katsura-san
will notice!
Now, we'd like you to fill out a
survey concerning your pet.
Why are you filling it out?!
And it's in Russian?!
Please look at this, Katsura-san!
This is the truth of the unknown
organism next to you!
Please wake up!
Can your Elizabeth write in Russian?!
Is this the Elizabeth you know?!
Th-This is...
Y-You...
I'm so happy, Elizabeth!
Why?!
There's obviously something wrong here!
Your Elizabeth can't write in Russian!
You've finally gone from someone
who could only write on that sign
to someone who can write on paper!
That's your concern?!
This is wonderful...
I was starting to get sick of constantly
throwing away signs.
He just revealed how he really felt.
And why don't you realize that the Elizabeth in that
flashback isn't the one next to you, dumbnuts!
Let us go, Elizabeth!
This country has a bright future!
What do we do?
Forget about waking him up...
Katsura-san doesn't feel the
slightest hint of doubt.
Man...
I give up.
There may still be a way.
Hey there, big guy.
[Hostess Club SMILE]
What do you want?
We've got some cute girls.
Right now, a samurai accompanied
by a pet gets in for half the price.
How about it?
A samurai like myself would never have
time to fool around with such women.
Let's go, Elizabeth.
Yes, two coming in!
Elizabeth...?
Why welcome!
We'll take extra special
care of you today!
Enjoy yourselves.
Party of two coming in!
Please, you're such a kidder, sir!
It's Elizabeth, not sir.
What's going on, Shin-chan?
Was that how the thing with
Katsura-san always was?
W-Well, it's a long story...
But this is a great plan, Gin-san.
The fake Elizabeth is obviously
a fan of hostess clubs.
An obvious difference from the real thing.
Katsura-san should be confused.
Th-Then Elizabeth, shall we get going?
Oh, Katsura-san?
You're already leaving?
It's so rare of you to come visit.
As a citizen who's concerned
about the future of this nation,
I have no time to play around.
Let us go, Elizabeth.
Excuse me!
This customer wants an extension!
An extension?!
What are you saying, Elizabeth?!
Wh-What's wrong, Elizabeth?
You're not your usual self!
That's right, Katsura-san!
That's what we've been trying to tell you!
This isn't the Elizabeth you know!
That's right!
It's a completely different fake!
Wake up already!
I understand...
I'll go wash my face to wake myself up!
That's not what we meant!
No, Elizabeth is Elizabeth
and nothing but Elizabeth.
He seemed really disturbed...
Did we bring Katsura-san to his senses?
Beats me.
But he should have noticed that
thing isn't Elizabeth by now.
Excuse me!
This customer wants a bottle
of Dom Perignon Rose!
[Note: Often served at Hostess
Clubs at super high price.]
And a fruit plate, a whole ham,
and order out for sushi!
Hey! Cut this out already!
You're really starting to push it!
Hey!
You're already running one scam
by pretending to be Elizabeth,
and now you're going to gorge
yourself without paying!
This bastard's an appetite robber!
If you're gonna drink that much, you should
be buying us a round, fake Elizabeth!
[Order whatever you want]
[Why don't YOU play around in grand style?]
[Note: Impersonating Johnny Kitagawa, the founder and former president of Johnny & Associates, a famous male talent agency.]
Uh, but...
Woo-hoo!
You're such an animal, champ!
You're incorrigible, champ!
It's Elizabeth-san, not champ!
Elizabeth-san! Would you
like anything else?!
[Let's go to Oke-Kara after this!!]
[Note: "Oke-kara" is Karaoke in TV producer terms]
Woo-hoo! One more round!
Elizabeth!
You...
Elizabeth...
["Katsura-san..."]
You dropped your TS.
You shouldn't be dropping
something so expensive.
At this rate, you'll end up losing
something more important.
Treasure your TS as you
would your friends.
Whoa, that stinks!
Hey, something stinks.
Ouch...
Huh? What is this place?
Where am I?
Wait, the closet?
Why was I sleeping in here?
Whoa, I can barely stand straight.
Did I drink that much last night?
And what's with the smell?
Why is it so strong?
Did Shinpachi hold a popcorn
party without me?
Or did Kagura's pickled seaweed
spoil somewhere?
Man, it smells like sweat.
My head's starting to hurt.
Hey! Kagura!
Huh?
Kagu-
What? Something's wrong
with my throat.
Did I drink too much?
No choice then.
I'll take some medicine.
Pretty sure the medicine was
in a drawer in the living room.
I'll just find something random to take...
H-Huh?
Wasn't that me? Huh?
Huh? Did I leave a mirror there?
No, I didn't...
Huh? Did I leave my body?
No, but I just hit my head, so I've got a body.
Wait, maybe it's a doppelganger?
No, no, no, no.
We had plenty of that with
the recent Tama incident.
The staff isn't going to reuse that
gag, even if they're out of ideas.
They'd wait a little longer...
Uh, excuse me...
Sorry to disturb myself
while I'm sleeping,
but I'm having a hard time understanding
the situation here.
Can I wake myself up?
Hello?
Hmm?
Er? What's this?
What's with the cute p-paw?
Huh? Huh?
N-No way!
What? No way!
Why?!
Whoa, thick fur!
No, that's not the issue here...
What?!
No, no, no, no.
No way, man.
This is impossible!
I don't get it!
Hey! Wake up!
I can't be sleeping at a time like this!
Wake up!
Stop!
["It's What's On The Inside That Counts,
But Only To A Certain Extent"]
Hey, hey.
What am I supposed to do now?
This is obviously me.
I'm Sadaharu and Sadaharu's me.
[Note: Play on the title of the book "I'm Her And She's Me"]
Why do I have to change myself?
Besides, the usual pattern is...
It's gone!
Something like that, right?
But it's there.
The real deal is hanging
a little bigger than usual.
Usually, you switch with a cute girl
for some hubba hubba To Love-ru.
[Note: Reference to the love comedy
manga "To Love Ru".]
And Sadaharu! Why are
you still sleeping?!
I'm starting to get pissed off.
I'll beat him awake!
Damn, I look fine!
I can't hit that face!
I mean, it's me!
But what am I supposed to do then?!
What's with all the noise this early?
Sadaharu, what are you doing?
Kagura!
Perfect timing!
What's wrong, Gin-chan?
Did you finally snap?
You're acting funny.
That's right, Kagura!
Way to notice!
Look over here!
Gin-chan's over here!
Though Gin-chan's also over there,
but Gin-chan's also over here!
You hung over?
And something stinks.
It's coming from the living room.
No!
You can't go to the living room right now!
That Sadaharu, or it was me, I guess...!
Gin-chan...
This is beyond sad.
I would hope that you could
clean up after yourself.
And could you stay away from
me for the time being,
bed-shitting samurai?
You've got it wrong!
You should know, Kagura-chan!
Gin-san may be a slob, but he knows
how to keep his stuff inside!
He keeps his ass tight and shut, too.
It's me, but it's not my fault!
Sadaharu, what are you trying to say?
Hurry over here before you catch
his bed-shitting habits, Sadaharu.
I wasn't talking to you!
Gin-san! I mean, Sadaharu!
Good morning.
Sh-Shinpachi!
You should be able to notice
the problem here!
You've been with me since
the first episode!
I'm sorry about calling
you a lame four-eyes!
Those glasses are the glasses
of truth which reveal all!
What's wrong, Sadaharu?
And something stinks.
What's this smell?
Gin-san, I was already
disappointed in you,
but I wasn't expecting you to get worse.
You've reached a new low.
You better clean this yourself.
What? He's looking down on me?
Kagura-chan, let's go kill time
at Otose-san's place.
Let's.
We'll catch his bed-shitting
habits if we stay here.
Shitface.
Sadaharu...
Why is Gin-san's status spiraling down?
How can you humiliate me when we've
only switched places for a little...
Switched places...
That's it!
A switch can be resolved by
falling down a set of stairs!
That's been the typical method
used to end these stories!
I-It didn't fix anything!
Good timing, Zura!
Stop that guy!
They say that a boy can transform
himself in three days...
Haven't you changed in some way?
Yes! That's right!
I knew you would understand!
Well, we shouldn't stand here and talk
so let's find a place to sit down.
Though it may take a shake
or two to find a spot,
but it's better than standing around
like we're trying to play dead.
What are you doing, Zura?!
How dare you use your conversation
to manipulate me!
In that case, I'll use gestures or pantomime
to tell him what's going on!
Well, Sadaharu-dono...
Creepy!
Stop, Zura!
Such a cutie.
[Note: Masanori Hata (a.k.a Mutsugoro) is a writer and naturalist. He was an owner of "Mutsugoro Kingdom", a ranch with various animals.]
Why the Mutsugoro-san impression?!
Can I fluff your stomach?
Stop!
I don't wanna admit it!
Don't wanna admit it!
But it feels so good!
So good!
No! No! Yes!
What a lovely day.
I've been violated...
Wait, Sadaharu?
Damn it! Where'd that bastard go?!
What's with the penetrating look?
You're not your usual self.
I love it!
You're making me numb!
Look down on me as much as you want!
Step on me!
I'm a poor little bitch who
wants your love!
What's with that pose?
Don't tell me you want hardcore
play in the middle of town!
Very well!
I'll accept whatever you have to give!
Bring it on!
Hurry!
Come!
What are you doing?!
Do you have any idea what
time this show airs?!
This anime may use a lot of toilet humor,
but there's a line you don't cross!
You can't show this hardcore
freak show on TV!
I've changed jobs from the main character
[Note: Changing jobs is a parody of Dragon
Quest, the videogame series.]
to a sub-character who might get to
show up once every quarter-year...
Farewell, fans of Gintoki Sakata...
Hello, fans of Sadaharu-kun.
I may have changed on the outside, but
my soul will continue to shine brightly!
For eternity!
Man, I'm, uh, you're taking this in stride...
Gin-san.
Gin-san, you awake?
Shut up, Shinpachi.
Don't talk right next to me.
Your voice is loud.
Huh?
Isn't that Sadaharu?
I can't be looking at Sadaharu
if I'm Sadaharu,
so if I'm looking at Sadaharu,
my eyes can't be Sadaharu's,
which might mean I...
returned to normal...
Huh? What's this?
That sucks.
These glasses are getting really loose.
Huh!
Er, what?!
Glasses?!
I turned into his glasses?!
Who's Gin-san then?!
Gin-san, please wake up already!
Noooo!
The next episode...
"People Open Up When
They're Locked Up."
[The Odd Jobs gang are trapped in an elevator, with no help in sight...]
[The second half is "Are There Still People Who Go To The Beach And Yell Out 'Bakayaro'"?]
[See you next time.]