[Sagaru Yamazaki]
[Note: Parody of Prince of Tennis.]
Edited at https://subtitletools.com
GinTama...
[Right after these messages!]
Right after these messages!
[Note: Ryoma's favorite phrase
from Prince of Tennis]
You're not there yet.
[Amazingly, June 26th is Katsura's birthday.
So this month is Katsura Enrichment Month.]
[Kotaro Katsura, 2X years old.
Why not have adults like this?]
Hey, did you hear? Takasugi
fought with the Shinsengumi.
He apparently sent a spy into the Shinsengumi
and tried to kill Chief Kondo.
Well, he ended up failing, though.
A spy, huh? We should be careful.
There may be a spy lurking about.
Umm, excuse me.
Wh-Who are you?!
H-Hold on a second. I'm not suspicious.
Who are you?! Give us your name!!
Umm... I see that you have a sword at your
side when there's a ban on swords...
I assume that you are Anti-Foreigner
Faction members.
What do you want?!
Please...
Would you...
Would you let me join the ranks
of the Anti-Foreigner Faction?
["Life is a Test"]
This is the most dangerous
part of my job as a spy.
It's called undercover investigations.
I sneak into the ranks of the enemy and
leak secret information to my allies.
The rewards are huge, but so is the risk.
Therefore, only the most skilled
spies take on these missions.
You must be skilled enough to
mask your true feelings while
risking your life when faced with the danger
of being discovered by the enemy.
And you can't make a single mistake
when in enemy territory.
You need finesse to perform your job
with precision in extreme situations.
And...
You need to be extremely bland in
order to blend in with everything.
The person in the Shinsengumi
who has all of these traits is none
other than I, Sagaru Yamazaki.
I never expected Anti-Foreigner Faction
members to be hiding in a town like this.
Akiba Neo, the underground city.
[Note: Parody of Akihabara.]
Called a holy land by otaku, it's Edo's
most famous mechanical district.
The town is like a maze. It's indeed
a perfect place for hiding out.
The Unstoppable Kotaro Katsura.
I have to get close to him. Find
out where his officials are...
And round up all of the Anti-Foreigner
Faction members.
I see. I understand.
All right. Let's begin the interview.
Huh?
Give me your resume.
Huh? Umm... I can't join the Anti-Foreigner
Faction without passing an interview?
It's a precaution against spies.
I can't fight and leave my back open to
someone with a suspicious background.
What is this?
Why do I need to take an interview to partake
in Anti-Foreigner Faction activities?
S-Sorry... I forgot my resume.
But I am more concerned about
my country than anyone else.
I don't care about that.
Just give me your resume.
Let me give this to you straight.
Don't you have any common sense?
When you go job hunting, you usually
bring a resume with you.
Job hunting? I'm job hunting?!
You're supposed to come in a suit.
What did you come here for?
I'm not the only one who will tell you this.
Just to let you know, any company
will say the same thing.
You're not a company!
Also, you sat down before I told you to.
Usually, you sit after your
interviewer tells you to sit.
S-Sorry...
All businesses want people
who have common sense.
We say that a person's education
decides his worth...
But anyone can learn their
job while they're doing it.
Master, welcome back.
I'm not "master." I'm Katsura.
If you pay a special fee, you
can have fun with the maids.
I don't need you of all
people to tell me that!!
Why do I have to be lectured
by someone who
holds an interview in a maid cafe?!
[NOTE: Jankenpon is the Japanese name for Rock-Paper-Scissors. "Aikodesho" is said after tied rounds. In one game variation, the winner of a round points in a direction and the loser has to look in a different direction, or else he loses the game.]
Jankenpon.
Well, anyway, even though we're
Anti-Foreigner Faction members,
we need common sense.
Aikodesho, sho, sho, sho.
Revolutionaries destroy
the existing norms.
And because of that, revolutionaries need
to understand what's common and normal.
I win!!
Turn that way!
Keep that in mind if you want to become
an Anti-Foreigner Faction member.
Huh? I thought I was going to fail,
but this looks kind of good, doesn't it?
Jankenpon.
Well, the interview is over. Hey, take him.
Aikodesho.
Aikodesho, sho, sho, sho.
He said it was an interview, but did
he really just want to meet me?
Let's go.
Oh, yes.
That's right.
Turn that way!
There's no way the Anti-Foreigner
Faction
would ever do anything weird
like have interviews.
I'm glad... I managed to infiltrate them.
[Anti-Foreigner Faction Employment Exam]
Why does the Anti-Foreigner Faction
have an entrance test?!
First an interview, and now a test?!
This is no different from
a regular business!
This is weird! This is definitely weird!!
This is bad.
I never expected it to be so difficult to become
an Anti-Foreigner Faction member.
What kind of questions do
they have on their test?!
I never studied for it!
What is everyone studying?!
Hey, did you prepare?
I'm in trouble. I didn't study at all.
I'm going to fail. This is bad.
This guy's bloodshot eyes
say otherwise.
There's always one faker in the class.
Oh...
All right, quiet down.
We're going to start the Anti-Foreigner
Faction employment exam.
Put away your textbooks!
What textbooks?!
It's too late to stuff anything
else into your head now!
You're no match for those who have always
been doing the review exercises!
Review exercises? What
review exercises?!
All right, take a look at this.
I'm going to put the questions
up on the screen one by one.
Everyone, use the panel in front
of you to answer each question.
Afterwards, I will announce the answer.
We have a proctor keeping watch
in the back, so try not to cheat.
Everyone, please try your best.
Let the test begin!
[Question 1 - Write down the correct reading
of the following word: Shinsengumi]
Question one. Write down the correct
reading of the following word.
What is this?! It's incredibly easy!! I see!
Even though we're Anti-Foreigner Faction
members, we need common sense.
Even if it's a test, it's a question to see
how much common sense one has!
I haven't studied for this test, but
it looks like I can pass this.
[Shinsengumi]
The answer is "Shinsengumi"!
All right, time's up. This is the answer.
[Scum]
The answer is "scum."
On what planet is that common sense?!
Well, this is common sense amongst
Anti-Foreigner Faction members.
Other answers like "idiots," "trash," and
"lately intrusive" are also correct.
All right! I got it correct!
Is that what these guys usually call us?!
[Shin (crossed out)]
Maeragumi]
Tsk! A trick question.
You got the question wrong, too!
What did you study all night?!
This is bad. I can't even get the correct
answer using common sense.
I need to answer the questions with the mindset
of an Anti-Foreigner Faction member.
[Question 2 - Write down the correct reading
for the following word: Shogun]
The second question. Write down the
correct reading for the following word.
[Shogun Shogun Shogun Shogun Shogun Shogun]
The normal answer would be "shogun."
But to the Anti-Foreigner Faction,
he is the boss of the enemy.
Which means...
[Smegma]
I'll get it right if I insult him.
[Correct Answer: Ken Matsudaira]
The correct answer is Ken Matsudaira.
Why is there a kanji reading
for a kanji word?!
Well, this is common sense
amongst faction members.
"Roughneck," and "cooking
lover" are also correct.
[Note: "Roughneck" is "Abarenbo" in Japanese. Ken Matsudaira is the star of the TV show Abarenbo Shogun.]
All right! I did it!!
Why are there people who got it correct?!
What kind of brains do they have?!
[Question 3 - Write down the following
word in kanji: Jackie Chan]
The third question. Write down
the following word in kanji.
This doesn't have anything to do with
the Anti-Foreigner Faction anymore!
Jackie?! I don't know! This
is just plain unreasonable!
The answer is "nose."
[Nose]
You just hate Jackie's nose!!
Well, this is common sense
amongst faction members.
[Note: Jackie Chan played Ryo Saeba in
the Hong Kong version of City Hunter.]
"Chair" and "Ryo Saeba was pretty
painful" are also correct.
That last one was just your opinion!
Don't mention City Hunter!
We've been doing Japanese until now.
Starting with the next question,
we'll be doing math.
This is bad... I still haven't
got a single question right.
Question number four.
There are ten Shinsengumi members.
Six Anti-Foreigner Faction members run
into them on the side of the road.
The Shinsengumi attack, and three of the Anti-Foreigner
Faction members are killed.
Unyielding, the Anti-Foreigner Faction members
kill two Shinsengumi members.
Amidst the confusion of the battle,
two more Shinsengumi
members are injured,
but six more join them and two Anti-Foreigner
Faction members are killed.
How many noses does Jackie have?
One, of course!!
How long are you going to
keep talking about Jackie?!
This has absolutely nothing
to do with the battle!!
Umm... This question is incredibly
difficult, so I'll give you extra time.
Think about it for an hour.
I don't need an hour!
No...wait! He's been giving us
deceptive answers until now.
What if Jackie was in this battle?!
What if Jackie's nose...
Was cut off in the battle?!
The correct answer is "one."
You there, be quiet.
Oh, sorry...
I was completely tricked!
I read into it too much and let a
question I could answer slip by!
Tsk! A trick question, huh?
That was close.
What exactly were you tricked by?!
Umm... That's it for math.
This isn't math!
[Question 5 - Translate the following passage.]
The next section is foreign language.
Question five. Translate
the following passage.
What language is this?!
I can't read it at all!!
Is this an alien language
from another planet?!
An illustration?! That's it! That illustration!
That picture has got to represent
the contents of the passage!
I've got to rely on intuition and
this picture to translate it!
No matter how I look at this,
it's a picture of a battlefield.
One guy is about to die and the other
is listening to his last words.
There's no mistake...
He has something in his hand!
A letter? No, a photograph!
Never mind me... Hurry up
and run away, you maggot!
The Sergeant quickly grew
cold in my arms...
He was a drill sergeant who
was so terrifying and hateful.
But right now his face looked so kind.
Can't you follow your superior's
orders, you maggot?!
Maggot! Tell me you're
a maggot, you maggot!
Sergeant! I am a maggot!
I was abandoned by my
parents like a maggot!
No one will be sad if a
maggot like me dies!
Please let me do whatever I want!
What a coincidence, maggot!
When I took up arms, I also
discarded my family.
No one will grieve for me anymore.
But you're different...
After the Sergeant said this he slowly
took a blood-splattered photograph
out of his inner breast pocket.
You have someone who
will grieve for you.
It was a picture of when my mother
was still young and healthy.
By her side was the Sergeant.
He was holding a baby.
Tell me I'm a maggot...my son.
Instructor...
You're a maggot.
You're a maggot's precious...good-for-nothing
father!
The instructor smiled
and ceased moving.
All right. This should be good!
Now, the correct answer...
Jackie's nose is big, isn't it?
That's it.
It was a picture of Jackie?!
How long a passage do you need to
express how big Jackie's nose is?!
It was wrong but I was touched.
Don't look at my answer!
It's too embarrassing!
The next question is the final
question in the written exam.
The last one already?! Most of the
questions were only about Jackie!
[Question 6 - Write down the reason why you want to join the Anti-Foreigner faction in Kamchatkan.]
[Note: Kamchatkan is a language spoken in northeast Russia.]
Write down the reason why you want to join
the Anti-Foreigner faction in Kamchatkan.
What?! Kamchatkan?!
This is impossible!! I can't write
in such a difficult language!
This is a difficult question so
if you get this right, you pass.
It's over. I failed my mission.
The Vice-Chief is going
to be angry with me.
I'll just write anything...
Umm... One person got it correct.
Examinee number 11!
Huh?
Wow!
I just wrote anything. Is this for real?!
Whatever the case, I can carry
out my mission! All right!
I did it!
Umm... Since he got it correct,
let's take a look at his answer.
When translated, it says, "I came here to
carry out an undercover investigation.
I will send all you Anti-Foreigner
Faction members to hell."
Huh?
What?!
Th-This is bad...
They discovered that I've come to
do an undercover investigation!
What's the meaning of this?!
Did they know who I was
from the beginning?!
U-Umm...
Hmm... You wish to become a part of
our undercover investigation squad.
Good job. Everyone, give
him a round of applause.
Huh?
They didn't find out who I was...
Thank goodness... Now I can...
Those who have passed the written
exam will now take the final test.
We will have a skills test.
Huh? Huh?
You will take a skills test for
undercover investigation.
Undercover investigation is
one of the most difficult
of Anti-Foreigner Faction activities.
The enemy isn't stupid enough
to overlook spies.
There is an idiot right in front of me!!
Even though it's a test, you
don't know what'll happen.
So you will take the test
under supervison.
Captain Dragon!
Captain...Dragon?
U-Umm...
Hello, I'm Captain Dragon.
Huh?
You're going to be sneaking into the headquarters
of a certain organization with me.
You'll pass if you can steal
a secret document.
Then you'll be a formal Anti-Foreigner
Faction member. Got that?
Well, anyway... You're one
of those, aren't you?
You're supposed to be him, aren't
you? You're a Jackie look-alike...
I'm not Jackie. I'm Captain Dragon!
Your face is really close to mine.
Let me ask you one thing.
What is the one thing you must protect
more than anything during an
undercover investigation?
Huh? Is this a test question?
The answer is "your nose."
Your nose?
That's right. Your nose!
There are many vital spots
on the human body.
Amateurs often guess that the testicles
are the most vulnerable spot,
but this is wrong!
The most vulnerable spot is the nose!!
Got that?!
The final test...
Project Z will now begin!!
There it is. This was unexpectedly easy.
I did it! I've passed the skills test!
What wonderful skills!
You've passed so far!
But you're being tested until you get that secret
document safely to our headquarters!
Your excursion continues until you
greet the people back home!
Shh... Katsura-san, the enemy's
going to find us!
Hey, who was talking just now?!
We've got intruders!
They're in the secret documents room!
They discovered us!
The enemy found you during a crucial
time. You're still too naïve.
They discovered us because of you!
Let's run away! Follow
me, exam student!
Wait! They're over there!
Th-They followed us!
[Question: Choose the correct action
to take in this situation.]
Here's a question. Choose the correct
action to take in this situation.
Huh?! This is part of the test?!
The correct action? Our only
choice is to run away...
[Clock Tower]
A bicycle?
Nunchucks? A hanger?
A dirty soccer ball?
A clock tower?
I see! I have to use one of these objects!
More than anything, I should choose
to escape. In that case...
This is it!!
This is the correct answer!!
Oh no! So that was the correct answer!
You fell?!
The answer is, "We'll use that cut for the
outtakes during the ending credits."
[Note: Parody of a Hong Kong
Kung-fu action movie.]
I can't use that!
Let's go! We're going to shake them
off with a car chase. I'm good at that.
There they are. Stop!
This is bad.
Why your nose?!
If you can protect your nose, you
should've protect your butt!
Don't worry about us! We've overcome
danger like this many times.
You're just fools!
It's a dead end.
Crap!
There they are! They're over there!
Oh no! They're after us!
[Question: Choose the correct
action to take in this situation.]
Here's a question. Choose the correct
action to take in this situation.
You should take the correct
course of action!
Honestly...
We've got to fight!
[Note: Parody of "Enter The Fat
Dragon" by Sammo Hung]
Wrong. The correct answer
is to call Fatgon.
Fatgon!
What is it, Dragon?
Why Fatgon?! Why is he here?!
If you called Un Pyao, you would
have gotten half a point.
[Note: Parody of Yuan Biao. Also
a Hong Kong action star.]
Why would I do that?!
Anyway, we've got to
get away from here!
I see! But I won't give you a point for that!
I don't need any!
Again?! Why is Edo filled
with dead ends?
What is the Shogunate doing?!
That's a poignant Anti-Foreigner
Faction-like comment.
I'll give you three points.
You're annoying!
This is the end of the line...
Here's a question. What do you think
Fatgon should do in this situation?
[Question: What should Fatgon do in this situation?]
That has nothing to do with Jackie
anymore! He's Fatgon!
Sorry, Dragon, I don't want to die.
I'm disappointed in you!
You're no different from
when you were a thief!
I'm disappointed in you for trying
to get help from a thief!
We'll talk afterwards. Get them!
Exam student, use your body to
protect the secret document!
You should protect more
than just your nose!
All right, now!
Here's a question!
Your comrade is being attacked!
What should you do?!
Why don't you just ask me for help?!
Katsura is my enemy.
Captain Dragon is allied with
the Anti-Foreigner Faction.
In that case, there should be no
problem if I abandon them.
But this is an undercover mission.
A spy must become an Anti-Foreigner
Faction member in mind and body.
In that case...
Let's run away, Katsura-san,
Captain Dragon!
An Anti-Foreigner Faction
member must sometimes
be cold-hearted in order
to accomplish his goals.
You should have run away.
I can't give you any points for the test.
But you pass as a human being.
Crap... We were almost there.
It's still not over, yet.
We've still got more tricks!
That's a really cool thing to say,
but this is all to much...
Here's a question.
Your comrades can't help you and
you're surrounded by bad guys.
Choose the correct course of action
in this hopeless situation.
I don't know... What should
I do in this situation?
The correct answer is...
To not give up!
But...
Take the secret document and run away.
Huh? But what about you two?
We'll...
Protect...
Our new comrade!!
Katsura-san!
Captain Dragon!
Go! Get outta here!!
Don't let our efforts go to waste!
Go!
I won't let you!
Katsura-san, Captain Dragon, I'll
come back with reinforcements!
Don't let him get away!
I won't let you!
I need to get help! I need
to find help right away!
Katsura-san and Captain Dragon are...
Huh? Huh?
You did well. You passed magnificently.
From today on, you're an Anti-Foreigner
Faction member!
Katsura-san, Captain Dragon...
You dropped something...
[Shogunate Special Armed Police Shinsengumi
Investigator Sagaru Yamazaki]
Huh?
What?!
[Preview]
The next episode... "People Are All Escapees
of Their Own Inner Prisons."
[Were Yamazaki's actions worthwhile?
Katsura is thrown in jail.]
[The steel fortress, Prison Island.
Can Katsura safely escape?!]