Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[Note: Parody of Dragon Quest
IV Ch. 5 title "The Chosen."]
["The Chosen Idiots"]
That's Lady Tama's main system.
It's already been taken over by the viruses
and converted into their stronghold.
The brains behind the Tapir
and their extensive invasion
dwell inside-the Archfiend Tapir.
The progenitor of all the Tapir spreading
throughout Lady Tama's body.
The king of the Tapir.
We won't be able to stop the Tapir
invasion unless we destroy him.
To return peace to this world...
To save Lady Tama...
We must defeat him.
The Archfiend Tapir is like the
main system for the Tapir.
Destroying him should render
the Tapir powerless.
The problem is how we're going
to reach the Archfiend Tapir.
As you would expect of the
enemy's main base...
Black bodysuits everywhere you look.
And they all look stronger than
the ones we've fought before.
This is the Archfiend Tapir's territory.
The place is swarming with the latest viruses
created by the Archfiend Tapir.
They won't be easy to defeat like before.
We'll need to come up with a plan.
Come on now.
Give me a break.
Why slow down after coming this far?
Those new viruses are just pseudo
DQ characters that spawned from
the virus eating her DQ-crazed brain.
Like this guy.
We don't need a plan to
deal with these freaks.
Just go on a rampage.
Wait!
Only the most foolish of fools
would suggest "rampaging"
straight into the Archfiend
Tapir's stronghold!
A party with you as its leader would run
out of MP before reaching the Archfiend
and be forced to jot down a long resurrection
spell to even make it halfway there.
[Note: Parody of Dragon Quest III.]
What an idiot.
The party would be wiped out
if we followed your orders!
I am the hero who will save Lady Tama.
[Note: Parody of Jester class and Luida
character from Dragon Quest III.]
A Jester like you should go
goof off in Luida's bar!
Who are you calling a Jester, damn it?!
Sure, I might goof off!
But the son of Bianca and I will
become the Heavenly Hero!
[Note: Parody of "Dragon Quest V: Hand of the Heavenly Bride." Bianca is one of two women whom the player can choose for the hero to marry.]
So I'm no ordinary Jester!
I'm the Heavenly Jester!
It would be best to avoid combat
before we reach the Archfiend
and conserve our health.
Use herbs to heal.
Hey! You listening to me, cosplay freak?!
We'll go with a "no magic" tactic.
Uh, we don't have any
magic to begin with.
How can we defeat the Archfiend
with such a conservative tactic?
Are you an idiot?
A stingy party led by you would
carry so many herbs
you wouldn't be able to open
any treasure chests
and get wiped out with full MP before
you even reach the Archfiend.
We should all use "Firevolt"
except for Kiryl.
[Note: Firevolt is a powerful spell.
Kiryl is a priest from Dragon Quest IV.]
I've never heard of that tactic!
Who's Kiryl?!
[Note: The Defeat spell one-hit kills enemies. Useless on bosses. Kiryl (aka Cristo) tried this spell on Archfiend in Dragon Quest IV.]
Kiryl is the Shinpachi-like character
that stupidly casts Defeat
on the Archfiend if you leave
him to his own devices.
It's better to keep him silenced.
Are you trying to say I'm useless?
You don't even know how to use
Kiryl properly? Laughable.
It appears that you are unqualified
to lead this party.
Shut up.
You wanna live on a cart with
Kiryl, Borya, and Torneko?
Wanna live a gloomy life badmouthing
the best members behind their backs?
There they go again.
The two of them are hopeless.
Tama, do something.
Understood.
Then we'll compromise and go with "Keep
everyone except Kiryl healed up."
You want Kiryl to die?!
Was that directed at me?!
Am I that useless?!
Whatever then. We'll go with that.
Firevolt Kiryl.
Why are you being mean to Kiryl?!
You're attacking Kiryl now!!
Whatever then.
I'll settle for "no Kiryl."
You think Kiryl's a nuisance, too?!
This will never end if we leave
it to the stupid heroes.
I'll go draw them out.
The rest of you head for the castle.
Kagura-chan!
She's the real hero here!
That was damn ballsy!
Way cooler than some
other people I know!
Stop wasting time!
This is our only chance!
Let's go!
Wait!
The lead position is reserved
for the hero!
I am the hero who will save Lady Tama!
What do you think you're
doing, Mr. Cosplay Hero?
The party will be wiped out with
a psycho like you in the lead!
I'll do it!
A Jester should be getting
a puff-puff in Ashalam!
[Note: In Dragon Quest III a woman in Ashalam town
gives a "Puff-puff" (wiggles her boobs) service.]
I am the leader of this party!
Don't mess with me!
Loto, the hero, should get lost!
[Note: Main character from the first
three Dragon Quest games.]
[Note: Main character for Dragon
Quest IV, V and VI.]
This is the age of the Heavenly Hero!
Hey!
What are the two of you doing?!
We don't have time for this!
Did you just cast Defeat?!
You just cast Defeat, didn't you?! Hey!
What's wrong with the two of them?
They have the exact same face
yet they can't get along at all.
Tama-san, was that person
really based on Gin-san?
They hate each other's guts.
Forget about being the strongest combo!
They're the worst possible combo!
While cake and ramen both taste good,
combining them into cake ramen
will ruin the dish,
leaving you with something that
tastes absolutely horrible.
I may have made a terrible
miscalculation.
That's a fatal error!
You brought the two of them together
without even thinking it through?!
Crap! The enemy spotted us!
Quick! Run away!
Gin-san!
Leukocyte King!
Do not touch me with your
virus-infested hands!
[Domestos]
[Note: A toilet-bowl cleanser.]
Domestos!
Is that all a hero can do?
Forget Kandar...
[Note: Boss from Dragon Quest III.]
[Note: Slime is the weakest
monster in Dragon Quest.]
You can't even defeat a single slime.
Now it's my turn!
Take this!
Magiclean!
[Magiclean]
[Note: A line of all-purpose cleaning products.]
Is that all you're capable of?
Forget slimes...
Your mother will come to wake
you up in the morning,
and you'll already be a corpse.
Behold the power of the hero!
[Ariel]
[Note: A laundry detergent.]
Can't touch me!
[Charmy Green]
[Note: A dishwashing detergent.]
Not yet...
[Febreze]
[Note: An odor eliminator.]
Not yet!
What?!
[Family Fresh]
[Note: A dishwashing detergent.]
What are you trying to hit?!
[Dove]
[Note: Refers to Dove brand soap.]
Now for the finish!
[Mama Lemon]
[Note: A dishwashing detergent.]
What are they doing?!
This is crazy!
No, look.
The army of viruses are being
wiped out by their fighting.
I didn't make a mistake.
Those two are the strongest...
That's...
Their attacks are melding...
This is...
That light is...
[Kamikaze]
["Super explosion caused by a mixture of light and dark power. Burn away the enemy, your own party and everything. It's very dangerous so please don't aim at people. Only use this in wide open spaces. Do Not Eat."]
[Note: Parody of warning labels.]
Hey now.
Are those guys okay?
Who's the strongest duo again?
Those two are obviously
not meant to be mixed together.
[Note: Parody of warning label on detergents.]
It was a mistake to pair them together.
You know how they say you'll die
if you run into your doppelganger.
At this rate, they'll get
the rest of us killed.
But they were able to do significant
damage to the virus army
and we have managed
to infiltrate the castle.
It's as I planned.
Liar!
This is like reaching the boss with
your HP and MP in single digits!
The window is all red!
What are we supposed to do?!
Don't worry.
Many of the recent final bosses,
right before the final battle...
Show me everything you've got.
I'll kill you slowly.
...say stuff like that.
Often restoring all your HP and MP.
We'll count on that.
Why are you depending
on the final boss?!
Just to be clear, this isn't a game.
There aren't any save points
or resurrection spells.
Die once and it's over.
Could you please stop fighting?
This isn't the time to be
hurting one another.
Are you scared of dying?
Go ahead and turn tail and go home.
As I said in the beginning,
I can handle this myself.
Hey!
Why do you have to be so abrasive?
Gin-chan and you...
No, we're all the same.
It isn't just your appearance.
All of us have been protecting Tama
on the outside and the inside.
Why do you refuse to cooperate?
Don't you care if Tama breaks down?!
That's why I'm telling you to leave!
You all came here to save Lady Tama.
I know you all care deeply
for Lady Tama.
But because you feel that way...
Because you are willing to
risk your lives for a robot,
it means there are also other things
you strive to protect.
Things and people on the outside...
I'm different.
I was made for the sole purpose
of protecting Lady Tama.
I live to protect Lady Tama.
I don't care about what happens
to anyone besides Lady Tama.
I have no interest in anyone
but Lady Tama.
Looks like you're interested in something
else besides Lady Tama!
Why are you getting greedy and falling
for such a cheap booby trap?
D-Do you understand now?
I'll have no trouble protecting
Lady Tama by myself.
It sure doesn't look that way.
You look hopelessly unreliable!
Idiot!
I-I've been through more ordeals
than the lot of you.
Your whole life must have
been an ordeal.
It doesn't matter how many lives you have
if you keep falling for these cheap traps.
Leave if you understand!
Uh, then let go of me.
You've got one heck of an iron grip.
Leave after you've dealt with this!
Damn nuisances!
I am the only hero needed
to protect Lady Tama!
Isn't he just like you?
He has difficulty expressing himself...
He's antagonistic...
He's all based on you.
You see me as such a
shameless person?
As I observed you and collected data,
he evolved into someone
more human than I was.
That is why I could not stand by
and watch him die alone.
You should be able to understand...
Why he keeps telling you to
leave so he can go alone...
Why he acts so hostile...
Did you bring the two of us together so...
Hey! Your body's...
It appears... that the... Tapir...
have reached...
the backup system... that
created this copy...
There is... no time...
Will you... listen... to my... final request?
It will... probably be... impossible
to... recover my... system...
The Tapir... are already... deep... inside...
At this... rate...
he won't... be able... to survive...
Forget... about... me...
At least try... to free... him...
from this... place...
My fr...d... who has... protected
me... for so... long...
Protect... my oth...r... friend...
Tama...
Sorry, but I can't honor your request.
If he really is my clone,
he would never want that.
And I won't let anybody die.
Not your friends
and not mine.
Listen up!
Do not let a single rat
into the throne room!
The system of this world will soon
fall into our Tapir hands!
Until then, we must protect
the Archfiend Tapir!
Victory is within sight!
Now go forth!
Wh-What?!
That wasn't what I meant
when I said "go"!
I didn't mean for you to go and die!
Hey! Come back, guys!
Yo.
I've always wanted to ask something.
How does the Archfiend feel when
a level 99 Hero comes for him?
Does he feel like turning
tail and running?
Or does he try leveling himself up?
If that's the case, I would recommend
the Capillary Caves to the west.
[Note: A Dragon Quest monster.]
There's a high chance you'll run
into Liquid Metal Slimes viruses.
In the end, it doesn't matter
how many levels you gain.
'Cause when you multiply 99 by
2, you get a level 198 Hero.
Except I'm level 100.
I'm actually level 101.
No, I'm actually level 103.
This world has already fallen under
the absolute control of the Tapir.
You cannot change anything.
It's all over.
Can you not comprehend that?
It's not over.
One last security measure remains.
As long as I, the Leukocyte
King, am still here,
this world will continue to exist after all
the systems have been knocked out!
I will protect Lady Tama!
You truly believe you can defeat
me and save this world?
Leukocyte King...
No matter how many heroes you bring from
other worlds, you are powerless against me.
I guarantee it.
You cannot defeat me.
You cannot even harm me,
let alone defeat me!
Because you have fought to protect
this world for so long...
Because you love this world
more than anyone else...
You cannot defeat me.
Th-That's...
I-Impossible...
It's...
Lady Tama!
Wh-Wh-
What the...?!
Why is Tama-san here?!
Why is Tama-san the Archfiend?!
D-Damn you!
You've assumed Lady Tama's
appearance to confuse me!
I won't fall for such a cheap trick!
Leukocyte King!
I-I can't control my body...
I can't get near him...
As I said...
The systems of this world
are under our control.
This is no disguise.
This is my true form.
This body now belongs to me.
You are trying to fight against
the person you have been protecting.
As one who was created
to protect this world,
you cannot defy me.
So my body recognizes
you as Lady Tama
and refuses to attack?
Impossible...
How could this...?
As I said, it's all over.
Defeating me will destroy this world.
There is nothing left for you to protect.
Will you still try to defeat me?
Will you still try to destroy the virus even
if it means destroying this body?
Can you kill Tama?
Firebane!!
[Note:  A spell from Dragon Quest.]
[To Be Continued]
[Preview]
We are left with no options
as we face the
overwhelming power of
the Archfiend Tapir...
Our last hope lies in those two!
The next episode...
"Tama Quest IV: And Into the Legend..."
[Note: Parody of Dragon
Quest III subtitle.]
Uh, that's DQ III's subtitle.
[Tama Quest comes to its conclusion next week!]
[The power of the Archfiend Tapir
sends everyone back to dots.]
[See you next time.]