Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hurry it up...
I'm begging ya.
Make it quick.
Please...
Hurry...
End my suffering!
Why don't you finish me off?
Why must you waste time?
Kill me!
Just get it over with!
Do you enjoy torturing me?!
Please!
I can't stand just sitting here
waiting for my death!
I'll go insane!
I beg ya!
Quick!
Kill me!
Um, Sakata-san.
Excuse me, but could you keep it down?
You're disturbing the other patients.
[Namu Dental Clinic]
Sorry about that...
["People Of All Ages Hate The Dentist!"]
No...
I hate going to the dentist.
That distinctive odor...
That shady easy listening music...
The echoing whir of the drill...
And the wait... It's like waiting
for your death sentence...
Damn! I SO wanna go home!
Go home, latch on to Sadaharu,
and cuddle in his fur!
But my tooth hurts...
No, but I'm scared of the treatment...
How many times have
I gone through this?
Just put me out of my misery.
Sure, a candy lover is doomed
to a life of cavities,
but that aspect of my character's
been forgotten, you know?
There was no scene of me
eating sweets lately.
They're gonna drill.
They'll stick that thing in my mouth for sure.
A drill doesn't belong in your mouth.
It's the last thing you
should stick in there!
That's not what a doctor's
supposed to do.
What do I do?
Will I die if I sneeze when
the drill's in my mouth?
Am I gonna die?
What do I do?
Will I die if that sucking tube
thing gets my tongue?
Am I gonna die?!
Stop, stop!!
Enough already!!
I'll stop thinking about it.
I'll read a magazine or something
to take my mind off that.
JUMP... JUMP...
What? This place prefers Magazine?
[Note: "Weekly Shonen Magazine"
published from Kodansha.]
I guess it can't hurt every
once in a while...
Here to clean your tobacco
stains? You nicotine addict!
Can't you tell from my face?
An old silver cap decided to rot on me.
Damn, anything with the word
"silver" in it is bound to fail.
[Note: Part of Gintoki's name is "Gin",
which is silver in Japanese.]
Let go. I grabbed it first.
No, we touched it at the same time.
And don't you prefer JUMP?
Let this Magazine fan have it.
It's a good idea to check
out the enemy at times.
So what if it's the 50th anniversary?
[Note: Weekly manga magazines "Magazine" by Kodansha and "Sunday" by Shogakukan celebrated their 50th year since being first published together back in 1959.]
Why are you teaming up with Sunday?
Something's up there.
What, are you jealous?
You want in or something?
You upset about not being
invited to the party?
Heck no.
Go enjoy it yourselves.
It's easier for us to go solo.
No point in cooperating when you
guys have no chance against us.
You've got it backwards.
Don't you understand that
everyone hates you?
Can't you tell that you're being shunned?
Please keep it down.
What? Pretending to be popular?
You're disturbing the other patients...
Haven't you realized that Sunday's only
pretending to be a buddy to Magazine?
He was trashing you on the way
home from school the other day.
Sunday would never do that!
Don't make shit up.
[Note: "Weekly Shonen Champion" is
manga magazine from Akita Shoten.]
Go ask Champion.
He heard it too.
Shut up!
What do you know about Sunday?!
Keep on pretending to be all tight!
Too bad you're anything but!
Hey! I told you to
shut the hell up!
Everybody knows already!
Gangan and Ace know too!
[Note: Monthly manga magazines. "Gangan" is published by Square Enix and "Shonen Ace" is published by Kadokawa Shoten.]
I just had to run into this jerk.
Why did I have to bump
into him of all people?
I have to act calm.
I can't let him know my weakness.
I can't let him know that I still
hate the dentist at this age!
Hey, can you cut that out?
Constantly fidgeting...
How many times are you
going to cross your legs?
You're making me nervous.
And what about you?
Your leg's been tapping like crazy.
[Note: Restless Legs Syndrome is known as "Poor People's Shake" in Japan, based on how poor people are often always shivering, etc.]
Could you cut it out?
You're gonna make me poor like you.
I'm all irritated because of your fidgeting.
Oh?
Is that it?
Are you scared?
The Demon Vice-Chief?
Huh? What?
No idea what you're talking about.
Scared of what?
Was there something scary
about the dentist?
No, not really.
Nothing at all.
You said that because there's
something to be scared of.
Which means you're the
one who's scared?
Hell no.
You know how people say that the
sound of a drill can be scary?
Not that I would understand.
I don't get it either.
Hell, I want a drill in my
mouth every week;
come in to get plaque removed
on a regular basis.
What? You don't do that?
I have the whole package
done every three days.
My mouth feels all icky if I
don't get that drill in there.
Oh, really.
I have my own drill at home so
I don't have to come here.
Since I'm a driller.
Driller?!
What the hell's a driller?!
Why do you have your own drill?!
He's crazy!
No fear of drills!
Oh, you're also a driller?
What a coincidence.
Interested in entering a
drill contest with me?
Drill contest?!
No way! I don't wanna do that crap!
This guy enters a contest like that?!
He's a monster!
Sure, if I'm off that day.
Well, I'll try to keep my schedule open.
Huh? What are you two
doing here together?
Hasegawa-san.
You guys are also having
teeth problems?
I was taking a walk and decided
to stop by for a drilling.
A drill? What are you talking about?
Are you also here for a drilling?
A drilling? Well, I'm here to get treated.
I just stepped out for a bathroom break.
But man...
The treatment here really hurts.
O-Oh, really...
I hate those month-long treatments that require
you to keep going back to the dentist.
I heard that they did it in one shot here.
Sure, they're fast, but it hurts.
I felt like screaming so many times.
Hasegawa-san!
Are you finished?
Oh, sorry! I'm on my way.
I'll be going then.
You'd better prepare yourselves.
I-I see...
It hurts...
W-Well, dental treatments are
supposed to hurt.
Th-That's right...
To the point where you wonder
if it worked if it didn't hurt.
Hmm? You look a little pale?
Not at all.
Hasegawa-san, don't struggle!
It's dangerous so you have to stay still!
Hold Hasegawa-san down.
Tie him down to the seat.
Ah, yes. Like that.
Doesn't this sound a little too painful?
What kind of treatment is this?!
Doctor! Hasegawa-san's pulse!
Perform CPR. If it doesn't work,
bring out the defibrillator.
Defibrillator?!
Why would a dentist need that?!
Doctor! His pulse is back,
but the shock threw "that" loose!
Threw "that" loose?!
What's "that"?! What's loose?!
Oh, it's okay. We won't
be using that again.
Dip it in the ponzu sauce.
[Note: Ponzu sauce is a citrus based sauce
often used as dip for shabu-shabu.]
Dip it in the ponzu sauce?!
What are they doing?!
Wouldn't this go better
with sesame sauce, Doc?
Sesame sauce?!
Are they having shabu-shabu?!
They're having shabu-shabu, right?!
Okay, that should do it.
It's over?!
They finished it with a ponzu sauce?!
How do you feel, Hasegawa-san?
Man, it's like the pain's completely gone.
Not just your pain, but like a part
of your body's also gone!
It's been dunked in ponzu sauce!
You'll be able to eat anything you
want now, just like before.
Man... Thank you very much, Doc.
We've included some painkillers and
a toothbrush specially made by us.
Thanks for being so considerate.
Take care now.
Thank you very much!
Man, I'm completely better now.
It was damn painful, but the
dentist was pretty good.
Look, they even included a toothbrush!
Included as in literally included?!
Wait!
Your teeth are fine now, but you lost
something more important instead?!
That's way beyond an
equivalent exchange!
You should come in for a new toothbrush
if the bristles wear out.
May I say something...?
Yeah! Speak your mind! Sue them!
That's one crazy quack!
I need a hard toothbrush
to get the job done.
That's not the issue here!
Yes, no problem.
We included a hard toothbrush
on your crotch to be safe.
It'll get hard when you play around with it.
That's not the point!!
How are you supposed to
brush your teeth with it?!
Only your wife can reach down
there to brush with it!
Well, you take care now.
Oh, it's Toshi!
You guys are also here to get treated?
Kondo-san...
Man, this dentist does good work!
I'm completely better now!
They even included an...
electric toothbrush.
Electric toothbrush...?
Isn't that Hasegawa-san's arm?
Well, it smells like ponzu sauce,
but it's pretty useful.
Hey! It's obviously Hasegawa-san's!
Really? I don't like the idea of
letting machines do the work.
You have to brush your teeth
with your own hands.
Yeah, that'd be your hand right there.
And hasn't your hand been
replaced by a toothbrush?
If Hasega...
The electric toothbrush starts to rot,
please come in to get it replaced.
She was about to say Hasegawa-san's
arm, wasn't she?!
Excuse me...
I'm having a hard time getting
the brush to reach my mouth.
Is that okay?
It's fine.
If it doesn't reach, use a toothbrush in
your own hand to brush your teeth.
Why'd you include the arm then?!
That's just harassment!
Take care now, you two.
Take care, my ass!
Why don't you take care
of your patients first?!
This isn't dental care. They're
modifying your body!
This dentist is crazy!
It's way too insane!
H-Hey...
What are you doing? Get outta here!
This is no dental clinic.
[Note: An Evil organization from the Kamen Rider series. Shocker performs modification operations that gives the subject superhuman fighting abilities.]
It's Shocker HQ.
Stop being stubborn and scram.
Hey, what are you doing?
Go home, please!
I'll give you 300 yen.
What's wrong with this guy?
Why doesn't he run?
Get a clue!
I can't leave until you do, fool!
Could the next patients
please step inside.
Two at a time.
No way. You're kidding.
Are we seriously going?
Well, let's see how deep
that drill will go this time.
Will it reach my soul?
No! I don't wanna go!
How would a drill reach my soul?!
I have no idea what I'm saying!
Why do people dig?
Because they have drills.
What was that?!
Am I an idiot?! An idiot?!
Stop pretending to be
a man and run for it!
Hey! Somebody!
Anybody!
Stop us!!
Hello.
I'm Yabuta of the Namu dental clinic.
Sakata-san and Hijikata-san, right?
I'll be taking care of you today.
Don't be so nervous.
It won't hurt.
Well, just relax. C'mon, relax.
A-A crime scene?!
Is a dental operation room supposed
to be this red?
Wasn't it supposed to be whiter?
All spic-and-span?
Was dental care always so bloody?
Weren't the instruments more compact?
Was there a chainsaw involved?
Is this how going to the dentist was like?!
Well, you've both got
some swollen faces.
Why did you leave it alone so long?
That's no good.
The mouth is like the
entrance to a human.
Also the first step to
getting to know a person.
You can judge a person by their teeth.
Yeah, most people with
dirty teeth are slobs.
People who keep their teeth clean
probably listened to their parents.
Yep, that's why I always tell my
young patients the following.
When you go on a group date, looks
and personality don't matter.
Check their boobs first.
Doc, the door to your entrance
has fallen off its hinges...
You can judge a person
after seeing their boobs.
This Doc is terrible!
Women with big areolae on their breasts have big
hearts that are more forgiving of adultery.
He's talking about boobs!
The door's fallen loose,
and there's a toilet-like smell coming out!
Like Niwa-kun's place where you go
in the door and it smells like a toilet!
The toilet is his entrance!
And women with small areolae on
their breasts tend to be smothering.
You've gotta be careful.
Nobody would want to smother you!
Areolae are the key to women.
Nothing else matters.
What kind of a group date would involve
looking at their areolae?!
What kind of group date did you go to?!
Okay...
Let's get down to business.
I'll have an assistant take
a quick look at you.
Well, it's possible that my assistants
will be able to take care of you.
G-Good... He's not doing the treatment.
Hey! You two!
Yes!
Yes.
Nakayama-san and Battle
Fairy Shazzan-san.
Which do you want?
Nakayama-san!
Definitely Nakayama-san!
Anybody but Shazzan-san!
Ooh, what to do?
Which one do you like?
I prefer the one with black hair.
And what the hell is that?
Why is Battle Fairy Shazzan
working in a dental clinic?!
What the hell is Battle Fairy Shazzan?!
Which do you want to look at you?
I want Nakayama-san!
Sakata-san was a little faster.
Then Sakata-san will
have Nakayama-san.
Wait!
Uh, hold on!
Right on...
I dodged a bullet there.
The name's Nakayama.
I'll be taking care of you, Sakata-san.
Y-You're Nakayama?!
Wait!
Hold on!
You totally look like a
Battle Fairy Shazzan!
You're obviously not Nakayama-san!
Suck on that.
I don't know what's going on,
but I guess this lady was Battle
Fairy Shazzan-san.
W-Well, I'm all yours, Shazzan-san.
I am Battle Fairy Shazzan.
I'll be taking care of you.
Why?!
Well, Nakayama-san, Shazzan-san,
do your best.
Roger.
So Nakayama-san and Shazzan-san
are both battle fairies?!
Then, we shall explain this clinic's system
before we commence treatment.
Before you do that, explain how you've
ended up as battle fairies!
Our clinic will treat your dental maladies,
and also provide operating services
to prevent any future cavities.
That's way beyond a dentist's job!
Then we'll move on to an explanation
of your options.
Option A provides treatment of your cavity
and surgery to modify your body.
Option B provides surgery to modify
your body and comes with free drinks.
Option B has nothing to do with my teeth!
Why are there free drinks?!
Uh, excuse me.
Isn't there an option that skips the surgery
and gets my cavity treated?
You'll save money by choosing Option A instead
of getting the treatment and surgery separately.
No, I don't want the surgery.
I just want to get this cavity treated!
Then I would recommend
either Option Z or X.
What are those?
Option Z includes a massage when
you get your cavity treated.
Option X includes a salad bar
when you get treatment.
A-Ah, then I'll take Option Z.
With the massage?
Yea, whatever. That'll do.
Roger.
Whew... I managed to avoid the surgery.
I'm Betty. I'll be taking care of you, boss.
They attached a massage girl!
I ended up getting modified!
And this has nothing to do
with preventing cavities!
This thing has no intention
of doing its job!
Couldn't they give me a higher
quality girl at least?!
Allow me to explain.
Pleasure Fort Betty and Sakata-san
have been neurologically connected,
which means that the robot
Pleasure Fort Betty
appears as an actual massage
girl to Sakata-san.
[In Actuality]
[Through Gintoki's Eyes]
Our service is perfect.
That was close!
I was about to end up the same way!
But I already learned that I should think
carefully from the battle fairy deal.
Option X!
Treatment with a salad bar service.
This is the right answer.
Uh, I'll have Option X.
Roger.
No way you can attach
a salad bar to a body.
Thanks. Your failure saved me
from making the same mistake.
[Note: "Baa" here is used to mean "old lady" not "bar"]
Th-They gave me a Salad Baa!
[In Actuality]
They got me!
This is what they meant
by a "salad bar"?!
And what's the point of this?!
[Through Hijikata's Eyes]
She's just sitting there eating salad!
And she's using dressing
instead of mayonnaise!
This just sucks!
I'll have to watch this old lady eat salad
without mayo for the rest of my life?!
Okay, that should take care
of the preparations.
Preparations?!
What could this possibly prepare us for?!
Then we'll begin the actual
treatment now.
Treat my body before you treat my teeth!
Give me back my original body!
Open wide.
Please relax.
There's nothing to be scared of.
You're damn scary!
Open wide.
Your face will be blown
off if it touches the drill.
That huge-ass drill can't fit in my mouth!
Don't worry.
The modifications mean that your body
will suffer less from the treatment.
Well? There shouldn't be much pain.
Now that you mention it...
It doesn't hurt at all.
Our clinic specializes in swift care,
but that puts a heavier
burden on the patient.
The surgery modifies your body to cope with
the care and allow for safe treatment.
Uh, safe?
This stopped being safe when
you modified our bodies!
Hold on a second...
Is all the damage being
shifted over to them?!
They bear most of the pain,
so relax as we treat you.
[Through Hijikata's Eyes]
Uh, that's no ordinary pain.
It's pretty hard to relax
while that's going on.
[In Actuality]
If it weren't for them, you would
be feeling even more pain.
[Through Gintoki's Eyes]
So we don't feel any pain, but whatever's happening
to our body causes that much pain?
[In Actuality]
Is that okay?! Huh?!
[Through Gintoki's Eyes]
No! Stop!
Don't look at me like that!
[In Actuality]
What? Is it my fault?!
Was I wrong?!
[Through Hijikata's Eyes]
This isn't my fault.
[In Actuality]
Yeah, I have nothing to do with this!
Huh? What is this?
I've got this weird image in my mind.
Hey! What is this?
Like my life is flashing before my eyes?
Or is this Betty's life?
And what's with the fake memories?!
I don't remember anything
like that happening!
Stop! Don't show me that creepy stuff!
I didn't do anything wrong!
This has nothing to do with me!
I'm the one who was modified
and getting screwed!
Huh? What is this?
Strange images are flowing
into my mind.
Hey, are these flashbacks...?
The salad old lady's life is
flashing before my eyes?!
And she has no actual memories!
It's all about vegetables!
Are you okay with this?!
Dying without any decent memories...
No, I want to get my cavity treated.
I don't give a damn about
a salad old lady!
It's not my fault! It's not my
fault! It's not my fault!
Yeah!
We didn't do anything...
WROOOOOONG!!
Um, excuse me.
This isn't a dental clinic.
I know.
Well, you obviously have cavities.
You should go see a dentist.
We don't care about the cavities.
It'll rot and fall out soon enough.
Then why are you here?
Please fix her...
[Preview]
Okay, people.
Clean out your ears and listen good!
Okay!
Will do!
Next time on GinTama the anime...
"Countdown Begins"!
Huh? Why isn't there any reaction?
Come on...
["Countdown Begins"]
We're not falling for that again.
[The countdown finally begins
for GinTama the anime.]
[See you next time.]