Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Do you know the origin of the word "hard-boiled"?
It comes from hard-boiled eggs. Right, the moon tonight looks hard-boiled.
Why would "hard-boiled" refer to something other than hard-boiled eggs?
It may still be too early for young kids who love JUMP to understand.
[Note: BUSINESS JUMP is JUMP for men in their 20s-30s.]
When you grow up and read BUSINESS JUMP, then ask that question again.
One thing I can say...
That is...it's on such a hard-boiled night that you feel an irresistible urge to drink.
Men can only quench their thirst with alcohol.
[THE HARD-BOILED DETECTIVE]
[HEIJI KOZENIGATA]
[Note: Kozenigata's name is based on Heiji Zenigata, a hero from a Japanese novel.]
I'm a hard-boiled detective... A lone wolf.
I'm a hard-boiled detective... Working for an organization does not hinder me.
[ACT 1]
[THE AFTERNOON OF THE WOLVES]
Attention criminal! You're completely surrounded!
Well, I don't care anymore. Harmony? Class cooperation?
I get tired of hearing about the morality of such impositions!
I'm really tired! People should just die!
I won't trust anyone anymore. I'll never be fooled again.
It's more important to conserve nature than protect humans!
It's a shame that I didn't get invitations from any club on the day of my college entrance ceremony!
[Note: In Japan it is very common for clubs to invite new students on the day of their entrance ceremony. Almost everyone is invited.]
But so what? You can't judge a person like that! I can't work anymore!
H-Help!
So, I'll get involved with as many people as possible,
stir up trouble and run away! Get ready, you bastards!
Is that all you have to say?!
Huh?
Boss Kozenigata!
I'll take care of this.
Boss!
If you follow an organization and its rules, you can't do something like this.
Yes, a little tip about being hard-boiled is...to have a little courage and...
[THE HARD-BOILED DETECTIVE]
[HEIJI KOZENIGATA]
I'm a hard-boiled detective... Life is a battle.
I'm a hard-boiled detective... No need to rest.
[ACT 2]
[A WARRIOR'S REST]
There's no rest for the hard-boiled.
In this ruined downtown, there's crime everywhere.
So we hard-boiled detectives keep fighting every day.
Boss! Something's happened! The terminal's been overrun by aliens.
Boss?!
Ah...No... I feel sick today, so I can't. I don't feel like doing anything.
I don't want to work anymore. It's like I can't get motivated.
Boss...
I'm a hard-boiled detective... Always faced with danger.
[THE HARD-BOILED DETECTIVE]
[HEIJI KOZENIGATA]
I'm a hard-boiled detective... Constantly risking death.
[ACT 3]
[TIME LIMIT]
B-Boss! It's a time bomb! What should we do?!
I'm always putting my life in danger.
But a hard-boiled man like me always gets into pinches like this.
B-But the time is...
[Note: Haji's name is based on Hachi (Hachigoro), who is an assistant to Heiji Zenigata.]
Ca-Ca-Calm down, Haji.
You're the one who needs to calm down, Boss.
Your hands are shaking. And you look like you're peeing in your pants...
There's more...
...my chest hair is growing!
[THE HARD-BOILED DETECTIVE]
[HEIJI KOZENIGATA]
[ACT 4]
[NIGHT]
Mama...
I'm a hard-boiled detective... A hard-boiled egg.
[THE HARD-BOILED DETECTIVE]
[HEIJI KOZENIGATA]
I'm the hard-boiled detective... Heiji Kozenigata.
[ACT 5]
[ENDING]
Hey, don't get carried away!
You'll be in trouble if you underestimate this TV show.
Hey, hey, stop being such a stick-in-the-mud.
A hard-boiled person won't yield to any threats or pressure. That's what...
[END]
No, it's not finished yet. It hasn't even started!
Shut up! If GinTama doesn't start right now,
they'll really pull the plug and cancel us this time.
Damn it! Five minutes have already passed!
Well, the hard-boiled anime, "GinTama," will now begin!
Do you know the origin of the word "hard-boiled"?
It comes from hard-boiled eggs. Right, the moon tonight looks hard-boiled.
Why would "hard-boiled" refer to something other than hard-boiled eggs?
It may still be too early for young kids who love JUMP to understand.
When you grow up and read BUSINESS JUMP, then ask that question again.
One thing I can say... That is...
it's on such a hard-boiled night that you feel an irresistible urge to drink.
Men can only quench their thirst with alcohol.
Master, give me a Camus on the rocks.
[Note: Camus is a brand of Cognac.]
[Note: Shochu is a type of alcohol common in Japan and Korea.]
Here you go, Shochu.
It's not Shochu. You can just call it Camus, Master.
Don't call me master. You can just call me Pops, sir.
Yes, I'm the hard-boiled detective, Heiji Kozenigata.
The current era isn't easy for us hard-boiled people to live in.
Yeah, this is Kozenigata.
What?! An incident?!
People on the road look like...
That's him. Over there!
...half-boiled eggs.
It's the fox!
It's Chogoro the Foxfire!
He ran in that direction. Follow him!
For those guys...
[Note: A Jutte is a specialized weapon used by law enforcement officers during the Edo period.]
...I use the Jutte at my waist as punishment...
Yo, why are you in such a hurry? Are you late for a date?
Girls don't like men who finish early, boys.
Boss Kozenigata!
If I give them just one big blow, they'll become scrambled eggs.
The fox! It was wearing the mask of a fox!
All right. Even if it costs me my life.
You guys go that way, and I'll look this way.
All right!
It looks like I had a bit too much Camus, huh?
Well, but it may be a good restorative...
Hey, are you all right?
You look pretty drunk.
You'd better throw up.
How about coming to our shop and having a nap?
[Costume Club]
[Monster Fox]
[Nurses, female ninjas... Can change into anything.]
There're many cute girls in there.
Instead of mice, foxes are finally showing their true colors.
Surrender quietly fox!
Can I role-play something like that?
Ah, it's a detective role-play. We offer undercover-agent role-playing, too!
Really? Basically, I'm an "M," so I love being treated rough.
I'm the hard-boiled detective, Heiji Kozenigata.
["Hard-boiled Egg On a Man's Heart"]
A smoke after work... There's nothing better than this.
It's my happiest moment. It's no exaggeration to say I work hard just for this.
Men can bet their lives on just one thing.
What's the deal of sounding like you accomplished something?!
You were playing during work! You bastard!
What the heck are you doing?! What does "one thing" mean?
Is that the 10,000 yen for one time?!
Men have one thing they can't stand.
Stop saying awful things with that hard-boiled tone!
Moreover, you came back drunk and brought them!
I said the mask of the fox. Why did you bring someone wearing a costume?!
Why are you always like this?
I always thought there was something uneven between your appearance and working ability!
You act like you can easily handle all of your cases!
But why are you so useless? Why is your hard-boiled so pointless?
Some things may seem useless to some people...
But that's all about men care about.
Shut up! I don't want to hear that from someone so useless!
Hey, stop smoking that cigar!
How can you smoke a cigar while your boss lectures you?!
I'm going to kick you out!
Heiji while you were off acting hard-boiled somewhere there was another victim.
Don't tell me...that fox again?
Right, it was him again.
He snuck into the shop and did everyone in, from the owner to the workers.
That fox became a wicked man.
And you Heiji have been chasing him for ten years and still can't capture him.
It's all your fault.
If you had caught him, there wouldn't have been any more victims.
If you had caught him, the fox wouldn't have turned so bad.
You're the real criminal! I should arrest you for being so useless.
You were suspended. Well, we're sorry.
It's because we invited you into our shop and put you in that situation.
But you also made the mistake of thinking that we were criminals.
So I guess we're even now. We did our job, anyway.
The Odd Jobs... You'll do anything as long as you get paid...
It's a job far from those who are hard-boiled.
What? Do you really look down on us that much?
I can't believe I'd...
I'm not depressed. It happens all the time. So many things happen in life.
It doesn't matter if good things... or bad things happen.
Either way, I have a glass of Camus... Nothing changes my day.
Camus... The man's...
That's enough. It's so annoying.
What did you do, bastard?! My hard-boiled...!
That's enough. You repetitive hard-headed fool.
Hard-headed?! It can't be helped since it's hard-boiled!
Your brain is so full of hard-boiled nonsense you can't work.
So quit being so hard-boiled! You idiot!
Mother?!
That way, both you and hard-boiled will be happy!
No, no! I can handle it! I can have it both ways, hard boiled and working.
Well, you already failed at being both hard-boiled and hard working...
Sir...
...you'd better stop now, or your wife will get upset again.
Don't bring complaints about work back home. That's how a man acts.
He's doing it again.
You have to be cool in front of your wife.
That's the key to couples living in harmony.
That's why I'm having Camus today to rejuvenate myself.
This guy just wants to say "Camus" all the time.
He thinks he's hard-boiled whenever he says "Camus."
All things aside, I'm surprised that he even has a family.
It's said that you can't judge people by their appearance.
No, it's the opposite. In this guy's case, he's messed up inside.
Even though I didn't say a word, it broke my heart... Camus...
Speak normally!
Sometimes you can make your wife happy just by sharing your problems and listening
to what she has to say. That's the way couples stay in harmony.
I bet you failed to capture the fox again, right?
Humph.
Really, this master is too wise for me.
He already knew so much about me.
Think about it, we've known each other for over 10 years, Camus.
He said "Camus" again. He's really pushing himself to be hard-boiled.
It's like he's my real dad. I guess he probably feels the same, too.
No, I don't.
Drop dead old man. Camus.
He can't be considered hard-boiled anymore.
By the way, the fox made his first appearance in Edo about ten years ago.
Well, you've been trying to capture him since then.
That means I've been hearing your complaints for ten years.
The fox has changed a lot over the years, too.
The elusive criminal and legendary thief-Chogoro the Foxfire.
There was a time when he didn't kill,
just stealing riches and giving them to the poor so that he could earn respect.
However, he became a wicked man who stole anything and killed anyone.
But he used to be a thief, so he wasn't really a good guy anyways.
...He's not like that.
I'm pretty surprised I actually said something like that on the fly.
You liar! You look pretty calm.
The thief... I can't believe I'm supporting the enemy I've been chasing for over ten years, Camus.
But as his enemy... or as his rival... we've had so many fights.
That's why I can see something like this.
Men are creatures who understand each other only after fighting it out with their fists.
What kind of flashback is that? It's not even fighting!
It's so one-sided, with you taking all the hits. That's your wish?!
That was...not the fox I knew...
A guy who doesn't live by his own rules is useless, regardless of whether he's good or bad.
You're the useless one.
I don't know if he's bad or good, but the fox I knew at least lived by his own rules.
[Thanks for the food.]
He's like a mischievous guy who sneaks into a house, leaving a piece of fried tofu and a thank-you note.
Although he was a thief, he had a sense of humor. He was really cool.
There's no way that kind of guy would kill people.
Boss!
Haji, what's the matter?
Something terrible has happened! Look at this!
This is...
[MY NEXT TARGET WILL BE THE GOLDEN FRIED TOFU STATUE AT OEDO MUSEUM. TRY TO STOP ME, IF YOU CAN. TO THE BAKUFU GOVERNMENT.]
[Note: In Japanese mythology, fried tofu is a favorite food of the fox.]
...A letter foretelling a crime?!
This was found in a house the fox snuck into tonight.
He completely underestimated us.
If we can't catch him after he distributes a message like this, we'll...
That bastard! How could he do something so hard-boiled?!
Wait.
Are you certain you want to violate your suspension just to clear your enemy's name?
It's not something like that.
I just...I just have my own style.
I'll destroy that rotten egg with my jutte!
That's my way of being hard-boiled!
Sir, you didn't pay the bill yet.
Oh, sorry about that.
He's not very cool.
And he's using only small change to pay.
What kind of hard-boiled person is he?
In case you don't return, I charged all your bills.
Hey, old man, you're really hard-boiled! He's so callous.
Good night, Master.
I told you not to call me master.
Well... Then I'll give all of these to you, sir.
Ah, what's this, old geezer?
Sir, you just said you're an Odd Jobs man and that you'll do anything.
I already told you that I've been hearing that man's complaints for ten years.
A fox or a racoon...
I'm getting sick of it. I'd rather not hear it anymore. I just want him to finish it.
Please help, Mr. Kozenigata.
Hard-boiled! It's the real thing!
He's the embodiment of hard-boiled!
I can't stand this anymore! Master is the best hard-boiled man, after all!
Don't call me master, I'm just an old man.
Hard-boiled?! You're hard-boiled! Was that hard-boiled?
As I said, you're using hard-boiled too many times,
so I'm getting confused about what it actually means!
Hard-boiled!
...Camus.
You're really insistent!
There's so much security.
Of course! Because the Magistrate's reputation is on the line.
We need to sneak in there and capture the fox before them.
But that'll make us look like thieves.
Don't worry about it. I'll guide you.
Most undercover agent teams consist of ex-convicts.
You need a thief to catch a thief.
And that is what I used to be.
So, I'm really good at this stuff.
That's what I'm so worried about!
Somebody get this kid outta here!
Hey, don't make so much noise!
What are we going to do if the security guards discover us?
What are you doing?!
At a time like this, you should give up being hard-boiled!
Are you an idiot? Really an idiot?
Idiot! This bike was abandoned.
A hard-boiled man always encounters a hard-boiled bike.
[Note: Taka is from the detective drama TV series, Abunai Deka (Dangerous Cops).]
In Abunai Deka, Taka always picks up an abandoned bike on the street and chases the criminals, you know.
Well, Taka is sort of hard-boiled...
You're seriously deranged!
This is really dangerous so get out of the way!
Everyone stay away from this detective!
All right. I have to get off, right?
Hey! I'm getting tired of pointing that out!
How much hard-boiled equipment are you carrying?
Why are you in a bathrobe?!
You look like a hard-boiled man who is done for the day!
[Note: Kagura is singing "Cat's Eye" by Anri in the background.]
Taka said that he wears a bathrobe to work.
You! Whatever. Stop trying to be like Taka!
Geez, take it off.
Huh? Take this off?
Just take it off. It pisses me off when I see it.
Change into tights.
No, tights won't do. They'll bulge.
It's all right. Cobra in Space Cobra wore them and he bulged, too.
[Note: Space Cobra is a TV anime based on the Cobra manga in JUMP.]
But where can I change?
Um... This kind of place doesn't look very...
What are you, a little girl?!
You're a man, aren't you?!
Aren't you a hard-boiled man?!
Because I'm hard-boiled, I have to struggle to do the right thing.
As a hard-boiled man, I can't change like mere kids...
I already told you to stop doing that! That's enough!
Hey, Kagura, give him another one. You...
Here I come!
The suspect! There's the suspect!
Good, the diversion plan worked like a charm.
You liar!
Use this opportunity to sneak in from the back.
Don't let Kagura's death go to waste!
[Preview]
The next episode...
Hey, what about Part B?! Didn't the eyecatch just air?!
We'll see you next week!
It's because you took up all that time before Part A!
The next episode... "Hard-Boiled Eggs Don't Crack," Camus.
Mitsumeru Cat's eye
Magic play is dancing.
Midori iro ni hikaru
Mitsumeru Cat's eye
Magic play is dancing...
[Chogoro the Foxfire's next target is the Golden Fried Tofu Statue.]
[Will Kozenigata be able to capture him? And... What's the pair's fateful past?]