Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[This week, after a long absence (?), it's a two-parter.
The common theme is "?????"]
[We'll reveal the answer at the end of the show!]
So this is that place... The restaurant exclusively
for Amanto that recently opened.
[Beauty SHOCK Club]
[Note: Parody of Bishoku Club a Gourmet Club
from the Oishinbo manga.]
Yeah. It's where discrimination
against us Earthlings begins.
They say Amanto VIPs live
it up all day and all night.
Tsk...
Let's go.
May I have your attention, everyone.
I'd like to introduce a new employee.
Let's welcome him with
a round of applause.
Let's give him a hand!
Okay, introduce yourself, please.
How do you do? I come
from Nebula Zura78.
My name is Joey Katsura.
[Note: Parody of Joi, meaning
Anti-Foreigner Faction.]
Please be good to me.
Isn't he an Earthling?
["Japanese Restaurants Abroad Taste Pretty
Much like School Cafeteria Lunches"]
[No Earthlings Allowed!]
No need to be concerned, everyone.
He's just a pitiful lad who's often mistaken
for an Earthling because of he looks.
Isn't that right, Joi-kun?
It's not Joi, it's Joey.
But I'd rather you called me Katsura.
As you know, we don't allow Earthlings.
We serve only Amanto VIPs.
Our specialty is sashimi on a boat.
How surreal.
Did you say something?
Anyway, we have a reservation
today by high-ranking VIPs
from a royal family of
a planet somewhere.
I'll need you to work hard on
your first day, Joi-kun.
No, please call me Katsura.
Katsura-san!
Are you serious about posing as
an employee at that restaurant?!
Rumor has it that radicals are
targeting Amanto bigwigs
at that restaurant and they're planning
to blow it up with the Amanto inside!
It's reckless to go in there alone!
It's too dangerous!
Don't worry. It's easier if I work alone.
I will put that restaurant out of business
and force it to close for sure...
In this case, I can understand
how the radicals feel.
But if they get violent, there'll
be needless casualties.
That's why, what I need to do
is make the Amanto leave
before the radicals do anything stupid.
Katsura-san!
That's reckless!
Come back!
[Be careful.]
Got that, Katsura-kun?
I'm going to introduce you to your
Senpai who'll oversee you.
You, step forward.
As you were.
This is Hata-koh. Although he
joined us just a week ago,
he's still your Senpai, so ask him
anything you need to know.
Um...Have we met before?
I don't remember anyone like you.
He's to be pitied, as well.
Seems he was mistaken as part of his own
collection and discarded along with them.
Let's see...we don't want
anything in this room.
Take them all away before
that idiot returns.
If you see anything that might
be of worth, leave it here.
Throw everything else out.
Damn old coot!
Anyway, he'll look after
you. Try to get along.
That's right. Ask me anything.
Joy Toy, was it?
It's not Joy Toy. It's Joey Katsura.
I can't do an S split.
[Note: Parody of Yinling of Joytoym, a swimsuit model
known for her leg spread pose that looks like an M.]
No, he's not an S, he's
an M. He can't do S.
[Note: S&M refers to sadism/masochism]
Yeah...
Don't worry.
But what if...
I said don't worry.
All I need to do is to set this bomb
to go off after the restaurant closes.
That'll put them out of
business for a while.
Hey, newcomer. What're you
doing? Give me a hand.
I was practicing my S split.
...Oh, you did it.
Done.
That's a lovely sea captain.
I'll buy you anything you want.
Really?
Welcome.
Stop.
Go and clean the windows
or something, newcomer.
But...
Watch and learn.
Hey, Earthling.
This is no place for scum like you.
Tch, I'm not sitting with apes like them.
Just having Earthlings in the
vicinity ruins my appetite.
Apes should eat ape food.
My eyes!
Hey! What're you doing
to the customer?!
You know, they say the eyes
are the window to the soul.
Not his eyes!
And you, Hata-koh! What're
you teaching him?!
Joey! How useless can
you be?! Do as I do!
Where are you wiping?!
They say the zipper is the
window to the world.
Shut up!
Huh?
I-It...came off? Y-You...are an Earthling?
Oh, come on. Look
how easily
this comes off. See?
You guys! Quit horsing around
and get back to work!
Why am I stuck doing this sort of work?
Just as I thought, this restaurant is an ugly
place where they make fun of Earthlings.
I'll revert to the original plan, and...
Hey newcomer, what're you doing?
I got a little hungry, so I was looking
for something to snack on...
I found dried squid, see?
That's my charm point!
Just curious, Senpai...
Why are you working at a place like this?
You said you were discarded
by mistake, right?
Why not go home?
Well...because John is here.
...John?
Yes. John, the space lobster who
lives in the restaurant's fish tank.
He's a lovable sort. I fell in love
with him the moment I saw him.
If I'm not careful, there's no telling
when John might get eaten.
I can't leave him.
If everyone believed in "love and peace"
and loved animals like I do,
everything would be fine.
Well, I'm worried about John,
so I'll go back first.
Love and peace, eh?
If I detonate this, the tank
and John won't survive.
It's a tiny life, but if there are casualties,
then I'm no different than the radicals.
I will use my own methods...
...to accomplish my ambition.
Wh-Who are you?!
This is divine retribution!
We've come to pass judgment
on the likes of you who
discriminate against Earthlings and
undermine and ruin our country!
Go repent in hell!
Hmph. Anti-Foreigner Faction samurai,
eh? I figured as much.
I'm ready for you.
Uh-oh...what's going on? If these
guys start fighting here...
the tank...
and my John...
Darn! I didn't think the radicals
would show up so soon.
Stop it!
I won't allow this! You're all
fools with no compassion!
You mustn't injure him!
Don't put a single scratch
on his precious shell!
If you do, I'll...I'll...
I won't forgive you!
Are you talking about Amanto lives?!
Then I'll start by...
killing you first!
What?!
Huh?
...No more...no more bloodshed...let
there be...
Love and peace!
Ka-Katsura!
S-So he was an Earthling?
We are all living creatures...
Doing harm to any of them
will not solve a thing.
I finally learned that today. Yes...
From Senpai here...
...Katsura...
Senpai...
Dammit! I paid good money to eat here!
What's the meaning of this commotion?!
I was having a great time after finally
finding a replacement for
the idiot I disposed of!
Isn't that right, my new Prince?
You see! The Prince is angry!
...Huh?
That's odd...there are two Princes.
Cut it out!
Damn you...I'll kill you! Enough of this!
I'm gonna pound you to death!
Out of my way.
[Note: Katsura is talking like a mother.]
If that's how it is, then you guys
can do whatever you want!
I've had it!
Mother?
I must say it took a long
time to get to this point.
Since joining this shop as an apprentice,
Chef wouldn't let me handle a knife, so
I worked the menial jobs in the kitchen.
Everyday, I diligently watched the Chef as he
made sushi so I could figure out his technique.
And I practiced his technique
for forming the rice.
Now finally, he's entrusted me
with a branch restaurant.
This time, I'm going to succeed.
Good for you, Chef Hasegawa!
Stop it, you're embarrassing me!
A man should have a trade.
Your wife who ran out on you
might come back now, eh?
You've worked hard.
Today, I want all of you
who supported me
to be the first ones to try
the sushi I've made.
Everything is on the house.
Eat all you want!
I haven't had sushi in ages!
What shall I have?
Here it comes.
My, how delicious the
cucumber rolls look!
Shall we share some, Kagura-chan?
Sure.
The next one is also a cucumber roll.
You're good at cucumber
rolls, Hasegawa-san.
I think that's what I'll have.
...Another one.
Oh well, cucumber rolls might be a good
way to get the stomach started.
What do you think we are, vegetarians?!
There are cucumber rolls
from here to Gandhara!
[Note: Gandhara is a location from the
Journey to the West Chinese novel.]
Why're you being so stingy?
Bring out the fatty tuna!
Bring out the sea urchin!
Why do you think we
took precious time off
to come and see someone like you?!
I can't make anything but cucumber rolls.
The truth is, I don't know
how to make sushi yet.
["Once You've Taken a Dish, You Can't Put it Back"]
[Edo Style Sushi-go-Round Kabukicho branch]
So you're telling us that the story
about the Chef recognizing
your abilities was a lie...
and the truth is the Chef is in the hospital
and unable to come to the restaurant,
so he hired you, a part-timer, and
left you in charge of the place?
He said everything would be fine because
there was this sushi machine,
but it won't do a darned thing.
It's almost time to open for business-
what should I do?
This place will become the "completely
hopeless sushi restaurant" Madao!
Right now, all we can do is
repair the sushi machine.
Take a look at it, Tama.
Understood.
What's that?
Tama can communicate with machines
and can find the cause of the
problem so we can fix it.
[Canned oil]
Want some? Mind if I stand
here next to you?
[Note: Parody of common soap opera
themes among office workers.]
What's the matter? You look blue.
Could it be you're still bothered by
the microwave oven manager?
Awesome. This is totally the scene
between two female office workers.
Who's the microwave oven manager?
I told you to forget about him.
That guy...has no intention
of leaving his wife.
You're not the only one.
He nuked Rejiko in
general affairs as well.
[Note: Rejiko means cash register.]
They're having quite an
involved discussion.
Stop acting like a child!
Don't give up.
Be strong!
Don't let Tokyo-or yourself-
get you down!
I did all I could, but it appears unfixable.
You completely destroyed it just now!
You finished it off.
Hey, what're you going to do about this?
That was my only hope!
There's no time left.
I'm starving.
W-Welcome.
Catherine and I will man the counter.
You follow our lead and take
care of things in back.
G-Gotcha!
Th-Thank you, everyone for
helping me out with this.
Don't worry, Hasegawa-san.
When we need help, we help each
other out, right? Leave it to us.
But you have less experience
with sushi than I do-
there's no way you can make sushi.
No one expects perfection at a
conveyor belt sushi restaurant.
As long as there's a topping on top of a decently
formed rice ball, we'll be able to fool them.
Hasegawa-san, at the very least,
would you mind teaching
us how to form the rice?
Even if you know how to make
only cucumber rolls,
you did watch Chef make them, so
you know how it's done, right?
All right. It was monkey see, monkey
do, but watch closely.
First, you take the rice.
Be careful not to take too much.
Squeeze the rice not too
hard, and not too soft,
with one hand so that
air gets into the rice.
Put on the wasabi, then the
topping. And the sushi....
is done.
What the?!
How did that end up turning
into a cucumber roll?!
Something happened when
we switched scenes!
It's hopeless. I can only
make cucumber rolls.
You were so close just now.
You placed a slice of tuna on top.
How'd that change into a cucumber roll?!
[Note: The literal translation for cucumber
roll is "water imp roll."]
He must be cursed because his
ancestors killed a water imp.
He is hopeless.
This won't do. We'll just put Hasegawa-san
in charge of cucumber rolls.
I think I got the general idea.
I feel I can at least make something
that looks like sushi.
I agree. There's no heat involved, so
I'm sure even you could do it, Sis.
Shape it so air gets into the
grains and add the wasabi.
Place the topping, and give it
a squeeze. I did it. It's done.
What is that?!
Why is it burned to a crisp?!
When did you add heat?
What did you just do?
Actually, I've been a bit feverish
since yesterday.
How hot are you?! Go home!
Go to the hospital immediately!
For your lousy head!
You guys fail because you don't know
what you're doing and
you think too much.
You don't need masterful skill.
All we have to do is get the shape
right, even if it tastes bad.
See?
You get the shape right!
This isn't even sushi anymore!
Taste it before you complain. Will
you be able to, once you do?
I won't eat it! It has the look of
an entry in a pastry contest!
All right, we'll put Gin-san's parfait and
my toasted rice ball on the side menu.
That's not a toasted rice
ball. It's a burnt corpse.
Ow!
Kagura-chan, what're you doing?
What do you think of this?
Ohhh! Now this...
That's awesome, Kagura-chan!
It's a perfect piece of sushi!
It's sushi no matter how you look at it!
This would be all right to serve in
the restaurant, don't you think?
No, it's too big.
Where did you get a slice
of tuna this huge?!
It's been my dream to
bite into a huge sushi.
You're not supposed to
make it for yourself.
Where in the world are you going to
find someone who can eat this?!
We have an order for
egg roll and shrimp!
What're we going to do?
We still don't have any finished
sushi except cucumber rolls.
Let me handle this.
Tama-san!
I have sufficient data on sushi.
Would you please ready the ingredients?
She ate it?!
No.
Sh...She's...!
Done.
We can't serve that!
How gross can you get?! Are you King
Piccolo?! That's mostly vomit!
[Note: Refers to a Dragonball character.]
A robot does not vomit. I simply prepared
the sushi inside my body.
There's something gooey all over it!
That's oil.
This is no time for talk.
Regardless of how it was made,
this looks the most decent.
I'll save you the trouble-
I'm putting it out.
Just a minute!
Wait!
Delicious!
[Note: Customers are parodies of Kaibara Yuzan
and Yamaoka Shiro of Oshinbo manga.]
What is this new texture? It has a
flavor I've never tasted before!
Thick and smooth, yet not overpowering!
What is this?!
It's a revolutionary new sushi!
Hey! I want the same thing!
Me, too!
Same here!
The same!
It's a miracle. A miracle happened.
We can do this! This is going to work!
Keep her spitting them out!
Keep her fed and keep
her spitting them out!
Bring all the ingredients we
have in the restaurant!
This is incredible! The plates
are flying off the line!
There's a long line out front, too!
We did it! We've done it!
Hasegawa-san! With so many customers,
we're running low on ingredients.
What?!
Dammit. This was my
chance to make it big.
How much of a Madao can I be?!
Go.
You go and do whatever it takes
to gather up ingredients.
We'll hold down the fort
here until you get back.
Hurry and go!
I'm counting on you!
Toshi, what's with this place?
I came because I heard this was a conveyor
belt sushi restaurant, but...
the only things on the belt
are cucumber rolls.
The guys said this place was cheap
and delicious. Was it bull?
The attitude of the staff is the worst.
What's with them? I'm
going to tell them off.
Don't, Toshi. Let's eat our meal quietly.
What's with that melting parfait?
Why're they sending it around?
Keep it chilled.
Hey, Toshi, what's that?
Could that be dark matter?
Why would dark matter be spinning on
the belt alongside cucumber rolls?
It's 300 yen. What should I do?
Should I take it, Toshi?
Never mind the dark matter.
When's the flatfish filet sushi
I ordered going to show up?
[Flat Curry]
What was that just now?
What's curry doing in a sushi shop?
Didn't it have "flat curry" written on it?
Toshi, maybe that's your order.
No, it's not. What I ordered
was flatfish filet.
Well, yeah, but...
[Flat Curry Filet]
Toshi, after one cycle, it's
getting a little closer.
No, it's not. I ordered flatfish filet.
[Flat Curry Filet on Flat Board]
Hey, it's gotten to "flat curry
filet on flat board."
This has to be yours.
I didn't order curry, I ordered flatfish.
[Hurry up and take the curry, stupid.]
Who're they calling stupid, dammit?!
Hey, it's totally sending you a message.
Hmph. I'm not taking it.
Why do I have to eat curry
at a sushi restaurant?
[Note: "Ika" means squid.]
Anyway, what's keeping my ika?
I haven't seen it at all.
Hey, wasn't that Ikazo Sandaime? Could that
be your order, Kondo-san?
No, it's not. I ordered ika, not Ikazo Sandaime.
Maybe not, but he's giving you the eye.
No. Don't look at him!
He's stuck. Ikazo's stuck.
He's stuck but he's still looking this way.
Ikazo's looking this way!
What's with this place?
Let's go home. This is creepy.
I don't get this place.
Hey! Ikazo's bringing curry!
He intends to force us to eat both of them!
Stop!
Isn't it delicious?
Wait for me, everyone! I'll be there soon!
[Preview]
Can I do it, Senpai?
Cattle abduction? Sure, go ahead.
Hey! Give me back my analog stick!
The next episode... "Novices Only
Need a Flathead and a Phillips."
[Beings from the planet Gamer arrive at summer's end.
The Odd Jobs are modified one after another!]
[What? What were the hidden words?
The common theme was "giving up."]