Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Who...are you?
Where's Utsuzo?
He's not here.
He left this world a long time ago.
What?!
Was it you?
I'm asking you if you're the
one who killed Utsuzo.
The foolish son won't come
out even though Boss dies.
The gang will need someone
to take his place, right?
That's right. You can't have the
unreliable heir take over.
You need someone with sharp
skills and a sharp mind.
A real yakuza.
Find him!
Drag the river if you have to, but find him!
[Utsuzo, who had supposedly locked himself
inside the storehouse, is no longer alive.]
[Kyojiro Nakamura, the Mashiroi Gang's junior boss, was next in line. What secret from the past did this man people called Guardian Dog know?]
Who could have imagined that
Kyojiro would be in charge...
of Boss Mashiroi's funeral ceremony.
The one they call Guardian Dog.
The Boss had only one son, I believe.
I hear they butted heads a lot over
him wanting to live an honest life.
They say he ran away from home
and no one knows where he is.
Rumor has it that Kyojiro killed him.
Who knows what really happened.
Before the Boss took him in...
he lived like a stray dog.
Hey, he might bite you in the throat
if he hears you spreading
rumors like that.
How frightening.
["Some Things Are Better Left Unsaid"]
We're asking you where Gin-san went!
I don't know what to tell you...
He hasn't returned since that night.
If you know anything, please tell us!
I don't know anything...
Dammit, you! If you're monkeying around
with us, I'll rip out your hair!
Kagura-chan, think a little before you
speak. These are scary people.
You're a spunky young lady.
But I don't know anything.
And even if I did, I probably
wouldn't tell you anything.
We're not getting anywhere with
you. Call Nakamura-san!
Right! We don't want
to deal with small fries!
Do you people understand
what's going on here?
Brother doesn't have the time
to be bothered by you.
Go on home.
That's enough.
Come this way. I'll hear
what you have to say.
So you're saying that when he learned
the Boss died, he left right away?
That's right. His client died.
It's what anyone would do.
Something's odd...
What do you mean?
It's not odd that Gin-san
didn't come back,
but I can't imagine Gin-san giving up
on the job for a reason like that.
The Boss's words were full of sincerity
when he said he wanted to confront
his son face-to-face.
That's why Gin-san accepted this
job. I'm sure that's how it was.
He commands a great deal
of faith...that man does.
Well, most of his life is
about slacking, but...
That's right! Most of his body is made
up of sugar and useless syrup,
but Gin-chan would never
give up halfway on a job!
Tell me something.
What is that man to you?
He's like family.
Family, huh?
Nakamura-san...you know
something, don't you?
Let me tell you one thing...
Nothing good happens when decent
people stick their noses
into yakuza business with
a half-hearted resolve.
That's a warning to you.
[Shutenkaku]
You all know why I called this meeting.
I wanted to discuss the
Mashiroi Gang situation.
About a successor...?
Wasn't there a spirited guy there...
What was his name now?
Kyojiro Nakamura, the Mashiroi
Gang's junior boss.
They call him Guardian Dog Kyojiro.
Guardian Dog? Are you kidding?
He's more like a mad dog.
He's sharp and he's got balls. But...
It's just a rumor, but...
However, we do have to
decide on a successor.
But we have to set an example
for the other gangs.
Okay, it's unanimous. Is that okay?
Brother!
Brother.
There's a letter for you.
It's from the organization bosses.
It's been decided.
What?
The date for the inauguration
ceremony's been set.
Then...
Yes, they've officially decided
that I am the successor.
But I'm worried...
About what?
That rumor's been going around.
Will everything be okay?
It's the truth, so there's nothing
we can do about it.
Let people talk.
But Brother...
That's enough! Leave
me alone for a while.
There he is!
Over there!
To survive, I did anything
I had to...except kill.
Anything to survive that day...
Everyone despised, detested
and feared me...
Boss! This is the brat who's
been raiding our turf!
Around here, he's known
as Guardian Dog Kyojiro,
a brat so well known that even adults
make way to let him pass.
He's a street urchin with no
parents and no home.
No one's going to complain-hey,
they might even thank us-if we wrapped
him up and dumped him in the river.
Guardian Dog.
He certainly does look
like a Guardian Dog
with those scowl lines between
his eyebrows.
You can't form lines like those
without going through a lot.
You've suffered a lot, haven't you, kid?
That settles it. I'm taking this dog.
I want to see him lose those scowl lines!
There was no enmity or insult.
The first adult who ever smiled at
me was a bigger villain that I was.
Utsuzo, come here.
Come...
From today on, this is
your friend, Kyojiro.
Kyojiro?
Kyojiro, this is my son, Utsuzo.
He's a yakuza's kid,
but he's a weakling. Look
after him for me.
From that day on, the stray dog...
became a Guardian Dog.
For someone like me,
unwanted and hated by everyone,
to be needed by someone
made me happy.
I didn't mind being a guard
dog. That's how I felt.
What?! Utsuzo was attacked
by the Zannenbi Gang?!
Utsuzo!
Daddy!
Kyojiro!
Boss was more worried
about my injuries than about his
own son...his tears felt warm.
The person who taught me-
someone with no family-what
it meant to be family was...
you, Dad.
[Inauguration Ceremony]
Dad, I made up my mind that day.
Your blood may not run
through my veins.
But I will shed my blood at the same time
and for the same things that you do.
...Yes, that's what I've decided.
That's what I decided, but...
Let's not all be so formal. Drink up.
Only those who work can
enjoy the taste of sake.
Of course the work you do
is probably only crime.
Yo! Is this a birthday party?
Happy birthday.
You're...?!
I thought we were friends?
You could've at least invited
me to your party.
I intend to repay you in full for the present
you gave me the other day.
I've been in this business a long time
and met a lot of strong guys.
But I've never met a guy who returned after
getting slashed and shot up like you.
I'm glad you're not a yakuza.
You put on quite a show here.
Those guys are the bosses
of our organization.
You'll never get out of here alive.
Is that so?
Was it because of the Boss?
You intend to take on the
entire organization
just for the sake of a yakuza
you only met once?
Yakuza or not, it doesn't matter.
Lawless fellows like you and me
have nowhere to go once we've
lost our honor and humanity.
You're exactly right.
I may've sunk low, but I'm still a yakuza.
I can't survive in this business if
I've lost my honor and humanity.
They're not my guys. It would appear...
the inauguration ceremony
was just a pretense.
Rumors of my actions have gotten around
inside and outside my own gang.
The association never had any intention
of allowing me to succeed the Boss.
They were after my life.
Kill me.
It'll be payback for blowing
a hole in your belly.
I'll let you take my life.
Having a guy like you take my
life rather than those guys
would give me something to boast
about in the other world.
You came here knowing what
would happen, didn't you?
You came here to die, didn't you?
Honor and humanity?
I'd forgotten those words
a long time ago.
I have nothing left to protect.
Nothing...
What? I dare you to say that again!
Calm down, Boss!
I'll repeat it as many times as you want!
I don't want to live with you
and your men, Father!
If it's a successor you want, there's
someone much more suitable!
I'll live the way I want to live!
Wait! Utsuzo!
Father, you have Kyojiro-san!
He's got guts, brains and strength!
He's a much more decent son than me!
Stupid fool!
Boss!
Young Boss!
Young Boss! Come on out!
This is so stupid...
Having him succeed me...
Maybe I thought that was the way
to show my love for my son.
Laugh at me, Kyojiro.
My arms may be good at hitting
and threatening people,
but they don't even know
how to hug their own son.
Young Boss...
Listen up...
Don't let the Boss near the storehouse.
Boss will die soon.
Until then, take turns living
in the storehouse
and don't let him know that the
Young Boss is not there.
Understand?
Brother...where is...the Young Boss?
Young boss...
...I killed him.
This is...how it should be...
Boss died without knowing
anything. My duty is...
Fulfilled.
I have nothing left...to protect.
Wh-What...?! Are you...
doing?!
I already repaid you for the
hole you put in my gut!
Like I told you, I only came to fulfill my
obligation to honor and humanity.
I promised the old man, you know.
That I'd bring his foolish son to him.
So draw your sword! Fight!
You understand, right,
that I'm the guy who
tried to take your life!
That kind of thing wasn't going to kill me.
I was just going along with
your lousy playacting.
You...
I saw right through you.
You're a lousy actor!
Was it you?
I'm asking you if you're the
one who killed Utsuzo.
You would kill me and shoulder all the
blame to keep the secret hidden.
And what's more,
you were going to die and take
everything to your grave?
Stop trying to make yourself look good!
If you really think of the old
man as your father...
If you're really doing this for his sake...
Live. Bring even a single lousy flower
and go visit him at his grave!
I won't allow any more of the
old man's sons die!
I won't let you die!
I'll drag you to that old man's
grave if I have to!
Out of my way!
Scumbags!
Kyojiro!
Hang on! Hey!
Dammit! Wait I'll get a doctor!
Don't bother. It hit me in the worst spot.
Don't be so weak!
You're a yakuza, aren't you?!
Don't whimper just because
there's a hole in your gut!
This is...how it's supposed to be.
I...can't face the Boss.
I couldn't protect what
was precious to him.
It's divine punishment.
He helped me so much, but I couldn't
do a single thing for him in return.
I was a useless Guardian Dog.
Once a stray, always a stray.
When I die, throw my
body in a back alley.
It's a death befitting a stray dog.
You're not a stray dog.
The rest of the world might scorn
you, but I know the truth.
Even if you had to take all the blame,
you protected it until the very end.
You're not a stray dog.
You're a noble Guardian Dog.
Guardian Dog.
He certainly does look
like a Guardian Dog with those scowl
lines between his eyebrows.
You can't form lines like those
without going through a lot.
You've suffered a lot, haven't you, kid?
That settles it.
I'm taking this dog. I want to see
him lose those scowl lines!
[Preview]
A spy's most dangerous assignment
is the undercover investigation.
I will do anything in my power to approach
the Unstoppable Kotaro
Katsura and round up the
Anti-Foreigner Faction.
The next episode... "Life is a Test."
...You mean, there's a test for that?!
[Though unremarkable, he appears more often than one would expect. Sagaru Yamazaki of Shinsengumi Investigations.]
[When he tries to join the Anti-Foreigner
Faction, what test will Katsura give him?]