Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Squiggly and squirty!
Mayonnaise.
Damn light yellow stuff!
Yummy, yummy.
Mayonnaise.
Eggs and vinegar and oil!
Naturally delicious on salad!
Still great when sucked
straight from the bottle!
A perfect miracle!!
Revolutionizes cooking!
Mayonnaise!
Hey, everyone!
Is everybody doing slurpingly well today?
Here's an announcement from Mayorin!
Does anybody want to know where mayonnaise
comes from and how it gets to you?
Guess what?
Whoever finds a ticket, 1 in every 30,000 bottles,
gets an invitation to Mayorin's home!
Mayo lovers should suck
away to find a ticket!
I'll be waiting!
That was a squishy message for your dinner
table from Mayorin Mayonnaise.
Mayo...rin...
["Hometowns and Boobs are
Best Thought From Afar"]
And so starting today, amendment
25 to bureau policy,
as you can see,
Less than Five Mayonnaise a Day is Unacceptable.
requires each person to consume
five bottles of mayonnaise a day!
What?!
Shut up!
This is an order from your
Vice-commander!
What is this?
We were told to assemble on short
notice for the sake of this order?
Maybe the Vice-commander's lost his mind
after eating too much mayonnaise...
Hijikata-san.
What is it, Sogo?
Well, I don't know what you're plotting,
but I can't understand why the rest of us
have to go along with your mayo fetish.
Eh?
'Sides, it's got nothing to do
with the samurai code.
Yeah! Yeah!
This is oppressive, even
for the Vice-commander!
Toshi, when you decide something, you need to
explain it in a way that everyone else can accept.
This is too much even for...
Hey, Yamazaki.
Explain this to everyone.
Huh?!
U-Uh, no, but...
You never told me anything...
In fact, I'd like to have this explained
to me, you know...?
Hey, I'll kill you.
Listen up, you morons!
Ya' think keeping the streets safe is enough for us
Shinsengumi during the time of this great recession?!
We need to keep the economy safe too!
Gotta do our part in building
domestic demand!
Consume lots of mayonnaise
to help the economy recover!
Our organization needs to appeal
to the public in multiple ways!
You got that, fools?!
Okay, good job.
Everybody who understands
should applaud.
Applause!
Don't hold back.
There's still dessert.
Squiggly and squirty!
Mayonnaise.
Damn light yellow stuff!
Damn it!
Squiggly and squirty!
Mayonnaise.
Damn light yellow stuff!
I can't find one...
Get that mayonnaise away from me!
Ketchup... Ketchup is better...
Everybody! Have you already
found your tickets?
There's only a little more time until
the deadline for invitation tickets.
Hurry, hurry!
That was a smooth and shiny message for your
dinner table from Mayorin Mayonnaise.
Why...?
Why can't I find one...?!
What the hell?!
What's wrong, Yamazaki?!
Vice-commander, please look at this!
I was squeezing mayonnaise out
when a weird piece of paper...
Th-This is!
This is it!!
What do we do with this?
We should probably call the manufacturer
to complain about a foreign object...
Ya-Yamazaki, that's...
Congratulations.
Huh?
Isn't that great, Yamazaki?
You can go to the mayonnaise
factory now.
Huh?
Oh? You look pale, Hijikata-san.
What? Did you force everybody to eat mayonnaise
because you wanted to go to the factory?
Even if it means taking away someone
else's winning ticket?
O-Of course not, you fool!
We said that it was to help
build domestic demand!
H-He figured it out!
That's good to hear.
I couldn't imagine that the Vice-commander would
take a winning ticket from a subordinate.
Then go have fun at the mayonnaise
factory, Yamazaki.
I-I don't really understand...
Should I be happy about this...?
Yamazaki, you...
You're really...
No, really...
Congrats, Yamazaki!
You're scaring me!
Uh, you can have this if you'd like...
It's too late for that now!
'Cause you're the one who found it!
'Cause it's only natural for you to go!
'Cause I'm sure Mayorin
is waiting for you!!
Hey, don't be so stubborn, Toshi.
Eggs...
Kondo-san...
Everybody knows your
love for mayonnaise.
And we went along kind of knowing
what this was all about.
So think of that ticket as our
blessing and accept it.
Vice-commander...
Thank you...
All of you... Thank you so much...
Gori...
I mean, Kondo-san.
Huh? Were you about to say Gorilla?
After I said all those nice things, you
were about to call me Gorilla?
[Mayorin Mayonnaise Factory]
[A few days later]
Now then, members of the special field
trip, I shall take you to the next step.
I heard that we get mayonnaise
as a souvenir this time!
All right!
These new facilities are amazing!
Thank you for visiting today.
Ma-, Ma-...
Mayorin...
Where are you?
Ah, man. Give me a break already.
Why do I have to wear
this suffocating thing?
My underwear is stuck
to my ass like crazy.
It's all like, is that my underwear
or my ass?
Like I'm it and it's me.
We don't have a choice.
It'll get ugly if we don't go in prepared.
Would you rather be killed
or have sticky underwear?
Getting rid of a beehive?
Why did you accept this job?
And from what I heard, we're up against
their violent brothers, the wasps.
It'll be fine.
Since we came in full gear.
Hey, don't underestimate those wasps.
They're nothing like those soft honey
bees making their high school debut.
These big guys aren't satisfied
by transporting pollen.
[Pollen]
They even carry out hits.
It'd be no problem for them to raid
another school in small numbers,
and end up slaughtering them all.
They don't care if they knew you
back in middle school.
Not to mention impregnate the school madonna and
raise the young by feeding them the corpses.
They're devils.
Insane bastards.
And we're crazy enough to
go destroy their home?
There's still time.
Let's buy some soba and sake and give
them a warm welcome to the hood.
Pathetic.
They're just a bunch of bees. Bees.
They might be big,
but that's only relative.
Seriously...
Ah, are you Odd Jobs?
Over here, over here.
Ah, sorry to keep you waiting.
I apologize about making you
come all the way out here.
Well, that's the one I mentioned.
It just popped up when I wasn't looking...
Can you do something about it?
["The Whole Peeing on a Bee Sting Is
a Myth. You'll Get Germs, So Don't Do It!!]
How does it look?
Well, I'll leave it up to you...
What's that supposed to mean?
[Note: From a 70's dating game show
called "Propose Daisakusen"]
Are we playing "Feeling Couple" here?!
Are the two of us supposed
to build a love nest now?!
How is that a beehive?!
More like a salamander nest!
F-Forgive me!
But, there wasn't anything
there last night.
These popped up all over
the place overnight.
What kind of world would have bees that
could build a nest like that in one night?
Is the queen a slave driver?
You shouldn't be talking when
you don't even pay us.
Master Monk, I'm sorry to say
that this isn't from Earth.
It's an alien species.
It's too dangerous.
We can't handle it.
Could you please deal with it?
Consider my occupation...
I couldn't take a life.
But you're okay with humans dying?
You're okay with us being incinerated
by salamanders?!
This will be a nuisance to the
neighbors if I leave it alone.
I beg of you.
We shall also cheer you on.
We shall pray for you.
Stop the chanting!
That's bad luck!
Then rap should be okay.
Hey!
They'll do it if we rap!
Ah, hey! Wait!
What are you...
Right, there was a tape.
Yeah, yeah!
What do we do?
They went to get a tape deck.
We're leaving.
Who knows how big the
bees in that thing are?
These protective suits won't do a damn.
It'll be over if they plunge into us.
But what will happen to the
monks if we just ignore it?
Don't worry about it.
Monks and bees get along
well so they'll be fine.
[Bouzu = Monk]
Didn't Shonen Magazine
have a "BOUZU BEE"?
No, that was "BOYS BE..."
Same difference.
It's that manga where everyone's
crotch stinger is twitching, right?
It's over.
What are you doing?
Hey, Gin-chan, Shinpachi.
Don't talk to me!
I know nothing at all!
I'm a rotting corpse who has
nothing to do with that fool!
Nothing good will come of stinging me!
I'm just a rotting corpse!
Gin-san!
Does playing dead work against bees?!
I've never heard of anyone doing that!
Are you sure about this?!
Is it going to work?!
Don't talk to me!
Do you wanna die?!
And why are the monks
also playing dead?!
Hey!
How dare you play dead by
yourself after talking to me?!
[Please take good care of the garden.]
Huh?
It's awfully quiet...
Gin-chan, what do we do next?
Huh? I don't sense anything
coming to attack us.
Normally, they would come swarming out
in a rage after that much of a mess.
I guess we should be safe.
Hey, maybe this wasn't a
beehive to begin with?
Huh?
I mean, who's ever heard
of such a huge beehive?
Then what is this?
A prank?
That monk didn't seem very nice.
The neighbors probably hate him.
Don't mess with us!
We don't have time for this crap, damn it!
Hey! You two!
Oh dear...
Whatcha doing, big guy?
Uh...
Don't give me that crap. I asked
what you were doing.
Yeah... Sorry.
I didn't realize that there were
people...bees inside.
I see.
So it's okay to kick a bee house
if there aren't any bees inside?
N-No... Huh?
Bee?
So you're a bee?
So you're actually a bee?
Hey, boss!
The support's snapped in half!
No, you've got it wrong.
That wasn't me, it was her...
So the earthquake was your doing?!
Could you come down
to the office with us?
H-Hold on! Hold on!
You've got it wrong!
Coming through!
Coming through, my ass!
Whose fault do you think this is?!
Excuse me, more honey!
Allow me to introduce myself.
I'm the young head of planet
Royal Jelly, Hacchi (Bee).
Well then, we need to have a talk.
How ya gonna pay up for this?!
One or two stingers won't be enough!
Actually, we don't have
stingers to begin with.
Uh, I don't know about your
planetary customs,
but on Earth, we make a practice of eliminating
beehives for safety purposes.
And?
It's our fault for building a nest on someone
else's planet without permission?
I wouldn't say that it's your fault...
Nobody would mind if you made hives
away from residential areas...
I've also got something to say to you.
If you want us to leave,
shouldn't you ask?
Using force without even trying
to talk things through...
Isn't that how the yakuza would behave?
Earth is a damn scary place.
And we aren't angry about
our hive being ruined.
The youngins will have it back
to normal in no time.
But some things in this world
will never come back.
That earthquake sent our Lady on
her way to the hive in the sky.
The old QS3 fell out of the dresser.
[Note: Parody of PlayStation 3]
Forget about Qlaystation...
She's been sent to a completely
different station!
How you gonna make up for this?!
The Lady was our only female!
We were all her sons!
The Queen Bee dying is the
same as the planet dying!
I'm gonna stab you all dead!
Stab every Earthling dead
and destroy this planet!
Stop that, Riki.
But boss!
You were the one who bought
this QS3 at Akihabara!
Didn't I tell you?!
Be careful because the
QS3 is damn heavy!
The QSP is better!
[Note: Parody of PS2 dating
game KimiKiss.]
But boss! You were also obsessed
with ChimiKiss!
You so wanted to play that thing!
ChimiKiss was on QS2!
Not QS3!
Besides, I wouldn't bother
with that pussy crap!
It was Fetal Gear!
[Note: Parody of the Metal Gear Series.]
Fetal Gear was on QS3!
Too bad!
Liar! It was Chimi Kiss!
What's wrong with Chimi Kiss?!
Berakami was also great!
[Note: Parody of PS2 dating
game Amagami.]
Now, now, enough of that.
Have some honey and calm
down, for crying out loud.
No more fighting, you hear?
Sorry.
This is bad.
Bad.
What do we do, Gin-san?
What do we do?
Uh...
So you won't need to destroy our planet if
we do something about your queen, right?
Gotcha.
We'll be responsible for that.
In return, you'll leave if we patch
up your queen, yeah?
What?! You're saying that you
can bring the Lady back?!
You know what's gonna happen
to this planet if you fail!
Gin-san, what do you intend to do?
The fate of the planet is in our hands.
Don't worry.
There's a way.
We just have to find another queen.
Huh?
Did you forget?
These popped up all over
the place overnight.
That wasn't the only hive
built on these grounds.
We'll talk to the other hives and
ask if their queens can help out.
Is that possible?!
Didn't you say that wasps didn't hesitate to beat
up others who were in the same middle school?!
I brought plenty of honey
for negotiating purposes.
They won't turn us away.
Okay, I'm off then!
Wait!
You keep quiet and drink your honey.
Excuse me!
We were sent by Planet Royal Jelly!
Huh? Are they out?
Did they go to harvest pollen?
I'll go take a look.
Get this over with in a jiffy.
You guys better not do anything dumb.
Sit tight.
Especially you, Kagura.
Don't even twitch.
Nothing good happens when you move.
Excuse me, more honey!
Uh...
How are you going to make up for
what's happened to our Lady?
You killed her!
You actually killed her!
Wait. Calm down, Masa.
You were the one who
bought an old Zbox!
[Note: Parody of Xbox]
Didn't I tell you?!
Be careful because the
Zbox is damn heavy!
The TS is better!
[Note: Parody of Nintendo DS]
[Note: Parody of Xbox 360
game iDOLM@STER]
But boss, you were also obsessed
with iDOLM@SKER!
You so wanted to play that thing!
Who would bother with pussy
crap like IM@S?!
It was Gears of God!
[Note: Parody of Xbox360
game Gears of War]
You're obviously an IM@S fan when
you know the abbreviation!
Gin-san!
What are we going to do?!
Another hive!
Find another hive quick!
This is no good!
She's still breathing!
That's it!
[Note: Parody of Nintendo Wii]
The Owee is lighter than the other consoles,
so she was only slightly injured!
Hang in there, queen lady!
C'mon, we're beggin' you!
Can you take care of all those bees?!
Hey, don't die!
You're the only one left!
I followed you because I was worried,
and I've run into our blood enemies!
Planet Royal Pudding!
Why did you come to Earth?!
Planet Royal Jelly!
You were also targeting this place?!
I see...
Everybody was after the same thing.
Planet Royal Yogurt?!
There was someone else to deal with
before we conquered this planet
and exterminated the human race.
You aren't getting this!
I'm not letting anyone touch this!
You fools...
The QS3...!
The Zbox...!
The Owee...!
...is ours!
On that day, what started
as a beehive removal
turned into the destruction
of three planets.
We inadvertently stopped their
attempts to conquer Earth,
but it wasn't anything to feel good about.
One beehive
is the same as an entire planet.
It shouldered the burden
of countless lives.
Our lives were built upon as many lives
as there were stars in the night sky.
Yo, Odd Jobs!
We ready to rap.
Huh? You're already done?
Chant away.
Huh?
Would you say a prayer for their sake?
To all living creatures in this universe...
Namu.
You know where they went?
Not the slightest.
Anyway, wanna go hunt
down Queen Aragosta?
[Note: Parody of Queen Rangosta from Monster
Hunter Portable 2nd G for the PSP]
Let's, let's.
They're alive.
Next time:
"Beware of Foreshadows."
Is that meant for me?
[There is a "death flag" which signifies that you will die.
And once you think everything is right and well...]
[Yuden raises the deathflag and viciously
sets out to get revenge.]
[See you next time.]