Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[The man in the cell opposite Katsura who has recently been imprisoned is Suekichi, who has been trying to escape from prison for 15 years.]
[What is going to happen to this man?! This
week is "Katsura Enrichment Week" part II!]
There's Prison Island.
Throughout the ages, it's been the one prison
where the worst offenders are sent.
It's a steel fortress that encompasses
the entire island.
Once you enter, you will never
see sunlight again.
It's a real netherworld in
the land of the living.
Starting today, that's your home.
So you'd better bid a fond
farewell to the sun.
Don't worry.
I've already finished saying farewell to everyone
from Yaoyorozu to Amaterasu.
[Note: Yaoyorozu are spirits that dwell within objects and part of the Shinto religion. Amaterasu is a Japanese mythological sun goddess.]
All men are prepared for death every
morning they sit down for breakfast.
For me, each day brings absolutely
nothing special.
It's said the world is very large,
but my world has been this
small cell for a long time.
The view behind steel bars
has been my whole world.
I spend every day in this moldy-smelling
cell where my heart has been corrupted.
I don't remember how many times
my heart almost broke.
But finally the time has come for
me to leave those days behind.
That's right.
There's a boundless beautiful world out there
that's not meant to be seen through bars.
To gaze upon that world
is all I've ever wanted.
["People Are All Escapees of
Their Own Inner Prisons"]
Finally... Finally I've made it.
It's taken 15 years to dig
out of here. 15 years...
I've pounded into my mind
the guards' routines
and the times when other
prisoners are asleep.
I took advantage of a little overlap
time to dig through rock and stone,
little by little, every day. And I kept
at it for 15 years... And finally...
It's the day I escape from Prison
Island, the invulnerable fortress.
Suekichi, you've really outdone yourself.
...It was all your tenacity...
All I need to do is find the right time
to carry it out... I can't be impatient.
The best time is early morning
when the prisoners are asleep.
The best day is when the sea is calm.
I've already secured an
exit route for escape.
So I need to carefully pick the
perfect day and carry it out.
Fortunately, the prison
cell opposite mine,
which I have to watch the
most, is now vacant.
If I can escape before a
new prisoner arrives...
...there won't be any problems.
Oh, you're awake. Good morning.
Isn't it a nice day?
I'm sorry I didn't introduce myself.
You looked like you were asleep.
I just came in today. Prisoner
number "Ha-206," Katsura.
It's nice meeting you, cell mate.
Why?!
Until yesterday, it was completely vacant.
But why today, of all days, did they
have to bring in a newcomer?!
Here's something for you.
It's an Anti-Foreigner Faction towel.
It's very good at wiping away filthy stains.
Especially those from our world.
[Note: Wordplay on Joi (which also means Anti-Foreigner
Faction) and Joy dishwashing liquid.]
Because it's Joi.
Th-This is bad...
My cell is completely visible
to the opposite prison cell.
I've been able to accomplish
my work thus far because
there was no prisoner
on the opposite side.
But now... It can't be...!
And this guy looks so irritating!
Um... This is an Anti-Foreigner
Faction towel.
It's very good at wiping away filthy stains.
Especially those from our world.
Because it's Joi.
He thought I didn't hear him so he
repeated the same corny joke!
I heard it! It's not funny no matter
how many times you say it!
Calm down.
All I need is a chance to crawl through
the tunnel and escape from this island.
Even if this guy is in the cell opposite mine,
there'll be an opening within 24 hours.
At this point, I can't be picky
about the date and time.
As soon as I get the chance...
Luckily, the labor in this place is like the agony
of hell so it wears out all the prisoners.
Most likely, he'll be exhausted and fall asleep
right after he gets back from his first night.
I'll take that chance tonight when he's
so tired he'll fall right to sleep.
Just as I thought...
I can't see well in the dark,
but his snoring...
...means it's unlikely he'll wake
up from any sounds.
I've been spotted?! It can't be!
But I can feel his gaze on
me. It's boring into me!
No way!
Don't tell me!
What kind of sleeping face is that?!
This is bad! I've heard about people
who sleep with their eyes half open.
But his eyes are wide open!
His eyeballs must've dried up! He's
definitely looking right at me!
His dried-up eyeballs are
looking right at me!
What a strange sleeping face!
That was a shock. It should
be all right, right?
He's not really awake, is he?
He's snoring, anyway...
Huh? But what if he's not asleep?
This should be all right, right? No,
he's awake, isn't he? He is, right?
Something like this is not good.
I should check.
Ka-Katsura-san.
No need to worry. He's sleeping,
just as I thought.
All right!
I can go now...
So he is awake!
Why is he sleeping in a runner's
crouch?
He's not sleeping, is he?! He's
in a runner's crouch!
He looks like he's about
to run somewhere!
What should I do? Things are
getting more complicated now.
He's snoring, but... no...wait...no...but...
What's the matter, Suekichi-dono.
You didn't sleep well last night?
That's not good. You won't be able
to handle the hard work here.
Whose fault do you think it was?!
I was completely tricked by him.
I thought there was no way in the world
a guy could be this bad a sleeper.
If I keep up this lifestyle,
I'll lose all my strength.
I have to solve this as soon as possible.
I should preempt him.
Lights out!
I don't need to make him fall asleep.
I just need to create a chance
for me to escape.
Well, I've had problems
falling asleep lately.
Do you have any tricks that
would help me fall asleep?
Let's play UNO. I'm pretty good.
No, I'd better get some
sleep for tomorrow.
I see, but I'm really good at it.
No, thanks, but do you know
anything a bit more basic?
I know! Why don't we count
sheep, Katsura-san?
They say counting sheep with your
eyes closed helps you fall asleep.
Is that so? I think UNO would
be better. I'm pretty good.
Yeah, but it'll just keep me awake.
Then let's close our eyes and
start counting sheep together.
How about that? Here
we go... One sheep.
Two sheep... Three sheep...
Yes!
He won't open his eyes
until tomorrow morning.
And if it works out, he'll fall asleep.
But I shouldn't start moving yet.
I'll see how it goes after
he's counted 20 sheep.
11 sheep...12 sheep...
13 sh...?
What is Matsuko doing?
Hurry up and jump! You're
holding up the line.
What happened, Matsubara?
Did you twist your ankle?
A ladybug...was here.
Geez... You're really...
Matsuko Matsubara. She was
always smiling like that.
She could jump higher than anyone and
she was always smiling like that.
That's all.
These five people will make up the
starting lineup for the tournament.
This will be the last tournament
for you guys as third-graders.
[Note: In Japan, a third-grader is a senior
in middle school/high school.]
Do your best!
All right!
I heard Matsubara Senpai was benched
even though it's her last tournament.
She hasn't even been showing
up to practice lately.
She's not even here today.
There's a rumor that she has a boyfriend.
He's Fujimura Senpai, a third-grader.
I think he just hangs around her.
But it works well for Sugiyama Senpai.
There's no way she could
beat Matsubara Senpai.
Hey, you're talking too loud!
Sensei.
Do you have a minute to talk?
[GYM STORAGE]
What's this all about?
Why isn't Matsuko in the starting lineup?
She's our ace, isn't she?
I'm not happy about wearing the uniform of a starting
player just because Matsuko didn't show up.
I'm returning this to you.
...She quit the club.
You're the only one who can take
Matsuko's position in this club.
I'm sure you know that, because
you and her have been
competing against each other
as rivals for three years.
...I wanted to get to this
position by beating her.
Because she's my best friend, I wanted
to win the position by beating her.
...Sugiyama.
I'm sorry...
How could you?
I won't lose to you!
I'll definitely score more points than
you and outperform you...
...and I'll win the tournament!
Sugiyama...
She...
...found out about your health.
More than anyone or anything...
...she wanted to jump higher.
Hey, isn't Sugiyama here yet?
It's thirty minutes to tip-off.
What is she doing?!
Sensei! Sugiyama Senpai's
mother just called!
When Senpai was on her way...
...she fell and was taken to the hospital.
...Idiot.
You weren't supposed to come, right?
...No, I needed to come...
...to pick up...my team uniform.
Here you go.
I'm so proud that you're my rival.
Matsuko...
I regret that I chose the
same position as you.
Actually...it doesn't really
matter if we're rivals.
I just... I just wanted to...
...play on the same court with you.
That summer...
...after knowing real kindness...
She jumped higher...
...than anyone or anybody ever...
Sh...Sh...
13 sheep!
That was too long!
What's wrong, Suekichi-dono?
You didn't get any sleep
last night, either?
That's not good. You've been
looking like that for a while.
...Damn it.
All I need to do is just go through
the tunnel and escape this island.
Then I'll finally taste freedom.
Why is it so difficult to do
something so simple?
He's the biggest curse of all.
At first, he didn't seem to have any
flaws, but he's actually full of them.
Once he was provoked,
he revealed his fangs.
But he still has flaws, in fact, It's
like he's the Hell of Infinity.
As long as this guy is in the cell opposite
me, it's impossible for me to escape.
I should give up any hopes
of exploiting his flaws.
I should kill him. I won't be able to
get my freedom unless I kill him.
But how...?
Hey, are you the newcomer?
Now we have a pretty boy.
Hey, young master, what did
you do to get thrown in here?
That's...Shachi!
Robbery, murder, kidnapping...
He's the king of crime, the boss of all criminals who's
committed multiple crimes...the killer, Shachi!
Hey, what's with that look?
What are looking at, huh? Huh?
Are you picking a fight with me?
Hey, stop it! Don't get in
any trouble with him!
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I offend you?
I'm sorry. I had something
I was concerned about.
That's right! Be quiet and
don't go aggravating him.
Well...
...your kimono is torn.
Fashion!
That's just the fashion!
It's a fashion statement that
makes him look wild!
And there're scribbles on your face, too.
It looks like someone played a joke
on you while you were asleep.
Are you making fun of him?! It's
supposed to be like this, dude!
Huh? You did this on purpose? You
purposely cut it so raggedly?
Stop it! Don't mention it!
Don't talk about that!
...Not really...
Somehow...the sleeves bothered me, so I
just cut them off, and it came out like this.
Shachi! Now he's getting
all shy! He's losing face!
Hey, what are you doing?!
Be quiet and eat!
Tsk. You guys, we'll remember this.
You guys?! What's with "guys"?! They'll
all keep an eye on me, too?!
This is the worst. In order to keep my escape
plan a secret, I've kept quiet until now!
This was going to be over soon! But if
people like them keep an eye on me...
But wait! I should turn this predicament
into an advantage!
I'll plot to offer Katsura to Shachi.
That way, Shachi will owe me
and Katsura will be dead!
Two birds with one stone!
First of all, I need to get close
to Shachi's gang members.
Oh! They look pretty hostile towards me.
...Oh, well. I have to show them
that I'm their comrade.
What?! You want to meet Shachi?
Yeah. I want him to know that I have
no hostilities toward any of you.
That crazy man isn't my friend at all.
That reminds me, you didn't
bother us that time.
Shachi-san, Suekichi wants to see you.
Well, this is perfect.
Just as I thought, this ragged
sleeve style is really effective!
What is it? What do you want?
Leave me alone. Just leave
me alone, already.
Shachi?! He's cutting off the
ragged part of his sleeves!
He's been like that ever since.
He's cutting off all the ragged
parts from his kimono.
Stop it, Shachi! It's so cool!
Stop worrying about it! Those
ragged parts are really cool!
I really don't care if it's cool or uncool!
That's not the reason I wore it like that.
I'll never wear ragged sleeves again!
You're so annoying! Shachi, you really
are! How sensitive are you?
Let me tell you something...my ragged
bangs and my sleeves are not related.
Don't get me wrong! Ah, I'm going
to cut this, too! I'll do it!
Stop, Shachi! Not the ragged hair!
Hey, what are you wearing?!
Damn it! In this situation, my outfit makes
it look like I'm making fun of him!
I found another one here!
Another ragged one!
Are you hurt, Suekichi-dono?
Huh? Um...
You bastards! You made Suekichi-dono's
sleeves ragged. Shame on you!
No, his sleeves were already like that!
We didn't do that!
Shut up! What are all these
triangular pieces?!
They're enough evidence!
No! That's from Shachi's...!
Shut up!
What's wrong, Suekichi-dono?
You couldn't sleep last night again?
Katsura-san!
It's because we were playing UNO all night
until early this morning in your cell.
So he couldn't sleep with all the noise.
We're sorry, Suekichi-san. We
were so excited playing UNO.
Because Katsura-san is so
good at playing UNO.
No, Shachi, you're too weak.
That's right, Shachi.
You're way too weak!
Why?! Why did it turn out like this?!
Instead of being led to his death, Katsura
has extending his influence!
All right, everyone, it's about
time we went to work.
Yes!
He's acting like the head prisoner!
Take care, Katsura-dono.
Yeah.
How did he manage to
influence the guard?!
Who is he, anyway?!
In just a few days, he's gained
control of this hellish prison.
It could be that I've challenged
an extraordinary man.
Even if I realize the huge size
of the wall in front of me,
somehow I don't despair.
This Prison Island was called Hell,
but it has been gradually
changed by that man.
Backbreaking work has changed
into something worthwhile,
even if it's still really hard.
And criminals' eyes aren't so empty and
lifeless. They've started repenting for their crimes,
making up for their past sins
and correcting their ways
Their eyes have started looking
towards the future.
Through interaction with the prisoners...
...the guards have started
realizing the joy of forgiveness
and the value of rehabilitating people
instead of just abandoning them.
And for 15 years...
The man who avoided facing up to his crimes, who
only thought about escaping his hardships...
...and digging a tunnel...
...finally closed it off.
Man, I worked pretty hard today, too.
I've been sleeping well lately!
By the way, even that disgusting
prison food...
...is starting to taste good.
Human beings are creatures
that eat, work and sleep.
If any one of these is satisfied, the other two
will eventually become satisfied as well.
And only when these three have been satisfied
do people truly realize that they're alive.
Katsura-san, I've been looking forward
to the next day so much lately.
We're treated like earthworms,
but I feel like we are remembering what
it means to be human, day-by-day.
For the first time, I feel like I'm alive.
The one who taught us this was...
...you, Katsura-san.
Thank you...for helping us
become...humans again.
Hey, why are you crying at lights-off
time? The guard is coming.
Sorry...
Well, let's get some sleep for tomorrow.
Eating, working and sleeping.
That's what humans do.
Good night, Katsura-san.
Good night!
What's the matter, Suekichi-dono?
You still can't sleep?
You said you were a revolutionist,
but what brought you here?
I'm just curious about what kind
of crime you committed.
I didn't commit any crimes. I came
here of my own free will.
What for?
I'm a revolutionist of course.
So, I came to revolutionize Hell.
That's amazing! You make
such a bold statement!
Suekichi-dono, did I change
anything here?
...Well...I don't know, but...
...at least I've changed.
My sleeping problem is gone.
I've decided to dig a new tunnel.
It's a long tunnel and I don't
know when it'll open.
That's right. It'll lead to tomorrow.
I don't need any escape routes anymore.
I'll fight for the sake of tomorrow.
With that guy... With that man...
I'll be able to reach it.
He's finally asleep. He
gave me a hard time.
Thanks for waiting.
He was a tough guy who
didn't have any flaws.
Although I already had an escape route,
[THIS WAY!]
I never imagined I'd have a man with sleeping
problems in the cell opposite mine.
But I can easily handle it.
It looked like he was completely tricked by
me and seems to have let his guard down.
It's too bad I won't be able to see his
shocked face when he finds
out that I disappeared,
but it can't be helped.
Goodbye! You guys will stay
chained here forever!
I've been spotted?! No way! No, he's looking
at me! Someone is watching me!
All right! Looks like he's finally asleep!
He gave me a hard time.
He was a tough guy who didn't
have any weaknesses.
Although I already had an escape route,
I had some trouble getting
him to let his guard down.
I've been spotted?! No way!
No, he's looking at me!
Someone is watching me!
All right!
It looks like he's finally asleep!
He gave me a hard time...
All right! He looks like he's finally asleep!
All right!
Senpai, there're so many
holes on the island.
Huh?
Just fill them in. Fill them in.
The next episode... "There's Almost a 100% Chance
You'll Forget Your Umbrella and Hate Yourself For It."
[And another episode will be "Definitely Do Not Let Your Girlfriend See The Things You Use For Cross-dressing." For the first time in many years, those ladies will appear.]
[Huh? You want to know what happened to Katsura afterwards? Never mind. Never mind. Take a break. Take a break.]