[Focus In]
Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[Gintoki]
[Ceiling (morning)]
Hm? Something's not right.
The ceiling I usually see when I wake up isn't here today.
Actually, I just see the word, "ceiling" up there.
[Pillar]
[Background Odd Jobs
Japanese-style room]
[Screen door]
Huh? Huh? What?
What the hell is this?!
[Gintoki]
I'm all white! I'm not colored in.
Actually, this whole world is all white.
What the hell's going on?
What is this? What is this? What the hell?
Hey Kagura, this is terrible!
[Footsteps]
[Gintoki]
Yikes, this room too?!
[Footsteps]
Hey, Kagura!
Hey, wake up!! Kagura!!
[Kagura]
What is it? Why are you making so much noise in the morning?
Hey, what's wrong with you, Gin-chan? Your face is all white.
[Note: Sankai Juku is an internationally known Butoh dance troupe. Performers typically have shaved heads and bodies covered in white rice powder.]
Are you in the Sankai Juku?
[Gintoki]
Now why on earth would I be in the Sankai Juku dance troupe?
Besides, not everyone will get that joke.
Take a look around. It's not just me.
You, your room, and everything else is all white, too.
[Kagura]
Oh yeah, you're right.
What's going on?
[Gintoki]
That's what I wanna know.
[Kagura]
Huh? I feel so disjointed.
[Gintoki]
I know. It's just not smooth.
And when I talk, my mouth doesn't move either.
And this weird nametag thing keeps popping up.
[Kagura]
What's this number floating in the air?
[Gintoki]
I don't know. All I know is that something terrifying is happening.
Ah...
[Gintoki]
Oh, Shinpachi is here.
[Shinpachi]
Good morning.
[Front entrance]
[Gintoki]
Shinpachi, this is terrible. We're not colored in!
[Kagura]
Actually Shinpachi, you're all white too.
[Shinpachi]
I know that.
[Kagura, Gintoki]
Huh?
[Gintoki]
You know?
Then tell us, Shinpachi.
What the heck is going on?
Why is this happening?
[Kagura]
[Shinpachi]
It's all that guy's fault.
[Kagura, Gintoki]
That guy?
[Shinpachi]
This is "line photography."
[Gintoki]
Line photography?
[Kagura]
What is that?
[Key animation]
[Shinpachi]
Usually, a television animation production starts out with a storyboard.
[In-between animation]
In-between animation is interspersed throughout.
[Color]
Color is added and then the background.
This is the process it goes through before photography.
[Photography]
[Gintoki]
Hey, there's color in those.
[Shinpachi]
These are archives.
During this process, there may be times when they have to do
the voice-overs before the animation is completed.
[Line photography]
They have no choice but to photograph the line drawings from the original pictures.
This is what we call line photography.
The voice actors who do voice-overs are familiar with this, right?
[Gintoki]
What, Kibayashi? That means this week's GinTama hasn't been completed yet?
[Note: Kibayashi is from the manga, MMR (Magazine Mystery Reportage).]
[Kagura]
So you're telling me it'll be all white till the end?
[Shinpachi]
No. We have three people working on this week's storyboard.
The only one behind schedule is the guy working on this introduction part.
Phew, thank goodness.
[Wearing a different costume]
[Kagura]
I wasn't sure what I'd do if we stayed like this till the end.
[Gintoki]
Hey, Kagura. When did you change?
[Shinpachi]
Oh, that's a retake of the wrong costume.
[Kagura]
Come to think of it, Gin-chan, you look different, too.
[Gintoki]
Huh?
[Shinpachi]
The animation director has yet to correct the key animations.
[Kagura]
You look weird!
[Gintoki]
Dammit, what's happening here?
Oh man, what the heck is this? We've turned into very simple drawings.
[Shinpachi]
Oh, looks like even the key animation isn't done on time and all we have are the rough drafts.
You can't tell who's who anymore.
[Kagura]
[Gintoki]
Dammit. Who's responsible for this?
Who's the one who lost the schedule so the storyboard was late?
I'll tell the director and have him fired.
Who the hell was it?
[Shinpachi]
It was the director himself!
[Gintoki]
[Taizo Hasegawa (38 years old), also known as Madao has finally found a new job.]
[If he can lead a steady life with this job, then there's something he's decided to do...]
Hello.
Oh, it's me.
How unusual for you to call me.
Did something happen?
No, not especially...
I can't call you unless something bad has happened?
Oh my, do you have to talk to me like that?
Are you calling to pick a fight with me?
Are you eating well?
You can't just eat fast food boxed lunches, you know.
Oh, cut that out. I'm not a kid, you know.
I know. You're a full-fledged adult. That's why you need to eat properly.
So? What happened?
Huh?
Something good happened, right?
It's nothing special...it's just that, I...
...found a job.
Really? Congratulations!
It's nothing that spectacular, but at least it's a stable job.
Really? That's wonderful.
This calls for a celebration.
Never mind that. It's not like this is my first job or anything.
That's okay. Let me treat you.
I couldn't do anything for you when you were down-and-out.
Hatsu... Um...
Once I start this job and my life becomes stable, can you and I...start over...?
Hatsu-san.
Are you enjoying the night view?
Ah... I'm sorry, I'll call you later.
Huh? Hey, wait-
Huh? A man?
I'm pretty sure it was a man's voice.
As soon as she heard his voice, she hung up.
What's going on? Is that guy more important than me?
That's adultery. Adultery!
Adultery? But weren't you two divorced a long time ago?
Don't be disrespectful! We've just been separated.
I don't remember putting my seal on any divorce papers.
You want me to investigate an extramarital affair?
I'm really not interested since I know you and all.
I'll pay you well.
I'm no longer just a freelancer, you know.
No longer just a freelancer?
You're working for some loser ol' man that you hit it off with at some bar, right?
You sure he's reliable?
Don't be rude.
True, it may not be a top-notch firm,
but it's rare these days to find a company that lets me wear sunglasses to work.
You sure all their workers don't wear sunglasses and sell white powder?
How did you know? They also sell something called "chaka."
[Note: Chaka is gangster slang for "gun."]
Not sure what that is.
I think you should quit.
Don't worry about it.
Anyone who wears sunglasses can't be bad. They're just shy.
Shy guys don't wear such embarrassingly short pants.
Shut up. Hatsu bought me this suit when I first got a job.
Humph. If you keep thinking about your woman,
you'll fail at your new job again and screw up any chance of getting back together with her.
Leave that part of your life to me and you just focus on not getting fired, okay?
...Thanks.
Gin-san, I'm gonna do it.
This time, I'm gonna find happiness for sure.
Don't screw it up now.
Huh?
Pervert!
No, no. This is...
It's the Kinniku Buster! Kinniku Buster!
[Note: Kinnikuman's trademark attack and one of 48 killer moves. From Ultimate Muscle.]
[Edo Police]
[Interview room 1]
Did you bring me a rope?
A strong one that won't break even if a person hangs from it.
No, they were all sold out. But instead...
...Here take this.
The investigation report on your wife.
Go ahead and check it with your own eyes.
Is she guilty or not?
Something good is bound to happen if you're alive.
Tomorrow is another day.
I'm asking you, is she guilty or not?
Hey? Did you get a haircut?
[Note: Spoof of Cozy Tomita, who impersonates Tamori.]
Kill me! Just kill me!
Even if I'm alive, I'm just destined to dance a bloody rondo all my life.
I'll have to keep climbing a tortuous spiral staircase.
Just end it all for me.
I'm sure you guys suspect me of performing lewd sex acts.
I don't blame you.
After all, my own wife walked out on me!
The train almost hit us and before I knew it, I was doing the Kinniku Buster move.
But you wouldn't believe that anyway, right?
Total strangers like you guys would never believe
I'm innocent or that it was an accident, right?
You idiot!
What the hell are you doing?
Total strangers? If I thought that way, I wouldn't be here.
If I thought of you as a total stranger,
then I wouldn't give a damn which slammer you're in...
...or if you're dead!
If I thought of you as a total stranger...
...then I wouldn't borrow or lend you this!
You totally suspect me!
It's confirmed now.
[The Pervert]
It's not like that, okay?
I can differentiate between fiction and reality.
I'm innocent!
I know, I know.
I believe you. I believe you. Believe!
Really. You really believe me, right?
God, enough already. He said he believes you, didn't he? Man, you're gross.
That's not the face of trust.
She's looking at me like I'm trash.
You're wrong. Girls this age are sensitive to stuff like that.
Hey, don't get too close, Kagura. He's dangerous.
Hasegawa-san, is the investigation still going on?
Yeah, today's the seventh day.
Although I feel more like I'm being threatened than investigated...
I've been denying the allegations, but my mind and body are at its limit.
Honestly, I don't think I can take anymore.
Huh? You did it, didn't you?
The Kinniku Buster!
Now that Hatsu, my last sanctuary, has been destroyed,
I just don't care what happens anymore.
Isn't there anything we can do?
For starters, stop spitting on me.
After that, a strong rope.
Hasegawa-san!
I'm kidding.
I'm tired... Sorry, but can you all leave now?
You're Hasegawa-san, right?
There's something I'd like to talk to you about.
Who are you?
I'm Haga, the prosecutor in the court of law where you will be tried in two days.
In other words Hasegawa-san, I am your enemy.
Prosecutor Haga.
The remarkable prosecutor who has convicted many criminals in examinations.
An elite in the magistrate's office.
The Madao of the past may have been able to deal with him, but now that he's...
degraded himself into a sex offender he won't be able to compete with him at all.
That's not true, Kagura.
Hasegawa-san may not have money or luck,
but he's got more guts than anyone I know.
For a man, it's all about heart.
Besides, he didn't commit any lewd acts.
Face reality, Shinpachi.
If you don't have money, you're going to end up unpopular like Gin-chan.
Besides right now, that Madao...
...doesn't even seem to have any guts.
He's become a real Madao now.
What is this?
It's exactly what you see...divorce papers for you and Hatsu-san.
I have been going out with Hatsu-san with the intention of marrying her.
What?
You have no right to complain.
I hear you've been separated and practically divorced.
I'd like you to officially put an end to it right here.
Please put your seal on this?
You gotta be kidding me.
Why should I take orders from an outsider like you?
You're no longer related to Hatsu-san either.
Or were you planning on reconciling with her?
Can you, being in a place like this, really make her happy?
Besides, I already told you. I am your enemy.
In two days, I can help decide if you are guilty or not.
I'm sure you understand what I mean.
If you put your seal on this, I promise that you will be proven innocent.
And if you don't...
Well, let's see...
Hasegawa-san, when you left the Department of Immigration Control,
[Note: Seppuku is a form of Japanese ritual suicide by disembowelment.]
I understand the Bakufu ordered you to commit seppuku,
but instead you chose to run away.
I said shut up, you freakin' space flounder!
Commit seppuku.
Are you serious?
What will happen if I mention this during the questioning?
Well, most likely your head will roll.
Please give it some serious thought, Hasegawa-san.
Well, in either case, Hatsu-san is mine.
And, what awaits you is the life of a loser.
Um, excuse me.
Is this the Odd Jobs?
Yes, it is...
Oh, then you must be Gin-san.
My, your hair really is silver.
Thank you for always taking care of Taizo Hasegawa.
I'm Taizo's wife...Hatsu...
Why...
Why am I always like this?
Whenever I try to grab happiness, it runs away...
...at full speed.
That's right...
[Note: Refers to the TV animation version of Heidi.]
It's Heidi. Heidi lives inside of me.
The flowers of happiness are about to bloom,
but an impatient Heidi picks them,
even though they're only buds.
[Note: He looks like Peter from the TV animation version of Heidi.]
Heidi! It's too early. They haven't blossomed yet.
I tried to stop Heidi many times. But she would never listen to
what Peter says.
The only way to put an end to her acts of violence
was to throw myself and her into the ravine of the Alps.
Peter! No! I don't want to leave the mountains!
You must die!
That's all I've been thinking about the last few days.
You've got a visitor.
So, did you bring me a rope?
He offered me a deal. That bastard prosecutor who's going out with Hatsu.
[Note: In Japan, an official seal, used like a signature, is stamped on divorce papers.]
He told me to put my seal on the divorce papers.
If I don't, he will make sure my head gets cut off at the trial.
I'm planning on putting my seal on it.
All I'm doing is dragging Hatsu down by not being able to let go
and hanging on to this one piece of paper.
I don't want to stand in Hatsu's way
if she's trying to leave her hopeless husband and start a new life.
Besides, I don't wanna die.
Go ahead and laugh.
I'm gonna sell off my wife so I can save my precious life.
I...
Your wife came to see me.
She couldn't get in touch with you so she came to see me.
She wanted to wish you good luck on your new job.
And she asked me to give you this.
Th-This is...
She doesn't know...that I've been arrested?
I don't know. But I haven't told her anything.
Well, that's all I wanted to say. See ya.
Oh yeah, and about that rope.
I'll bring it next time I come.
I have no intention of getting you a rope so you can hang yourself.
But...
If it's a rope to pull you out of hell, then I'll bring you as many as you want.
Just remember that.
Peter!
Peter, you want me to stamp it?
I know you can't do it. I'll do it for you.
You don't wanna die, right?
Heidi!
Yeah, just like that, you keep living your life as a doggone loser.
Stop, Heidi!
That's perfect for you.
Joseph!!
[Note: Hasegawa is dressed up as Joseph from the TV animation version of Heidi.]
You're right. I may be a doggone loser...
But!
Even if I'm a worthless mutt...
[From the story "A Dog of Flanders"; a novel and anime about the boy Nello and his dog Patrasche. Nello and Patrasche freeze to death as they go to see Rubens' painting.]
I'm the mutt who goes to see Rubens' painting before I die!!
Just remember, I'll keep coming back!
I gotta fight.
It's all over if a man loses his fangs.
Even if I'm just a good-for-nothing mutt,
as long as I've got fangs, I'll keep fighting till the end.
I'll be a dandy man who won't be defeated...
[Note: A MAkenai DAndy na Otoko or a Madao.]
a Madao!
We will now start the trial for the Oedo Line Kinniku Buster molestation case.
The defendant, Taizo Hasegawa, please raise your head.
You must swear on this document
that any testimony you give here is true.
If you break this promise,
you will be subject to punishment regardless of the outcome of this trial.
Haga, if you want to cut my head off, then go right ahead.
But, I refuse to hand over Hatsu to a man who uses dirty tricks like you.
Even if my head gets chopped off, I'll bite your throat with just my head.
Hatsu...I will protect Hatsu!
Hang on a second.
Who is representing the defendant? Where is he?
Well...he's not here yet.
Perhaps something happened on his way here.
Oh, sorry. I'm late.
Attorney Shimoyama, who was supposed to be here, was arrested on molestation charges,
so I'm his replacement.
I'm the attorney, Sakata.
Nice to meet you.
Gin-san?!
Here? Do I sit here?
Take your shoes off. Your shoes.
Why...?
So you're gonna help me fight?
You and me together?
But can an amateur defend me?
So shall we start, Mr. Prosecutor?
We're up against that Prosecutor Haga, you know.
We will now start the trial.
[To be continued]
[Preview]
At 7:25 on February 21st, the defendant Taizo Hasegawa,
forcefully grabbed the hand of the victim, Ms. A,
on the platform at Kabukicho station and dragged her down into the railway.
He is suspected of performing a Kinniku Buster in front of everyone.
This is clearly an act of molestation and assault.
And depending on the circumstance, it may even be considered attempted murder.
Objection!
It's true that the defendant performed a Kinniku Buster on the victim.
However it is questionable as to whether he did this with the intent to molest.
And therefore, I plead that the defendant is not guilty.
["Men, Be A Madao"]
[Attorney Sakata vs. Prosecutor Haga. The battle has begun.]
[And will Hasegawa be able to win against the Heidi living inside him?]