Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Some things in this world aren't
meant to be known, little girl.
Besides, you shouldn't go off talking
out of character like that.
See? You've triggered my death flag.
Kirie?!
Don't move.
If you don't want to take the daughter's
life after taking the father's.
Right, Mr. Sogo Okita, the murderer?
Kamiyama, listen to me.
Forget everything you just saw.
Rokkaku was already dead
when we found him.
He was caught up in the battle and
killed by the Anti-Foreigner Faction.
["It's Goodbye Once a Flag is Set"]
Liar...
You tricked me.
You said you would help
me avenge my father!
You promised to help me kill this man!
You were using me?!
Oh? Don't make me sound so bad.
Weren't you the one to break
our promise first?
You were supposed to approach the boy
and serve as bait to draw him out.
Yet, you moved on your own
and created a mess.
This boy is our prey.
You aren't allowed to act on your own.
Be grateful that we've used
you as a tool to kill the boy.
Revenge will still be yours.
Your dead father must be happy for you.
Honestly...
Such a foolish daughter,
just like her father.
Dying while manipulated by others.
That is the fate shared
by you and your father.
Manipulated...?
Father was...?
Do you know something about Father?!
What a pitiful child.
Shall I tell you?
How your attempt to avenge
your father is misguided?
How your father isn't worthy of being
avenged by his daughter?
What are...
What are you saying?
I don't understand.
You see...
Your father, Muneharu Rokkaku...
Are you a Rokkaku Inn staff member?
Get a hold of yourself!
Are you hurt?
Everything's fine now!
We've taken care of the Faction!
Can you stand?
This is...?
Kamiyama! You okay?!
The next thing I knew, the Rokkaku owner
was lying on the floor, covered in blood.
Captain Okita wasn't the one
who killed her father.
It was me!
The Rokkaku owner was a member
of the Sokai Faction.
I heard from the captain afterwards.
His wife and daughter were taken hostage and he
was forced to cooperate with the Sokai Faction.
Not only was he forced to offer
his inn as a hiding place,
his savings were also used
to help fund their activities.
His wife and daughter never knew.
That's right.
The Rokkaku owner was fighting
all alone to keep his family safe.
Never telling anyone else so
they wouldn't have to suffer!
Even then, he was trying to protect
his family, his daughter!
Listen to me.
Don't tell anyone that he tried
to kill you, that you killed him.
No one will find out if we stay quiet.
But, Captain!
Hasn't he suffered enough?
He's drenched in blood.
There isn't any point in shaming
him any further.
Let him die a father.
The captain didn't do anything wrong!
It was all my fault!
Even after being forced
to shoulder the crime...
After people have tried to kill him...
He's still protecting that secret!
Even after being called a murderer,
he's still hiding the fact that the father got his hands
dirty, lost his life for the sake of his daughter!
He's trying to protect what the Rokkaku
owner was protecting!
That idiot.
Please help the captain!
The girl isn't the only one
who's after the captain!
The girl is being used by remnants
of the Sokai Faction!
Sotatsu Tendo, the younger brother of the Sokai Faction
leader, Koutatsu Tendo, who died at Rokkaku Inn!
He intends to crush us for destroying
his brother and the Sokai Faction!
So the kid wasn't the only
one who wanted revenge.
We should let Kondo-san and
the others know immediately!
Before something terrible happens!
We can't!
He said he'd kill me if I told
anybody else in the force!
This isn't the time to be
worrying about that!
A call from Captain Okita!
You have him under super
sadistic bastard.
You were crying just a second ago, but you
have him under super sadistic bastard.
Why don't they kill you
and get it over with?
Beats me.
Maybe they plan on using me as bait to lure
in the Shinsengumi and fry all of us together.
Where's the kid?
The lady's asleep. Staying up
late is bad for your beauty.
She isn't asleep.
You're the one who knocked her out.
You see...
Your father, Rokkaku...
Would you normally knock someone out because
you didn't want her to hear something?
It seemed like you really wanted
to hide something.
You were the one who was saying
to tell the kid the truth.
Pretty abrupt change of heart.
[Note: A Japanese celebrity known
to frequently change her hair style.]
Like they say, Kaela Kimura's
hair and a woman's heart...
Two things that constantly change.
That would mean Kaela has it rough when
her hair and heart are changing all the time.
More or less.
Don't reply like you're Kaela.
Well, Kaela schamaela,
you have my thanks.
I don't need a weeping kid
next to me in this situation.
I'm the one who wants to cry.
I've never seen you look so unsure.
Sadists can't take the heat.
I wish people would be more
considerate to me.
What have you done in your life to
make so many people hate you?
Even if you have a million lives,
isn't enough make up for it.
It's because I live by killing others.
No difference if a kid or two
starts hating me now.
Since I can't deny that I'm a killer.
You're one hell of a killer.
You've managed to piss off all of these people
yet you can't stand to watch a little girl cry?
A kid wouldn't understand.
Some things in this world must be protected,
even if it means getting your hands dirty.
Some things can only be seen
through a tainted eye.
Of all the things that have to
stay clean, no matter what...
Well, I'm not saying that it has anything
to do with a kid's tears.
Oh, and one more thing...
I want to ask you something.
Is it okay if I take a dump here?
Not good! Definitely not good!
I've got it bad! Real bad!
What, are you serious?!
Hold on!
You just said some things has to stay
clean, and this is what comes next?!
This is the part where
you CAN'T get dirty!
Impossible! It's impossible!
It's gonna come out!
Hey, lend me the covers on your head!
They'll do, so hand them over!
What are you going to do with them?!
It's not going to fit!
Help!
Excuse me, guards!
This guy wants to poop!
Could you let him go to the restroom?!
He's probably trying to escape.
Tell him to hold it in.
Don't give me that crap!
Do you know what will happen
if he poops here?!
Don't underestimate a sadist's poop!
I've seen one Gin-chan forgot to flush!
It was super huge!
It was super long!
You could spell the letter "S" with it!
S-Sis, wait up.
Take me with you.
Huh? Why is there a river?
Oh, it's a washlet.
He's seeing things now!
He's trying to cross the washlet Styx!
Hey, get a grip!
Hey! Don't get the place dirty!
Don't we have a bedpan or something?!
B-Bedpan? I'll go look!
Oh, it's okay now.
What?
It's okay?
Huh?
Could you have... Uh?
Let it out?
No, I didn't.
Wait, h-hold on.
Uh? But you have this enlightened
look on your face.
You're looking far into the distance!
I didn't let it out. Please give me a break.
He's sitting funny now!
He's trying to keep his ass from touching!
No! How filthy!
Clean!
Clean it up immediately!
I'm starting to feel sick...
Gonna hurl...
Nooo!
Now the kid who's feeling sick
from the poop is gonna hurl!
Hello! Do something about that kid!
Bring a Kitaro barf bag quick!
[Note: From "GeGeGe no Kitaro". "Gegege" is the
Japanese onomatopoeia when vomiting.]
How much did that kid eat?!
It's like a waterfall of barf!
Ew! Do something!
Hurry! Do something quick!
Filthy...
Lord Sotatsu!
Here's a Kitaro barf bag...
Is this what you meant when you said
some things must be protected,
even if you have to get your hands dirty?
Are you an idiot?
My anal sphincters aren't
weak like Kondo-san's.
Like I'm going to poop
my pants at this age.
They escaped!
After them! After them!
Don't let them get away...
Can't get anywhere when
we keep slipping...
Damn it! Don't let them get away!
What do we do?! What should we do?!
I have to come alone!
They said if I call for help,
Captain Okita's a dead man!
They intend to kill everyone who was
involved in the Rokkaku incident!
Oh really?
Let's go, Shinpachi.
Yes.
Hold on!
Didn't you hear me?!
If I bring any help, the captain...!
You don't need to worry.
We aren't on your side.
You aren't on our side?
Then why are you going?
Because we're the same as him.
Samurai, that's why.
Don't let them get away!
After them!
The kid sure hooked up
with an annoying bunch.
There's no end to this.
This is bad!
The three of us won't be
able to escape together!
At this rate, we'll be wiped out!
We have no choice!
Leave it to us!
While we run away, you
deal with the enemies!
What do you mean, we have no choice?
You're making me do all the work.
A couple of little girls will
only hold you back!
Get going!
To be a decoy!
You call yourself a little girl when
it suits your purposes!
What are you doing?
My leg! It won't move!
A rifle?
Those bastards are even armed with...?!
Stupid girl!
This way, hurry!
Stop taking your time!
I want to take my time! Damn sadist!
Look over there!
Yes, sir!
I'm beat.
This is why I hate kids.
I refuse to be a burden on you.
Take Kirie and run.
I refuse to be in your debt.
Besides, there'd be no point if the
kid stabbed me from behind.
They're after me.
Once I show myself, run
in the opposite direction.
You should be able to
make do with one leg.
Listen up.
Don't talk to anyone about this business.
You intend to settle this alone?
I fabricated evidence in this case.
If Hijikata finds out, I'll be fired.
Is that really what you're trying to hide?
Aren't you trying to silence them all so Kirie
doesn't hear about what her pappy did?
That's not it.
Do you really think that's
the right decision?
I don't know what kind of bad
stuff Kirie's pappy did.
I don't know why he died.
But do you really believe that
shouldering the sin
and covering up what he did is
best for Kirie, best for you?
Like I said.
Some things can only be seen
through a tainted eye.
Her old man died with dirty hands for the
sake of his family, to protect his daughter.
Now the daughter is getting her hands
dirty for the sake of her old man.
Isn't that stupid?
As long as she considers me the target
of her revenge, she'll stay clean.
Since I'm invincible.
Revenge won't make anybody happy.
Especially not her old man.
That should be our job.
It's our duty
to get our hands dirty.
You...
Look.
The enemy's found us because
you took too long.
It's the same as two years ago.
You fighting alone to protect
your comrades.
While we have you surrounded.
The only difference is in the numbers.
Which means, boy...
You're the one who will lose this time.
Lose?
That'd be the same result as last time.
When you fight, it doesn't matter
how many enemies you kill.
If you fail to protect what you're
supposed to protect, you lose.
We lost that battle two years ago.
We weren't able to protect
what we needed to.
I refuse to let that happen again.
I refuse to lose again.
This time, I'll protect what I need to.
No matter what happens.
I won't let a single person
get past me!
D-Don't insult us!
What can you possibly do by yourself?!
D-Don't fall back!
Everybody rush him at once!
Hurry up and run!
Th-That's right!
Snipe him from afar!
Fire!
I said that it's useless.
Can't you understand?
I'm not budging one step,
not even if I die.
That guy's an idiot.
He still made a girl cry in the end.
Were you holding it in the whole time?
Were you pretending that
you weren't awake?
You probably wanted to stay
and stop that stupid fight.
You probably wanted to apologize.
You probably wanted to thank him.
But you pretended you didn't
hear a thing for his sake?
You didn't have a choice but to leave without
a word, out of respect for his feelings?
You don't need to cry.
There's no need to thank
or apologize to that idiot.
That isn't why he's standing firm.
Just try to kill him the next
time you see him around.
The idiot will be happier that way.
You don't need to worry.
He won't die until you've
gotten your revenge.
This is looking a little bad.
I keep swinging away but their
numbers won't go down.
Hell, it looks like there's
more of them now.
My vision is starting to fail me...
I see that you've finally given up.
Now! This is our chance!
Everybody attack him!
Because that idiot has...
Plenty of more idiots around him.
Sorry. Sounds like a pain, so I refuse.
Captain! Are you okay?!
Who are you?
Who are we supposed to cut down next?
The idiot who violated bureau policy?
A written apology won't be
enough this time, Sogo.
Sh-Shinsengumi!
Why are you here?!
What are you doing?!
Hurry and dispose of them...
Sorry, we already disposed of them all.
Why?! Why did this happen?!
Seriously...
Why did this happen?
Who was the
snitch?!
There are these things known
as death flags in our world.
A spoken line which foreshadows death.
A bad guy who suddenly
becomes a good guy.
Well, in any case, it means that you shouldn't
do anything out of character.
Even if you manage to survive the flag,
you'll end up suffering as
much as if you had died.
Captain, how many more do you have?
I'm gonna die...
That's right, Captain.
Did you ever run into the Rokkaku
owner's daughter again?
No, haven't seen her.
What?! Doesn't that mean she still
thinks you killed her father?!
She might come after you again!
I heard that she was taken in by
some relatives in the country.
We probably won't ever see her again.
Man, that kid was one
hell of a troublemaker.
I hope she's able to lead a happy life.
So happy that she forgets
about the captain.
But you tend to leave
a lasting impression.
You're one to talk.
But it's possible that these flags
don't always bring misfortune.
Sometimes, it isn't so
bad to trigger a flag.
You may find yourself feeling
that way on rare occasions.
Huh? What did it bring?
Hey, old man.
Give me this, this, and this.
Gotcha.
And top it off with tabasco sauce.
That's something for you to find
out when you trigger a flag.
[Preview]
One boiling hot summer morning...
A middle-aged man who's
lost everything...
A boy who's been emotionally scarred...
That was the day they met.
["An Observation Journal Should Be
Seen Through To The Very End"]
[Daigoro reads his observation journal for a free
study project during summer vacation.]
[In it were the summer memories of an encounter
with Madao, and then their farewell...]
[See you next time.]