Edited at https://subtitletools.com
The first thing to do when you
wake up in the morning
is to look for toy store ads that come with
the newspaper during the holiday season.
Then you study it while standing next to your old
man when he reads the paper in the morning.
You must not make any direct references
such as saying "I want this."
Show that you're thoughtful enough to refrain from
asking for presents because of money concerns.
A sigh can prove effective.
You old man may pretend
he doesn't notice,
but I guarantee he does.
Be patient and continue this
routine every morning.
And then one morning,
you wake up to find
that your old man has pulled
out the toy store ad for you.
This means that victory
is within your grasp.
"Price dropped on the TS."
Casual little pushes like that.
Be wary of your pronunciation.
Your old man is unfamiliar
with foreign words.
Enunciate each and every word.
Then you just wait for
Christmas morning...
["I put together your favorite ads.
Merry Christmas. - Gin"]
...Merry Christmas.
[Merry Christmas!! Never mind that
it's March, Merry Christmas!!]
Hey, where's the usual "This show is
brought to you by" segment?
[Kagura had no luck with Santa last year.
How will her Christmas turn out this year?]
Don't tell me the sponsors
are no longer...
[You know, we ended up with some extra runtime.
Sorry, Gin-san, but can you handle the rest?]
Huh? Hold on a second!!
What sort of stunt are we trying to pull
off here?! Screw you, bastards!!
The hell am I supposed to
do with my voice only?!
[We're not screwing around. (lol)]
[You can do it, Gin-san!! (lol)]
And why is there so much
runtime left here anyway?!
Dear Dad.
How is your hair doing?
I wonder what part of the universe you're
shedding hair right about now?
I'm on Earth with a full
head of hair as always.
There's an Earth holiday called
Christmas coming up,
and everybody is excited.
Because there's a legend that Santa
Kurosu, a red old geezer,
comes to give presents to the children.
This time of year, everybody
gets excited about what they
should ask Santa for.
But that old Santa fella
has never visited me.
I asked for a present last year,
but Santa never showed up.
See the beginning of this episode
for further details.
Dad, does old man Santa hate me?
Or does Santa not even exist?
It seems that your daughter's having
a hard time on a distant planet.
Kids end up leaving you after twenty years or
so, no matter how much you care for them.
But the memories from
those twenty years
will help support those kids
for the rest of their life.
In other words, childhood memories
can never be replaced.
If there's something you need to do,
go ahead and do it, Umi Bouzu-san.
She won't keep sending
you letters forever.
Old timer, send this to
the branch on Earth.
You aren't going to see your daughter?
War's broken out between planet
Kameda and planet Naito again.
Planet Kanehira's asked for assistance.
I see.
Guess you don't have a choice.
Since you're even busier
than this Santa fella.
Don't die out there.
What the...?
Dear Kagura-chan.
I read your letter.
I'm glad that you still have
a full head of hair.
Your father also has a full
head of hair, as always.
I would love to go see you
as it's been so long,
but I'm busy with work,
so I can't go to Earth.
I'm sorry.
I pray from far away in
space that you have
a merry Christmas with
your Earth friends.
There's no need to be sad.
I won't be able to go see you,
but if you're a good girl, I'm sure
that he'll come visit you.
Thank you very much.
With a large bag full of presents...
Clad in red clothing...
Santa will come...
[Santa Claus Red is Blood Red]
Merry Christmas!
And here's to another year gone by!
Boy, there's a real sense
of refinement about
sitting around a kotatsu with
a hot pot on Christmas.
Right, Sis?
Sorry if this doesn't feel very Christmasy.
I heard that this would also
be an end-of-the-year party.
No, I'm fine with this.
It's too much effort to hold
a Christmas party
and end-of-year party separately, right?
It's not because we have no
money! It'd just be a drag!
A blend of eastern and
western cultures.
The informal atmosphere
is very Japanese.
You got that right!
And you don't need to worry.
I brought something Christmasy with me.
Here, a special order cake.
Wow! That's amazing, Hasegawa-san!
Though it's kind of small...
But it looks very delicious!
Quality over quantity.
The lovable look is very Japanese.
You got that right!
You'll just feel sick if you eat too much.
This is the perfect size.
Then let's cut it up.
Here, Kagura-chan. You get
the part with chocolate.
Lucky you, Kagura-chan!
Boy, that's no fair!
No fair that Kagura-chan gets everything!
Stop fighting now.
Here, I'll start serving food
so pass me your plates.
Oh, yes!
What would you like, Shin-chan?
Oh, what's in the hot pot?
[Note: Spoof on a brand of
Japanese starch noodles.]
There's Malomy-girl, Malomy-boy,
and Mr. Malomy.
Doesn't that mean there's
only Malomy...?
Then I'll go with Malomy-boy!
After all, I'm a boy!
Come on, you need to interact
with girls for a change.
When are you ever going
find yourself a girlfriend?
You got me there!
Man, wow...
Christmas is so much fun!
It's too bad Gin-san couldn't join us.
Seriously, what's he doing?
He's probably walking around drinking.
Just ignore that scoundrel.
You're right!
Let's have fun talking about
Gin-san behind his back!
It appears that I'm in time
for that Christmas event.
But what a meager party...
Is this truly Christmas?
Kagura-chan is completely bummed out.
Hold on, Kagura-chan.
Daddy's coming.
Daddy will transform this destitute
night into a lovely Christmas Eve.
Kagura will be so surprised when
she sees me here in Edo.
Oh wait, that can't do.
I must play through this Santa
character for tonight.
She's been discouraged by the reality
that Santa does not exist.
A parent has the duty
to help a child dream.
It's sad that I cannot visit her as a parent,
but if it means I can help make
this a fond memory...
Huh?
Is someone in the yard?
Oh? What?
Oh no, is it a thief?
They've noticed!
Here I go!
Merry Christmas!
Have you all been good
little boys and girls?
Santa Claus is here to make you happy!
Kagura-chan's completely surprised.
Yep, Santa Claus really exists.
Your personal Santa is right here...
Huh? She's a little too surprised.
Shouldn't she act a bit more happy?
Huh? What?
Did daddy do something wrong?
Is there hair sticking out my nose?
Huh?
It's... It's Santa!
There are two Santas!
Who are you people?!
What's going on?
Why is there another Santa here?
Who is this guy?
Why is there another Santa
besides Gin-Santa?
I've been waiting here the entire evening in
this freezing weather to surprise them...
Why?
Why did this happen?!
The worst possible timing...
What do I do?
She's scared now, not happy.
There could never be two Santas!
One must be fake!
A thief who disguised himself as Santa
to rob the houses of innocent people!
I'm turning you over to the cops!
Nononono, you've got it totally wrong!
It's daddy!
Santa-Daddy whose come
to help you dream!
Hey! They're treating me like
a fake because of this guy!
Wait, hold on sec...
On second thought...
[FAKE]
I am a fake.
This is bad...
Maybe I should reveal myself before
they turn me over to the cops...
No, but my goal is to
help Kagura dream...
Hey, why are you standing there?
Say something!
It'd be embarrassing to tell them the truth
after all the trouble I've gone through.
Because I haven't accomplished anything!
Haven't accomplished a single thing!
Uh, excuse me.
Who might you be?
Huh?
I'll force him to back down.
I should be able to maintain
the act once I'm alone.
Well, it's not that I think you're
a thief or anything.
Uh, do you belong to some kind
of volunteer organization?
Er, what?
Who are you?
Do you belong to some neighborhood
children's association?
Not at all. I happen to be, well...
Santa, as you can see.
No, you can stop acting now.
That beard is obviously fake.
Well, I don't particularly care
about you copying me.
But I would prefer you
don't half-ass the job.
You'll get yourself hurt if you
underestimate Santa.
Please...
That's a harsh joke.
You're the one who's copying me.
Why isn't this guy backing down?
Well, some people don't realize
they're copying others.
Just like how everyone casually uses the manga
system developed by Osamu Tezuka.
This old guy is digging in.
What's with this guy?
Why does he refuse to back down?
He's just a fake.
Say.
Do you listen to rock?
They say that every current rock and
roll band was born from the Beatles.
Meaning, you more or less
spawned from me.
What? You're Santa and you
listen to the Beatles?!
Huh? What? I can't?
What do you listen to then?
Santa's supposed to listen to Enya, man.
That new age stuff.
Could you cut this out, old timer?!
I know you're a fake! So scram!
Oh, yes. Enya, you say.
I've heard that Enya la-la-la...
[Note: The late Chosuke Ikariya,
Japanese musician and comedian.]
That's Ikariya, not Enya.
Odd, this man has no shame...
[Note: Singer-songwriter Tatsuro Yamashita.]
Well, there's also the obvious Tatsuro.
He's ancient.
Now, it's about his wife, Mariya.
[Note: Mariya Takeuchi. Song was
used for Holiday commercials.]
Who sings the fried chicken thing.
Tatsuro and Kazumasa are
classics in every era.
[Note: Kazumasa Oda, another
veteran singer-songwriter.]
This old man hasn't flinched at all!
That confidence... Could he be...
Don't tell me this guy is...
The real Santa Claus?!
On closer look, this guy may
have a unkempt appearance,
but he carries himself
with a certain grace.
Like a master of the sword.
He's an old man with a beard of white,
yet he's brimming with vitality.
He has the skin of a man in his twenties.
Is he even human?
I once met a man who
called himself Santa.
He was just an old man with no ambition.
But this guy's completely different.
He doesn't have a white beard,
the symbol of Santa,
but that short mustache,
that short mustache he doesn't even try
to hide, actually looks more realistic.
Maybe Santa's supposed to
just have a short mustache?
Like the letdown when you see
Lord Frieza's final form.
Like how the real deal's are actually
quite simple-looking.
No, but that can't...
For real?
This is the worst possible place
to run into the real Santa.
What are they doing?
They've been staring at each other in
silence and haven't budged an inch.
What am I supposed to do?
Should I apologize?
Is he like, mad?
It's too late to apologize now.
It'd be absolutely disgraceful.
[Note: Performed by the
singer Shinichi Mori.]
This is like a comedian doing a parody
of the song "Ofukuro-san"
when the singer himself
shows up behind you.
I won't have it!
I can't disgrace myself
while they're watching!
Then what am I supposed to do?
What is the fake "Ofukuro-san" supposed
to do, Kings of Comedy?!
As he walks up behind me
and goes, "Nice try, kid,"
how am I supposed to not embarrass
myself, Kings of Comedy?!
Tell me, Kings of Comedy!
Take out Ofukuro-san
and become the real deal!
Wait!
What are you guys doing?!
Aren't you two supposed to be Santa?!
The hell are you doing in
front of the children?!
Santa... You really are good...
I find it hard to believe that you're a slacking
senior who only works on Christmas!
This old man was able
to land a blow on me...
Is this the power of the real Santa?
But it no longer matters
who the real one is!
Santa!
Is!
Me!
Stop!
Enough of this.
It would be rude for one
who claims to be Santa
to shed blood on this holy night.
If you insist on sullying Santa's
name, leave at once.
This turf belongs to me, Kyuta Claus!
We got another Santa here!
But this Santa isn't even
concealing her identity.
It's Kyu-chan. That's Kyu-chan, right?
I am not Kyu-chan.
I am Kyuta Claus.
Beautiful princess, please
accept my present.
A year's supply of your favorite
Baagen-Dash...
What?!
Can't let you have fun without
me, Kyuta Claus!
This is not your turf!
I, Monkey Claus, have
marked this jungle!
I won't allow you to lay a finger on
the female ape who lives here!
Who are you calling a female ape?!
Otae-san!
I am willing to meet you every night,
whether midsummer night or holy night!
If you so desire, I will be the Santa
who brings you happiness
365 days a year!
This won't be a simple holy night!
Yes!
We will be joined together
on this hole-in night!
Um, excuse me.
Is Gin-san here?
I can't seem to find him anywhere.
I want to give him a present.
Where might he have gone?
There's nothing Santa about it anymore!!
One Santa after another!
I can no longer tell who's real or fake!
Actually, over half of them
are just stalkers.
Just a bunch of perverts.
They all insist that they're Santa.
I'm not wearing anything inside,
so it's pretty cold...
Of course.
I am the real Santa.
I have no intention of
relinquishing this title.
I am the Santa who will
make Otae-chan happy.
I mean, Kyuta.
It's me! I'm the Santa who wants
Otae-san to make me happy.
That would make Sis the Santa.
This world only needs one Santa...
I got it!
Then I'll represent the children of this world
and decide who the real Santa is!
A contest to determine
who is Santa Claus!
I don't think anyone of them
are fit to be Santa.
The very first very merry contest to determine
who the real Santa Claus is!
Why are you taking the lead
here, Kagura-chan?
Listen up, Santas!
I'm going to give you the Santa test!
If you are able to pass this test
that would be simple for Santa,
I will name you as the real
Santa for proving yourself!
Kagura-chan, what is this Santa test?
That should be obvious.
Santa's purpose is to give
presents to little kids.
To read the wishes of all the children
and grant those wishes
by delivering presents.
Yes, Santa's job is to
help children dream.
When they're lined up here to be
judged by one of those kids,
there's isn't anything to
dream about, is there?
I'm going to pretend to be a girl
who's going through various different
Christmas situations.
You just have to grant that girl's wishes.
You'll be judged on your performance.
Wait, hold on!
I didn't come here to give presents
to the china dress girl.
Yes, my apologies to Miss Kagura, but
I only want to be Otae-chan's Santa.
That's right. Don't try to butt-in, little girl.
Now bring out Gin-san.
My present is fresh.
I must deliver it before it rots.
It's already rotten, you Natto Santa!
How can you call yourself Santa when
you refuse to help a child dream?
Listen up.
Don't forget that if the whole Santa helps
children to dream story doesn't fly,
you're a bunch of trespassing
old pedophiles.
That's crazy talk!
Forget about presents! The Feds
are going to come calling!
If you can't prove you're the real Santa,
You'll be led away by the reindeer
(a.k.a. the police)
in a sled (a.k.a. a patrol car).
That's a low blow...
Aren't you the police?
If you don't believe you're up
the task, feel free to leave.
I see no problem with this test.
Because I am...
the real Santa!
The others don't matter.
This guy here is the problem.
I can no longer turn back.
I'll defeat the real Santa...
And I'm...
I'm...
gonna be king of the Santas!
[To Be Continued]
[Preview]
Wait!
Gonna be king of the Santas? It's March!
We're still doing these
Christmas episodes?
Don't be so anal.
Keep talking like that and Santa
won't visit your home this year.
Really?
And so, the next episode...
"Everybody's a Santa!"
[Next week is filled with everything from
American, Classic Tales, to School Drama.]
[Who will fulfill the dream of a girl played by Kagura,
and become the real Santa?!]
[See you next time.]