Edited at https://subtitletools.com
[New TV Show]
[Kin Tama]
[Episode 3]
Shinpachi...
I was dreaming...
Dreaming?
Yes... It was a happy dream...
I was working in Kabukicho...
I became the number one host...
and Kintoki was next to me...
And the owner of the place was Kagura-san...
Such a happy dream...
I wanted to become the number one host...
So badly...
I didn't choose to end up with this buttchin!
What's so bad about having a buttchin?!
There isn't anything wrong with a buttchin!
There might be customers who find a buttchin attractive, who knows!
Just stop!
Everybody should end up with butt-like chins.
All hope was lost as rain fell upon Kabukicho.
We lost our will to fight
and could only curse at the sky.
[To Be Continued with the Final Episode!!]
I can't sleep.
I can't sleep at all.
Can't sleep a wink.
The harder I try to fall asleep,
the more awake I feel.
I don't feel like sleeping at all.
["Sleep Helps a Child Grow"]
What?
I can't sleep.
Oh, really...
Don't stay up too late.
We have work tomorrow.
What is it?
I can't sleep.
You already said that.
If you can't fall asleep, stay up until you're sleepy.
You're so annoying.
Let me sleep, okay?
I said we have work...
I can't sleep.
Hey! What are you doing?!
I can't sleep a wink at all.
Like I care!
Stop bugging me!
I can't sleep...
Put me to sleep.
Use everything in your power to put me to sleep.
Just go to sleep by yourself!
Is that how you ask somebody for a favor?!
Man...
I can't put up with this.
That futon looks more comfortable to sleep on.
Switch with me.
I'm gonna sleep there.
You sleep in the closet.
Don't be so picky.
All futons are the same!
How am I supposed to sleep in that small space?!
Just move outta the way.
Ah, I think I can fall asleep like this.
This futon might put me to sleep.
Never wake up again, stupid brat.
Man...
What is this...
I'd managed to fall asleep.
I don't wanna sleep on a cold futon.
I can't sleep.
So nothing changed?!
This is no use.
I don't feel sleepy at all.
I can't fall asleep 'cause the pillow smells like an old man.
You're the one who told me to switch with you!
That futon looks more comfortable to sleep on.
Switch with me.
This will never end!
I can't fall asleep
so I've been thinking of ways to fall asleep.
And now, I'm no longer sure how I used to fall asleep.
I've forgotten how to fall asleep.
How do I fall asleep?
How do I make my way into slumberland?
Start by shutting up!
Then close your eyes and stay still!
You'll eventually fall asleep.
But Gin-chan, when you stop and think about it,
what is sleep?
When we close our eyes, we're just shutting our eyelids.
Our eyeballs are still darting around.
It's completely dark, but that's because we're looking at the inside of our eyelids.
It doesn't mean we're asleep.
To prove it, if you close your eyes during the day, it's completely red.
What do I do with my eyeballs if I want to fall asleep?
Should I just stare at the inside of my eyelids?
Or should I look up?
What do I do to-
Cut it out!
Now I can't fall asleep!
What are you going to do about this?!
Now that you got me thinking about it, I can't fall asleep either!
Did I look up? Did I look down?
I don't know what to do with my eyeballs!
And do we breathe with our mouths when we sleep?
Or with our noses?
Or do we breathe in through our mouths and out through our noses?
Or do we breathe in through our noses and out through our mouths?
Cut it out!
Should I cross my arms?
Should I leave them at my sides?
Outside the covers?
Inside the covers?
How should the pillow be placed?
Face-up?
Face-down?
Cut it out!
Where do we come from? Where are we going?
What's beyond the edge of the universe?
Why doesn't anime make lots of money?
Cut it out!
I can't sleep!
I don't feel like sleeping at all!
Was it this hard to fall asleep?!
Did we go through such an ordeal every night?!
What is sleep again?
Shut up!
You'll never fall asleep if you make everything so complicated!
How much of a failure are you?!
Even Ken Takakura could do a better job!
[Note: Actor Ken Takakura is known for the phrase, "I'm a failure."]
I feel more and more awake.
What do I do?
At this rate, I'll never fall asleep for rest of my life.
Give me a break.
Didn't I tell you that we have work tomorrow?
It's 2:30 in the morning.
We have to wake up at 7:00 tomorrow.
We only have four and a half hours to sleep.
That'd even make Napoleon bitch when he woke up.
"My dictionary says I only sleep for three hours but read between the lines!"
[Note: Napoleon is known for only sleeping three hours a day. He is also known for the quote "The word impossible is not in my dictionary."]
What should I do?
Don't fall asleep before me, Gin-chan.
For now, stop thinking about that stuff.
Don't use your head.
Okay?
Sleep isn't supposed to be something you can consciously force.
Humans who live regular lives will naturally fall asleep at night.
If you work your sweaty ass off for a whole day,
you'll be so tired you can comfortably fall asleep.
That's how sleep is supposed to work.
I see...
I can't fall asleep because I was lying around the whole day.
Right?
The problem is with your lifestyle, not with your sleeping style.
["Don't just lay there! Help me clean up the house!"]
You're one to talk.
If you understand, go run a lap around town.
What you lack is fatigue.
I got it.
I'm going off for a run.
Gin-chan, you can't fall asleep before me.
You'd better stay up.
Gin-chan...
Hey, Gin-chan...
I can't fall asleep.
I did the running...
But now...
I'm so hot...
I can't fall asleep.
Who told you to run as hard as you can?!
Of course you can't fall asleep when you're all sweaty like that!
I figured I'd fall asleep faster if I was more tired,
so I ran fifty laps around town.
Sleep is out of the question now.
It feels like all my cells have activated.
Feels like it?
Your brain cells are dying!
You can't fall asleep right after exercising so hard!
Go take a bath and cool yourself off!
You've gotten my futon all sweaty now!
No.
I don't have time for that.
I have to fall asleep as soon as possible.
You're a busy person, huh?
First you want to sleep.
Now you're hungry.
I envy you!
It must be fun to have so many things to do!
That isn't my stomach. I'm farting.
I don't care what it is! Can you be quiet?!
How long is that going to continue?!
It's so noisy I can't fall asleep.
Fine.
I'll go make you something to eat.
You go take a bath during that time.
Food?!
Everybody feels like sleeping after a meal, right?
It's not very healthy, but that's a sacrifice you'll have to make.
At this rate, I won't be getting any sleep either.
Gin-chan!
Man, you stink!
Stay away! Go take a bath!
Thanks, Gin-chan!
Gin-chan...
Hey, Gin-chan...
[Note: Kagura is using the Lamaze method of breathing for expectant mothers.]
What are you doing?
I don't feel like sleeping at all.
I took a bath,
but I'm having trouble breathing so I can't fall asleep!
Who told you to eat so much that you'd start breathing with your diaphragm?!
Of course you can't fall asleep when your stomach's that full!
But...
You made all that food...
The rest of that was for breakfast!
Why did you eat my share, stupid brat?!
It's no use...
I'm in so much pain I can't even turn over...
[Note: "Shape Up Ran" was a JUMP manga from the 80s.]
I'll go run myself into shape...
By taking a run.
Who told you to be witty?!
Cut it out!
That'll just put us back where we started!
Ah...
Fine.
You don't have to work tomorrow.
Shinpachi and I can handle it.
So don't force yourself to sleep.
Just let me sleep, okay?
No!
Staying up late is bad for my skin!
Someone whose stomach is sticking all the way out shouldn't be talking about skin care!
Come on.
It's already 4:00.
I have to wake up at 7:00 tomorrow.
That's in three hours.
That'd even make Napoleon bitch at his mom in the morning!
He'd probably whine about the quality of the miso soup!
"The word eggplant is not in my dictionary."
Fine.
I'll stop making a fuss.
I won't bother you anymore.
You already fed me.
But if it's too quiet, I start thinking about stuff.
Can I turn on the radio?
If you keep the volume down.
Young Night Train!
So let's get started!
This is DJ Junnijiro, who just had a kidney stone removed,
with stories that make you cry within three minutes!
Young Night Train!
So let's get started!
This is DJ Junnijiro with stories that make you cry within three minutes!
Allow me to introduce the first letter.
This letter is from Radio Name Tom.
[Note: From Tom and Jerry.]
"Sorry, Jerry."
I will never forget about the first friend I ever had.
It happened during summer ten years ago.
I was a shy and quiet child who always played by myself.
So my father brought me a friend.
That was Jerry.
Jerry and I were always together.
We went everywhere together.
We did everything together.
Just like real friends.
I taught him many tricks.
Wait!
Jerry's best trick was to wait.
He would wait as long as I told him,
even when a feast was placed before him.
I didn't need any friends besides Jerry.
That's how I felt at the time.
But on the other hand,
an increasing number of children showed up who were interested in Jerry.
The next thing I knew, I'd made lots of friends besides Jerry.
Wait.
It didn't take very long for my interest to shift from Jerry to other things.
Jerry longed to play with me the way we used to.
Jerry would bark at me.
That was when his best trick would come in handy.
I would say one word to Jerry.
"Wait."
Jerry would always wait there for my return.
Without moving an inch.
He just waited for me to return.
By chance, my father's store went out of business,
and my affluent family fell to ruin.
Chased by debtors,
we were forced to escape with only the clothes on our backs.
Though I was only a child,
I was still able to understand what must be abandoned in that situation.
Perhaps he realized his own fate.
Jerry chased after me without pause.
Wait!
I delivered the usual word in a cold voice.
Wait.
I left Jerry behind without ever looking back.
A few months later, I returned to that spot.
I had already moved to a faraway city,
but I couldn't stop thinking about Jerry.
Jerry had to be fine.
Somebody must have taken him in.
In retrospect, I probably wanted peace of mind.
I wanted to see Jerry alive as soon as I could,
so I wouldn't have to feel guilty.
Jerry hadn't become someone else's pet or a rotting corpse.
Jerry was waiting as always.
Without moving a step.
Waiting for my return.
Sad, isn't it?
He was abandoned there a while back.
Kind people would try to take him with them,
or feed him or the like.
But this boy refused to budge at all.
In time, people stopped paying attention to him.
He couldn't have expected his owner to return.
Either way, it's a sad story.
I reached out to softly pat his head,
and his eyelids slowly parted to look up at me.
Jerry's tail wagged ever so slightly.
And then, he never moved again.
Little lady...
I see, you were his owner.
Jerry was waiting for me to come back!
Waiting the whole time...
The whole time...
Jerry!
How can I apologize to you?!
How many times do I need to apologize to you?!
You gave me so much!
You taught me how to shed my loneliness when I was all alone!
You opened up the world to me!
You were my first friend!
And yet...
I...
I did...
I did such a terrible thing to my precious friend!
There's no need to apologize.
He was always waiting for you.
And you came.
What else did he need?
He must have been happy to meet his owner in the end.
That's not true! He must hate me!
Because I was the one who caused Jerry's death!
Jerry isn't dead.
He's still alive.
Where?!
Where is he?!
Of course...
Right behind you!
What is this?
What kind of story is this?
Why did a touching story turn into a scary story at the end?!
How would this make people cry?!
More like cry out in terror!
I can't sleep after hearing such a crazy story!
The station must be getting barraged by complaints right now!
That really caught me off guard.
Not that I was scared or anything.
Hey, Kagura!
No more radio!
I can't listen to this...
H-Huh? She fell asleep.
R-Really...
She finally fell asleep?
Way to cause so much trouble.
That's a relief...
Now I can sleep in peace.
Then I'll go to sleep, too.
Right behind you!
Y-Yeah, right...
Y'know...
That crazy story isn't enough to scare me.
Though it surprised me a bit.
That was just a comedy.
There isn't much of a difference between horror and comedy.
This was totally...
Right behind you!
C-Crap...
I'm starting to hear things 'cause I didn't get enough sleep.
Hey, now I can't fall asleep...?
Ah. Sorry if I woke you up, Kagura.
Looks like I'm sick.
K-Kagura-chan. You're actually awake, right?
You were wide awake just a second ago.
This isn't funny, seriously.
Kagura-chan?
Hey, are you listening?
You're awake, right?
Awake, right?
Wake up!
Don't mess with me!
How much effort do you think I spent to put you to sleep?!
You just abandon me the second you're done?!
You could at least talk with me a bit!
You could at least come with me when I go to take a piss!
Are you going to keep pretending to sleep?
I'll beat you awake...
Okay, that's good.
Bring it on!
Like you're ready to die!
If you're gonna hit me, you had better knock me out!
No, really...
Please knock me out!
Somebody put me to sleep!
Kyu-chan, happy **th birthday.
The next episode...
"That Person Looks Different From Usual During A Birthday Party."
[Tojo gathered everyone together to throw a surprise birthday party for Kyubei.]
[The truth is the characters in this show don't actually age, so just let us stick with "**th."]
[See you next time.]