Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Let's defeat Otohime.
Now that everyone on this
planet has become old,
we're the only ones who can do it.
But since you're not, I can toss
you aside. I'm much cuter.
Huh?! Bring it on! Show your face!
Huh?! You want to fight?!
You think you can beat me?!
Otohime gave up her quest for
eternal youth and beauty.
And decided to use the box as revenge
against those who had what
she no longer did.
In other words,
she planned to turn all the people
of Earth into old geezers.
You're just a young brat, that's all!
If I was younger... If only
I was younger...
Your age isn't your only problem, tramp!
[Gintoki and the others split into three
teams... And head for the palace!!]
[Shinpachi's fighting power is 362 K. What's a K unit?!]
["Beauty is Like A Summer Fruit"]
Yes... Otohime won't let anyone
be more beautiful than her.
In order to insure that she's the most
beautiful woman in the world...
she plans to turn this world
into a planet of the elderly.
No way... That's such a selfish reason.
She thinks she has the
right to throw our world
into chaos for a crappy reason like that?!
She thinks people will let her take
away their summer vacations?!
History is always moved
at the whim of its rulers.
She's 3,000 years old. She's lived
a very long time...too long.
During all that time, she's lost
so many important things.
The only way to stop her is
to put an end to her life.
Isn't there any way to
turn everyone back?
What about Sis?
All our answers are probably...
in there...
with Otohime...
All right, let's split up into three teams.
If we stay together and are discovered,
we'll all be caught.
If just one of us is caught, the rest
of us can still get to Otohime.
Even if in the end there's
only one of us left.
But can we split up into three groups
and still take out Ryugu
Palace's security?
It'll be tough with our numbers.
We can a least confuse and
distract them by splitting up.
Let's see if we can divide
up our power evenly.
What is that? I think I saw that in
a another manga somewhere.
It's a spouzer. It basically
measures fighting ability.
[Note: Parody of scouter from Dragon Ball.]
No, that's a scouter, isn't it?
It looks just like a scouter,
don't you think?
No, It's a spouzer. I won it in
a festival night stall raffle.
It's just a copy!!
I'll use this to measure
your fighting power
and split everyone into three
equal teams. First...
You.
362 K.
Oh? That's pretty impressive
for your age.
What is a K?
I don't know what you're basing
that on. Is that impressive?
It means you have the fighting
power of 362 leaves of kelp.
[K=Kelp]
Why kelp?! A single leaf of kelp
doesn't have any fighting power!
Taking into consideration that a
normal person is about 360 K,
you're two leaves of kelp better
than the average person.
Just two leaves?!
What exactly was my ten years
of sword training for?!
Hey, Kamenashi, can I have
these sunglasses?
I can't relax if I'm not
wearing sunglasses.
Your fighting power is 654 K.
Why?! Why is Hasegawa-san
higher than me?!
You shouldn't judge others
by how they look.
Without his sunglasses, he's only 1 K.
What?!
Oh, Madao is really nothing more
than just a pair of sunglasses.
It's like his essence.
That's weird!! 1K? That
means I'm not human!!
I'm just a single leaf of kelp!!
You're next...
Amazing. 7930 O.
What's O mean? That's a different unit.
The units change when I scan
girls. It becomes cuter.
Oh, does it stand for 7,930 flowers?
[Note: "Boobs" in Japanese is "oppai."]
7,930 boobs.
That's not cute at all!! That's perverted!!
Are you trying to make fun of a
warrior?! I don't need boobs.
Change it to 7,930 penises!!
Stop!! That's even more disgusting!!
Hey, how many boobs am I?
No... Wait a second.
8,000... 8,500... I can't believe
it. It went up again... No, it's...
It's dropping?! It's not 8,500 O!
It's minus 8,500 O!! Unbelievable.
What's the meaning of this?!
What's this?! It's those two behind her?!
Those two geezers equal a fighting
power of... -15,000 ... NO, -30,000.
I-It's still going down!
It's simply immeasurable.
-30,000? How much of
a burden are they?!
All of us together can't overcome that!!
-30,000... Even the whole staff of a
retirement home can't handle that.
If I place one of them in each
team, they're still -15,000.
That's a big gap.
Oh well. In order to raise their
numbers as much as possible,
I'll have each of them carry
100 leaves of kelp.
It's a mere consolation, but
it's better than nothing.
No, nothing is better!!
Why does their power level increase
when they're carrying kelp?!
I'll hold 300 leaves! I'll
cover Gin-chan's gap!!
That's...
Oh no!! They found us!!
They're going to fire.
Everyone, scatter!!
We'll attack from this side!!
Shinpachi and everyone
else take a different route!!
Hey, wait!!
Weren't you going to split our fighting
power into three even groups?!
What was the point of the spouzer?!
There's only trash here!!
At least take one of the old men!
Hey, don't ignore me! I know
you can hear me, can't you?!
They're coming after us!!
Shinpachi-kun, leave this to us and run!!
Run?! I'm stuck with these
old geezers?! Why me?!
I'll leave the future of Ryugu Palace...
the future of the world
to you young fellas.
They're not young!!
You're going to fight with me, huh?
Sorry for sticking you with
such a terrible job.
I'm the one with the terrible job!!
It doesn't matter. I discarded
my life once before.
Old soldiers like us should just pass on.
The old soldiers are right over here!!
Let's go!!
We're taking all of you...
with us to hell!!
You guys were completely useless!
Are you putting all your
hope in those fools?
They are this planet's last hope?
I have nothing to worry about then.
They'll meet your fate soon.
Why don't you go meet
them in the next world?
This is your punishment
for incurring my wrath.
If you want to kill me, then go ahead.
You kill people you don't like,
you turn people who are more beautiful
than you into senior citizens.
You won't ever gain eternal
beauty that way.
Even if you did gain eternal youth.
No matter how beautiful
a kimono you wear...
I know without a doubt...
that you will always be ugly.
Your heart and soul
are ugly and rotten.
Watch your mouth, little girl!
What do you know?!
You're young and beautiful!
What could you possibly know?!
What do you know about the feelings
of a woman who's been left to live
and grow old by herself
for thousands of years?
What do you know about my feelings?
About getting uglier and decaying
all alone but never dying!
You're not the only one who ages.
Everyone, no matter how beautiful,
grows wrinkled and dies in the end.
But even if their looks change,
there's always some things
that never change.
Even if our bodies are destroyed.
No matter how many years pass...
We believe there's something
that can never be destroyed.
But even if we become wrinkled,
we still won't lose to you.
That's because we know
what true beauty is.
Something that is truly beautiful
cannot be destroyed, you say?
How interesting.
In that case...
Show me...
That beauty you speak of!!
It's you or me... The winner is
the one who's truly beautiful!!
Where did they go?!
Find them! They should be nearby!
We managed to escape.
Please, Gin-san, Katsura-san, run
away on your own two feet.
I don't care what happens
to you geezers anymore.
Honestly. Young people these days...
Complaining about something
like this? How pathetic.
[Note: Parody of Dragon Ball.]
When we were young, we
had to carry Master Roshi,
who had a turtle shell on his
back, and deliver the milk...
Who's Master Roshi?!
Don't revise your memory to include
parts from a mega-hit manga!
Hey, Zura ...
What was I going to say?
You're taking too long to comment,
and you even forgot what you were saying!
Oh yeah...In the end, you played
with the Mega Drive, too.
That was your comment
from the last episode!!
Why are you commenting on something
that happened an episode ago?!
No one will remember that!!
As I expected of you, Gintoki.
That's one of those surrealism comments
that's so popular lately.
A fine surreal comment.
Young people just don't get it.
Zura, who is Master Roshi?
Don't go revising your memory to include
parts from a mega-hit manga.
Old fart!!
If you don't cut it out, I'll dump you
off in the mountains, damn it!!
Crap. If we fight against Otohime
like this, we're going to lose.
What should I do?
What's this?
That's long enough. Pull her up.
What a foolish woman.
Does she think she can get
away with defying me?
I'm sure she's become
quite beautiful now...
A beautiful bloody corpse.
I-Impossible! What?!
Y...
You fools! How did you get in here?!
Th-The water!!
I-Impossible!! You broke in by smashing
the ceiling of the lower floor?!
Get them, my guards!!
Fire!!
Tsk. She's so fast that
we can't get near her!!
Yahoo!
Tsk! She's on top of the shark!!
Shoot her and the shark down!!
What are you fools doing?
They're all rebels!! Hurry
up and get rid of them!!
Yes!!
I told you.
We won't lose no matter
what happens to us.
I-I won't accept that!!
I'm the most beautiful
woman in the world!!
I'm going to win this battle!!
I won't allow anyone to be...
more beautiful that I am!!
You're just a little girl who only has youth!!
That face!!
I'll make it ugly and swollen!!
She's beautiful?! I-Impossible!
Why is she so beautiful
when I'm hitting her?
It's like the ethereal beauty
of a falling flower!!
You think your weak slaps
can make me ugly?
Now it's my turn!!
What?! A punch?!
Who punches a woman's face?!
Furthermore, she's hitting places
that'll definitely make me ugly.
What a formidable woman!!
And she's made all the flowers behind
me scatter so gracefully.
I can't keep up with this.
I need to use my trump card!!
Take this!! Nose hooks!!
No one can escape such
a devilish attack.
No matter how beautiful you are,
you'll become the ugly one...
What?! She looks like Naoko?!
[Note: Naoko Ken is a Japanese
actress and singer.]
Compared to her, whose nose
is even more upturned...
this girl doesn't look ugly at all even when
I've got her stuck in such a position!
Now it's my turn!!
I won't let you!!
In that case, I'll use...
Shinji!!
[Shinji Tanimura is a Japanese singer.]
Shinji?! Impossible!! She punched him out first?!
You lose, Otohime!
Give up and let go of me!
Turn everyone... Turn the whole
world back to normal!!
You already know that...
doing this won't change anything!!
Shut up!!
Who do you think I am?
I am Otohime, the ruler of Ryugu!!
I am the most beautiful
creature in existence.
I must be beautiful!
What's this?
It's a man...
There's a man in there.
I wonder if it's a massage device.
I want to get one, too.
What kind of massage device
takes up this much space?!
This is something else.
It's probably a deep-freeze capsule,
or something like that.
Whatever the case, my back is worn out.
Hey, wait!! Don't touch anything!!
What's wrong?!
It's a Tengu!! It's cursed!!
What's this?
Something's written here.
Space century 079, July 15...
He still hasn't awakened.
According to the doctors, they've
managed to keep him alive,
but they don't know if he'll
regain consciousness.
It's all my fault.
I kept him in this palace too long.
He was left behind in his time.
He lost all hope and chose death.
Is this what Kamenashi-san
was talking about?
Believing that he'll regain
consciousness someday,
I've placed him in a cold sleep.
Now his body will never be destroyed.
He will continue to sleep
in his beautiful state,
never changing, until
the day he awakens.
But I don't know if I'm
doing the right thing.
He was so depressed about being
all alone and chose death.
Even if he wakes up in the far future,
he'll awaken in a completely
different world.
It'll be just like before only worse.
If that happens, what should I tell him?
I may be repeating the same mistake.
Even so... Even if I am... I...
It sure is beautiful...
It looks as if pearls have been
scattered, doesn't it?
This is one of the most famous
places in the universe.
This is the first time I've seen
something so beautiful.
Otohime-sama... You're...
absolutely beautiful.
I want to see him...
Once more...
No matter how many hundreds
or thousands of years it takes.
Countless men after him have
told me that same cheap line.
But his words... Why can't
I forget his words?
I've lived for thousands of
years, but his words...
I must live and stay beautiful.
No matter how many thousands
of years pass.
So that he can recognize me.
So that when he awakens,
he won't be lonely.
Even if the world changes,
I must remain the same.
I must wait for him looking as beautiful
as I was when he knew me.
I must let you know that
you're not alone...
that there was one person in this
world who was waiting for you.
I'll become the pearl that shines
in the depths of the sea.
Follow that light and return to me.
I'll always be waiting for you.
Otohime...
Ryugu Palace is shaking?!
What are these tremors?!
Hey!
No matter how much you
resist, it's useless.
Ryugu Palace will soon be above Edo.
The Heavenly Old Age Cannon
contains pressurized gas...
[Heavenly Old Age]
...the equivalent of 100,000
Treasure Box Gs.
If I fire this in the middle of Edo...
Everyone who remains on the surface
will become ugly and old.
Who would want that?
Who would want you to do that?!
Do you think the person
you're waiting for...
would really want you to
do such a terrible thing?!
I must be his guide.
I must be the most beautiful
pearl in this world.
The only thing that shines in
the dark depths of the ocean.
I'm sure he'll notice that light.
He'll follow that light and
come back to me.
In order to do that... In order to become...
the only shining pearl...
I need to sink everyone else
into the depths of the ocean.
[To be continued...]
[There's barely any time left before the
Heavenly Old Age Cannon fires.]
[The fate of the world is left to Gintoki and Katsura!!]
[Ryugu Arc - The Final Chapter]
["Even if Your Back is Bent, Go Straight Forward"]
[The smoke has turned everyone old. Can they stop the Heavenly Old Age Cannon even in such decrepit bodies?!]
[At the brink of despair... Urashima calls...]