Edited at https://subtitletools.com
As I said...
The systems of this world
are under our control.
Defeating me will destroy this world.
Will you still attempt to defeat me?
Can you kill Tama?
[Note: Original text, "Begirama" is a spell
from the game Dragon Quest series.]
Firebane!!
["And Into the Legend..."]
Ow, ow, ow...
Wait! Hold on! Time-out!
No, wait! Wait!
Weren't you listening to what
I was saying?! Open!
Huh? Something about offering
us half of the world?
And it doesn't matter if we pick yes or no
because we still end up fighting, right?
Forget it. Too much of a hassle.
Wouldn't that be the Dragonlord?
He didn't listen to a single word I said.
The Archfiend always talks too much.
I usually just skim through.
What do you think you're doing?!
Any damage to the Archfiend Tapir
will mean damage to Lady Tama!
Aren't you capable of exercising discretion?!
Uh, you realize you just
indirectly attacked her?!
The Archfiend is completely beat-up?!
What do you think you're doing?!
Get out of my way. Scram!
You scram!
Hey!
What are you doing in
front of the Archfiend?!
Curse you...
So you do not care if this
body is destroyed?
Heartless bastards...
And you call yourself heroes?!
Like the Archfiend's in
any position to talk!
I can now see that you are big douches.
But will you be able to continue
after seeing this?
Leukocyte King, do you remember
your father's face?
Yes, your father, the previous
king, Fortega,
fell into the anus during
his battle with me
and lost his life.
But what would you do if
Fortega were still alive?
What would you do if he still lived in pain
within me after being consumed?
It can't be...
You couldn't have...
Yes, exactly...
My son...
Father!
Hey, wait! Hold up!
You move too fast!
I didn't even get a chance
to reveal his father's face!
I was still talking!
And why is everybody
hitting me this time?!
We don't feel a thing when you
use the "I'm your father" setting.
This is much easier than beating Tama-san's face,
so I figured I'd use this chance to finish you.
Don't you people have any respect for this
tragic meeting between father and son?!
Nobody uses "the last boss is
your father" twist anymore.
Come up with something better.
Curses!
I pulled the plug and we lost our
connection to the system!
Plug?!
You people were controlling the system
with such a half-assed method?!
This is it!
Now that he's disconnected
from Lady Tama's system,
we can defeat the Archfiend Tapir
without harming Lady Tama!
This is our only chance!
Let's go!
Don't underestimate me, brats!
Your cheap appliance store security
measures can't possibly defeat me
after I've consumed high-level technology
and undergone an extreme evolution!
I can no longer be considered a virus.
I have transcended human
understanding...
Yes...
A god!
A being you humans cannot cope with...
A perfect being known as a god!
A god...?
God schmod.
You're supposed to be fighting
it out with some
yeast cells on a rotten piece
of bread, Germfiend.
This isn't where you belong.
Get the hell outta Tama-san.
We won't allow you to contaminate
our friend any further.
This will be the last clean-up job!
Let's go, guys!
Yeah!
Huh?
My body won't move the way I want it to.
Huh? Huh?
What's with Kagura?!
Wh-Wh-Why?!
Why did Kagura-chan turn into pixels?!
Wh-What's going on here?
Don't tell me Kagura got
infected by the virus?
That can't be it...
How could a human being be
infected by a computer virus...
As I said...
I am no longer a pathetic computer virus!
Shinpachi!
Shinpachi! You okay?!
Somehow...
Shrunk
down...
M-M-My legs are short!
Looks like you're okay.
Like hell I am!
My body's over here!
And my legs are like this!
Why was my transformation
so half-assed?!
I'd take a full body change over this!
Huh? Something changed?
[Note: Guntank is a weapon from
the anime series Gundam.]
Didn't your body always
look like a Guntank?
Who are you calling a Guntank?!
G-Gin-chan...
It's like... my body's like stone...
I can't move...
Hey, Kagura! Hang in there!
What is this?
The pixels are advancing!
My body's getting heavier
and heavier, Gin-san!
Shinpachi!
Help... Gin-chan...
Kagura!
Gin-san! Do something!
Shintank!
Who's that supposed to be?!
Gin-chan...
M-My body is...
Why are you standing around?
Do you want to die?
They're...
It's no use.
They've been completely pixilated.
We need to retreat for now!
Kagura! Shintank!
I won't let you get away!
It appears that he wasn't lying about having
more power than a normal virus.
His extreme evolution has given
him the power to control viruses,
which affect human beings
in addition to us programs.
You've gotta be kidding.
I've heard of an animator, who didn't take a bath
for so long that he had fungus on his penis,
but I've never heard of anyone getting
infected by a computer virus!
It appears that you're running out of time.
Your entire body will eventually
become pixels.
Why?!
Why is enemy fire always
concentrated here?!
Because I haven't used
it for a long time?!
You upset?!
I'm the one who's upset, moron!
Is my penis going to get better?!
Will Shinpachi and Kagura
ever recover?!
Just stay there.
I'll handle the rest.
You and your friends...
Hey! Wait!
I told you to stay there.
Who's going to protect
Lady Tama if you die?
How sad do you think Lady Tama
will be if you die here?
I was created for the sole purpose
of protecting Lady Tama.
I have nothing else to protect.
I am merely your substitute.
I should be the only one who
has to die for Lady Tama!
Forget...about...me...
At least try...to release...
him...from this...place...
Tama said the same thing to me.
She told me to forget about
her and protect you.
To release you from this place.
That's why I told her,
if you were really a copy of me,
you would never want that.
Even if you died, you'd never dream of running
away and leaving you in charge behind.
Guess I overestimated you.
You're dumping what's important off on
someone else and stepping down?
I am your copy.
It doesn't matter if I die. As long as
you live, more copies can be made.
I don't remember having
such a pathetic copy.
You wouldn't have a chance
of taking my place.
And I absolutely refuse to take yours.
Nobody can take anybody's place.
There isn't a person in this world
that could take your place.
It doesn't matter if you were based
on me or have the same face.
You're the one who's devoted yourself to
protecting Tama this whole time, not me.
As far as Tama's concerned,
you're no copy or substitute.
You're someone who's always
been there for her...
A precious, irreplaceable friend...
If you truly care about Tama,
never talk about dying again.
Never call yourself a substitute again.
I'm done fighting with you.
Let's survive and have a
drink together, brother.
I have no interested in fermented juice.
[Note: Delicious Water from Rokkou is a brand
name of mineral water from House Foods.]
It's a different story if you have
Delicious Water from Rokkou, brother!
Got it?
If we don't stop him here,
Lady Tama won't be his only victim.
The viruses will invade your entire world.
We have no time.
We have to stop him before your
entire body turns into pixels!
The two of us will end
this once and for all!
Foolish brats...
I see you're finally ready to die.
This will be the end for all.
All shall be darkened by me.
White shall vanish,
and everything shall be crushed in black!
You're the one who's going
to get crushed, Germfiend.
This is the end, Tapir.
We shall see if white or black survives!
Time to settle this once and for all!
Cease your prattle, worms!
Return to the sea of pixels!
Let's go!
Release all of your power!
Put everything
into this single blow!
Go!
What?! They stopped my wave?!
Curse you!
Are you contesting me?!
Crafty bastards!
I'll crush you and your impertinent wave!
My body is turning into pixels...
I cannot be stopped!
Nobody can stop me!
We won't last long against this.
At this rate, we'll both
be kicking the bucket.
Go.
What?
I'll hold him back.
While I distract him, you defeat him!
He should be defenseless right now.
This is our only chance to defeat him!
How can you possibly hold him off yourself when
the two of us can barely cope, moron?
I have a plan.
And I can't move with my legs like this.
You're the only one who
can reach him now.
Hurry it up!
While you can still move!
Bastard...
You better not have forgotten our promise.
Do not worry.
He cannot hurt me.
Who do you think I am?!
Gintoki Sakata.
A man based off you.
Brother...
Friend...
I earned many titles for a mere copy...
But no matter what I'm called,
I cannot lose sight of my role...my duty...
Lady Tama, forgive me.
My duty is not to live,
it is to protect you.
I cannot live for the sake of another,
but grant me the right to die for a friend...
To die for my brother!
Impossible...
His power is surging..
How does he have so much power left?!
I have plenty of power left...
My very life...
C-Could you be releasing
all of your life energy?
Impossible!
If you do that, you'll...
You'll...!
You think you damn viruses
can defeat the Leukocyte King?
Defeat...
Gintoki Sakata?! Never!
Attention to everybody inside this body.
The virus, which infected this
body, has been destroyed.
This body will now engage
in reparations.
All surviving security members
should take a vacation from their
regular duties to make babies.
The surviving viruses should change
into white bodysuits at once.
You are already under our control.
Please assist with making babies.
Sorry I couldn't keep my promise...
I'm irresponsible by default.
I got that from you.
Looks like it.
I broke my promise to Tama.
It's extremely regrettable.
I never expected to become
a piece of junk.
I was an excellent security measure
before you all came.
A hero guarding the princess.
I would have been happy to throw
my life away to protect Lady Tama.
And yet I gave my life to save this stupid
party instead of the princess...
Before, I wouldn't have thought
twice about dying...
But now...
I want to live a little longer...
I wouldn't have minded a little more adventuring
with Lady Tama and the lot of you...
Leukocyte King-san...
For such words to come out of
an easily replaced substitute...
It's all your fault...
It appears that I've completely
broken down.
You haven't broken down.
You're no substitute.
You're a much better guy than I am.
You protected what you needed to.
I don't just mean Tama.
You also protected our lives.
So don't die.
Don't die for your friends.
You have to live for your friends, for us...
Lady Tama will be fine with
you people around.
Besides, I can no longer...
Gintoki-sama, everybody...
Thank you for protecting the
Leukocyte King all this time.
It's Tama-san! Tama-san's voice!
It's Tama. Are you okay now?
Where are you? Where are you at?
Here. Over here.
Here. I'm right here.
Tiny!
L-Lady Tama...
What are you doing, Tama?
Why are you so tiny?
My system has not completely recovered,
but I was able to send a pixel copy over.
Leukocyte King, thank you for protecting
me for such a long time.
Now it is my turn to save you.
Tama-san, can you...
I shall enter the Leukocyte King's
body and repair him.
Leukocyte King, I will not let you die.
L-Lady Tama...
We're coming along then.
[Note: Moshasu is a spell from Dragon Quest
to transform one of the characters in the party.]
We owe the Moshasu Gin-chan.
Uh, but how are we supposed
to go inside him?
We're too big to enter...
I knew you'd say that.
That's why I brought the magic mallet Z.
Okay! Line up if you want to be shrunk!
I'll smash you all good!
Th-They're...
There you have it.
Your life is no longer
yours to throw away.
You're more than someone
who protects Tama.
All the protecting you've done has led to
people who will protect you in return.
All squirmy-like...
Just like a white blood cell.
I just had to be the copy
of such a difficult man.
Even now, I can't offer any words
of gratitude or tears...
What would you do in this situation?
Smile.
[The End?]
Enemy spotted.
An unidentified new virus.
An extremely large army is
advancing on our position!
Unbelievable...
And we haven't recovered from
the Tapir invasion yet...
Will we be able to fight them off
with our meager numbers?
What is there to fear?
Every white flag may vanish from this land,
but our army will not fight on its own.
Our army may be destroyed,
but we will not be alone.
Though we may be in different places,
there are others who carry
the same will and fight.
Though they may fly
a different color flag,
we have comrades who possess
the same proud, white spirit!
Even an army one million strong
cannot darken this white!
Tally ho!
[Preview]
It could happen to anyone...
Even to an animated character...
As long as genes, unhealthy behavior, stress,
and other various factors are involved,
["You Don't Know What You've Got Till It's Gone"]
all people have a chance of going bald.
[Next week's episode is a two-parter. The other part is "You'll Get Sued If All You Do is Copy Others."]
[Two cat burglars break into Odd Jobs followed by tons of unexpected visitors.]
[See you next time.]