Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Hey, Gin-san?!
The movie we mentioned
last week was for real?!
What? You didn't believe me?
I mean, this show's been
nothing but lies...
That's not true.
In the story of the Boy Who Cried Wolf,
a wolf actually showed up at
the end and the boy died.
Same goes for this show.
Isn't that metaphor a little ominous?
In any case, we should celebrate.
So this week, we have
something special.
In celebration of the GinTama
anime becoming a movie!
And for DVD sales breaking one million!
The Second Character Popularity Poll!!
Here are the results!
Except we're reusing the same CG.
Well, this is still amazing!
Not only has a movie been announced,
but we've sold over a million DVD's
without even realizing it!
More or less.
To be precise, we've
sold 878,236 copies.
If you round up, we've broken a million!
[Seasons 1-3 retail sales only
- Through Aniplex Research]
Hold it!
I've never heard of rounding up
over 100,000 copies like that!
Stop sweating the nitty-gritty.
100,000 is NOT nitty-gritty.
Plus, you said this is the
second popularity poll,
but since when did we
ever do a first one?
The first one came before
there was an anime.
The anime staff had the same question
so they went back through the manga.
And there it was in the ninth volume!
They should do a better job of reading
the manga before they make an anime.
And so, here are the results
of the Popularity Poll.
Starting with 30th through
21st all at once!
Count...
Down!
[Second Character Popularity
Poll: 30th-21st place]
[30 / Mutsu / Previously 15th / DOWN]
[30 / Kyojiro Nakamura / Previously - / NEW]
[29 / Prince Hata / Previously 18th / DOWN]
[28 / Abuto / Previously - / NEW]
[27 / Tsu Terakado / Previously - / NEW]
[26 / Ayame Sarutobi / Previously 20th / DOWN]
[25 / Ayumu Tojo / Previously - / NEW]
[24 / Tama / Previously - / NEW]
[23 / Matako Kijima / Previously - / NEW]
[22 / Justaway / Previously 19th / DOWN]
[21 / Kamotaro Ito / Previously - / NEW]
That was 30th to 21st!
A four-year gap leads to lots
of new characters placing.
Then moving right along...
Since we can't waste time
on low-ranking losers,
here's 20th through 11th place.
Count...
Down!
[Second Character Popularity
Poll: 20th-11th place]
[20 / Mitsuba Okita / Previously - / NEW]
[19 / Bansai Kawakami / Previously - / NEW]
[18 / Taizo Hasegawa / Previously 13th / DOWN]
[17 / Tae Shimura / Previously 12th / DOWN]
[16 / Hideaki Sorachi / Previously 14th / DOWN]
I wish I could become a cheesecake!
[15 / Isao Kondo / Previously 10th / DOWN]
[14 / Kyubei Yagyu / Previously - / NEW]
[13 / Sadaharu / Previously 16th / UP]
[12 / Tatsuma Sakamoto / Previously 9th / DOWN]
[11 / Elizabeth / Previously 11th / STAY]
Huh?
Didn't one of them get to say something?
Sure.
Special privilege of the original author.
Anyway, there are loads of new
characters showing up.
It's interesting how most of the old regular
characters have been dropping.
What?! Crap...
And here's what you've
been waiting for...
10th through 4th.
Count...
Down!
[Second Character Popularity
Poll: 10th-4th place]
[10 / Tsukuyo / Previously - / NEW]
[9 / Sagaru Yamazaki / Previously 5th / DOWN]
[8 / Shinpachi Shimura / Previously 8th / STAY]
[7 / Kamui / Previously - / NEW]
[6 / Kagura / Previously 7th / UP]
[5 / Kotaro Katsura / Previously 6th / UP]
[4 / Shinsuke Takasugi / Previously 4th / STAY]
Like I'd lose to my stupid brother and
the swarms of new characters!
Hell, I even went up a spot!
They only served to make
me look better!
Shinpachi, on the other hand...
You get all this screen time...
Yet nothing changed, huh?
Just move on...
Now all that remains are the top three!
Here comes 3rd and 2nd place!
Count...
Down!
[Second Character Popularity
Poll: 3rd-2nd place]
[3 / Toshiro Hijikata / Previously 3rd / STAY]
[2 / Sogo Okita / Previously 2nd / STAY]
The mayonnaise/nicotine
addict and sadistic freak!
Only number one remains!
Well, we all know who it is.
Kind of embarrassing, yeah?
Though it's only natural
as the main character.
But we still have to announce
it as part of the process.
So number one in the Second
Character Popularity Poll!
[Cue card]
Count...
Gin-chan.
Huh?
We're out of time.
Huh?!
And here is the weekly
ranking for DVD sales.
This in fourth place? What a laugh.
Humans are creatures
who love rankings.
Here are the top ten most watched
shows for the month.
They have a tendency to
compare everything.
Like sales rankings...
Listing the richest people...
Viewership ratings...
Shonen JUMP survey polls...
For a while, there was a movement
against this trend.
There were schools that held sports
festivals without standings,
claiming everybody who tried
hard should be first place.
But that's been abandoned now.
It's said that rankings are a way
to know your own standing,
so you can better improve yourself.
However...
If your ranking doesn't improve
after grueling hard work,
what are you supposed to do?
If your ranking leaves you feeling
defeated instead of inspired,
is there a point to that ranking?
[8th place]
Are popularity polls really necessary?
Even if they are,
is it necessary to publicly
announce the results?
If I couldn't budge from
my 8th place ranking,
am I necessary?
["Screw Popularity Polls"]
Shinpachi-kun?
What are you doing here?
Oh, 9...
Yamazaki-san.
You were about to call
me 9th place, right?
Not that I care, but you were about
to call me 9th place, right?
Aren't you working?
Yeah, I'm just not in the mood...
I see.
You work with 1st and 6th.
I've got 2nd and 3rd.
Oh... The same for you too, huh?.
I can't stand the smug looks...
Captain Okita didn't say
anything last time either,
but that look on his face...
Even if they act normally,
it still pisses me off.
Like, they're being conscious
about it, aren't they?
Deep down, they're being all proud
of themselves, you know?
Kagura-chan and Sadaharu
both went up...
I'm the only one who didn't
change... Still at 8th.
What's so bad about not changing?
My rank went down.
Oh, sorry. That wasn't my intention...
Maybe the mohawk was a problem...
I'm very sorry...
No, it doesn't matter.
Less stress this way.
My previous ranking was
odd to begin with.
Must have been an organized vote,
or some under-the-table business...
Th-That's not true.
It's impressive, considering how
little screen time you get.
I have the second-most screen
time in the show...
Uh... Did we do something wrong?
No... It's not an issue of right or wrong...
The problem would be that
we haven't done anything...
You've gotta catch their attention...
Whether in a good way or a bad way,
if you can't hook the audience, you're
going to pass under their radar.
A hook...
It's true that we haven't done that.
Ah, sorry about grouping us together.
Nah, it's fine.
You don't need to be considerate today.
But it's too late to try to hook them...
Quite frankly, I think it's over...
This is as far as I can go...
No matter what I do, my image's
been established.
And Bandai-Namco is clearly
looking down on me...
Maybe it's just wrong for me wanting
to be more popular...
Wishing for character merchandise
based off of me...
Maybe they've realized
how desperate I am...
Maybe it's turned people off...
Shinpachi-kun...
Is it so shameful to place 8th and 9th?
Huh?
Wouldn't 8th and 9th place be as good
as first for boring characters like us?
Yamazaki-san...
Even if we're to place 1st or 2nd,
would that be okay?
No, right?
There are plenty of colorful
people, flowers, around us.
And those flowers need dirt,
a steppingstone, to bloom.
We don't need to become number
one in a popularity poll.
We can be number one at
being their steppingstones.
Do the best you can in the role you've
been given, the position you hold...
Yamazaki-san...
You're such an adult.
But I'm...
I'm no adult.
I was the same as you a while back.
I thought that if I worked hard...
If I worked hard...
I could place 1st...
Yamazaki-san...
Huh? That's odd...
I gave up on that a long time ago...
Why is this happening now?
Sorry!
Ya-Yamazaki-san!
H-Hang in there, Yamazaki-san!
What...
What happened?!
Yamazaki-san's ranking
is sinking like a rock!
His underwear being removed
to reveal a shameful sight
has led to a dramatic change
in his popularity!
Th-There's still... someone who hasn't accepted...
the results of the popularity poll...
Quickly... Run away...
Th-That person intends... to forcibly
alter the results... of the poll...
[Popularity Poll Arc]
Th-There's still... someone who hasn't accepted...
the results of the popularity poll...
Quickly... Run away...
Th-That person intends... to forcibly
alter the results... of the poll...
Wh-What's that?!
Hurry...
Protect your 8th position...
Th-The number one position
for a boring character...
Y-You must... protect it at all... cost...
Ya-Yamazaki-san...?
Yamazaki-san in 136th place!
I-Impossible!
How can you alter the results
of the popularity poll now?!
The results were announced before
the opening sequence!
What could possibly be
accomplished now?!
In any case, I have to let everyone know!
They're all targets!
But who did this?!
I don't know who it could be...
The perpetrator removed Yamazaki-san's
underwear to climb the rankings...
It must be someone ranked
below Yamazaki-san!
Damn it!
There are too many candidates!
Who can I trust?!
Th-That's...
25th!
Sa-chan-san!
Why is she here?
Could she have...?!
So you're the one who's trying to ruin the
popularity of the higher ranked characters
and stir up the rankings.
The perpetrator?! She's talking
to the perpetrator?!
Who is it?
Despicable.
Will you be satisfied with a high
ranking through this method?
Who is it?!
Sarutobi-san, could you not
make odd accusations?
If that's your reason for calling
me out here, may I leave?
I'm quite busy, you know.
S-Sis!!
Don't play dumb.
Look above your head.
Your ranking's gone up.
So has yours, for that matter.
It must be nice to sit at
such a round number.
Oh, but it doesn't matter if
everybody's rank went up.
Sorry, the gap between you and
Justaway will never go away.
But don't beat yourself up about it.
You haven't had much screen time lately.
It's not your fault if you
lose to a lifeless object.
Oh, but Justaway hasn't had
any screen time either,
so I wonder why it's a higher
rank than Sarutobi-san...?
I-If I had more screen time, Gin-san and I
would have finished in 1st and 2nd place.
But look at you, Otae-san...
You had so much more screen
time than I did and yet...
Huh?
I see gorillas...
Twin gorillas?
What are those? Pets?
Huh?
But you're ranked below them!
Why are the three of you
lined up together?
Gonna start a band?
Gorilla triplets?
N-Not good...
This is starting to look very bad...
Hey, I don't care about the rest.
But don't group me with those animals.
Animals? Otae-san...
You shouldn't say that
about the manga artist.
Wait, you also called them
twin gorillas, remember?!
Otae-san, you'll be the one
that's ignored this year!
What?!
I'll make it so you never
show up again, whore!
Bring it on!
Once you're gone, I'll get a little
more screen time, gorilla bitch!
Sis! Stop!
That's enough, you two...
Ky-Kyubei-san!
Kyu-chan...
Now isn't the time to be fighting here.
Both of you must be aware by now...
There's an insolent villain ruining the popularity of
the higher ranked characters for personal gain.
Yes, yes! That's right!
This isn't the time to be fighting!
We must prepare preventive measures.
That's right! That's right!!
They should be fine.
None of them seem to
be the perpetrator.
Okay, I'll join in...
We must take advantage of the
chaos to attack the keep!
Eliminate every high-ranked
character and conquer all!
Wh-What is she talking about?!
Wait, Kyu-chan! Are you serious?
I know that I'm being unreasonable, but...
I can't stand the fact that
Otae-chan isn't 1st.
The rest doesn't matter.
She isn't the perpetrator,
but she might as well be!
In war, he who strikes first, wins.
Fortunately, the highest-ranked
characters didn't gain anything.
They haven't noticed this mess.
Now is our chance to
catch them off guard.
So you say, but you're the highest
ranked character here.
Won't you end up 1st in the end?
Once I have completed my conquest...
I will...!
Take my own life.
Why are you risking your
life for a popularity poll?!
You don't have to do that, Kyu-chan!
Besides, I can't possibly do such
terrible things for personal gain.
Ranking in the top 10
is more than enough.
She intends to take out most of
the higher-ranked characters!
That's right! Gin-san's included, so
we can set the cutoff at 8th place.
That barely includes me!
Couldn't you barely leave me out?!
But maybe we shouldn't...
Yes! That's good!
Peace is good.
After all, that would include Kagura-chan
and Sadaharu-kun...
Hey, what about me?!
Oh?
Who is this girl?
Tsukuyo? What is this?
Who is this? What's with this girl?!
Why is she ranked 9th ahead of us?!
Wait, Otae-san.
This girl had twice the votes you did!
O-Oh...?
Ah, she's fairly cute, I guess.
Fairly cute? This girl...
is loaded with hooks!
A scar on her face plus the pipe!
How greedy is she?!
What's wrong with this girl?!
According to Tojo's investigation,
she speaks with a classic
prostitute accent.
What?!
What's with this girl?!
Otae-san, what's with this girl?!
O-Oh...? She's determined
to make an impression...
What?! What?!
There's no need to speak
in such a manner.
This is starting to get scary...
And also according to
Tojo's investigation,
Gintoki groped her breast.
Groped?!
What the hell?!
I ain't never been groped, biotch!
Say, this is starting to get ugly...
Oh...?
Ah, that's why Gin-san's
been down on his luck.
This girl must be a bad luck woman.
You're right.
Her face screams bad luck, biotch!
Right? Nothing good can come from
getting involved with this type.
Poor thing.
What, this is the bad luck
woman I've heard about?
Coming from three of the
worst bad luck women!
Stop it!!
I don't want to see any
more of this ugly act!!
And according to Tojo's investigation,
she was featured from episodes
177 through 181.
Oh...?
Then starting from episode 182...
She shouldn't need any
more screen time!
Sis! Sa-chan-san!
Stop! Somebody stop them!!
I see...
Then we should attack her first?
Otae-chan, where are you going?
I'll let the two of you handle her.
I'm going to deal with the source.
Source?
To make sure there aren't any more new female
characters taking away my screen time...
I'll go crush the gorilla in 15th.
Not the gorilla!
This manga, I mean, anime will end!
This is bad!
This is getting really bad!
On second thought, I shouldn't
be searching for a perpetrator,
when I'm surrounded by all these egotistical people
who could become perpetrators at any minute!
What do I do?!
What do I do to stop this?!
I need someone's help!
The one person who would never become
a perpetrator in this situation...
I'll have to rely on the guy in 1st!
Huh?
Wh-What is this?!
Something's wrong...
All distorted...
Is this...
Could it be...
[Please wait one moment.]
Sorachi's been taken out!!
[To Be Continued]
[Preview]
And so, since the original
author's been taken out,
the GinTama anime will be off next week.
[Or so we thought, but that wasn't doable. You should give us a break every once in a while, TV Tokyo.]
[The original author's gone and we're out of stock footage. Can we use backgrounds only for the entire episode next week?]
[See you next time.]