Edited at https://subtitletools.com
Boss!
I apologize!
We didn't realize they were your
friends and mistreated them!
Who's the guy with the stony face?
Lord Seimei.
Head of the Ketsuno clan.
A genius onmyoji who's said to
be the strongest in clan history.
[Note: Based off the Onmyoji Seimei Abeno.]
Seimei Ketsuno.
Lady Christel's older brother.
Huh?
["Not Losing to the Wind"]
I apologize for the uncomfortable experience.
Gedomaru, you did well to
protect Christel's friends.
You have my gratitude.
Please rest to your heart's content.
Christel will yell at me if I allow you to
leave without offering any hospitality.
I can also serve liquor if any of you drink.
He made a feast appear with
a snap of his fingers.
He's a monster!
A Paul Maki monster!
[Note: Japanese Comedian who was popular
with his constant finger snaps.]
Gin-san, I think I'm going crazy!
We've got fox spirits wrapped around us!
Wrapped around us?
More like they've been
suckling at our nipples.
This may be the work of a devil.
I shall test it for poison first.
Hey, you're drooling.
That's mine!
Uh, Seimei-san...
How did you know we were acquainted
with Ms. Ketsuno?
We of the Ketsuno clan have used
our knowledge of Onmyodo
to defend the Bakufu and
Edo for a long time.
Do you know how we have
carried out that duty?
Through our sight.
Give it to me!
When foretelling disaster or ill omens,
one must first analyze the target from every
possible angle in order to see anything.
I have stationed shikigami all around
Edo to serve as my eyes.
It is my duty to process the
information they send,
determine what direction this nation is heading,
and how the Bakufu should act.
How could I not be aware
of my sister's situation?
Heh. I see that Big Bro knows
everything that's going on.
That makes this simple.
What did you people do to Ms. Ketsuno?
You believe that we are the reason Christel
can no longer forecast the weather?
Wouldn't the strongest onmyoji ever
be capable of such a thing?
It's true that when Christel left the
Ketsuno clan without a word
and chose to use her power
for the common people,
the traditionalists were
vehemently opposed.
I was also one of them
until I saw her as...
Boss!
Could it be?!
Wait! Seimei-san, where are you going?!
I apologize for being off with
the morning forecast.
I hope to do better as I give
you the afternoon forecast.
Christel!
Why?! Why is Christel, morning personality,
reporting a daytime weather forecast?!
Boss! That's because the other weather
lady got sick and took the day off.
Just hurry!
Hurry up and record this on DVD!
But boss!
The disk is full after recording
Spider-man yesterday!
Erase it!
Erase Spider-man!
We've already seen it so many times!
No, we can't!
Erase King Kong...
No, stick to Spider-man!
Just erase the parts where
the heroine shows up!
The annoying one!
Here I go then!
Boss! Her forecast is starting!
Hey! You bastards ready to pray?!
Don't miss what she says!
We'll do whatever it takes to make
Christel's forecast accurate!
Pray the second she speaks!
The very instant she speaks!
Yes, sir!
The afternoon forecast for Edo...
Is sunny.
Make it sunny!
Gin-san, the entire clan is supporting
her, not interfering.
Seimei-san seems about ready
to literally burn up for his sister.
Shinpachi, it's no use.
He already joined their family.
Say, why is the person who was
suspecting them joining in?!
How can he blend in so perfectly?!
What is that?!
So they've also begun!
Don't give in, men!
Break their spell!
The two sides are pushing and prancing
around with each other.
It is the Shirino clan.
Shirino clan?
A family of onmyoji that
rivals the Ketsuno.
The Shirino clan.
The Ketsuno clan and Shirino clan
have been in a savage struggle for political
power since the Heian period.
If they hate each other so much, why
do they live next to each other?!
After many years of fighting,
they finally joined to serve the Bakufu
together in this Edo period.
Through Lord Seimei's efforts.
However, a new tragedy was born.
The Shirino clan placed one condition
in the peace accord.
To offer Lady Christel as a bride.
Is that when...
Ms. Ketsuno, known to everyone as the
weather lady, has gotten married.
Lord Seimei accepted the condition,
believing that it would serve to bring
Lady Christel back to this world.
And Lady Christel also agreed,
believing it would make peace
between the clans.
However, she was unable
to lie to herself.
After getting married,
she grew weaker every day.
Lady Christel spent most of her time
gazing into the sky back then.
Once Lord Seimei saw her,
he realized his mistake,
broke the peace accord,
got Lady Christel divorced,
and returned her to her position
as weather lady.
Leaving two clans, allies only in name,
serving the Bakufu side-by-side...
And the hatred was greater than before.
The emotions of the two clans towards
Lady Christel were tangled up,
and their battle grew into something
never seen before.
A mystic battle.
Over the weather.
So the ones who messed
with Ms. Ketsuno's weather forecast
and got her fired are...
Boss! We can't hold on much longer!
Stand strong!
We must make it sunny!
We can't hold on!
Guys!
Yes...
The misfortune which has befallen Lady
Christel is the work of a single man.
The head of the Shirino clan,
Lady Christel's ex-husband.
The black onmyoji, Doman Shirino.
[Based off Doman Ashiya, Seimei's rival.]
That's Ms. Ketsuno's...
Ex-husband...?
Yes, though they were married,
they never opened up to one
another or held hands,
before Lord Seimei
stole his wife away.
Doman...
Seimei, it appears that I win again!
Your sister's weather forecast is wrong.
She should quit before they force her off.
How does she have the nerve to appear on
television with her inaccurate forecasts...
I see that both siblings are thick-skinned.
Doman, damn you...
Circular flyer!
What?!
Seimei, you may strive to
be the greatest onmyoji,
but your abilities are no longer
able to even scratch me.
Oh, a neighborhood matsutake-picking trip.
Should I participate?
I am no longer the person I was before.
I was reborn to extract revenge
against you siblings.
Seimei, you won't be participating?
Then I'm going, up yours.
Bastard...
After challenging and being defeated
by the Shirino clan multiple times,
you no longer have anyone able to fight.
You are the only one left
to protect your sister.
This rain will never end, Seimei.
Christel may be fired from her
position as weather lady...
The Ketsuno clan may be obliterated...
And this rain will still continue.
This rain will continue until the wails
of you siblings have forever ceased.
Pass this to Iwashita-san
next door, will ya?
Seimei-san!
Get a grip, sister lover!
I never imagined that a battle over
the weather was taking place.
An argument between neighbors gets blown
out of proportion when onmyoji are involved.
They were all beaten up.
Gedomaru-san, Ms. Ketsuno doesn't
know about this, does she?
I've been keeping her out of the loop.
Huh?
Why's that?!
Ms. Ketsuno was suffering so much!
If she knew about this fight,
she would return to Doman in
an attempt to end the fight.
Quite frankly, I don't give a damn about
this battle between the clans.
I couldn't care less if the Ketsuno clan, which
tamed and used me, were to be crushed.
But...
I never want to see Lady Christel
look so sorrowful again.
You really care about
Ms. Ketsuno, don't you?
Lady Christel was the only onmyoji master
who ever treated me as a friend.
And he does not wish for Lady
Christel to learn the truth.
Hello, Ketsuno here.
I apologize for being wrong with
my afternoon forecast, too.
I promise to do better tomorrow.
Shut up!
How many times are you going
to screw up the forecast, girl?
Ah, excuse me.
Camera's rolling.
Who gives a damn?
Stop giving forecasts that are wrong!
Yeah! Yeah!
Nobody's watching your
forecasts anymore!
Please stop throwing things!
Ms. Ketsuno, run! It's dangerous here!
Then I'll be giving the forecast now.
Wait! What are you doing, Ketsuno?!
It's dangerous!
The hell?
Are you okay, Ms. Ketsuno?!
Aren't you a fan of Christel?
I can't believe you can watch this.
Yeah, I'm a super sadist.
Besides...
Ms. Ketsuno is putting up with
this crap to give her report.
It isn't known when this rain will
end, but by tomorrow morning...
We have a duty to watch.
Isn't that right, big brother?
Who are you calling your big brother?
I am the one responsible
for Christel's suffering
and Doman's turning
down a dark path.
I am not allowed to avert my eyes.
I am obligated to watch every second.
In the past,
I was so focused on protecting the family
as the leader of the Ketsuno clan,
that I allowed duty to blind
me to everything else.
I selfishly used my own sister as a tool
before selfishly taking her
away from Doman.
Pathetic for the greatest onmyoji, who,
supposedly saw all as he defended Edo.
Only after blundering was I able to see.
Only after suffering loss was
I able to understand.
You must watch the things that are
important with your own two eyes.
Dear brother, what's that?
Who are you calling your dear brother?
A letter sent from Doman.
Seimei, you should know well that continued
skirmishes will only serve to waste our men.
It is the duty of the head
to defend the family.
And it is the duty of an older brother
to defend a younger sister.
I won't tell you to choose between them.
If you wish to defend both,
face me in a contest.
In a Shikigami Tag Team
Mystic Deathmatch!
This contest shall serve as the
final battle of the weather war!
Shikigami Tag Team
Mystic Deathmatch?
The hell is that, broseph?
Who are you calling your broseph?
It refers to a 3-on-3 onmyodo match.
I see. So this is a challenge.
So he isn't satisfied by
pestering Ms. Ketsuno.
He's come to directly crush bro-bro.
Who are you calling your bro-bro?
Cut that out already!
How desperate are you
to join my family?
No, I don't really mean anything by it.
I just wanted to let you feel as though
you'd suddenly discovered
that you were about to live with
twelve adorable little brothers.
That's one creepy-as-hell
Brother Princess!
Oh, so you do know Sister Princess.
[Note: Sister Princess is a popular beautiful girls
novel, manga, anime and game franchise.]
So you do have a thing
for little sisters, ro-ro.
What the hell is ro-ro?
What does that have
to do with anything?
In any case, I believe this challenge
to be an opportunity.
If I win, I can save Princess Christel.
That would be like walking
right into a trap, nutbro.
The hell is a nutbro?
That makes it sound like I'm a nutxxxx!
I will accept the challenge alone.
The responsibility is all mine.
Are you protecting Ms. Ketsuno
because you feel guilty?
Guilt...?
No, I may have been jealous.
Here I was, using my power for the
Bakufu, to protect our traditions,
while she was using her power
to give people the weather.
As I watched her smile on rainy days and
windy days, I couldn't help but think...
That she was doing a magnificent job
of protecting the people of Edo,
of bringing them happiness...
She was a much greater onmyoji
than I could ever be...
She is...
My... Our clan's...
Pride and joy...
I wonder if the rain will stop.
Beats me.
Sadly, I don't know how
to read the heavens.
But there's one thing I can say.
Lord Seimei will die.
Doman has become exponentially
stronger than before.
The mark on his face...
He must have dabbled in forbidden
arts so he could defeat Lord Seimei.
On the other hand, Lord Seimei has dispatched
countless shikigami to watch over Edo
and his power is dispersed.
He might have a chance if he
were to focus his power,
but his duty will not allow that to happen.
He won't be able to defeat
Doman as things stand.
Will that change if we go?
Master Gintoki.
I didn't want to say this,
but you should butt out.
Do you know why Lady
Christel sent me?
To stop you.
I was ordered to keep you out of danger
and prioritize your lives.
That can't be!
Are you telling us to stand by
and let Seimei-san die?!
We're the only ones left who can fight!
Don't you realize who will grieve the
most if sister lover dies, bob cut?!
You're okay with Ms. Ketsuno crying?!
You never had any intention of
letting me order you around.
Oh well.
I'm not used to having people
serve me anyway.
Now I'm free.
Don't you understand that a bunch of
amateurs who can't use shikigami
would be reduced to a rain of blood?
Fine by me.
Look at this weather.
Not much difference if it's
blood instead of water.
Spring showers, fall showers,
rain of blood...
I'm willing to stand in any of those.
But...
I'm done standing in a girl's tears.
As I said...
A shikigami is always judging its master.
I've been waiting for those words.
Master Gintoki, I accept you.
You are my second master.
From now on, I will carry out
your every command,
no matter how difficult it may be.
I shall protect you from bullets
and the elements.
So Master Gintoki...
Please assist me in helping
Lady Christel.
You didn't need to ask.
But in return, skip the
master-servant crap.
Too much of a pain.
And don't call me Master Gintoki.
Call me President.
Pachi-boy, let's get going!
Wait!
We can't summon shikigami or anything!
Are we really going to be okay?
Don't sweat the small stuff!
Small stuff?!
Isn't this a shikigami tag match?!
You don't need to worry!
We don't have any shikigami,
but we still have familiar spirits!
Huh?! Where?!
Huh?
So you've come, Seimei...
I praise you for coming alone.
I can handle you myself.
Simple as that.
Hah, you never shut up.
Doman, if I win, you will stop
interfering with Christel...
Unlike you, the Shirino clan
keeps its promises.
Seimei, the weather war was all but over.
Yet do you know why I would bother
challenging you to a contest?!
To show you my strength!
I will destroy your pride
so you can die in despair!
Seimei, ever since that day,
I have lived solely for the sake of
revenge against you siblings!
Focused only on the moment when
I would tear the two of you apart,
as I sharpened my claws
in the darkness!
And that time has finally come!
The long weather war will finally end!
Who are you?!
Hey! Walk faster, shikigami!
How did this happen?
Ah! Sorry about being late!
Is this where the world martial
arts tournament is being held?!
[To Be Continued]
[Preview]
Pandemonium...
Pandemonium-san...
Pandemonium-san!
Pandemonium-san!!
The next episode...
"Not Losing to the Storm."
[Shinpachi and Kagura enter round one of
the Shikigami Tag Team Mystic Deathmatch!]
["Deathmatch" means if you lose, you die.
Shikigami Shinpachi dies for love...?!]
[See you next time.]